<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[How the world blindly gave away everything to China to manufacture, without Made in China goods, they become disabled. In 2007 somebody said Americans made themselves Chinese slave, now it's everywhere. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That green areas are Claimed by China as lost to others by yr, which govt, eg Jiang Kaishi, Sun Zhongshan, Qing dynasty, Zhonghua minguo, which is Jiang Kaishi's govt. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China used numerous trolls armies to portray their plotted Washington DC 6.4.2020 was worse than this Beijing 6.4.09, saying Chinese troops stopped for tank man, more caring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not about war, I wasn't going to US to start war or work with military, CIA, I was about to work on STEM, real estate business, cultural dialog, linguistic based projects. I have all proposals. Planned it since Sep 2013 until my son was kidnapped in Feb 2015. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They want me to look up to them as my savior, to learn from scratch about bible again like babies, crawl under their feet like dog, that's what their plan 6.5 yrs ago as they indicated in "Jewel in the Crown."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# On one hand they beg US not to fight war with China; on another they boast about US president being led by Xi like a dog, to do whatever Xi wants them to do. It's psychological warfare, one hand sword, another honeypot #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great job!!! If Australia crawls under Emperor's Xi's arms, why would gracious Queen accept them anyway? I support Britain taking such stance against Australia. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The mom cook for them, he said delicious food. They have to smile at him. That's what Australia has done to my son &amp; me: my son's 8th yr Indonesian teacher groomed him before kidnapping him when he was only 14, in Oct 2014. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aussies demonised South Sudanese refugees too to help China delegitimise all others’ dreams &amp; hope for independence, human rights, as “independence” reminds them of Uyghurs, Tibetans; that’s why they destabilise Ukraine, Chinese spy in my office said Russia ruled Ukraine 100 yrs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You see? Chinese said US &amp; EU have listed Russia &amp; China as targets, hence China &amp; Russia should work together to confront them: China reports SCS, Indian Ocean situations to RU, When RU reports Eurasia, Ukraine situations to China, carrying out joint military exercises often]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese visit Afghan elders' homes, Talibans' homes with presents to buy their heart. 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why? Did he asked for it? It doesn't look good. Ordinary uniforms are still better. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what Chinese sides posted on my screen instantly after my son's abduction, To "undo" my mind, knowledge, erase my memories, force me suicide, make me homeless. As my friends advised me to write my memoir after hearing my stories, I was planning to do it. China was scared]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If Russia &amp; China qork together against Anglosphere, you want to kill me instead of fighting with Russia? You want to punch on my face Veronica? Am I your defender against Russia &amp; China? Who defended my so &amp; me? Where is my son? Who kidnapped my son in Oz if not Chinese, Aussies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gain my son's death, brutal death after Exploiting him so much. What else do you eat? Do you care about your rubbish 5 eyed countries or intelligence when all 5 eyes are blind, Filled with red blood wanting to eat me up after eating my son alive?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Americans trated Chinese very well, investing there, what's happening to US now? Chinese don't treat anybody nice. We know them. I treated Chinese extremely well, what have they done to my son/me/families? I even visited a Chinese colleague in 2012 hearing in 2008 he had stroke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why would world treat Cninese like babies anyway? Nobody trigger them, they've planned to take over Taiwan after HK, Afghanistan after XJ. They never stop 4xpansing, building heavy buffer region around them after expanding continuously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you do it to your own Christian families, single mother &amp; kid who got nobody to help them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't Chinese police in HK do the same last yr, spraying to HKongers face to face, sitting on girls, elderlies, young people's bodies? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thus itself is attack on Australia denying Australian citizens urgently needed medical supplies when attacking Oz &amp; entire world with covid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ghja concrete forest now. Chinese new comers say it's like big city. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can happiness be found by self awareness? How about your entire families, friends are killed by Chinese, &amp; you're forced to live under Chinese control, you mean Jewush people would find happiness in Nazi camps, or in graves? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# By inflicting so much pain on Uyghurs through torture, they could disfigure rest of the Uyghurs, so they would be lost by appearance. Chinese instead polish themselves up as supreme Han people as China's "White," while Uyghurs are destroyed as China's "blacks" or "ugly" folks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew you Chinese started south Sudanese gang rumour in Australia 5 yrs ago to sabotage newly independent S.Sudan, attack S.Sudanese refugees, because "independence" of any countries scares China due to E.Turkistan/Tubet issues. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only 1.3 million Uyghurs were in concentration camps, where are the rest?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese hate everybody, Christians especially, Muslims they manipulate like Pakistan. China detained many Western scholars, Russians, missionaries, tourists, intimidated them, expelled them merely for giving people bible or some books.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese videos say they've found alternatives #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's how Chinese isolated Uyghurs &amp; other inhabitants of East Turkistan after setting foot there, Restricting Uyghurs' economic, cultural, educational exchanges from Russia, EU, cut us off from everywhere, kicked Soviets out after using them to sign peace deals. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Unlike US or EU, Australia recognise de dacto relationships, as long as they cohabitation over 2 yrs time, it's in similar situation as marriages. Many heterosexual people live in de fecto relationships.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If any other nations do 1% of what Chinese do, they would face global condemnation, attack. But Chinese are treated as spoiled brats. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China threatens Ukraine already with nonsense lawsuits as they've done too many times to US. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They finished Uyghur genocide, so there's nothing can be done, so they pretend as defector to leak already known information to make bargains with US. Maybe behind it, he has more to hide from public, we would never know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What else do you want to use my son &amp; me for after exploiting us for numerous things for 25 yrs? Who else do you want to free? You've freed Talibans, ISIS members, Meng Wanzhou &amp; 2 Michael's exchange, annexing all buffer regions, conflict regions, when will West Bank job be over?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thus one us about a roommate who is obsessed with a woman.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My son's stories &amp; mine have gone far worse than "Oliver Twist &amp; Me" I wrote 5 yrs ago. Far worse than Hensen &amp; Gretel's, Qua vadas. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese make up fake news like this to blame motary on dropping bombs. That's lie. Eg South Sudan was liberated, made independence from genocide, sav3d S.Sudanese from genocide. nobody dropped bombs there. But Aussie, Chinese dempnised s.Sudanese refugees 6 yrs ago. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9.8.19 article about China's upcoming revenge against HKongers. 
#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The money I gave is only to get my son &amp; me our from here, that's what they all promised but never delivered. Chinese planned it, saying so they could drag me here in debt, in jail, so I can't move anywhere. During worst humanitarian crises they stonewalled me, kidnapping my son.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World needs to remember how Chinese troops open fire, killing tens of thousands students, civilians. Such things happened many times in Uyghur region, Tibet, Beijing, HK. Now China has been working hard to erase this memories from HKongers so they wouldn't tell Chinese.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They just want to break my relationship with all reasonable compatible men, they did for over 30 yrs, in China same. They sent Chinese woman to chase after man I dated in Australia, married in Belarus escaping from here. They sent a man overseas once he proposed, with a ring. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it why Chinese taught African kids to chant in Chinese "I am Black devil, I have low IQ?" When did you measure African and Chinese IQ? How?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We warned you, they used my son for gene editing related medical experiments. China used genetic attack on Uyghurs to turn them Black, as Aussies call Aboriginals "Black fellas."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If you want to stop killing, stop Afghanistan take over, blackout, Uyghur tragedy; covid casualties in the US. Those are more important for us than your endless infighting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of making fake criticism of China, Oz govt should tell truth about their kidnapping of my son, torturing my son &amp; me for 25 yrs, especially in past 7 yrs, Using my son &amp; me for Nazi experiments, using my son for medical experiments, killing my son &amp; me. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China will never give up waging biological warfare with virus,as their military chief said it's inexpensive weapons that target enemies accurately based on Genetic traits when sparing themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Someone posted an image of vaccine cleaner, sucking up immigrants in the borders in the beginning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #URL#
This is what it's about. Gaslighting on my screen. China doesn't want cold war, they don't want divorce, they want to be America's little concubine, playing petty lady's role, on bed night time, day time acting as greatest warrior to conquer America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without China, there are 5.5 billion people with much more decent products to trade with. Turkey has great taxtole products, Italy has fashion, shoes. Even Russua, Belarus have great products that Chinese can't even dream of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Relaxing. It makes me feel sad about what's going in now, hitting every industry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not what West said. This image isn't West, or current West. Chinese taught African kids to chant in Chinese "I am black devil (hei gui), I've low IQ." Plus China jailed 6000 Nigerians, without cause. That's out of proportion, as there aren't many Africans in China. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I really didn't miss your posts. Honestly speaking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# In the similar manner, numerous Chinese, including Taiwanese, Singaporeans attacked me viciously over sine love poems, Asking me to "rentong," identify myself as Chinese, to learn to live like Taiwanese. Aren't they democratic Chinese? Why do they do the same as PRC Chinese?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If Wei, as a Frontline of Chinese democratic movement, Given so many opportunities in the USA when living there so long, if he call religions as cult, Uyghur genocide as Uyghits deserved it, I can't imagine how other Chinese who have no chance to learn about democracy think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You live a comfortable life, that's why you have no concern for others, except worrying about who are investing with who. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not many Uyghurs left on the streets, except very few disabled, left alone elderlies, those married to Chinese carrying babies, a few street beggars, actors to entertain Chinese tourists, for proof of life, to prove to tourists how poor, uncivilized, ugly Uyghurs are with torture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's like exporting Uyghur slaves made Uyghur Naan to Central Asia, birth place of Uyghur Naan, It's a loud slap on Central Asian people's face, To export your own products with your own brothers' blood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No wonder there areigrant crises on Maxico borders each time during election campaigns. There are Chinese mafia in Maxico. Now they claim US stolen Maxico. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever I see the name Campbell &amp; Borg, my blood starts boiling. Borg gave virtual death sentences to my son &amp; me on 60 June in her recommendation to Court magistrate. You Campbell is just my torturer,  abuser, exploitative person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After my son's abduction, a pastor said we don't want war. But I never had anything to do with war. Oz govt refused to give me job openly saying due to my work in US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are the fake Chinese Christian pastors who made up lies including prophesies, end time.  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can anybody tell me which one of them are HKongers in Australia, mainlanders, Vietnamese Chinese or from other countries? They were taking that guy Carli &amp; his Chinese spy girlfriend Winnie Cheng to 6 wks' luxurious overseas trip, including US to reward him for kidnapping my son #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Killing my son &amp; me doesn't help anybody. Now my phone can't receive texts. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is his speech at Arab leagues about his building common destiny for mankind lies in 2016. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When facing Chinese virus, people still support China is shocking. Bit they fight so hard against my son &amp; me. Why? What have we done? Did we attack US?
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They've been doing it for 7 yrs since kidnapping my son, using gene editing on him to make up stories, saying all kinds of rubbish about somebody who sent messages on FB. UK dirty job with Aussies. They are Dracula not humans. Devil worshippers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do you understand? When I recognized that person my heart cried without me helping. That's miracle. You can't fight such kind of power that's beyond imagination, control. When 2 hearts find each other, it's miracle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's not possible to have Uyghur militants there with China's surveillance technologies used on Uyghurs, Chinese embassy there wouldn't sit idle without paying a few dollars to mafias to get any Uyghurs whoever living there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is sickening, spreading such fake news to attack world leaders #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How many experiments have Chinese, Oz, maybe US govt have done with my son &amp; me in past 7 yrs? Do you have any clue about that? How much would you have to pay for it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's what people said trade war, economic sanctions hits ordinary people when real wars hit bad guys. Australia, NZ, UK lost without joining world against China or without UK leading with so much power of British Commonwealth countries. What a waste!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In 2014 my internet &amp; computer was hacked, I asked help from a pastor, he gave me Kaspersky software, then later reports said it also had problems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thank European friends for supporting my son &amp; me. Australia has distanced them all with fake nuclear submarine that's not feasible to realize or defend anybody.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese also said they found resources in Guinea. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian ties &amp; collaboration with China is much deeper than you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Many people did that, Using me to post things they had no courage to post, then once achieving their goals, they stabbed on my back, killed my son. I know who they are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In China, in 1990s, they suddenly told me they canceled a small hotel &amp; mosque after I finished design completely, then after a yr or 2 I found my hotel was built in the exact location I designed, nearby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the bar where my son's kidnapper Carli went for drink each Fri, I believe kidnapping deal was arranged with these mobs, Labor politicians. Only less than 0.5 km away from our home then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They criticise about China, US, but these investors, many fake Aussie friends visited US while keeping my son &amp; me hostages here, torturing us. One Aussie man who came to stalk me at church has his son living in US, another in EU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are Chinese, daily death threat "the world wouldn't miss you if you vanish" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I know all your games for 25 yrs since I arrived in Australia. They said China &amp; Russia were Christians when I spoke about human rights issue  about China, Uyghurs. Instead of mocking me here, you should cry for your kids, grandkids for losing everything to China.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Even American Indians got support from around the globe during Dakota pipeline dispute in 2016 or so, over 2000 US veterans went there supported them, Maoris, Mongolians showed support, but Aussie Aboriginals never get any outside support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Dai Qi mean engaging with China about trade but not inflame tensions? Kowtow? I bet China would give her lots of favoritism in trade not to inflame tension, right? 1st thing Democrats passed was anti-Chinese racism bill when Chinese attacking me, call my suicide/death]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's how seriel killers are made, by starting one innocent person's blood then get addicted to killing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They don't want to acknowledge of adopting dictatorship, but kill &amp; silence others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This one says "When Japan occupied Taiwan, they killed 400,000 Taiwanese!! Hidden History" it says. Understand? If China takes over Taiwan, everybody is at risk, from Japan to Russua, Mongolia, Eurasia, as both Taiwan, PRC claim lost territories to these countries all way to Ru #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Australia &amp; China has trapped me, even Twitter,  FB don't work on my phone properly. 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's what Chinese mean "hurting Chinese feelings" when Americans criticise their human rights violations. They just want to me Anerica's "sweet heart," by betraying American people, their 1st love, to be concubine. Chinese are very good at it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frexit what? Why Frexit? I see on my screen about French military bases across the world. They attacked US &amp; me considering US military bases. Is it why they mention Frexit? What Frexit is about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# During 2014 Israel Palestine curfew, how many Palestijes were killed? It was reported on media. But in the meantime, Chinese quietly washed entire village clean in Yerken, killing about 5000 Uyghurs, without leaving anybody alive, nobody reported. Reporters weren't allowed there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There're numerous Chinese immigration offices, everywhere to sell visas to all other countries in the name of investment, businesses, marriages. Most of those investment money isn't there by the people who invest, migrate, its Chinese firms or merely by showing bank statements]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Plus covid is said by Chinese military general on a video as genetically, racially targeted inexpensive biological weapons, that could shield the hosts when targeting enemies precisely. People of different races could respond to virus &amp; vaccines differently]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I am for confronting China. The world has engaged too much with Chinese lies. I can't watch Chinese news or Chinese leaders speeches without banging my desk as they tell too much lies in every sentence. I can't stand why others can sit there listen for hours. Let alone engage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 yrs ago after my son's abduction, When I turned TV on, I saw Tatar people were put next to Australian Aboriginals on Aboriginal channel, I was shocked. Tatars are also civilised people with sophisticated cultures.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the past 6 yrs China has killing millions of people, caused more harm with covid, economic shutdown. They contributed significantly to Climate change also. Others' freedom, living space have shrunk, eg HKongers aren't safe in HK, Aussies can't speak freely in Oz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing slowly, my daeling,
You've reached age of fifteen.
You are yoked with more tyranny,
As time goes day by day.

You've befriended enemies,
Without knowing their brutality.
Your heart is broken,
By bloodthirsty tyranny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China claims lost these red areas, which belonged to China before, to Russia during Qing dynasty. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Chinese are nationalists with far left ideology to program &amp; swallow everything, everybody into Chinese belly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Depopulate who? Americans? Depopulation isn't possible. Mao killed 45 million people when in the meantime encouraged Chinese to breed. Xi does the same, during Wuhan virus lockdown, they put banner on locked buildings asking Chibese to stay home breed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plus China has built Health Silk Road to monitor your health in BRI involved countries, so your health data are in Chinese hands. Who told you to give your countries to China to build? If sb build sth on your property, you would need to kick them out. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Instead, UN praise Chinese troops doing "peacekeeping" in Sudan, when South Sudanese refugees get targeted in Australia. When Chinese send troops to newly independent countries, e.g. South Sudan or conflict regions, such as Sri Lanka 10 yrs ago, we need to be concerned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the stories of refugees in Aussie detention centres. They are Kurds, Rohingyas, Iraqis, Hazares, Tamils who faced oppression, genocide often with Chinese involvement. Then they got tortured, killed in Australia. China's blood $ is top sweet for Christian Aussies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese nationalism is too strong compared to their willingness to live decent life with dignity, freedom, human rights. They want to build huge Chinese empire then slowly change name without changing systems. It's typical Chinese approaches to handle things under the sleeves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's why I saved HK protest videos. We've lived through it in China. You can carry your dead person to protest but I can't hold my son's dead body in Oz. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I blocked several Canadians, Aussies today saying "don't worry, all will fall into places, we are hunting gem." Yes, When I due it will fall into places. Right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They would feel sorry later. Chiba did build roads, railways for African nations for 70 yrs before buying off the West. Africa is practically Chinese colonies. China worked in Yemen, Yemen's in crises. Chinese tought African kids to say in Chinese "I'm black devil, have low IQ."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I shared a story I saw in China before about a filthy beggar in a restaurant messing a man's newly ordered meal with dirty hands, only to get that man's meal himself. That man saw it &amp; left in disgust without eating his meal, but paying for it. So that beggar enjoyed the meal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You don't know what you are talking about. Oz govt even used a few lines or conversations I had about my meeting former vice Beijing mayor in Qld in 1997 after Chen Xitong's suicide to help China catch corrupt officials working together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't protect anybody if you couldn't protect my son &amp; me, my families. Keep your lies to yourselves. I just posted Dan Andrew's lies, how he represent Chinese interests; then Monash University qork with Chinese espionage. I am dying, sick, grieving. I don't work you you. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to my live thrill movie, to explore how much can people hate a mother &amp; kid to death, by inventing so many ways to blackmail, exploit, kill, in the name of love. Feel free to share, let the world learn such love craft.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China buys agricultural products from  Ukraine, then export finished Uyghur bread to Russia, Belarus, Eurasia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can celebrate but my son, my families, I can't. There's no injustice in human history as my son, my families have endured. What My son &amp; me have endured in past 25 yrs is unimaginable for your pleasure seeking people. If you could just give me one reason, why? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chineseus4d Australians to demonise South Sudanese refugees in Australia too in 2014-2017 accusing them of criminal gangs. Behind story is Chinese UN peacekeeping troops worked in South Sudan. Chiba get hirts when others get independence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Chinese are holding them, Central Asians against the Uyghurs, against US call to help Uyghurs. Over 30 yrs after independence, what kind of countries have they built? No proper independent media, military to defend themselves. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st started with Brexit drama putting allies apart into geopolitical tribalism with Xi Jinping visiting Buckingham Palace with extravagant welcome with beautiful princesses sitting on Xi Jingping both sides. That trip was led by Jacky Chen, movie star]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You don't have any clue. Uyghurs used to call Chinese Kitay, that's normal Russian word, meaning Chinese. But Chinese took offense of it, created many massacres, so Uyghurs stopped using that term Kitay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When I started cultural dialog business 6 yrs ago, I was told "they didn't want dialog, they wanted war" by pro-Chinese Aussues, Aussie business teachers said it was controversial. Bit Oz, China stole my ideas to promote own things by destroying Uyghurs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not merely about one person or two, it's about entire world. Eliminating Uyghurs with Chinese bloodthirsty tyranny wouldn't help anyone, or nations. Befriending such brutal genocidal regime, greedy people you can only ruin yourselves, entire world, civilisations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plus I saw Chinese fm industries are working with others to surpass American Hollywood. I see them working with British film schools. Australia is setting up their own. But I admire American Hollywoid as they have produced great inspiring movies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Australian TV even put Tatars next to Aboriginal people. Bu5 Tatars are beautiful civilised people, as a professor said Uyghuts were civilised people, couldn't use native, Aboriginals to describe them, as these terms have uncivilized meanings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every country in the region has right to be concerned about China's aggression. China didn't stop killing, assaulting others in XJ, Tibet, HK, it's impacted every other country in the world, especially in close neighborhoods of China.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This kind of things would never happen in Uyghur community or Muslim countries. Elderly people would always be surrounded, pampered by kids, grandkids, nwighbours. Nobody would be left like this. Chinese did it to inflict maximum pain to each Uyghur, young &amp; old, babies/elderlies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Taliban or AL Qaeda don't have money to bribe or integrate others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That person said he would send his medals to me. Understand? You get so jealous of such secret love, go on full forces to attack somebody, my son &amp; me for yrs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's pretty bad, devastating news. What will it take to stop virus? US has made concessions to China. What else do they want?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He says Bingtuan 4th regiment has 2+ million paramilitary soldiers in his promotion of their achievements, taking over Uyghur region. There're many Bingtuan regiments across XJ, plus formal military. Imagine how many military, paramilitary Chinese stationed in XJ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On 29 Jul, Saturday my son uploaded his last photo on FB looking gravely ill. I saw his photo uploaded instantly after returning from library. At library a lady gave me a DVD film to watch saying a woman died of cancer in her friend's arms. I saw cancer/cancer treatments on FB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What's her problems, aging or covid related? I will pray for you &amp; her. I hope she gets well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Since Deng Xiaoping became president in 1979, they made huge 10+ million population city in Shenzhen put of a tiny fishing village, we visited there in 1985, it was empty concrete jungles, ghost city. In 1993 when I visited there, it became huge city.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Chinese set fire, commit suicide to protest against govt brutality, tyranny. China can't put their household in order yet boast about being great nation. They blame Uyghurs as terrorists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Nobody have the rights to cheat me, my son, force me settle down in Oz when Oz govt &amp; China threatened me, denied me &amp; my son opportunities in the name of my work in USA. We were given clear threat by Chinese openly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Australian govt us making money working with China, digging on every others' dirt with Xi Jinping's so-called anti-corruption campaign. They did before in 2015, they did again. Who are actual beneficiary of their collaborations? Only China &amp; Oz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's defence chief jobs to earn malign forces from taking aggressive actions against others. That's what military is for, to intimidate, hold bullies accountable. What else do BLM want? How many seats have they got in US senate, both parties? Uyghurs/Tibetan lives matter too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly. You can't collaborate on intelligence issues with a leaking boat, not only leaking boat, a little minor province of China, like Oz. Chiba doesn't treat Oz as important as a province. Before demolishing Uyghur Mosques, Chinese bought Oz churches &amp; turned them own places. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese pretend like innocent peace loving babies when attacking others repeatedly. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# China, Australia are working together by monitoring everything I do, even if I cough, to benefit themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By killing me, taking me down from online, phone,they ended lockdiwn, US &amp; Australia. Congratulations, blood thirsty people. How many ways would you use my son &amp; me for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You mean Australia &amp; those who've cheated my money out in the name of helping my son &amp; me are your allies? You are not fighting with China, you are killing my son &amp; me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By claiming Uyghurs &amp; others who have faced genocide in Uyghur region, London Court effectively debased Uyghurs ad indigenous people, Who have no right, who can't decolonise, who can't get justice just like American Indians &amp; Oz Aboriginals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Left over Aboriginals represents very little percentage of Oz population, left for proof of life purpose, driven to the brink of life, with lowest lifespan, tortured into bitterness, isolated from all other countries, nations. Nobody knows which other nations they are related to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's how Chinese from all over the world stalk me online/offline, some Pretending as activists like Falungong, some are from PRC. Bit their goal is same, fight against me, trap me, To isolate me from everybody else, turn me into Chinese group. Extremely greedy nation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Chinese gov even used my Cultural Dialog logo on Chinese sleepover Mafia's handbook to sleep at Uyghurs home after detaining their spouses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Chinese planned to exterminate or merge Uyghurs &amp; other Turkic people since set foot there even before Mao Zedong’s CCP; merge was an option only considering Uyghurs &amp; other Turkic “compatibly white,” wait how they would treat Islamic people with anti-Muslim, anti-Arab banners.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Gates, Facing seal American buildings, peoples' homes to kill them? Like Chinese?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Those pastors want their wives live with man involved with Chinese spy, monitored, controlled by Chinese spies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You mean China can use its population number to kill as many people as they like? How clever you are! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the world treat Uyghurs amid genocide when consuming everything made from Uyghur homeland, Uyghur labour, depend on Chinese money thats made from Uyghurs &amp; Uyghur region is sickening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 1998, An Australian professor Colin McCarras said reading my history chapter, Thesis on Uyghur architecture, Uyghurs couldn't be called Indegenious as they were civilised people, Indegenious means uncivilized.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This happened many times in China. In 2009 or so a European man was beaten up in Beijing or so for walking with a Chinese woman #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The plans to turn Uyghurs into American Indians or Australian Aboriginals kind isn't new. Since coming to Australia I've argued with them as they said Chinese &amp; Russians were Christians whenever I spoke about human rights as if Uyghurs were to be cursed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I just saw somebody who advised vaccine saying Trump got vaccine so others should too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is China helping Saudis to build ballistic missiles? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saw Myanmar proresters asking for donations on Twitter. Maybe China's struct rules, killing of own people with virus, flood, forced Chinese to flee overseas, eg Myanmar. But Xi is monitoring online activities to force them back to China.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They put my mom's photos on community education centre pamphlet cover. Asked her to teach mathematics. She attended local community group events taking Uyghur food my dad cooked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For helping China to become a humane, responsible nation, every other nations have suffered China's covid attack, financial deprivation, intellectual theft, bit these scumbags profit from others' loss for helping China, vulnerable Chinese who r treated by them as animals, robbed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Gone what? Who? Nobody is tying you up. You can dump me anywhere you want without my son, without anybody. After all my families, friends are killed, including my son. You can use me when you want &amp; dump me wherever whenever you want, in the cage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I didn't see anything on FB about so-called insurrection. Usually I notice things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They can't use it to cheat me, by showing how Chinese make Tibetan temples their pilgrimage or kowtow sites; they've done same wearing Uyghur costumes dancing for Uyghur tunes. Tibetan Buddhism belong to Tibetans, so does Uyghur dance, music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During that time leading up to 7.5.09, Chinese were demolishing Uyghur settlements one after another, forcing Uyghurs to have their traditional homes rebuilt, by forcing unnecessary debt upon them when demolishing their homes forcefully, building ugly apartment buildings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was sent to US by China to tell them not to fight war with China.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese always cry like babies to justify genocides to Uyghurs, violence against HK, now doing the same to Taiwan, saying if they aren't allowed to takeover Taiwan peacefully, they would use forces. Nobody created HK difficult situation for China. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So exactly what have Americans done to Russia, Eurasia &amp; Turkic world? They raised dragons up pampering them like precious babies, concubines. If that much money, energy that Americans invested on China went to Russia, Eurasia, what a difference it would make!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For your one little old man you kill my son, blackmail me forever, get my entire families &amp; friends killed, yet want to exploit me for your own sake? How much do you want to exploit me? Am I supposed to get my son's body back? Offer him memorial service?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How about my son's abduction, torture, using him for gene editing related medical experiments in Australia, Torturing me for yrs overseas, in Oz. You mean Oz is not to be named? At least others r mentioned on news, why my son is murdered overseas, in your country  Pompeo? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Thank Bonnie. I always enjoy your talks. Great talk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# China's satellite urban planning systems is broadly used in everywhere. XJ borders 8 countries, China has built large cities on borders moving Chinese people there by killing Uyghurs. Kashgar, Ghulja, Urumqi &amp; several others r similar to Shenzhen to erase borders for expansionis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# When people have doubt, you can't silence their inquiring mind. You can put prove it. Not all Republicans are bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Many Taiwanese have invested in China, HKongers too, to bring up PRC to Taiwan, HK, Singapore level, they said if PRC economically reached their level, they would become democratic, unite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 1990s, Chinese built a dragon statue in front of Bingtuan headquarters in Urumqi, in front of our company. But Uyghurs opposed it during Chinese people's congress, Able Abdurishit organised expert meeting in Urumqi address it, I spoke as dragon is offensive in Uyghur culture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They want to enslave their women too, to meet  40 million surplus Chinese men's needs? To breed White curly haired Chinese babies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aussies, Chinese demonised south Sudanese refugees 6 yrs ago portraying them as gangs who would rob others; I didn’t believe refugees would become violent gangs without somebody paying &amp; organising them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many Western countries have faced civid &amp; financial attack for criticizing China's human rights abuse, not only against Uyghurs, Tibetans, more against Falungong, Chinese dissidents, but these scumbags profit quietly helping China to rot western nations with dirty money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's why amid Uyghur genocide, 1st genocide deniers were Russian Duran news &amp; a big Tatar mosque Mufti in Kazan in 2016-2017. Chinese are behind everything. That's what they've done by encroaching Uyghurs from everywhere, sealing their lips with honey pot cash.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where is he? He got paid by media to speak about what Chinese have done to Uyghurs, including himself, he said. What kind of arrangement is he in?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wrote Sinking Boat 7 yrs ago to indicate what was going on, what would happen. What do you want now? How is East Turkistan independence going? How about Canada? I visited Canada in 2013, Chinese occupied everywhere there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look how China is playing Ukraine, To incite Russia against Ukraine. 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese have Systematically destroyed Uyghurs, Uyghur culture, education, industries. Then used imposters everywhere to pretend them as Uyghurs, Wearing silly clothes, eg in Shanghai, making up fake mustache]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They lie about exchanging 2 Michael's with me using gaslighting..but I have nothing to do with China. They just want to use me for everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# How do you know? Maybe you will make it popular with occupied Chinese? To prepare full occupation,  undesirable people to China, e.g. newly independent S.Sudanese refugees have been blackmailed in Australia. You want to live in Australia? Welcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Russia helped China build up everything in 1950s China wanted to fight nuclear war with Russia with technology learned from Russia, built up nuclear bunkers everywhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why can't they stop virus? How is it transmitted? From air or ground?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China gave countries on BRI surveillance tech to monitor/protect own investment/interests. B&amp;R is a road to slavery/despotism. It's Chinese invasion with own people &amp; money. Nobody invest in others' countries for free. If others build sth on your land, it's called trespassing #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL#
Oz govt is like Chinese govt, they keep scandalous politicians quiet for a few months or so then promote them to top positions somewhere else. Exactly like China.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese used Indian guy to teach Uyghur dance to Chinese dressed up with skirt? Maybe no more Uyghur dancers left to teach Uyghur dance any more? This is how China makes up fake China's Indians or Aboriginals. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I can't understand this level of spinelessness of Australia for over 25 yrs. Can you imagine Confucius Institutes operating in XJ universities in 2003? Not even in 2012 when I visited there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are Aussies so privileged to visit Uyghurs shipped to inner China factories when UN human rights groups can't? Have Aussies replaced UN with China to guard everything when they are the ones teaching China, copying everything from Oz using my son &amp; me for Nazi experiments?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Australia, China made it happen like this. That's why I've been crying to get put from here for yrs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What else do they want? Why don't Black politicians listen to their voice, find solutions for their grievances? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nobody cares for your selfish needs. If you love somebody, you would help in her difficult time, saving her son &amp; her instead of occupying her for yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# After many massacres, British settlers detained Aboriginals but allowed them to protest in detention, same as refugees detained in detention centres, while bringing British to settle Oz. Then after fully settled, they let them out with banner "Your country is taken."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trump's admin almost lost everything by following Aussie guide maybe to take Americans' gun away during Les Vagas shooting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Former XJ gov chairman Huang Baozhang had 40 Uyghur women across Uyghur regions having affairs during his business trips. They offer women, banquets, music, dance to appease gov officials from higher level, with local music dance Troup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Numerous Chinese Australians openly mocked Uyghurs by making videos amid Uyghur genocide, saying Uyghurs were lucky to be alive, by Chinese mercy as Chibese were superior.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘They’d have made me a spy’: China uses LinkedIn to steal state secrets | News | The Times #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do those countries want to be ruled by Maga China, greater Chinese nationalism? I saw Chinese posted YouTube videos mentioning Central Asian people as Chinese like Muslims 5 yrs ago. They want them all to become Chinese? Like what they've done to Uyghurs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese jails: this woman jailed for 6 yrs in Mao Era for speaking up about Mao cult, raped often, lost mind in torture, so she ate steamed bun with her own menstrual blood, sitting in own discharged waste. Govt cut her vein to kill her, instead of shooting to stop her chanting. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Although China used militarized tones before, but last 6-7 yrs, China indeed waged war on Uyghurs, they used professional military terms eg "jue zhan" (final battle), "without victory we will never retreat," carried guns at local village, school, community meetings ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# When being tortured, when I get out for a walk, or shopping, being stalked by tens of thousands of Aussies, Chinese from door to door, for 25 yrs, given virtual death sentences disguised in natural death, everything ripped away without money to pay rent, bills, doctors, dentists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are emptied Uyghur cities, shops, everybody is dead. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All Uyghir homes were sealed using virus as excuse, so they starved to death inside. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During the past few yrs, there have been attack on South Sudanese refugees, maybe lynching them as violent mobs, then broadly demonizing them on media. I didn't  believe S.Sudanese refugees would dare to commit so much organised crime in Oz, but S.Sudan gained independence.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>