<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Animal rights advocates raise bloody hell in Midtown over carriage horse collision | amNewYork #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feds: Kansas woman led all-female Islamic State battalion #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN’s Jim Acosta Has Case Tip For Gov. DeSantis’ Vote Cops: ‘Coup’ Plot At Mar-a-Lago #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Harlem vigil for cops shot in ambush, Adams and other leaders pledge to shut down the ‘iron pipeline’ | amNewYork #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long Covid study finds previously undetected abnormalities in lungs #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Ku Klux Klan Hall In Fort Worth Being Turned Into ‘Arts And Community Healing’ Space #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phillips 66 income, revenue beat analysts' expectations for quarter, full year 2021 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wild Edge Rangers To Spoil Lundqvist Jersey Retirement #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former AFD arson investigator sentenced to 4 years probation #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadine Dorries faces squealing lefties: HENRY DEEDES watches Culture Sec shredding the licence fee #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Road crews in Philadelphia in a race against heavy snowfall, high winds #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millions of Brits are happy to ‘live with’ Covid and continue to wear face masks #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italian parties to beg president to stay on, leaving Draghi as PM #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden family adopts cat, names it Willow Grove after first lady’s hometown #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slain Mexican reporter described vulnerability in last show #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghan women’s rights activist ‘hopeful’ after talks with Taliban delegation in Norway #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laicisation of Catholic priest in Tipperary causes disappointment and anger in parish #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 person, 2 dogs saved after falling through ice in Brighton #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paris Hilton on the Age of the Influencer, Predicting the Future &amp; the Genius of Jason Derulo #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pregnant Kiwi journalist promised safety by Taliban after being declined emergency MIQ spot #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Diego Unified approves redistricting map meant to increase racial minorities’ representation #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Take It Very Seriously’: Gov. Baker Urges Mass. Residents To Stay Off Roads During Nor’easter #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CDC: Third COVID-19 vaccine shots reduce risk of hospitalization for immunocompromised #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No One Does a Press Tour Quite Like Lady Gaga #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CBD and Omega-3: Better Absorption &amp; Better Results – LA Weekly #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH: Ireland international Ciaran Clark sent off for punching opponent during friendly in Saudi Arabia #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man, teenage girl critically injured in triple Brooklyn shooting: cops | amNewYork #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Butler Scores 26 points, Heat Hold Off Late Clippers Rally For 121-114 Victory #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Much Snow Have You Gotten So Far? Check Latest Totals Here #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Walker made the surprising decision to stick with the North Carolina Senate race. 3 reasons that stuck out.  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawyers question how partygate report could prejudice police probe #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kyrgios and Kokkinakis vs Ebden and Purcell LIVE: Australian Open men’s doubles final #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘I don’t fall into male or female’: AFLW player Tori Groves-Little on coming out as non-binary #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forecast for solar industry: Government, financial analysts see sunny year ahead #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Boulder County evacuation warning system should be in place by April #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PennDOT Issues Road Restrictions As Crews Across Region Work To Clear Highways #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gardai investigate alleged sexual assaults on teenage girls in Sligo #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘We Are Ready To Go’: Power Crews From All Over Country Arrive Before Nor’easter #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Guide to Tempe FanCon 2022: Cosplay, Vendors, Schedule, and More #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Denver High School Students Plan Walkouts Over COVID Concerns #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students identifying as furries using litter boxes? Michigan superintendent debunks rumor. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID Omicron News: Kids 5-11 need to be fully vaxxed for NYC indoor venues starting Friday #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK weather: Storm Malik to batter Britain with gales of 80mph as amber wind alert issued #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Festival Pass: Tailgate Fest, Smoker’s Club announce lineups #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 Semi Trucks Overturn on I-95 in New Rochelle During Nor’easter #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait, Are Mike Pence and Donald Trump Not on Good Terms? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charlotte man offers different way to bury loved ones #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Short Stop: Turkish Eggs at Mercantile’s New Saturday Brunch #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adams to NYPD’s 35,000 Cops: ‘I’m Here for You … New Yorkers Are Here for You’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Jersey Residents Battle Inches Of Snow, Rough Road Conditions #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing NJ mother, 2 young sons found safe, won’t be returning home #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful nor'easter storm blankets much of US East Coast with snow #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia says it won’t start a war as Ukraine tensions mount #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FAA clears Verizon and AT&amp;T to turn on more 5G cell towers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crypto super PAC plans to spend $20M #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omicron infections have peaked nationally, Canada’s top doctor says | CBC News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UN rights chief: Reparations needed for people of African descent #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two men who spent years in prison for murder, say they were tortured into confessing by cops tied to Jon Burge, offered $14 million settlement #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chicago anti-abortion rally expected to clash with pro-choice demonstrators in Loop #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Irish clowns defeated orange Toronto cops #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dori: Seattle K9 killed in line of duty mourned; loss triggers memories for dog owners #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn’t get a third stimulus check? Here’s how to get your remaining payment #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden arrives in Pittsburgh as bridge collapses, exposing his ‘infrastructure’ law as ‘Orwellian lie’: Ryun #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jury selection begins in lone trial over Breonna Taylor raid #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberia’s abandoned hotel stands as a symbol of a haunted past #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burglary leads to high-speed chase from Clairemont to Santee #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does America Still Trust the Supreme Court? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another KZN political killing! Municipality speaker gunned down overnight #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dwarf Actors Slam Disney’s ‘Snow White’ Wokeism After Peter Dinklage Criticism #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pittsburgh bridge collapses ahead of Biden’s visit to discuss infrastructure #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Art Basel Hong Kong Has Been Postponed from March to May #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free at-home COVID tests will ship soon, but could the cold conditions impact their accuracy? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7-Year-Old Michigan Boy Dies After Being Run Over By Bulldozer #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joni Mitchell joins Neil Young in pulling music from Spotify over ‘lies’ | CBC News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s Working: Rising rents and other costs outpace wage gains in Colorado #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paper license plate problem hits close to home for one mom; TxDMV cracks down #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chevron reports $5bn profit amid surging crude and natural gas prices #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reward Set, Tips Sought in Arson Fire at Supervisor Fletcher’s Home in City Heights #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giants hiring Brian Daboll as next head coach | amNewYork #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pittsburgh Bridge Collapses Hours Before Biden Infrastructure Visit #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Native American tribe's eviction plan raises civil rights concerns. Should US government intervene? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ocean City Police Officer Jacob Harris Arrested After Allegedly Using Tracking Device #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspect in custody for slaying of Spring Valley woman #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Our culture has changed’: young Thais boycott graduation ceremonies #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CHP officer cleared of wrongdoing in fatal shootout at O.C. homeless encampment #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somber vigil remembers Tijuana journalists killed for 'just doing their jobs' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joni Mitchell joining Neil Young in protest over Spotify, Joe Rogan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free N95 Masks are Arriving in San Diego: Where to Find Yours And When to Expect Them #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Oakland County Priest Pleads Guilty In Sex Abuse Cases, Sentenced Up To 15 Years #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AFD: Firefighters pulled unconscious person from apartment during fire #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dori: Seattle-area thieves claim ownership of truck, handed keys at tire center #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID-19 pill will be available to thousands in Britain in February – National | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avs’ MacKinnon Could Miss All-Star Game After Taylor Hit #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live updates: Pittsburgh bridge collapses under heavy snow in Frick Park #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tribal eviction plan pits Native American authority vs. civil rights #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | Let Kids Take Their Masks Off After the Omicron Surge #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indigenous, Native American tribes are pushing for voting rights #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Sweeney Sues NJ Democratic Chairman Over Getting Tossed from Redistricting Panel #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car Crashes Into City Snowplow Truck In The Loop #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State failing to protect sex workers – Amnesty #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Francisco’s ‘Mayor of The Mission’ Helps Feed People Struggling To Survive During Pandemic #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Prioritizing Antiviral Pills for ‘Non-White’ People #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: Andy Williams brought San Diego’s PGA tournament to Torrey in 1968 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID hits one of the last uninfected places on Earth #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gay’s 30-yard FG Lifts Rams Over Brady, Buccaneers 30-27 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kia Recalling 410K Cars, Minivans and SUVs Over Airbags #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man Found Shot, Wounded In Arcadia Terrace #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In blow to telecoms, California's net neutrality law upheld #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the pandemic’s unequal toll on people of color underlines U.S. health inequities – and why solving them is so critical #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AG guidance to New Yorkers following expired eviction moratorium #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police working homicide after woman shot dead near northeast Austin motel #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photos: Antifa supporters, Proud Boys clash in Portland | US &amp; Canada News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covid-19: B.C.’s Ministry of Education will review guidelines for school sports tournaments #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taliban, Western officials hold landmark talks on food crisis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aerial Footage Shows How Close Big Sur Wildfire Got to Bixby Bridge #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elevate Your Business with the TRD Brand Studio #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jersey Shore Residents Concerned As They Prepare For Incoming Nor’easter: ‘I Hope We Don’t Lose Power’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lamar and Yuma schools cling to Savages and Tribe after being told to drop Native American mascots #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China to receive significant payments for years in deal to return Irish businessman | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britney Spears calls sister Jamie Lynn ‘scum’ in scathing online post #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tracking a warming trend; historic winter storm to impact northeast #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regis Jesuit High School fires advisers, pulls student magazine over pro-choice column #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can former Scientologists take the church to court? Or are religious tribunals the only recourse? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[49ers Faithful Stream Toward SoCal for NFC Championship Game #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detroit Public Library Branches Distributing Free At-Home COVID-19 Tests #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six arrested after investigation into robberies targeting Asian women in San Jose #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sue Gray report: redacted version is imminent, say government sources #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gaston County Mugshots January 28th – WCCB Charlotte’s CW #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Mom’s Farrah slammed for claiming she’s a LAWYER after exit from Harvard #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immersive Van Gogh Detroit Event Rescheduled For Second Time #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice system failed 8-year-old killed, teen linked to shooting, say activists #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 16 best winter boots at all price points, according to experts | CNN Underscored #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBA-Best Suns Roll To 9th Straight Win, Topping Timberwolves 134-124 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A self-described ‘Freedom Convoy’ of Canadian truckers opposed to vaccine mandate arrives in Ottawa #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deputy who mentored young officers is gunned down during traffic stop, Texas cops say #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shocking image shows lion chewing its way out of zebra freaks out Reddit users #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honduras: Chaos in congress as politicians brawl over election of new president #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sussex County braces for blizzard as upstate Del. may see 7 inches-plus #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man admits to assaulting woman in her home #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Early Addition: Everyone Loves LaGuardia Now #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murder suspect caught after backyard standoff with police in North Hollywood #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Studio Ghibli Theme Park Set to Open in November #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See the top vehicles sold at 2022 Barrett-Jackson on Thursday #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot homes: 5 cool houses for sale in Charlotte starting at $385K #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Point Roberts business owner says despite border opening, revenue barely up #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horse racing titan Richard Duchossois dead at 100 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ukraine Releases Photos of President Zelensky After Controversial Biden Phone Call #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wounded Warrior Project 5K raises money to help injured veterans ‘Carry Forward’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Mom’s Bar Smith shares throwback photo with daughter Holly #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covid Live Updates: World Tops 10 Billion Vaccine Doses #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Mom’s Javi Marroquin praised as ‘the best dad’ after sharing video of son Lincoln, 8, crying over Christmas gift #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syrian refugees face yet another struggle as heavy rains flood displacement camp #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finnish diplomats’ mobile devices hacked with spyware #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Top Sundance Picks Screening at Northwest Film Forum This Weekend #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow quickly pilling up as nor’easter hits New Jersey #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspected DUI driver arrested after crashing car into Taylor Swift's NYC building: Police #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pittsburgh Bridge Collapse Brings Light To Infrastructure Concerns Across The Country – WCCB Charlotte’s CW #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin gambles Russia’s economy over Ukraine #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloomington man faces attempted murder charge after shooting at apartments #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman arrested for string of arsons in Tacoma #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quebec’s Muslim community to honour victims on 5th anniversary of deadly mosque attack | CBC News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vermont students focus on educating community about Holocaust #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British diplomats meet Taliban for humanitarian talks in Oslo #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 priests, 2 lay people to be beatified in El Salvador #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dolphins as Far as the Eye Can See Off SoCal Coast #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Veritas Tenants End Rent Strike After Winning Significant Concessions on Back Debt #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bidens welcome new cat Willow to the White House #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Promise of DAOs, the Latest Craze in Crypto #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Leather Leggings to Elevate Your Winter Style #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A market crash will depend on which bit of the equation investors got wrong #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fulham v Blackpool, Celtic v Dundee United: Championship, Scottish Premiership and more – live! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UNC Charlotte Reports 12K Gallon Sewage Spill On Campus – WCCB Charlotte’s CW #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump facing legal, political headwinds as he eyes comeback #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US 31 closed between 226th and 236th streets #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Maus’ Is an Amazon Bestseller After Tennessee School Ban – Author Art Spiegelman Compares Board to Putin #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[January transfer latest: Burnley chairman Alan Pace in Croatia to seal Mislav Orsic deal #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oklahoma tribal sovereignty case gets Supreme Court review, not reversal – Cronkite News – Arizona PBS #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the Killing of Two N.Y.P.D. Officers Means for New York #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michigan High School Students Participating In Safe Driving Campaign #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damaja Jones takes over as head football coach of Helix High School – #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Best Redhead OnlyFans (Top Only Fans Red Heads)  – LA Weekly #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: Tom Brady’s Formal Retirement Announcement ‘Expected Shortly,’ According To Members Of QB’s ‘Inner Circle’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The City’s LGBTQIA tech entreprenuers shine in new book – The San Francisco Examiner #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hotel industry is missing 25,000 jobs but still can’t hire workers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman who suffer miscarriage have greater risk of dying before age 70 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How long does your 'natural immunity' last? Expert weighs in #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family of 6 escapes Murray Hill house fire #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayer and Prostitutes: Redeeming Love Tackles Faith-Based Romance – LA Weekly #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Navigating On Cinema’s Giant, Underground Universe #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Texas teachers call out sick, student outcomes could suffer. What can districts do? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ski Club with Chicago Roots Sends Three Ski Jumpers to Winter Olympics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michigan State Police Trooper Rescues Cat Hitching Ride On Truck Before Falling Off In Metro Detroit #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ready to deliver on your sustainability promise? It starts at the top #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghanistan’s Taliban have started their first talks in Europe since takeover #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$58m Fury-Whyte heavyweight boxing blockbuster locked in #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Emily the Criminal’: How Far Would You Go to Pay Off Your Student Loans? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sonic employee survives car explosion that police are calling a ‘miracle’ for him to be alive #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ska’s Boulder Brewstillery Has Closed After Two Years of Pandemic-Related Woes #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$15K reward offered in killing of 15-year-old West Town high school student #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massachusetts Reports 7,181 New COVID Cases, 65 Additional Deaths #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>