<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I care about the filibuster. It should be eliminated. But also, corporate campaign finance &amp; dark money needs to be eliminated. If Manchin didn't get a free yacht with coal $, and Cinema didn't get a free mansion with pharma $... The conversation would be different]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# In a lot of ways, but there are still exceptions.
Overturn Citizens United, and we have a chance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easy to see why #HASHTAG# seem to "stick together" in politics, and why Dems seem divided. Citizens United tends to funnel in self-serving sociopaths... and while Dems are arguing nuance....Repugs devolve to "my freedom Trumps your rights"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You wanna make a bunch of lilly-whites "feel bad"
?
It comes with the privilege.... we get to 'feel bad' a little for our chock-full fridge and Mercedes and Ford Explorer, Windows Mackin-Tosh comp-puder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Put corporate political finance on there....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's better if you have more evidence than just 'talking points' when making such serious allegations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's sort of common sense.Particulates the viruses ride on will tend to get caught in cloth. If you're less sick because you got the vaccine, you're going to produce less phlegm and fewer viruses to spread to others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# If you were telling the truth, I suppose, but since you're not, I agree with #USER# Get yourself a job picking strawberries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I didn't either. It was supposed to be a 'free country'!! Well dig you heels in &amp; put the hurt on, they haven't stopped.... Ironically, the way to get to the pawns on the other side is to ..... listen to them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The Oscars are probably the most risky, indoor crowds...but if vaccines and masks are required, and at outdoor venues, the risk is mitigated.
"State of emergency" is more a function of assisting hospitals with the added workload]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I've been an advocate for 1000000 white rooftops and roadways for years. I'm totally against SAS 'stratospheric aerosol spraying' of aluminum/barium salts by aircraft...it traps as much heat as it reflects... and poisons bees &amp; humans in the process]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's what there's amendments for.....
or what the hell.... let's just start from scratch.....and put AFFIRMATIVE voting rights language in there.... instead of the double negatives there now.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Fucker Tarlson trays pribute poo the peepee Torn Lawyer....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You clearly think the attempt to subvert the vote count on Jan 6th was a spontaneous grass-roots effort...
Remember why they left the Capitol grounds? It was a tweet from Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[% Tax rate on Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, etc model:
Income ratio between highest &amp; lowest paid worker is proportional to tax rate:
10,000:1.....99.9%
10:1.............1%
(and on ALL capatalistic businesses for that matter)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You still haven't answered the question as to why he thought it would be a good idea to go to a riot with and AR15....[instead of a first aid kit]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# phonecall after hot mic event [Biden]: "Hey, Peter, look, would you just find me ... 11,780 votes...?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Boo fucking hoo. I got vaccinated. All of my 15 to 20 close people did too (and my 100s of co-workers). No ill side-effects other than sore arm and 2 days of flu-like symptoms Anti-vax is not the arena to express 'your freedoms' ..at the expense of your loved-ones and neighbors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...she needs to be pressured into supporting Ossoff's bill banning stock trades in Congress....then I'm 100% for her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You kind of have to respect others, by, like, getting the vaccine to help protect them from possible death....to be considered a candidate for not getting hostility...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's "once removed" from having a direct effect on SCOTUS, but it would tend to bring in the people who CHOOSE SCOTUS who have the country and peoples' best interest in heart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Self defense doesn't apply 30 miles away #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...and remember, 'Truth' and 'fact' are not necessarily equivalent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# so you would think a charge of sedition shouldn't exist then.... ie would be unconstitutional because of the 1st amendment...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You're thinking in binary, as has been the case with said Communist/totalitarian oscillations.... and seems to be the case now in the US and the world..... so maybe you're right, but there should be a fair tax structure that keeps cocks out of space and people off the streets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Are you going to offer any evidence, or just call names? My statements make sense, because if you have antibodies in your system, it will tend to kill the virus before it can proliferate...not completely, but on average....and that's what the evidence is supporting...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 'Vaccine mandate' isn't at gunpoint Masks save others' lives...you chose reckless endangerment of others? Banning CRT is anti-school-choice 2nd says 'well regulated...' Capitalism and socialism co-exist Raising taxes means poor people have more choice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ....but you're ok with Twitter and Google data-mining you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's a good theory, and I'd like to never take away anyone's free speech... and even go so far as to prohibit corporate 'persons' from doing same, even though the first amendment says "congress shall make no law abridging.." ...but if the result is tyrants rising in power....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Based on your video, absolutely. I wouldn't send him to prison based on that alone, but would arrest him and make him defend himself against a charge of incitement, possibly seditious conspiracy....and give him a public defender if necessary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Does "take over Elections" mean "allow everyone to vote"??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Depleted uranium, U239, was used extensively in Iraq as 'armour-penetrating' rounds to destroy tanks, etc
Now we have Chernobyl and about 10 or 15 other chances to end humanity due to reactors in Ukraine in war zone which could easily melt down if abandoned..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd be all for eliminating prisons..... just revoke 1st and 2nd amendments for those individuals for time periods....and abolish the 14th alltogether.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ....and because I want to be less likely to spread Covid and be an incubator for variants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're evading the question. How is the inherent dis-proportionate representation fair? I mean, you're calling that 'roughshod'....which implies it's unfair.... but what's your reason?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I mean, if you have a doctor saying your nose condition makes a mask an undue burden, and they assign only Covid-vaccinated people to you, I'd have no problem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I was a young sprout in '91 and fell for HW Bush's rhetoric about attacking Iraq then. In '02, I railed against the false pretenses for war in Iraq and Afghanistan.

The US has blown it in so many ways.....if they (we) hadn't, we could bomb the convoys of tanks heading for Kiev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Government's only recourse isn't force of violence. It's fines to corporations that pollute our common space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If you have to SAY you're telling the truth..... it's pretty clear you're lying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Then finally, you have the racist, ignorant masses who actually thought they were saving the country for Trump, because that's what he'd been broadcasting, saying they weren't going to have a country left. Those are the factions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As compared to RWM, which it appears you are exposed to, is funneling fear, hatred and doubt. Your search-engines learn about you, Google, Facebook, Twitter - they know you'll bite, they know your associations. Try a public computer sometime, without cookies...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When there's no time to wait for the punkrock song...the birth of the meme #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Another #HASHTAG# sociopath...essentially mocking the 1000s of Americans dying every DAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure he deserves a couple years in prison. How about the members of Congress and former president who convinced him he was justified?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I absolutely don't root for Putin. We have to be introspective, though, hold up the mirror, and remember that membership in NATO implies buying F16 fighter jets, most likely from the US]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "...your not going to have a country left..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You haven't looked at my tweet history if you think I'm content with current leadership.
Progressive tax to pay for
-Saving the environment...for our sake
-Federal minimum income...eliminate homelessness
-Eliminate corporate personhood,
-Eliminate $=free speech...
...to start]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wealthy elite donors skewed the election by 'legal' means...influencing minds to vote a certain way.... not by tampering with individual ballots]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...you can't pardon someone you've grabbed by the puss-why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The lies about election integrity involve top-down manipulation by #HASHTAG#.... fraudulent slates of electors just received by the National Archive.... not the approx 58 individual fraudulent ballots cast...(which incidentally were extra votes for Trump mostly)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Weeee.e.e.eellllll, guns ARE more convincing than....logic...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...a majority of states voted for him....
but more to the point....the individuals who DID vote for him did so on the belief he would "drain the swamp" - a concept Reagan planted and Trump harvested]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Law matters until you try to stick it to THE MAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right. But dragging their leaders in front of Congress for a grilling is hardly that. We need to REPEAL Citizens United which gives corporations 'personhood' status...in the form of unlimited campaign finance donations....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Self deprecation, especially in a sarcastic tone, is not redemption]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I hope you're not still operating under the assumption that there were many individual votes that were fraudulent, i.e double votes for Biden.
It's looking more and more like the 50 or 60 or so individual fraudulent votes were excess for Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Accountability will bring unity. won't. Or do you actually have a point? If so, please state it, otherwise you're #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Of course, but Biden &amp; crew are more opportunists, riding that wave, like Pelosi..... they're not orchestrating exploitation.... at least only slightly.... taking advantage of existing laws.... unlike the phalanx of right-wing sociopaths who ARE orchestrating major exploits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Or maybe it's more about the 14th amendment.
You're free, until you commit a crime.
Then you can become a slave.
That, my friend, is constitutional.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# In a few years the climate crisis, the increasing chemical concentrations, the melting methane reserves under the Arctic tundra, the proliferation of gun violence.... at the rate we're goin'.... is going to make sperm, pure-blood or not, a thing of the past]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It depends how free. Sure, you have the right to say it, but you also need to be prepared to face the consequences "Congress shall make no law abridging...." But if you inspire a crowd to cause harm to others.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It can be pretty much chalked up to his mannerism.
Sure, there's room to criticise, but you're just calling names with no substance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...the problem is discovering what appeals to them. Ending domestic violence? Gun control? Hot Dog ingredient disclosure?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I tend not to dwell on the sputum of the msm political punditry...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...sooo, you'll use this one instance to justify expanding the police state......?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How many times can you fold a piece of paper in 1/2?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...contingent on the accountability levied upon the highest levels of gov't officials
My family will bail on the US if Trump somehow makes it back into Whitehouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "I'm a fool for following Manchin, his line about 'they'll just buy drugs' while he drinks his whiskey on his yacht"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Science is not 'fact'
Science means you have an idea, you test it, you observe the result, that gives you another idea.
Then you test that.
Every time, your idea is refined, your test is refined, and the result is different and subject to interpretation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah, send the F16, blow up the mail boxes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That was a sharp turn away from relative salvation, a relative salvation that was already a sharp turn away from equity and justice that occurred with Reagan in 1980]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ..."overwhelming majority"....until it's your best friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's mysterious deciding "acceptability" of 'free speech'? Inconvenience others, or place them in harm's way directly or indirectly, that's not protected. Inconvenience others but speak to a larger injustice, go to jail, but repeal unjust laws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easy to tell what #HASHTAG# are lying about....just listen to what they accuse #HASHTAG# of

(I'll criticize Dems separately)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'd be surprised... his mentor was Jamie Gorelick....
But at least this statement is public
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electoral College and Citizens United have resulted in Dem/#HASHTAG# false dichotomy

now we're told to think it's one or the other, possibly they're simply opposite.....

...but neither, in their present state, promote democracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right, because you're conflating skin-color with oppression. Yes, one has a tendency to be indicative of the other...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# AAAArrrrrGGGhhh! Don't use those friggin sðŸ™ƒiley FðŸ«ces
They make me want to ðŸ”¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "I've go nothing to hide..."  ...or do I?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# There is no such thing as 'hard core proof' in epidemiology, or science in general for that matter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If you would just spend 1/2 this effort to end fossil fuel emission, you wouldn't even NEED to be fuc*king Brandon in the first place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 'Freemason' physical relics are still present, but their identity, influence &amp; tactics has shifted and hydra-split.... now we've got Fox, Meta, Google, Amazon, Tesla, Bannon, XOM, KPMG, Heritage, Koch.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# as....many.....times......as......it.....takes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Garland is not doing his job.
He's busy locking up the pawns for a day or 2,
....and letting the real criminals off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He did say "create pseudoparticles" in the same sentence as "spike protein"....but he didn't say they were attaching those pseudoparticles to the viruses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do you realize what #HASHTAG# is doing with his hand?? He's shooting boogers at the American Flag And you have that as your background picture Some patriot you are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assuming it wasn't some medical emergency that caused the SUV driver to plow the xmas parade... Would you 'wonder why they did it'? Do you also wonder why the context was removed from Rittenhaus trial....why did he go there at all?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Your vague accusations, sure they stir animosity, but are they USEFUL?
What is your specific grievance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The 'Left' will weaponize weapons and wwwwwwwwwep the wwwweeep to weeeeeeep for the sake of the 'Right'
Death is your core, rep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So you mean, like Cyber Ninjas presented bullshit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why don't you go straight for the "cough cough" and call out the 2010 SCOTUS 'citizens united' decision promoting corruption in the form of unlimited dark money funneled to elected officials?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Some enter politics for power. Others for justice.
So both constructive and destructive forces exist therein.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Manchin not only kills a bill, but insures hundereds of thousands, if not millions, will be displaced as ocean levels rise, because his cronies continue to sell &amp; burn coal..... and give him handouts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You just put your finger on it.....it's a matter of 'culture' for you.
You've been seeped for so long, and so universally you're standards and reference points have been altered...... without notice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't remember anything about Hitler leveraging any pandemics and vaccine mandates as an excuse to kill 1000s of people.... I could be wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Remember Bush looking in the Oval Office for the WMDs he couldn't find in Iraq? Yeah always wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems like Pompeo is a little bit excited Russia is making advances.....in front of a Q-Pac background that looks remarkably like CCCP #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ...god forbid one of your gametes should result in a zygote...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...as they should fine ALL businesses that knowingly broadcast mis- and dis-information for malevolent intent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ironic that when Trump admits to felonies he remains popular....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trump thoroughly divided Americans - those of us critical of Biden and not in the Trump cult..... are not joining the Trump cult now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Watch out for the GQP, they're more dangerous than Corona]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well, you can either choose something you KNOW is dangerous - not taking the vaccine, or something that MIGHT be dangerous - taking the vaccine.
Same logic is why I don't own a gun.
Same logic not eating fast food
Same driving slowly
&amp; conserving energy..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There probably are actually some ordinary people who consider themselves 'Republican' and are also essentially good people....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Dick Cheney's daughter of course" Fish in a barrel ...but, you're saying now "we're going to break...." Just break it now already! What's the holdup? You're spinning web of black widow web on top of web, that's why. So you can f#HASHTAG# right off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voting rights. Thank you Warnock! There is no single more important issue....well, other than carving out a place in the filibuster rule so it can get passed! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pay off one credit card with another.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Glad to know donald has masqued sinister-looking instigators feigning 'patriotism' Oh BTW the hotels are going to be closed too BC hotel owners want nothing to do with 'white supremacy']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I was thinking
1-Love
2-Food
3-Shelter
...but yes, then those 3 things too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I mean, on the one hand it would generate plenty of capital for blue lives, but on the other it would lift so many ppl out of poverty that 'blue lives' wouldn't even need to be a thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Welcome my son....tooo...oo the machi-ine....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Now, fertile grounds for Carlson, Zuckerberg, Tarrell, Jones, Limbaugh, Elder, Hannity, Bannon, Levin, Ingraham, McDaniel, Ellis, Powell, Batchelor, Nory etc to promote hatred, fear and doubt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sorry for calling you an idiot. I think it may just have been a linguistic issue, they way I interpreted a comment you made. I'm glad you are member of humanity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I want Elon to 'thank us from the bottom of his heart'....I mean, after all, Bezos did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That's the "official story"....however, the result is, the residents are under-represented: they have no senator, and yet they are still taxed. 
Taxation without representation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spent fuel is a greater hazard than meltdown of the active core. Chernobyl was a "new reactor" when it melted down. Now, there are vast caches of highly-radioactive spent fuel at multiple sites in Ukraine..requiring active cooling... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# .....um you mean trying to get as many legal voters to vote as possible.....?
[if all eligible voters voted....a Republican would never win again ..]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# On a foundation of Reagan's war against unions, defunding mental institutions, demonization of financial compassion in general...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wait, wasn't it Bannon who pocketed most of the funding for the wall?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Great, more guns and balls in the capitol exactly what we need]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I want him to thank us from the 'bottom of his heart'.....just like Bezos did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'll give him credit where credit is due. I'm glad he's gotten a package through that's going to help America.
Don't expect me to join a cult though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Believing you're not racist is a good first step. It's sort of like hypocrisy... it's not a question of whether we are are not....it's a question of how much, and in what ways, and what we do about it when we realize we are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Remember the Great Society, 95% top tax rate? Reagan, Bush, Clinton, Bush ended that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google, Spotify, Facebook and Twitter have no obligation to "uphold 1st amendment rights"

1st amendment is GOVERNMENT shall make no law abridging....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's time to remove 'person' status from corporations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Were the 'made in america' stickers made in america?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I agree with what you're trying to say, but a more accurate way to say it would be "there is no Voter fraud" ...there was actually election fraud: the false slates of electors submitted.... But the #HASHTAG# are targeting [practically absent] 'voter fraud']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hopefully they're holding out to drop the bomb when he announces he's running for House]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When your "rights" abridge the rights of others.....what about then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How many people is that going to affect? Yeah, I'll lose a couple $100 a year due to 'unrealized gains' tax But, look at tornados, wildfires droughts and floods... At this rate, taxes are going to be moot in a decade or 2, so what are you worried about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...as long as you're doing what's good and right, GO FOR IT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Hey I can translate "Black voices for Trump" for you... it means "Sacrifice my morals for crap in return"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'll tell you one thing, a DINO is a Democrat who votes to undermine the democratic system]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't! We need you!
Well, take time away from the Twitter black hole, but BE POWERFUL!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trump just admitted he's a seditionist on National TV...and you think that's.....right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's not a 'domestic spending plan' ....
It's an investment in the future of humanity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Both #HASHTAG# and #HASHTAG# are racist. We all are...due to extent to which it's been embedded into our society.... Repugs are overtly racist...Dems more covert... It's time we accept that...and go progressive in a way that helps reduce the racial divide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Philosophically illegitimate, sure...and definitely far too interested in war profiteering.... but you can't still be clinging to allegations of illegal tampering of 2020 election (?). Humans are too fallible for it to have been executed that well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# OK, I'm all ears.
Are you also going to tell this L.T. character to take a hike? Because it sure seems like you're coming down in his vein of union busting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow, modeling? I'll bet she makes 100s of millions. Then buys Chinese goods]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Yo, we got some HATs now, mutha fu*ckers"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Pandemic elucidates need for rail transit......"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow, that's going to make it so much better for so many people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I mean, there's hardly a comparison...Biden is basically decent, but a political opportunist, so not free from corruption... Whereas Trump is the epitome of a sociopath, a narcissist, and actively planning every possible deception in attempt to re-attain presidency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# and remember Fukushima....that almost became an extinction-level event....and may yet....and there are 104 in the US alone that could end it all....
and we have melting methane permafrost....dislodging icebergs...
Where's the Jack Daniels?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Philosophically that sounds great. Then you have laws like the recall law in CA where you can get a Gov with a small minority of vote in a recall.....which if we had gotten Elder what a Trumpian disaster he would've been...not that Batman is without fault...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The idea is not that "masks stop [all] viruses" The idea is more that "many of the viruses tend to ride in water droplets, and those droplets tend to get caught in masks" ...so the 'viral load' is reduced to proximal crowds...reducing the tendency of transmission]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Insurrectionists will be fined $500,000 and serve 3 to 5, and be paid $0.12/hr to clean the latrine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You absolutely fucking disgust me. You're talking semantics when the intent of your semantic diversion leads to the deaths of 2 people, the implied excuse of negligent homicide, and the resulting terror permeating society]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Holy sczh*it I was thinking about this #USER# sequence just today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ok, explain to me the corporate tax structure, and how my cheeky response isn't actually factual....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...and "repayment of the debt" only comes as a result of having enslaved the inmates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What is your native language? It will help me to accept your as an American, presuming you are American that is...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Financial interest. Phizer and Moderna don't want to kill off their hosts (us). They want to prolong the pandemic so they can keep selling vaccines. They are a virus speaking in $. But in the short term, we need their creation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Are you absolutely out of your friggen' mind? Of course the government dictates what we earn. Not on the individual scale or course, like I'm suggesting, but the more you lobby, the more you earn. I'm suggesting a slight adjustment from that norm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, everyone 'can be'
It's just a matter of what advantage they start out with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stiff little fingers Streetlight manifesto Agnostic front Assorted jelly beans NoFX Citizen fish/Subhumans Deadline The Mighty Regis The bastard suns Catch 22 Flux of pink indians Conflict Propaghandi Screeching weasel Choking victim scuicide machines dropkick murphys fear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Confucius say 'go to extreme effort to make people look bad, starve thy wife and phallic reduction result'"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "Blue and Red" is an artifact of the sick pseudo-democracy we live under. "State" is a geographical territory, but represents oppression when its residents don't get senators like everyone else does]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They boot pretty quick, like less than a minute, if it's working right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why are pensions being put in 'ASSETS' to begin with.... I mean, I know there's the investment portfolio and all..... but what about good old-fashioned save-up-for retirement....interest be damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The establishment's coordinated operation against the American people arguably started in the '80s with Reagan, and every president since has been complicit... because of the pressures of our capitalistic system...which arguably laid the groundwork for 1/6 invasion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's great to see you've removed the gun-toters from your profile background]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So which is it, is Putin great, or is America weak? Seems like you want it both ways]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...also, that power would always be available to cool the spent fuel so the zirconium-clad rods don't create an inextinguishable nuclear fire.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Except it wouldn't be the OWNERS of the press. It would be the minions who speak their minds who would lose their jobs and/or their lives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'll take bizarre brows over braggarts blathering any day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I gave you names......Pelosi doesn't count until she's on board with banning stock trades for Congress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Drug companies come to him, say "Kill BBB, and we give you a $1M. Don't kill BBB, and WE kill your 3 or 7 grandchildern"
How 'bout that?
[not that I ACTUALLY think that's what happened, at least not EXACTLY like that]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Don't forget, Garland's mentor was Jamie Gorelick.
Democracy is on thinner ice than you think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Of course he is... but even so, and even though he bears AT LEAST SOME of the responsibility for the deaths of his victims.....
He should only spend SOME time in prison - American prison is NOT rehabilitating...

But if he gets off with NO PUNISHMENT? That's injustice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's funny how yelling on Twitter doesn't really seem to intimidate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...partial death of Fascism....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There should be rioting and mayhem if he gets NO punishment.

He should get 1 year in prison and a $50k fine that should go to the families of the victims]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right ( ) Only allow those who can afford to take a day off work to vote... not risk being fired... drive and wait in line for hours... brave intimidation... Part of the #HASHTAG# strategy is to limit voter participation in every imaginable way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nominally on "our side" yet one of the principal agents of the demise of humanity #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Guaranteed minimum income, with government monitoring of bank accounts, travel, car ownership, limited 1st and 2nd amendment rights, studio apartment, aggressive income tax structure.. that's what I want most to be subject to instead of what we call 'prison']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I mean, the mRNA makers are making obscene profits, but do you really think Hitlers are popping up all over the world? I checked out several of the websites advertising Covid internment camps....and it appears to me the concept is being blown out of proportion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wouldn't limit taxation to just billionairres.... it needs to be sliding scale....if you have a bn income in a year, tax rate is 95%. If it's 100M in a year, it's 75%. If it's 10M in a year it's, say, 40%.....don't focus on the exact numbers....just the progressivity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Right, and where is Ali Alexander that seditionist fu*ck?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Here's a hell-freezes-over moment...I agree with LT.
Ironically, LT also exploits the Black voter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# : "Yeah, who needs minorities anyhow?" It's about the law of averages...more minorities will die if we 'open up' before 'herd immunity'. Why? Who has the best access to health care? Who has less access??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...in the game of Chicken....with Democracy itself on the line...which may not matter when you consider the climate catastrophe and that the US is now not committed to ending coal-fire because of Manchin.....
and many island nations will literally disappear soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Great. What's your plan for Covid? Oh, it's a hoax. Right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How dare Newsmax call out the ..... cult   (?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Unfortunately, he knows exactly what he's doing.... a tried and true tactic that whips up a lot of furvor, appealing to peoples' grievances, peppering a few truths in among inflammatory rhetoric.... then spinning the web]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'd settle for a windmill outside his cell...wouldn't want to disgrace a perfectly good accordion player]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# ....when you tell 3/4 lies for 4 years, anything can happen....

[or would that be 15/16ths, or 537/578ths?]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What % of city employees is that, what % have fallen prey to your toxic narrative?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Vaccination status isn't a window into the rest of your medical records]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "yeah, it's such a sign of obedience to a repressive government if you wear a mask [at times when you don't need to]"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And they wonder why we're cynical....and why there are terrorists...... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# ...and held in prison starting tomorrow, until he testifies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Almost makes you pity him....almost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...because you have respect for human artisans, embodied energy, and you can't stand the idea of a 'landfill']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Trump is double-daring Garland to act by sending Grenell to Serbia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just carrying a gun like that in the charged environment is likely to be interpreted as brandishing - which forced his 'attackers' to choose how to interpret his stance and to decide whether to 'take the law into their own hands' as Kyle was doing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're slightly too cynical.... they do WANT it, in theory.... it's just that they're allowed to make their own profits a priority within the current system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No textual definition of what an AR15 supposedly is, when you see someone walking down the street with one, war-zone or not, it invokes certain emotions....
....which might begin to come clear to Kyle if he spent a year in prison for his folly...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>