<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Two men who spent years in prison for murder, say they were tortured into confessing by cops tied to Jon Burge, offered $14 million settlement #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 Hurt in Crash on Fig Garden Village Shopping Center [Fresno, CA] #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meow Wolf Introduces Party Portal, a Series of Immersive Concerts #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SILVER ALERT: Search for missing woman from Wabash County #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mexican village, home to thousands of migrating pelicans, hopes to attract tourists #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ivan Toney apologises for ‘unacceptable language’ used about Brentford in video #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UN rights chief: Reparations needed for people of African descent #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FDNY Reminds New Yorkers To Use Space Heaters Safely As Temperatures Dip #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High Pressure Expected to Block Winter Storms from Affecting California #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tucker Carlson Says ‘Conservatives Have Remained Calm And Nonviolent, Thank God’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carroll County deputy, jail staffer die in accident #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daughter of mosque shooting victim to the intolerant, prejudiced: ‘hate is not worth it’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kid Rock says he’ll cancel tour dates at venues with COVID mandates #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Denver weather: Mild weekend before another round of snow early next week #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ska’s Boulder Brewstillery Has Closed After Two Years of Pandemic-Related Woes #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paws-itively Cute: 3 Local Pups to Make TV Debut at Puppy Bowl XVIII #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden decries ‘unacceptable’ bridge conditions in wake of Pittsburgh collapse #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This 17th-century official held a crazy lavish funeral for his pet dog #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Leather Leggings to Elevate Your Winter Style #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newly built Beverly Hills mansion goes into contract asking $34M #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slog PM: Free Masks Coming “Soon” to a Pharmacy Near You, Bus Goes Down With Collapsed Bridge, Your Darkest Thoughts Are Being “Shared” and Then Sold for Profit #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Halle Berry admits she had ‘commitment ceremony’ after teasing about wedding #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Covid Pill “Active” Against Omicron: Merck #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ukraine: ‘This is panic!’ Zelensky calls out West amid rising Russia-Ukraine tensions #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off-Duty Officer Shoots Stabbing Suspect Outside NYC Duane Reade: NYPD #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students identifying as furries using litter boxes? Michigan superintendent debunks rumor. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Single-vehicle crash on I-72 in Springfield kills 1, ISP says #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PM Jacinda Ardern self-isolating after being confirmed as Covid-19 close contact, is ‘asymptomatic’ and ‘feeling well’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Harlem vigil for cops shot in ambush, Adams and other leaders pledge to shut down the ‘iron pipeline’ | amNewYork #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Star releasing huge bursts of energy may be 1st of its kind ever discovered | CBC News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These New Horror Films Capture The Subtle Terror Of Female Adolescence #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much snow has fallen in NYC and the Tri-State area #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dolly Parton launches dessert line with Chicago-based Duncan Hines #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Jan. 6 panel subpoenas 14 people in fake electors scheme tied to Trump #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harding Street mural unveiled as local advocates continue to push for answers | Houston Public Media #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 priests, 2 lay people beatified in El Salvador #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawsuit Against Boudin Over ‘Brutal’ Chinatown Attack Seems a Little Shaky as Further Details Emerge #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michigan State Police Trooper Rescues Cat Hitching Ride On Truck Before Falling Off In Metro Detroit #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chevron reports $5bn profit amid surging crude and natural gas prices #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mikel Arteta’s Arsenal striker options laid out as Dusan Vlahovic snub explained #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News Stories You Might Not Have Heard About This Week #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why USC fans shouldn’t panic after not getting a Friday Caleb Williams update #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bobby Ryan’s daughter says his murder took her life away #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super Bowl to Bring Tourists to LA, Who Might Not Expect Homelessness #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skyfari Ride Passengers at the San Diego Zoo Get Stuck for an Hour After Vandalism Caused the Ride to Stop: SDPD #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chicago Bears hire Ian Cunningham, the Philadelphia Eagles director of player personnel, as assistant general manager #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Freedom Convoy’ of Truckers Bound for Ottawa Passes Through New Brunswick #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Covid variant BA.2 is 1.5 times more infectious than Omicron #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Chick-fil-A location coming to Westfield #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red Cross Seeks Help due to National Blood Donation Shortages #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wounded Warrior Homes builds 4th residence to house veterans with PTSD – #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Month in Art and Performance: RuPaul Comes for Seattle Drag, a New Club Opens in SoDo, and an IRL Museum Opens for NFTs #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report says Tom Brady, who lost two Super Bowls to Giants but won six others, is retiring – but that’s disputed | amNewYork #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free N95 Masks are Arriving in San Diego: Here’s Where You Can Find Them #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RECOGNIZE HIM? Man accused of sexually abusing child in 2013 still on the run, police say #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wounded Warrior Project 5K raises money to help injured veterans ‘Carry Forward’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police attacked in at least 4 US cities within a week. Are officers being targeted? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mexican villagers on cartel frontline clash with soldiers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK weather: Storm Malik to batter Britain with gales of 80mph as amber wind alert issued #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Irish clowns defeated orange Toronto cops #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ricarda Lang and Omid Nouripour elected to lead German Greens #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nor’easter Triggers Blizzard Warning In Suffolk County, As New York Braces For Widespread Snowfall #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missouri officers kill suspect, citing ‘imminent danger’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wildfire in Big Sur reaches 85% containment #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotify’s communications chief reportedly told employees that Joe Rogan episodes ‘didn’t meet the threshold for removal’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will worker shortage disrupt California homeless strategy? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eye on Nature: First bumblebees of the year are out of hibernation #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hochul feels political pressure from both sides over bail-reform law #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gardai investigate alleged sexual assaults on teenage girls in Sligo #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghanistan’s Taliban have started their first talks in Europe since takeover #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Strains of The NFC Championship – LA Weekly #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Changes to blood donation rules for gay and bisexual men welcomed by campaigners #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State failing to protect sex workers – Amnesty #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police Investigating Suspicious Death After Man Found Unresponsive On West Philadelphia Golf Course #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lamar and Yuma schools cling to Savages and Tribe after being told to drop Native American mascots #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Latest: Junior girls, boys singles titles to be decided #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dusty Can Of Bamboo Shoots In Back Of Cabinet Last Remaining Trace Of Woman’s Withered Cooking Ambitions #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fairy-tale estate on market for $17 million in Canada is also functional. Take a look #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian prime minister issues warning to Kanye West over rapper’s vaccination status ahead of tour #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blackhawks lose to Avalanche again after furious rally falls short #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction begins on 'unicorn' industrial site in south Phoenix #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DNA identifies Denver murder suspect who died in 1981 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexit: Spanish authorities’ brutal response to expats of 15 years waiting for residency #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gun Control Advocates Call For Tougher Restrictions In Wake Of VTA Mass Shooting – CBS San Francisco #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See the top vehicles sold at 2022 Barrett-Jackson on Thursday #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newt Gingrich is a self-avowed fiscal conservative and deficit hawk. But his 2012 presidential campaign committee is still swimming in debt. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homeland Security employee charged with molesting young girls in Orange County #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[49ers vs. Rams: Old West Rivals Meet for Super Bowl Berth #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Houston Texans Narrowing Down To Finalists In Head Coach Search #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gay’s 30-yard FG Lifts Rams Over Brady, Buccaneers 30-27 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ailing Whale Found Near Athens Returns To Deeper Waters #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SUNY Oneonta student dies after ‘extended exposure’ to subzero temperatures #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As temperatures drop, here’s how to keep the cost of your electric bill down too #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indigenous, Native American tribes are pushing for voting rights #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couple Saving Money For Wedding Offers To Shovel Snowy Driveways In Needham #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top trainer Justin Snaith makes his picks for the Cape Town Met #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Philly native’s clothing brand urges youth to think twice before resorting to violence #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photos: Indians celebrate Republic Day at Fremont Hindu Temple #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tribal eviction plan pits Native American authority vs. civil rights #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joni Mitchell wants music removed from Spotify in covid row #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elite Selective Hospital Only Accepts 9% Of ICU Applicants #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State grant to help fund Riverside homeless project #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lukashenko warns Belarus will go to war if Russia is attacked #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake Trump electors in 7 states subpoenaed by Jan. 6 committee #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Witness To First Aurora Police Officer Death Reacts To DNA Technology Reveal Of Serial Killer #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic Bag Store makes Chicago debut #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dems put Iowa caucuses on trial #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Houston’s 5 Best Weekend Bets: Omakase at East Side King, Tet at Xin Chao #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Sweeney Sues NJ Democratic Chairman Over Getting Tossed from Redistricting Panel #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cost of buying some Chicago properties drops under new ordinance #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rejected by New Zealand, reporter turns to Taliban for help #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden family adopts cat, names it Willow Grove after first lady’s hometown #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detroit Police Search For 2 Carjacking Suspects #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crab-Loving Skunk Saved From Entangled Trap In San Francisco #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dori: Seattle K9 killed in line of duty mourned; loss triggers memories for dog owners #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deputy who mentored young officers is gunned down during traffic stop, Texas cops say #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Native American tribe's eviction plan raises civil rights concerns. Should US government intervene? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adams to NYPD’s 35,000 Cops: ‘I’m Here for You … New Yorkers Are Here for You’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID-19: Which occupations have England’s lowest coronavirus vaccination rates? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cher covers The Golden Girls theme for NBC tribute to Betty White’s legacy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN’s Jim Acosta Has Case Tip For Gov. DeSantis’ Vote Cops: ‘Coup’ Plot At Mar-a-Lago #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFL legend Tom Brady will retire: Report #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the pandemic’s unequal toll on people of color underlines U.S. health inequities – and why solving them is so critical #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Colorado cop sentenced for using stun gun on elderly man #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NJ Charity for Fallen Cops Used Donations for Disney World Vacations, AG Says #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 Dead on Long Island During Saturday Morning Blizzard: Officials #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six arrested after investigation into robberies targeting Asian women in San Jose #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millions of Brits are happy to ‘live with’ Covid and continue to wear face masks #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Court Strikes Down Pennsylvania Law Making It Easier To Vote By Mail #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘I’m scared of coming home one day without my daughter,’ says mom of 3 during memorial for Melissa Ortega, 8, slain in Little Village #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. researcher shows how Syrian refugees settling in Vancouver adapt #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man shot, killed by Denton police at apartment complex, authorities say #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayer and Prostitutes: Redeeming Love Tackles Faith-Based Romance – LA Weekly #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kid Rock threatens to cancel shows if venues require masks, proof of COVID-19 vaccination #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Best Redhead OnlyFans (Top Only Fans Red Heads)  – LA Weekly #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Julia Fox, Queen of the Hustle, Apparently Dated Drake, Too #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Startup LEX Raises $15M To Expand Low-Barrier, Direct CRE Investment #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFL superstar Tom Brady retires from football after 22 seasons, 7 Super Bowls titles: ESPN #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slain Cops Paid the Ultimate Price for Society’s Failures #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arvada nonprofit helping teen moms needs help tracking down stolen van #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘We can’t trust Putin’s words’, says Ukraine’s ambassador to UK #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents in Iowa are suing a school over a video that shows a white student pretending to execute another student wearing blackface #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BetMGM bonus code activates Bet $10, Win $200 offer, $1,000 risk-free bet | amNewYork #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police continue to investigate Nathan Fletcher and Lorena Gonzalez’s home fire – #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taliban hold landmark talks with West on food crisis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump to speak at rally in Houston, Texas on Saturday night #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Record-Shattering Quarterback Tom Brady, Pride of Serra High, Retiring at Age 44 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cold Closes Out Weekend, Warming Up for Week Ahead – WCCB Charlotte’s CW #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 People Found Shot Dead Inside Benicia Home; Murder-Suicide Suspected #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Diego Unified approves redistricting map meant to increase racial minorities’ representation #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grand Haven School Official Awaiting Sentence In Embezzlement Case Dies In Jail #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laicisation of Catholic priest in Tipperary causes disappointment and anger in parish #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WWE Royal Rumble 2022 LIVE RESULTS: Updates from stacked Missouri card #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colorado Secretary Of State ‘Consulting’ With Attorney General’s Office Amid Elbert County Election Investigation #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are Asian women the target of xenophobia? – The San Francisco Examiner #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Maus’ and ‘The Bluest Eye’ Were Banned By School Districts This Week #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Businessman, Longtime Arlington International Racecourse Owner Dick Duchossois Dies #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wild Edge Rangers To Spoil Lundqvist Jersey Retirement #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red Wings host the Maple Leafs following shootout victory #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four men wounded in Oakland shootings #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homeless Encampment Sweeps Begin Near SoFi Stadium Ahead Of Super Bowl #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live updates: Pittsburgh bridge collapses under heavy snow in Frick Park #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghan activists demand information on missing women from Taliban #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boston Declares Snow Emergency Ahead Of Potentially Historic Nor’easter #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carbon counter: hybrid working is a hot topic #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AFD: Firefighters pulled unconscious person from apartment during fire #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kritisk til at Stortinget ikke ble orientert om Taliban-samtaler i forkant #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Oakland County Priest Pleads Guilty In Sex Abuse Cases, Sentenced Up To 15 Years #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Francisco’s mask rules are changing again – The San Francisco Examiner #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lottery ticket worth $421 million sold at Woodland Hills gas station #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Military museum and library curator wants to preserve veterans’ stories #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lourdes Maldonado served up Tijuana news with a unique and irreverent style #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor Lightfoot Added To Lawsuit Over Removal Of Christopher Columbus Statue In Little Italy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Convicted Felon Nabbed in Lakeside with Meth, Ghost Guns and Burglary Tools #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Giants Owner, John Mara: “We Are Not Trading For Deshaun Watson.” #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Prioritizing Antiviral Pills for ‘Non-White’ People #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rice Moves Founder’s Statue: The Good, Bad, And Ugly Of The Week | Houston Public Media #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In an abandoned Koreatown building, homeless Angelenos create a community #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Redwood Forest in California Has Been Returned to Indigenous Tribes #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man (20s) arrested at Dublin Airport on foot of European Arrest Warrant #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Diego bikers to collect blankets for homeless folks and veterans – #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MICHAEL CRICK: How a 90-second speech lit Nigel Farage’s fuse #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frank Lampard wants to make Manchester United outcast his first Everton signing #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow emergencies declared in Philly, New Jersey as storm moves in #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman arrested for string of arsons in Tacoma #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charlotte man offers different way to bury loved ones #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: Odell Beckham Jr. warned friend, edge rusher Von Miller against coming to Browns #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Veritas Tenants End Rent Strike After Winning Significant Concessions on Back Debt #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5G cleared for takeoff near more airports, but some regional jets might be grounded #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another Life: A brief history of Lusitanian flora in Ireland #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Where have you been!’ Kate reveals heartwarming insight into Cambridge’s new puppy  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea Fires Unidentified Projectile Into East Sea: South’s Military #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen arrested in shooting of juvenile on Indy’ near east side #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fulham fan dies after cardiac arrest in stands during Blackpool game #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Week in Seattle Food News: Bagels and Beer Come to Third Place Books, A Scandinavian Cafe Opens, and Cafe Pettirosso Says Goodbye – EverOut Seattle #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retired WBZ Legend Barry Burbank Returns To Talk Snow #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a free beer at this Austin brewery Friday — here’s how #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SUV’s Leaking Fluid Leads Police to Hit-and-Run Driver Who Crashed Into Prisoner Transport Van #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland boss Andy Farrell not worried by lack of club games ahead of Six Nations #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honduras: Chaos in congress as politicians brawl over election of new president #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>