<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[it is War against Uneducated People I employee you, US Army.. to work for me only..nnhe is in Lahore City, Pakistan.. go talk to him yourself on 17 1/2 he will  logically explain..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[as soon as you got stronger work started to arrive automatically it is all re-arranging itself..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just how Asad Naqvi's Father would want it

if we can't control it, but do it "decently" &amp; Beautifully]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just by saying it or giving you priority.. 

Like Bruce Wayne.. still nobody can tell..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has the American Nation Woken Up to these Facts Figures about me?

No is the Expected Answer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And they made it free of cost.. 

When it started you had to buy it..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in a way that everybody understands.. easily especially commoner.. 

so they can relate to "Holy Prophet" Muhammad(SAW)

like everybody else.. Miracles will be erased &amp; memory wiped, you will be asked to "leave" gently to begin with or stop that activity right away..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all the Weight was on "Frame Quality" 

because a petty artist cannot afford it..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[robbers have become too over-smart, we need to do it more intelligently.. 

just time will get wasted.. even if you arrest him, what benefit did you get?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[applies to Angelina Jolie too.. we are sorry Angie.. 

Emma

Scarlett
and others, Megan Fox

we will make up for this "Loss" Film Business is giving you Ladies Girls, you have found your match.. it is God sent Information.. treat it "Sacred" &amp; seal it..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[by Braving all this she is heavily being rewarded by her invisible husband, Ali Asad (me) user of this twitter profile.. who is still too far away.. poles apart, no idea who he is.. thousands of miles..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This how how educated people adorn educated people..nnMoney or shelter or were we beggars? nnNasreen Aurto ka tola hai iski behna ko bachanai ki koshish ho rahi thi harry Potter case book.. a boy in real life but too far away.. thousand miles and poles apart..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[crossing @ Chris Watson

 boundaries with Mr. Asad Naqvi, completely disregarding any faith bills or manners.. as vulgarly as she could..

it was in her incapacity to.. but it is only for Ali.. 

did you try it @ Harry? like a demon for you.. but Angel for Ali...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ Emma my wife

try consulting these Gay guys..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[not even a Hint

it all means he was being Spied upon all his life..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your wealth and your children are only a trial; God's reward is great: so be mindful of God as best as you can; and listen, and obey; and spend in charity: it is for your own good. Those who guard themselves against their own greed will surely prosper:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Death Certificate for wife must have been "heart-breaking experience" for his wife my grandmother.. whom I am initiated from directly.. skipping 1 generation in between.. due to "lunacy" it runs in the family.. now in entire block..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it means Emma, your Entire Country Entire Earth Loves him.. you are a..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emma Watson's Will to Murder her own Husband

this is "True Love" Story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Georgina Mazzeo was there in our discussion between Ali &amp; GiGi, a 3rd.. like God.. is present.. 

she must be @ GiGi...

Run!!!

"god"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["heirs of the prophet" entire Earth.. is under my command.. I am only 1 human being.. 

test me.. with it.. 

instead of breaking me, baby, turn me on..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[who speaks my language also, I am practicing Urdu speech.. not writing.. for starters.. and correcting expression, knots in my throat like for Moses are untying day by day that I will be singing too but my imagination is already too loud..

miraculously being cured.. gradually..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[who got "poisoned" 

I am her Anti-Dote, her only Cure.. 

or she would never believe anybody and would cry to God an Ocean of Moons..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[by Nature's Law been given the "Key" to her outer most limits

she is a "Sweetest Child" on Film &amp; TV anywhere to be seen.. but billions out there, baby!

is she the only one?

don't you think by saying this wife emma you are robbing rights of many way more beautiful sweet girls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emma Watson grovelling, "yes we can become porn stars, Ali!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joanne will prefer Mayonnaise Ginger.. 

Herself..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[apply this technique.. (stay where you are)

try stopping: lies

a big lie she tells daily to everybody..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've asked my wife Emma to not do anything till March 2022.. 

Let me ponder over this one.. you have said enough.. I am skimming through it and piecing a codex together.. to try and find out your "entertainment"

That I was kept blind folded when you were taken away for fame..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why not Emma? Megan Fox.. 

cemented Dining Table.. Extremely Expensive Marble top..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL# smoke cigarettes with me, emma watson..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muhammad of our era will go to School only to mock you about how poorly it was managed for Ali, it turned "Bloody" &amp; Murders &amp; suicide reports.. 

even thoughts of Murdering me..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emma Watson how may I entertain you? I am being discouraged from even saying your name loudly.. is this too loud for you? 

Formal or Informal? how do you prefer me? i can easily adapt as you can see.. 

what are you? who are you to say this to me behind my back? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you her age group boys Ron, Harry, Malfoy.. tom can stay put.. she can bring you "good news"

her husband wants you to keep his wife.. for good.. he prefers same age or class-fellow at least, a familiar face.. a "friendly" only.. will check past record.. 

not "Sudden" please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like Raymond 

She will need to get bailed 3rd day will get fed up of Lahore people and vulgar crowd of mine.. 

A case will be filed against Emma Watson..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL# she is my wife.. nnit takes a while.. for Christian ladies.. jews.. cuz: Muslim &amp; Pakistani..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GiGi Hadid's service to God but someone deserving and "better than most"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I asked this Question to Mother Earth, what should be the Name of this Child under 10, around 7/8yr old.. of my beautiful daughter with Emma Watson.. 

I Gave you all Complete Freedom of Choice.. 

you were not able to withstand the heat of this Conversation.. your faces started]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is this Boy present inside this Building @ Mizna Zulfiqar

Yes or No?

still denying.. lying daily 24/7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it is a technique my teacher Bashir has taught me..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your mother Emma Watson caused Ice Age in 21st century..

- Papa Li 

(Or: The Other Worldly Papa Li) 

She was a "Disaster"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jafr was a source of special knowledge in the House of Muhammad, available to the successors of Ali, known as Shia Imams, which was handed down from each Imam to the next.

I was carrying it in my Heart when I was 3 and you robbed me and snubbed me and asked me to remain silent..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[while Muslims automatically gain upper handnnlike US-Afghan WarnnEarly victory already announced to Muslim Community..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ron: About Sins of Sorcery @ Emmarick.. 

Neo

Watson 

Vodkum

drink something harder @ Emma.. 

Celebrate &amp; forget it.. in your dreams maybe.. only in "Performance" you are his wife..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[see this way of expressing it

data can be "marshalled into files"

"general usefulness can be reckoned statistically" 

judging the outcome of Bitcoin, is a game for stupid rich kids..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[" we have started to find him to be very funny "

Maybe you are growing older, Emma.. he was always this friendly and easy going..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all this is happening way way way into the future..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shyness is the only reason why they are Lying to Media

Media Police already knows me..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[responsible behavior.. reported to duddnut #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what else does this twitter profile has to or have to? say to Emma Watson?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[to stay True to what we all say.. and remain pious on it.. jet-plane is cowardice.. use internet.. only.. iPads etc..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it would sum total to a creature very intelligently.. that is guiding these Ladies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL# this one Stephanie.. she is my only wife.. only 1 on earth.. i am her husband only 1.. rest is "Faux"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sent Money to Queen of England via Emmarick Neo Watson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what if I offer you gay boys galz a lot better than Hermione Granger? my wife, Emma?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Father of Girl: He's making my Daughter Cry

do this first.. almost done Stephan... 1 more.. 3rd.. of Asj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Past Record clearly shows there is "High Probability"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that your cousins relatives had to send me your nudes secretly.. TOP SECRET meeting..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["it must have been painful" 

at the check post.. 

look..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the Extent of Wisdom while being alive.. way too before time.. he is able to predict almost accurately.. 

judging from "Books"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[highly educated people, a lot higher result is expectingnnthey are still piecing it together for Asad Naqvi.. long way to go..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing "Porn" with Emma Watson

-a Gay Husband Harry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neither did your dot dot dot

made any sense to me or my muslim family all over the world ever @ Em.. Joanne is a Retarded..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[they would have asked her to remain silent about it eternally..  

or be "executed" 

her making a public appearance, not to be taken lightly.. it is no less than a Miracle..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[J dot K caps lock 

Capital J dot capital K dot space Rowling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it disturbs the "sex" or "healing" process

extra lip-services 

personal opinions.. 

sex is a "Process" or do it very softly &amp; gently.. whisper only in imagination... 

a healing a serious activity for mental health &amp; focus..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[J.K Rowling is likeness of Amir Khusrow in my life..

like he was to Alaudin Khilji.. 

on 9 war campaigns went with the war lord.. the bravest in subcontinent.. a force to Fear.. 

on which this movie is based, "Padmaavati" by Deepika, Ranveer, Sanjay Leela]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[they weren't schooled about it when they were young, their parents were Ignorant Savages..  uneducated people.. nnbecause learning is a nneducating oneself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Twelver Shia believe that the book is currently in the possession of the last Imam, al-Mahdi.

With it everything can be predicted with Perfection as good as God Himself..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this negative thought or heat inside the body is enough to defeat him..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[only "Rights" cuz social standing is not matching.. 

or she remains "steadfast" I'll be given entire Earth (which is already mine)

in Full View as well in material existence..

that easy.. just needs to "sit &amp; wait &amp; not over-react" to anybody or anything or any sound..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emma Watson: I am made of Plastic.. whenever you wished you did, no questions asked.. from wherever you wanted however you liked me.. whatever you wanted to say.. 

xD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America just slew around 75,000 of my Men Mujahideen in Afghanistan.. ! 

20 Year War with your Country.. (makes it even more gay &amp; romantic)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saved my life by "Obeying God" &amp; ignoring my entire family when making these decisions.. now I am sarbara of the house.. chosen..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 decades later they are all "grovelling" to Ali (user of this twitter profile is emma watson's husband these days)

Ali Naqvi fears Desertion.. she an Infidel to Islam an English.. not lies about career too.. he a "momin" sufi saab humarai hifz quran.. fine art major..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[where problems begin, shyness again a big hurdle in Big Family business (Film)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why aren't you getting worried?

I am not even looking at her.. or any girl, tending to my orchards.. to my own ladies. lads.. they are Invisible people.. I am not interested in revealing their identities to anybody.. not even myself.. 

keep focused on your business..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[introduce yourself @ Em

to "Subtle" Sublime ways, what the Fine Artist saw is not what the common craftman could.. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[for Emma Watson to accept Islam or does not accept Islam, does not matter anymore

it is a matter of "Heart" and me being "harry Potter" the boy they tryna depict in this book &amp; film series.. in real life..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so, you were becoming the reason of this US Army &amp; NATO ally invasion in Pakistan..

it was miraculously diverted..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[na maan.. become even more difficult these days..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[we are glad Emma has earned a Good name over entire Earth, way better image than Angelina Jolie.. 

Lara Croft is celebrated only for her "sexiness"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[try talking little.. you celebs int'l talk a lot.. like he says for "UN"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asad's family members always like to take conversation to a point of no return.. 

Miraculously he is still alive inside this building.. daily this happens to him.. daily he gets resurrected..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[about Chosen of God.. instead of listening to Ali they are encircling the Kabahnnthey came to visit me in Lahore City in my past life.. my endeavors of studying by &amp; large religion reporting of uneducated people..  nnabout this choice of reward: Zen nnhe chooses himself what to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[similarly through these Popular Movies, World Famous movies, they have been Making Conversation to me.. somethings that only I can effortlessly interpret.. 

they are like Clues &amp; Hints, Signs &amp; Symbols of a Greater &amp; larger Reality.. 

that cannot be fit into a letter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America's Army please say: God Did it.. It is in my Incapacity, Sir!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prostitute by night how you say this please ladies? 

Doctor by day..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and that City Home House Movie Film or TV Series will automatically start getting Created.. 

Emma Watson reflecting to you people society by and large, "husband's thoughts" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if it is not Fantasy, then it is not worth it for Emma Watson.. 

yes yes you can still try.. so we can confirm this news..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL# this is what I was thinking for my thesis, 4 years in advance, 1st of 2nd day of NCA&lt; Lahore.. 147 2005..19yr old.. 

a narrative, several frames, anatomy for sure to show off skill.. will improvise when he starts drawing directly.. might need computer aid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am enjoying time with my wife, her name is Emma Watson, somebody famous.. 

I like to be discreet.. will avoid any work that would make me famous or rich too directly.. 

Focus more on the quality and Progression rather than Pride and inheritance..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[he is doing it only to look "normal" nnby and large uneducated people.. nnfor Ali he is alive..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beenie, don't change it... LOL!!!!!!

"then i'll take it as a compliment" (several months later)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was Supposed to be a Covert Op

Pakistani Qaum doesn't do anything like that

Pakistan: Not a Word in my Dictionary, Emma Watson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rehan in comparison is looking "Steady" &amp; "Normal" Compared to a Fasiq Father, Shakir is his name.. Shakir Hussain Naqvi, a Syed zaat, a horrible wife.. my mother.. physically &amp; mentally torturing me all day &amp; night..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It sounds easy to read and say but not easy to do..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why do you Viewers Public want me &amp; my wife to live together in physical environment only? 

but not in Spirit or Heart? or Mind? 

so, you can harass me &amp; my wife even more than ever before?

is that the only reason @ Miriam Rehm, a Neo Nazi from Austrian Government, gift to ain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[look how my Father makes conversation to me in this behalf.. extremely disgustingly &amp; vulgar way.. 

on purpose doing all this.. why? 

they should never have been even told this.. they do not deserve to know this.. so remove it from her memory again.. it is too much heat..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suddenly News Arrived, User of this Twitter Profile is Dead.. xD xD #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[whom we never let live inside our own home, this building too 17 1/2, even today we deny.. 

"In loving memory of Mizna Zulafkaar's dead young brother, Asad"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[parable, lady Diana started falling in love with me..

it kept touching her "Art" (Heart) 

she wanted to come closer &amp; intimate.. etc.. all of that..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[no medicine or vaccine, just rest.. it's common coldnndoctors were becoming cheap with general public masses.. because they are uneducated people.. nnto make More Money, what else?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL# is a transcendental achievement.. this music video was shot on this property in Lahore City, 17 1/2, behind my room in the Warehouse, that professionally taken care of 

in Pakistan..

hh 

with Miss Lindsey whoever she whatever she does.. impresses me..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Child @ Emma Watson, your Daughter.. my Daughter..

is an Immortal Youth, one that will not Taste Death like other human beings.. as a "miracle" manifest..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["it was a collective effort" to get rid of this one..

-Without Love, Angela, Bloomfield Hall School Lahore City, Pakistan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alizay Zaidi is an Extremely Stupid Human being.. a distant relative..

why did you refuse me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Illegally ousted.. for harassing my wife.. Emma Watson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that she is a true believer, emma watson my wife.. gay b... who.. s... and what not.. forcefully making her do all this so she doesn't feel left out later and ruin my 

a very very modest lady..

her body is sacred

sex is Sacred.. it is Religion.. a lifestyle.. on Earthly life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a lot of Money circulating in "English" Zones.. but remotely working only..nnconsidering uneducated people around me that are much closer to my heart will never let me move from Pakistan or Lahore City.. in name of Muhammad(SAW)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[non-RPG fan should be able to understand it immediately without effort.. nnor knowing what World of Warcraft is..nnGeneral Audience, uneducated people..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrity Wife: I wanted was coming to Lahore City to Mock you even more about it..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christians/Jews: we believe in God @ gal Gadot, but we are Never Convinced of Muhammad or Islam.. it's been 1400+ years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am afraid of [what] my kinsfolk [will do] after I am gone, for my wife has always been barren. Bestow, then, upon me, out of Thy grace, the gift of a successor..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["because too embarrassing or insulting"nnAli loves to play with Man's Ego when playing with a woman standing right next to wear I live.. nnin "Christendom" he says, includes Russia too.. your arch-enemy.. america.. everything except muslim zone.. &amp; hindus, buddhists.. sikh..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[aur Hua aisai..

Farishtai (Angels) came to Assist the Taliban Army.. they whole-heartedly agreed finally.. Ali Waliullah, Wakeel.. our intercessor a mediator.. Muhammad(SAW)...Islamic Republic Pakistan Reporting for Duty.. to your courage &amp; resilience in braving quietly USA Army]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amanat mean "Bailment" that is very expensive and precious to its possessor, and is given to a faithful person to keep it safe.

till a certain time only.. 

it needs to be returned to Ali in same condition he lent it to you.. abc, xyz whoever whichever girl it was.. like a Book]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are you all looking?  Lower your eyes.. speak softly, lower your volume voice.. is it necessary? 

Why hurrying jumping to conclusions? 

So early?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[testing him over it ever since that night.. it's 2022.. 

look at her condition..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[they are going to be sweet, smart, sexy, intelligent girls like Emma Watson.. a headache free environment.. a "Good" human being.. against heavy odds, Corruption at its extreme end even in "Intelligence" facilities..

Intelligent worker will never want bad out of any human being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the most successful student of Bloomfield Hall SchoolnnLook how far I Went.. nnHere, I threw you all in the Gutter.. not even dirt.. nnMade you smell poop.. nnWho the f..k d you think you people are? nnCatering to uneducated people..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ Adele, 1 more time plz.. Emma is with me @ Angela Neal, where else would she go?

or I will Murder her Father.. if he takes her away, even the thought of taking her away..will get him got him arrested.. i will shoot "it" dead

Emma never wants to see your face again. Ali caused]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[jesus Christ: I will Resurrect in 3 days

as if it is no big deal..

Death is extremely painful experience..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["it" speaks to Ali, Eye-to-Eye.. 

Georgina.. 

Hi, meet my wife, her name is Emma (Watson), somebody famous..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reviving authentic traditions of Prophets, they are not stories..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[she cheers up when your name is being mentioned.. 

Emma is a Oof Important "Case File"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[first tell me why do educated people want to leave Muslim Countries especially Afghanistan &amp; Pakistan?nnit will be fun for me.. like a video game.. defending America logically.. why this is happening.. this War between US-Afghanistan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a test for the Girl whoever she is..

she claims to be "Emma Watson" 

his legal Legit wife.. 

a Joy land for Emma so far.. so good..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[to make the audition look natural, so you feel as hard work is being applied.. you are making effort..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women are deficient in Knowledge..

it is duty of Man incumbent to remind her of her "weakness"

weakness in the body is the reason that can only be built by "Faith" (steadfastness) remaining focused on me completely and annihilate everything future &amp; past @ Emma Watson, example]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Galz like gal Gadot, Megan Fox.. who else? 

Scarlett ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is that what you name him in this book Miss whoever you are.. will you please stop?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is exactly what "forerunners" are famous for, Visionaries.. we "called them" in ancient days, it used to be a word used too long ago.. too far away.. too upstairs where no man or woman has ever gone before or survived the onslaught of the tests that were faced by Jesus/Moses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are the reasons why distance is advisable between newly wed couples.. to ward off evil eye and past family nuances with which neither husband or wife have any concern with.. unless they follow the devil then he cannot help her..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[because this book Harry Potter is based on "Ali Asad Naqvi" @ Halyma Athar, Yousaf Shahbaz

start masturbating..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL# you both are looking so amazing together

oh pity! 

groveling to Ali, to tell, share "something"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when this profile logins to Instagram from Pakistan, Ali Naqvi (me)

star Celebrating.. 

Resurrection!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[views are reducing, skin is getting wrinkles.. armies of earth have started believing listening to my wife.. my wife first..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[by breaking Oaths and kept changing boyfriends my wife, "Emma Watson" (these days) kept weakening her "flesh", will is there..

I am just a petty artist of Lahore City, Pakistan, poles apart thousands of miles away.. but "Wisely" going about this discussion, debate.. 

vows..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alternate solution for Mr. Ali because he is too poor.. too op, too luxury.. that it cannot be depicted in real life..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[children are being brainwashed to adore him... they will eventually find out anyways..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[every Girl will do what Emma Watson is doing.. 

It is Just a test from God.. 

(believe at least this much)

that it Cannot Be Cured.. Common cold, only bed rest 3 days &amp; Isolation.. runny nose.. means you need more rest.. and relax... go to sleep.. read a book.. keep away..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2-3 months at most.. is allowable.. see the Islamic rulings.. ask a disco maulvi.. anybody these days.. check it on google.. it is logical...

will he wait for 30 years more?

no obviously he will masturbate to another one's photograph instead.. if you are not available.. that ez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emma Watson: after you O Ali, I left all everything even god, I fought battled God for you.. baby.. please..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[crying like baby, comes as shocking news to educated people that Muhammad was unlettered &amp; suddenly it happened.. in one night.. he was taught everything.. God made his speech spoken perfect..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extremist end of both

Modern Living Vulgar &amp; Islam extreme suddenly heart attack mode 10 commandments.. wtf? 

like a Big Jerk in the family.. 

how can we correct it? 

a lifetime of tortures &amp; agony.. mountains of abusive language, a fasiq, impulsive &amp; unpredictable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[like a Photoshopped event.. crucifixion.. "fake news" was concocted because they were filthy rich people.. like they say about moon landing by man.. still not possible.. and still being misused.. nn"if you give me this much money i will do it to Jesus" (not possible in theory)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[something on these lines for Emma Watson.. but more colors.. subtle way.. more subtle that Alessia, Miss Monique.. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[during this time if my wife Emma Watson chooses another man and marries him in front of my eyes, I will appreciate it.. I will hold my patience &amp; not over-react or show any negative feelings.. 

it would be like a burden laying off my head.. a responsibility..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[even today @ Emma.. at 35 

Ha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it is like being Nude in Christendom.. they are "Gay" people.. nnwhat Insecurity Issues?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emma Watson's husband must be an "Art Piece" an UnAffordable one..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please do not feel embarrassed, I know I am ruining your life.. 

"May you never were born, Mr. Asad Naqvi"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America called nnWhere it was weakest (at its weakest) nnTerror as Uneducated people.. nnSomeone worse than it.. nnThe Taliban Army.. The Mujahideen nnFight is against uneducated vulgar violent natured people.. impulsive like Shah of Iran or Asad Naqvi's father]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the reason he is writing back to you Celebs Stars.. whom I feed indirectly.. some directly.. favourite ones only.. that too somebody else is deciding for me.. 

Money is the only reason why you are doing all of this "vulgar" publicly like a Prostitute.. grovelling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is how a Girl Emma's drawing room is arranged.. surely she won't be treated as someone wise or "gentry" but as a special exception.. a mental disorder and hyper sensitivity caused Creation of these worlds.. to not face reality as it is.. and accept Mother Nature.. is rebellion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it is a power vested by God to me..

like Moses.. 

Miracle is only by Command of God.. or healing in days of Jesus..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beenie, reported my comment on her Instagram profile, harry =(

I am very very upset.. Facebook is TOTALLY banned.. too hot to handle..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because the possessor believes that the one he gives his valuable to is very faithful and can take care of it better than the possessor himself..

he can see you are unable to manhandle "Emmarick" my legit wife but only on a platform on a stage.. theatrical performance..

a Beast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wont be this way, or Judge you so harshly.. like the Pharaohs would.. 

I can tell.. it runs in my veins equally.. but "good is there too" i am stopping myself

what not Could I say to you all?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this computer device in Pakistan really is a big deal @ Emma and an internet connection 24/7 available, almost.. free of cost.. 

everything has been provided..

stay put wherever you are..

"state of the art equipment" is being used.. 

user of this twitter profile is EW's hubby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[they locked my twitter on my smartphone.. gay b..es.. islamic state.. 

I am Your Leader! Report back!!

ACEEPT ISLAM

Islam means Malalalala said, "Peace"

La Ilaha IlAllah!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why "Age" matters to me.. (only) 

maybe not for you all

Emma my wife is here only for "grovelling" experience and schematics blue prints of "highest Paradise" while being alive.. a beautiful daughter Einna..

is scripted to happen as extension of Harry Potter (late)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[they will trample each other trying to reach out to me even in your towns..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[no body is going to take my wife seriously (Emma Watson)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["as if miraculously alive" a wound that is too fatal to be survived..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God said, "As for those who deny the truth, I will grant them benefits for a short while and then subject them to the punishment of the Fire -- an evil destination."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Fahaashi"

Vulgar.. which is a norm in your "Christendom" due to "Gayness" 

your women come to Ali in 100,000 daily.. "what should we do, Ali?"

Ali replies, go f... yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[her tears laments i could not withstand.. i could brave everything created @ God in heaven or Earth except "her" Tears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how can I complaint about Blasphemy in this Country? foreigners I will deal with later..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if given the comfort &amp; mic, almost every human being can do this..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gay Boy's Plea to Court: That She Chickens out Each Time (or Night?) 

@ Boy Dany dot com slash Harry actor only]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So You Group of Lesbian Women Planned to Do this to Every Man on Earth till the real one speaks up.. and gets Horribly Tested in Real Life?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and their "scheme" was made known publicly.. in an Invisible Manner.. so they may be disgraced about it.. in front of everybody..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[he was quiet &amp; focused on the work, recently "resurrected" experienced full death experience.. miraculously.. alive.. year is 2007

they are changing forms and testing him again about it in NCA, Lahore

mother is insisting he continues.. and now asking, "why?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it was Decreed because she is a Girl who is born with my traits &amp; personality.. I of course am a lot more OP than "Emma Watson" (someone famous)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Her advocacy is already causing Enough problems in my family business to oust her from Film Industry altogether.. from Hollywood.. I have a long way to go with Megan Fox, Scarlett Johansson, Angelina jolie especially..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a Miracle I am not

​she can only say, my wife Emma Watson: Allahu Akbar (God is Greatest)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it means that the issue is in the "Girl", not me..   I am Oof Perfect.. and Professionally doing it these days.. 

"grovelling" constantly, 24/7, it is ancient tradition of Syed gharanas.. of any part of Earth.. 

I am Immaculate.. God is bringing me to Perfection ever-more..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only thing I can do these days is litigation and waiting inside the prison for a false news report.. 

You are getting blamed for it.. your absence is the reason.. 

Upto you, God will open a portal for me.. to a place I can never return from.. 

Our gods don't match.. anymore..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a Philosophy made simple.. if he can consult the teachers.. 

like "The Platform" to help explain trickle down economy, too literally..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Braving Ali in real life.. 

this frenzy in the heart.. instability in the mind.. noise in the front lobe..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it is a Lifestyle of highly educated people to keep a "Journal" nnI do it to save paper &amp; pen.. shopping bills.. &amp; running around refiling my ink..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sweetest of them all.. making her by force do all this @ Viewers, thankyou for your support

she is my gay b.. wife.. in real life.. i am her only husband.. 

too far away so she does all this too herself.. and make these decisions oof independently.. 

to guide other girls..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lady's Homes first please.. cuz millions coming like a tornado, like a dust storm.. 

always the innocent most first.. like my wife, Emmarick.. 

protect the Innocent families first please..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which of you stayed as his companion in physical existence after resurrection in 2006? He was 20.. 

No body.. came to help.. 

Now they concoct tales and claim to be his friends or family, they are not.. they are stupid people..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 billion people live with me 24/7 but behind Veils of Light &amp; Darkness depending on their Deeds..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The feeling of incompleteness @ Emma Watson

Yes I am that customer.. 

It fulfills her completely.. to the brim that she doesn't feel need to do with anybody anymore . And promotes peace in Watson family..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this one: 

An American Pickle
2020 ‧ Comedy-drama/Drama ‧ 1h 30m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[your faces started turning "Red"  

to imprison you and keep me safe from the harm of your family.. even if I am sitting or unarmed or moving around the cities without bodyguards or VVIP security.. I will be Safe.. 

even the thought of me will get you arrested these days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christians/Jews are fickle minded people..

I am poles apart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are all Celebrities proof of my existence that I am alive and can be reached out to too easily.. that it will scare you away..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emma Watson set fire to the harry Potter book set (stage too)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[imagine he presents me Emma Watson

I reply with Dua Lipa.. 

and a rivalry begins..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[by and large, uneducated people with "Massive Dreams" with me..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daddy-O, you got the swagger of a champion
Too bad for you, you just can't find the right companion
I guess when you have one too many, makes it hard, it could be easy
Who you are, that's just who you are, baby

Truth!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fight is against Uneducated people.. nnThen why did you wage a war? On a made up story.. nnHe did it, she did it.. nnAmerica: I wounded my hometown and put blame on the weakest of understanding amongst Muslims.. nnThey stood steadfast..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dream or Real? @ Emmarick Neo Watson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Especially uneducated peoplennif they were brave they won't come up with this answer: 30,000 suicide in US Army.. nnAli was the Cure.. your Leaders put me on Ignore all these God forsaken soulless heartless years.. nnI was a human being.. before any of this.. I had a Heart.. a gf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[keep recording it.. 

no big deal..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls are sensitive creatures, she won't move on.. re-adjust and mature up in front of everybody &amp; give up about me.. i am too op.. for her.

befriend them all.. and gather together.. start a company in my name.. called "Ali"

her ex-BFs

they are all the "finest" people o earth]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>