<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Libs, finding out that it ain't so easy to buy a gun now is it? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So it's a lot easier to earn money now

In my day, I needed $16 for a cd. That was a week and a half worth of allowance.

Now, I stream songs for hours on end, every single day. As I'm sure millions of other do.

You're fine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did he also tell them that his bungling is the reason why most of them won't be getting what they asked for this year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And yet we now have sufficient evidence that Biden is batsht insane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone find it ironic that both major wrestling feds are run by Khan men #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I usually learned a lot of history from my father, but he was born the same year that this happened. That's how quickly they scrubbed this from history, that even his generation wasn't taught about it. And then Carter gave them a pass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Jesus, people cry about everything these days

I'm Italian. We eat sauce every Sunday. 

If someone called me 'very Italian', I'd puff my chest out with pride

Stop crying over stupid sht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Are they kidding? My father watched our births and then went and worked his next shift, like most fathers have done in the past. What a weak generation this is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Their inherent ability to climb is second to none]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We now have pigs claiming that retail theft is 'not that bad'

Society is deteriorating quickly #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was in a thrift store yesterday, and they had a double wide wheelchair.

I didn't even know they made them that big.

There's a reason why it was donated #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've had co workers rushed to the hospital, many after getting their hands caught in mail sorting machines Not much of an alternative than to go back to work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nah, I can't wear a mask while I'm downing my stash #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now my vaccinated aunt just called my mother from the hospital, she has covid

She said she felt like she was going to die

So I guess we've gone from 

The vaccine will stop you from getting it 

to-the vaccine will stop you from getting it badly

to-hey, at least you didn't die]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah, people (even libs) tend to stop listening to the media's whitewashing when it starts to affect their own pocketbook

They can't spin thousands of dollars extra, on the same exact items bought last year, as a positive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dude, that's a lib getting punched in your photo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How'd Afghanistan work out?

'Nam?

Iraq?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 90s hotness "Yo, we gonna have an overpopulation problem"

2020s hot take  "Yo, we needs more peoples"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm in awe that Trump was able to pull the rug out from under you TWICE 

You went running when you thought it would benefit you, then bashed him when you didn't get the job

Sit down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Says the white guy who gets home before sundown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just had burgers without fries because Biden can't wipe himself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He once called a black singer 'Michael Jackson' and 'Prince' within 60 seconds #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# More kids died from mini blinds, and it took the government DECADES to act

Funny how they jumped on the jab bandwagon so quickly though, right? $$$
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So after my double vaxxed and boosted Aunt and Uncle got covid last week, and my double vaxxed parents got it this week, Now my double vaxxed and boosted uncle has covid. He couldn't even speak on the phone when my mother called him for his bday. So who the fck did it protect?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're using Saget's death to scare you about covid. 

Nowhere in the article does it stat that he was double vaxxed and boostered 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It was great to a select audience that found that style entertaining. The same small audience that couldn't even keep ROH alive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "So the suspension was only an interim step"

Uh, yeah, we figured that out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Well, anyway"

That's all he says until 'mommy' saves him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The people hating on Greene for believing misinformation while they think that this is really her daughter.......... next level]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fans wearing paper bags on their heads Rank 2nd

(Hey, we still ain't the Jets)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The motherfcker is in the wrong business if he's worried about his 'portrayal'

His lack of maturity is the icing on his dud of a career. Not everybody is a headliner . Paul Diamond, Steve Regal, there are better who knew their role.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Every food deal on Slickdeals has a group of absolute morons citing fat/sugar/calorie content Meanwhile, our grandparents could lift cars and bend steel, while this generation can't lift their head of their pillow while using their phone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Balwdin was quoted as saying "Hey, if a car is being blamed for the Waukesha Christmas deaths, then I'm blaming the gun" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They became friends

Leaders need to learn from them
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The media in the U.S. has been showing warnings for people to leave over 6 weeks ago

You snooze, you lose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His overvalued sense of self worth is nauseating #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This reminds me of the Yankees paying an old player to sit out his contract rather than take up roster space.

By these imbeciles not 'shopping' there, Walgreens actually INCREASES profit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# He retired before I was born

When someone mentions Dick Butkus, I immediately think "Oh, the actor"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What's the matter science boy?

Picking and choosing again?
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Since you like people who use their real identities, I'll just leave this here #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I just saw this and almost lost my lunch The last part of my childhood looks like he has one foot in the grave and the other right behind #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# When my mother was in the hospital last week, her nurses name was Tabitha My mom asked if her parents were fans of 'Bewitched' She replied, well, my sister's name is Samantha 😅]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm a NC voter, and I say F ck them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Norman Lear is the Mel Brooks of tv

Guy outlived all of the actors on his shows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# People worried about climate don't build recording studios this large with these amenities #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Slappy, I was born in 77, and lived on Long Island

People were wearing Bell Bottoms in 95 when I was a Senior in High School. K.C. and the Sunshine band and others held packed concerts, I went to one.

I don't know what part of Idaho you're from, but it was huge here #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My father's coworker's son just bought a house next to his dad, last week Today, that coworker called out due to his son passing away. Mid 30s and he had a massive heart attack. Just too many 'sudden deaths' in the past year for it to be random.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 'So'

Every talking head starts their answer with it

WHY????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why is Kamala's face like this?

Does she even own a smile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, because fcking Moss Man, Beast Man and Orko were white #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is why AEW will always be bush league

Satiating the woke crowd doesn't grow your audience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah, because my food bill is 25% more than pre covid My 6 month car insurance premium went up $100 So yeah, consumer spending IS up, which doesn't equate to 'good']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nicky bagging more than Lester Holt, I bet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's like the last segment of 'Hee Haw'

I can't do this anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We're being repped by a guy playing records #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Every overweight, 60+ year old, female bus driver  played his music when I went to HS, back in the early 90s

He's the king of menopausal tunes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember this kid getting pissed back in high school, when I told him that he looked like Bill Parcels

Was I lyin'? 

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This one shocked the hell out of me

I never learned about this in school. I read every historical book I could get my hands on as a kid, none ever mentioned it. I only came across it in 2017, by accident

Yet they try to make Jan 6 into 9/11
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Media tries to keep you rattled

It's all about control]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Someone that sees the future but uses a profile pic from 1982]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That time WWE got a sweet deal on light blue boots that 'fell of the truck" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You're the kind of special person who thought January 6th was the end of the world You must've changed your undies 3 times already this morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How about the lower half pays for SOMETHING besides Air Jordans and braids #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Next month will mark 26 years online. I was here before 95% of the country

I've never posted a single picture, my real name or anything to do with who I am. It doesn't matter who I am. Everything I post is backed by articles or other evidence.

I'm not the only one #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We sent Chubsy Ubsy to war, and all we got were these lousy tweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The guy is a month younger than I am. It really isn't hard to get to be this age without being arrested multiple times or touching drugs. People make life so much harder than it has to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Is that why every country has a border

Stop with the prop, bro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The libs have been told about bot accounts for over 10 years, and they still fall for em #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# With Biden inflation, this is like 2 Super Bowl losses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You've got to stop going on conspiracy forums]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The 'fact checkers' are already tip toeing around his lies

Dictionaries are changing definitions

Twitter is banning his critics

WTF does Goebbels want now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Biden and Harris, alienating everyone on the way to a 2022 record loss of seats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# People went Christmas shopping and saw the new prices]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So less than 3 per day

Trump answered 20 questions before his take offs alone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Give him credit for being able to name 3 countries without calling one of them Candy land 🤣]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I guess when you have enough money, you gotta dig for problems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Most of the people who died spent their last years doing laps around dead malls #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Clean up what? The generations before them are the reason they can sit on their asses making youtube videos, playing video games + stuffing their faces, without working My grandfather was in Korea at age 16. These kids don't know reality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Apparently the physical fitness portion of the police test went the way of the dodo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Another frightened butterball who chose not to drop weight during the pandemic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They STILL can't find anything

Trump is like Irish Spring - Clean as a whistle 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She'd probably get hired to be on  'the View']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No, that's what the poor minorities do in Family Dollar and Dollar General. Those who can't afford to get locked into monthly contracts with $400 early termination fees I know because I shop there too. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's cause Elmo feels guilty about getting an innocent black man fired #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how much rear end work this car has had? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm about done with backing the blue They're mostly cowards This guy swoops in to take out a mother voicing an opinion, yet BLM destroyed city after city with zero repercussions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Walmart's brand ain't bad in a pinch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# First off, I ain't got that kind of time

Second, your last speech busted my TV's closed captioning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Riggghhttt, he chose happened to walk into the nearest building 

This is yet another example of our country having no credible media left]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Brady is probably the best All Time, but you can't compare eras

Montana had to pass to Rice and co without the benefit of modern day pass interference and roughing the QB rules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They do make some damn fine cookies, though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy sht, look what I just got in my inbox

Go ahead twitter, label Medscape 'fake news' 

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#variant #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah, I torrent like a madman, and was seeding well up until the 5th It seems that as everyone is having an epiphany over covid injections, they're trying to keep people from comparing notes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Can't wait to see what scandal brings down Sweet Potato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'd put it somewhere between Jim Neidhart coming to WCW in 1993 and Wayne Bloom's debut in 1998]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Meanwhile, we have Harold Baines and 3 guys who are only in because of a poem (Tinkers, Evers, Chance)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Bockwinkel had Heenan to do the exaggerated 'rasslin' part of the interview]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've had over 20 banks open in my town in the last 2 years Every time I get excited about a possible store opening, nope - bank Something's up, but who knows what it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's happened before and it'll happen again

It's not the end of the world
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Check out his stats since the garbage can was taken away They're garbage #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden's lying again

My taxes went up, and I don't even make 100k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That's false, because I've personally bought Disco Inferno action figure/ Johnny Lightning die cast cars back in the day #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Denies He Knew Fans Were Injured Until After Concert"

Yeah, we know. He knew DURING the concert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It took Biden this long to figure out what the point of this was?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Beefcake had a valid point.

Eddie in WCW was not the roided up main eventer he became in WWE, he was a slim cruiserweight at the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He looks like Sweetchuck from Police Academy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Kidnapping or false imprisonment, I'm fine with either charge being levied]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They jus be tryin' ta feed their family

Give em space, y'all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Jack's handing off the keys like Vince McMahon did to Mene Gene with Tuesday Night Titans, right when he noticed the ratings were about to tank Jack ain't gonna be blamed for Trump's new platform scooping up 3/4's of their user base]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hey, I've admitted for years that I wanna see those funbags

But you're still awful at your job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's ok, Biden 'stands with them' 

So it's all good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nah, he's saying that Comey and co would've tried another round of faux accusations after the Russia garbage was exposed Try to keep up, even my 6 yr old nephew is ahead of you on this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What's that date say?

2021?

Yeah, don't even try it 

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTF #USER#? Patton Oswalt voices a character named Mr. McSNORTER? Who let this one get by HR? #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You're over 18, take the ball cap off 

P.S., the count is still microscopic #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This reminds me of that original study about blacks getting less money than whites on ebay (not the baseball card/hand one)

That study even admitted that people couldn't see the person at all OR see their name. So how the fck would people know race when bidding?

Mental Illness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They're worried about the trucker convoy disrupting the economy, when these 'youths' are a drain on the system more than any other factor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When Left Wingers think that they can't make pizza outside of NYC in 2021

Homeboy, I'm half Italian/half Sicilian in NC, and I get my pizza made by 2 guys from Brooklyn, by way of Sicily 

One's an ex Golden Gloves boxer

In other words, sit down, white boy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Cooper'

Jeez, either I need glasses or I had a stroke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Everyone's piling on Russian citizens This isn't going to make them want to overthrow Putin, it's going to make them resent the rest of the world That's how you create more soldiers Good job everybody 🙄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The guy spends more time talking about his dead son than his living one

I wonder why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[50% tax rate on Corporations

Well, that will wipe out all the companies that didn't shutter due to covid lockdowns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's hilarious seeing which fails quicker, youtube or youtube tv

Both are spiraling downward, out of control]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Same reason when we questioned their Russian propaganda campaign]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did he answer the question over why there's over 100k more deaths this year, with a vax/new treatments etc , than 2020?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I thought this was Richard Lewis filming a scene for 'Curb' 🤣]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bad
Awful
Terrible
Dreadful
Worse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The guy got into the Hall based on only 5 dominant seasons

So put in Mattingly already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You people don't even put up street lights on major highways And what's with these purple bulbs on side streets? Certain people blend at night Step into the 21st century already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Biden's bankruptcy bills caused a lot of homelessness Now he's fleeing them for his safety]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No Maiden, Classics IV, The Guess Who, etc etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Not to mention my 6 month Geico premium renewal just came in, it went up over $60.

I haven't' had an accident in 20 years, never had a ticket. 

Biden is fcking us all over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Biden shut down the pipelines. 

Another fckup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bottom middle reminds me of Stevie Wonder without his glasses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If you told me back in the 80s that Jessica Fletcher and Rose Nylund would still be alive, but Skreech and Arnold Jackson would both be dead #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Um, you're very ignorant

HPV is transmissible and causes Anal, Cervical and Mouth cancers among others

I'm actually embarrassed for you right now #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[METV is doing a Betty White marathon

Right now, she's on 'the Love Boat' with Rue McClanahan, Alan Thicke, Dick Van Patton, Fred Willard and Carol Channing

All dead

Were the 80's really that long ago?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Political assassinations Always when the U.S. has a Democrat in the White House]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You'd think his mama would've chosen another name

Same way people named Bundy can't use Theodore anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I voted against him twice. 

Nader the 1st time, though I regret the Kerry vote (only Dem I ever voted for in 26 years of voting)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Of course Burr bailed, he had to go find more stock to dump before January]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The irony is that those plastic shields are on there BECAUSE of them 

Meanwhile, I gotta call somebody over to buy a razor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just like the libs who stand with BLM, from their gated communities, miles away from them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The internet - "Yo, they fired Samoa Joe twice"

Marty Jannetty - "Sit down, motherfckers" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There's a reason God gave you a back to your hand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same people cry that they don't want their kids to go to school #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's ridiculous

Do that sht in Spring Training.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What century are you in?

There are live cam all over Ukraine, free to watch on youtube among other places]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I can't stand McCain, but that girl walked outside her building during daylight hours, let's see her walk the streets after dark, alone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dems think that they can clap their way to getting Biden through this

Not happening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Or loot tvs or bust down doors or destroy businesses or police vehicles either

Learn from them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 1920s had gossip rags too (who knew?)

And ads like this #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But that sweet billing code pays so well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've never seen anyone's lips that consistently have to fight their upper teeth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Imagine fcking up a job, that you're guaranteed for life (with a paycheck, for doing absolutely nothing)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# WTF other job hires people with a liberal arts degree? Wait until they find out that teachers are used to working only 180 days a year and if they're in the upper grades, only putting in a half a day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# À la carte is the reason why people are now paying hundreds of dollars a month for 20 different services instead of $120 for everything through a cable service I said, years ago, that this would happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It depends on the career.

It doesn't take away from a player, like Banks, who never even played in the post season. But it can enhance a career, when said player is the key to the wins.

Look at Eli. He's getting in Canton based on 2 epic SB runs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just heard that my fully vaccinated uncle has covid

You know, for an unvaccinated person, I sure am sending out a hell of a lot of 'Get Well' cards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cuomo's daddy wrote the executive order that's gonna take out his own son #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Didn't your daughter's 'boyfriend' just get voted out in VA?

Honor your daughter, don't grift off of her
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She's about to find out that her boobs don't look like they did in the 70s , so she can't get away with saying stupid sht like this anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It came on when I was 10 Back then, we all watched it because the Olson twins were cute, in a babies are funny kind of way, not a hubba hubba that it later became 😬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My God, she's become the cat lady in Apartment 3C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking up some of my old teachers

Never realized that my jr high Social Studies teacher was Nick Di Paolo #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Do what we've been doing every single day."

Having the least watched channel on cable tv?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Same reason they silenced a sitting President

We let them get away with it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Not even the same species

WW2 Soldiers                           'Soldier of today' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For over 30 years, Ted Knight was the only dead cast member They really went down like dominoes in the last 4 years Well, there's still John Amos betty white #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Tony Khan would be a clown if he signed him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I don't remember wrestlers in the 70s with their huggies hanging out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So now you war mongers are even into hurting civilians?

Our grandparents didn't ostracize the Germans.

Pilots even arranged to give the children candy by air.

My God, the humanity level in this country.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any celebrities out there who were ever friends with this guy, start getting your affairs in order #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That's a lot of cash to blow to find out if a player is a scrub or not #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nah, little guy , it's because Dave Meltzer has always had a grudge against Vince and WWE.

He admits it right here. 1984. He actually claimed that the wrestling boom wasn't happening and that it was a product of Vince's 'mind control' of the media.

He's always been a mess #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This isn't going to work out NWA bought the UWF, Kansas City and Florida, and they filled all of them with jobbers until they shut down. Khan will fill ROH with wrestlers nobody cares about, and it too, will fail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And that dealership was right next door to a church that BLM tried to set fire to Luckily, 2 indie reporters on the scene put it out before it got out of control. Live stream was on youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bill Kristol is spending what little life he has left to pander to the woke, for cheap likes and retweets

Just like in every other case, he's late to the party, as the Dems have been wiped out while Billy cheered them on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Let me know when Putin's death toll reaches half of Georgie's 1 million]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I once spent 20 minutes standing at a PC Richards register, trying to buy Sega CD games

Nobody ever came

You'll live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 2 weeks ago, you were crying that only half the people were vaxxed and 5 year old breath would take out half the Teacher's lounge What changed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sorry to burst your bubble, but since you aren't capable of using google, I did it for you 92% had at least one comorbidity, in addition to being older (you know, where most of the deaths are) #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't worry, Rand, it's not just you who thinks Fauci is incompetent (or worse) From 1990 NY Times #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That's good. Hopefully the newest generation goes back to the old way of doing things

I can remember the last time I saw a baseball game in the street]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Trucks have cabs, deary. My uncle had a full bed and a fridge in his, way back in the 80s. No different than camping #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When you claim sexism, you've already conceded defeat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You can't judge a product from before you were born All of these podcasts have 20-30 yr olds who weren't around or too young in the 80s-90s. You didn't see the week to week build And they're all like Feinstein on interviews. When a wrestler asks for clarification, they go blank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That's a good deal for Giants fans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Plenty of livable wages out there. Walmart is paying $15-18 an hour These kids know that they have a shot at making millions, which is why they don't leave. Being an adult means taking your reward now or gambling on a bigger one later]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What about the last 5 years of Maddow's Russia nonsense?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wonder if the fcker goes to a mall during December #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Since I was a kid, the U.S. has always had a boogeyman. Hussein, Gaddafi, Osama And when they were killed, a new one arose Maybe they should learn from Reagan/Gorbachev and Trump/Putin, and stop the d c k measuring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The woman invents paper dolls, and can't even get a write up in a newspaper #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But television viewership will remain where it's been for 30 years- in the toilet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My childhood was spent watching Norman Lear sitcoms and the Gong Show, and having a shtty President in the White House I'm pretty much spending my adulthood the same, come to think of it #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You'd think they keep a healthy cut, and then donate a large chunk of this to science to eradicate disease But they won't. It was never about that anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boy, that sht changed pretty quickly #HASHTAG# And before twitter gets their undies in a bind, this is from John Hopkins So guy who replaced Jack can eat my hole #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WWE releases aren't even the biggest wrestling story of today #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So just like the aid Trump sent to PR, local dems couldn't handle the roll out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Speaking of duty, I heard you had a little problem in the Vatican]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>