<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Taliban and Afghan civil society members begin Oslo talks: Norway #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Royal crown slips as Elizabeth prepares to mark 70 years as queen #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Restrictions on schools after Corona- Center preparing- soon announcement | center preparing guidelines for reopening of schools post covid 19 with curbs soon #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Describe the children of immigrants as thieves and rapists! French court fines right-wing candidate Zemmour 10,000 euros #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The colorful opening ceremony of PSL will be held today #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kangana gets involved in Kishan Bharwad murder case: Posted on Facebook and said ‘Kishan Shaheed… .. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nepali man beat wife and son to death with stick in Kullu. police arrested | After a fight in Zari, both were beaten to death with sticks, arrested by the police #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two killed in road accident on Patna Bakhtiyarpur Highway | Was going to deliver the local ride by driving an auto, overturned on the forelane #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 star campaigners including Sukhdev Dhindsa will campaign in favor of party candidates #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Typhoon Anna wreaks havoc in East Africa, killing 86 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Union Budget 2022: Take a look at the country’s defense budget, will there be big announcements for the army? | Union Budget 2022: Take a look at the country’s defense budget, will there be big announcements for the army? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rafael Nadal win Australian Open 2022: Rafael Nadal Win: Rafael Nadal rises from the ashes; Making history by winning Australian Open – Rafael Nadal wins Australian Open 2022 by defeating Daniel Medvedev and made history with 21st grand slam title #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which players were given the title of Incredible 3 by the Chairman PCB? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ban sought on PUBG after teen guns down mother, siblings #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Governor wished the people of Telangana a happy Republic Day #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taliban hold landmark talks with West on food crisis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SBP to decide on interest rate today #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Robbins, The Voice Of Charlie Brown, Dies At Age 65 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fresh Vacancies Announced, Apply By Jan 27 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aquaman… Crazy role in “Fast and Furious 10” #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A website linked to the Vatican includes information about a campaign to ordain women priests #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health: Eating gram flour with tea reduces nutrients #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police arrest 50 Punjab University students for rioting on campus #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jamaat-e-Islami will close five highways in Karachi on Friday #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[quinton de kock creats world record: quinton de kock creats world record Sehwag backs veterans – sa vs ind: quinton de kock creats world record surpasses virender sehwag equals ab de villiers milestone #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pray that Nawaz Sharif will come today, Prime Minister #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neocov Virus: The answer to every question in your mind about the new virus ‘Neocov’ … – neocov new virus: india wuhan scientists warn of new coronavirus neocov, know everything about neocov #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are five simple ways to update your EPF account quitting date online … | Know how to update date of exit of job in epf account online #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syrian fathers keep night watch so children don’t freeze to death #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A ‘mistake’ on India tour … and time for German naval chief to resign! – german navy chief vadm kay achim schonbach comments on russia and ukraine in india had to resigns after back to country #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hundreds of bodies laid to rest in the hope of resurrection #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is possible to transfer chat history from Android phone to iPhone #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farmers are displaced, smuggling of fertilizers and sale in black continues, Shahbaz Sharif #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nigeria coach resigns after Tunisia defeat #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[REPSOL strengthens collaboration with civil society and authorities #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tork Kratos Electric Bike is Powerful, Learn Price and Features #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to play Test series at one venue, Cricket Australia #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State President Ajay Kumar has made serious against Lallu, saying that the State President is selling tickets by taking money. , Said- State President is selling tickets by taking money, took 27 lakh rupees from the former candidate #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good Luck Sakhi Twitter Review: How is the first talk .. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Viral Video | Earthquake in the middle of the World Cup match .. Video viral #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six arrested in robberies targeting Asian women in San Jose #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is necessary to make the city crime free, follow the guidelines completely #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Madonna have a butt augmentation? .. Bold pictures you posted and caused a stir! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foundation stone laid for Sports Hub on 17th #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review: Bro Daddy (Malayalam) Disney Plus Hot Star #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom as an introduction to alienation in the poem Lorca and the Gypsies – Quraish #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rising popularity of Virginia governor threatens Trump’s ambitions1 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[27 former pradhans including 18 current pradhans, 15 BDC members took membership of BJP, pledge to feed lotus on all six seats of the district | 18 pradhans, 27 former pradhans and 15 BDC members took membership of BJP #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agency: North Korea launched "unidentified shell" Towards the Sea of ​​Japan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neeraj Chopra | Olympics Gold Medal Winner Neeraj Chopra Awarded Outstanding Service Award #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smriti Mandana wins ICC Women’s Cricketer of the Year award #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[home remedies for kidney stones marathi: Kidney Stones: Kidney stones will fall out of the body easily without any medicine, do ‘these’ 8 simple home remedies! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Khiladi: Wife romance with astrologer in bedroom, husband patiently videotaped, Rs. Millions! | Khiladi: A couple arrested for honey trapping a priest by Rs 49 lakhs in Mangaluru in Karnataka. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salah: The current edition of the African Nations Championship is very difficult #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The main accused Amir Butt killed journalist Hasnain Shah over a transaction dispute, CCPO Lahore #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Star Hero contest in MLA, MP elections? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The writer and the devil’s whispering – Written by: Walid Rabah – Editor-in-chief #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite the horror of Europe, the Russians do not care about the war on Ukraine #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hasina fell in love with the dacoit and got engaged as soon as she came out of jail #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why bring food late? The customers who came to the hotel had to fight with the waiter #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The death of the inspector injured in the attack of the villagers in Aurangabad, the marriage of the daughter is fixed on February 16 | Inspector killed in attack by villagers; Daughter’s marriage is fixed on 16 February #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moderna announces good news after Pfizer – #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghanistan: 80 prisoners released from Helmand province jail #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least eight people have been killed in a stampede at a football stadium in Cameroon #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia’s Sydney gears up for Lunar New Year celebrations #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shahid Diwas in Panna, district administration played siren at 12 o’clock, people remembered martyrs by keeping silent | The district administration played siren at 12 o’clock, people remembered the martyrs by keeping a silence of 2 minutes #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrorist firing on policemen, officer martyred and 2 others injured #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Groups Call For Diplomatic Boycott Of Beijing Olympics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A source for RT: A car bomb exploded targeting a prison holding ISIS members in northeastern Syria #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broccoli (Cabbage Branch) Cancer Treatment, New Research #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Prioritizing Antiviral Pills for ‘Non-White’ People #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hebrew newspaper: This is how Israel spies on Arab activists and violates their privacy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 Indian fishermen arrested for violating Pakistani territorial waters #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India’s prime minister’s party ‘dominates the digital space, harasss Muslim women, threatens, harasss and even kills its critics’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trend of following offbeat sports started in Surat, but the destination is still far away. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FIR registered against four policemen, one held for receiving Rs1 million extortion money #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firing-baton charge on Netaji’s birthday in Bengal, clash between TMC-BJP activists #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haryana Police Arrested Four Accused Of Assault, Shooting In Rohtak | After a dispute while smoking hookah in Rohtak, four accused arrested for assaulting a young man and shooting him #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US, Germany step up pipeline warnings if Russia invades Ukraine #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pak-China relationship has grown stronger with time: PM Imran #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rohit Sharma Could Break Mohammad Azharuddin’s Record In Odi Series Against West Indies | Rohit Sharma to make history against West Indies; Behind this veteran player … | Maharashtra Times #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Times: Syrian refugees fear Assad will use Interpol’s red notices to arrest them #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video of Imran Tahir speaking Sindhi with Shahnawaz Dhani goes viral #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discussions on social media of Jale border pictures #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A clinic organized by the Argentine Yachting Federation and the Bahía Blanca Nautical Club will be held #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An early final between Egypt and Côte d’Ivoire in the Round of 16 of the African Nations Cup #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prime Minister Imran Khan will visit Lahore today #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mohamed Ramadan responds to Latoya Jackson #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dead body found thrown in bush in samastipur | Used to work as a laborer, villagers expressed fear of strangulation #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TikTok star Addison Rae aims to play versatile roles in films #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mutinous soldiers take over Burkina Faso military barracks #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controversy erupts in India over portrayal of lesbian women #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifi Abdo responds to a follower, describing her as “the choice”: I do not see all this femininity – (video) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sabarkantha: Locals protest against relocation of Kamadhenu University to Kutch #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[gandhi 74th death anniversary: ​​Solid tributes to Mahatma Gandhi .. PM calls on people to take Gandhi’s aspirations to the people – pm modi and other leaders pay homage to mahatma gandhi on death anniversary #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chairman PPP extends condolences to party MNA Nawab Yousuf Talpur #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swimming in the snow and its relationship to the hormone of love #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mentor of Quetta Gladiators Sir Vivian Richard reached Karachi #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Between harvests and sowings, wheat is the flagship of the 2021/22 campaign #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two brothers arrested for assaulting three policemen with a wood with nails #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vaccination of Agar Malwa 15+, Vaccine to people between 15 to 18 years will be done at 5 places on Monday | Vaccines will be given to people aged 15 to 18 at 5 places on Monday #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bihar bandh: blockade of roads .. agitators on fire #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are 10 things to keep in mind before giving a speech on the occasion of Republic Day #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chaudhry Shujaat advises PM to be wary of his advisers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ankush Chaudhari: Trailer of ‘Lochya Jhala Re’ screened in Danakya, the audience is eager for the movie – Ankush Chaudhari #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family that froze to death in Canada US border was from Kalol village in Gujarat | The family of Kalol village of Gujarat was found dead on the Canada-USA border due to minus 35 degree cold, 7 other Gujaratis also in custody #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abu Dhabi Crown Prince telephons PM, strongly condemns Lahore Anarkali blast #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ratnakar is happy with the formation of Puttaparthi district #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PM announces to challenge decision on River Ravi Urban project in Supreme Court #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are the textile traders happy with the transfer of all the policemen of Salabatpura police station? Find out what he said. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadal storms into Australian Open finals #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syrian refugees face yet another struggle as heavy rains flood displacement camp #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parade organized in Police Line, DM Inder Vikram Singh took the salute | Parade was organized in the police line, DM Inder Vikram Singh took the salute #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farmers are very important for Pakistan’s economy, Raja Pervez #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bird flu reaches US after UK and Europe, millions of chickens killed – #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India acquired Israeli-made Pegasus spyware under defence deal: report #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Statements like those of opposition leaders while in government weaken the political position, says Chaudhry Pervaiz Elahi #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Porn Stars Reveal Three Top Players Have Sex In London! | Porn stars reveal top three footballers have sex in London, #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Policemen above 50 or with TB, cancer, asthma and heart-related diseases will not be engaged in overcrowding | Policemen above 50 or with TB, cancer, asthma and heart-related diseases will not be engaged in overcrowding #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Times: The economic situation is forcing the Lebanese and Syrian refugees to sell their organs #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Testing of a new vaccine against omecron begins #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The price of British Brent crude rose 1.9 dollars per barrel in the world market #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PSL 7: Three players, including the captain, suffer from corona #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young hero Adit Arun changes his name to Trigun #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bharuch: Taluka Congress president assumes saffron #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delhi Guidelines- Restaurant-Cinema Hall with 50% capacity will open in Delhi from today, know the guidelines #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budget 2022: Finance Minister Sitharaman may announce formation of GST tribunal Budget 2022: Finance Minister Sitharaman may announce formation of GST tribunal #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jaime Goldsmith recovered from the omecron virus #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aditya Thackeray | Chief Minister will return soon, Shiv Sena will be the number one party if it gets the status of work done in elections: Aditya Thackeray #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 lakh property stolen from house in Fatuha, Theft of jewelery including 10 lakh cash from the house of brick kiln operator | Theft of jewelery including 10 lakh cash, licensed revolver and cartridges also took away from the house of brick kiln operator #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actress Faryal Mahmood’s dance video goes viral #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two young men were arrested for the theft of cables #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pakistan’s foreign loans soar to USD 10.4 billion in July-December #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JIT formed to probe Anar Kali bomb blast #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Endangered pangolins thrive in Margalla Hills #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the transaction of money, the operator of the tea kiosk shot Karinde, the injured admitted to Agroha Medical | In the dispute over the transaction, the operator of the tea kiosk shot Karinde, referred to the injured private hospital #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education illiteracy in Egypt. Al-Ahram Al-Jadeed Canadian newspaper #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Monks Arrested, Kept Incommunicado For Five Months For Standing Against The Statue Demolition Of Tibetan Buddhists In China’s Sichuan Province #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liverpool abort the Palace uprising and reduce the difference with Manchester City #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The money budget will directly or indirectly affect the common man #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nandini Reddy | Nandini Reddy shaking hands with a smile .. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haniya Aamir’s video goes viral on social media #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India’s Wheat Shipment To Afghanistan Via Pakistani Soil To Begin In Early February: Report #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 lakh looted from near Sukhbir Badal’s Reliance Pump in Bathinda area of ​​Punjab, incident near Dabwali, Haryana | The crime committed near Dabwali; Snatched the bag after hitting the workers with a stick with the cash #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[smriti irani: Smriti Irani’s post on Mauni Roy’s wedding goes viral, what exactly did the Union Minister say – smriti irani best wishes to mouni roy for her wedding #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[omicron sub variant in india latest breaking news: Omicron sub variant: sub variant of omicron BA.2 in India; ‘This’ shocking information came to the fore – omicron ba.2 sub variant found in substantial fraction in india #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite the poor financial situation, these five smallcap stocks made investors’ money three times as well as a lot of money !! | Multibagger stocks These 5 small cap stocks give up over 300 percent return in one month #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Escalating congestion.. Attacks on the property of Syrian refugees after the murder of a Turkish youth in Izmir #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fear of committing suicide by jumping into the river, the deceased middle-aged was not identified, police engaged in investigation | The fear of committing suicide by jumping into the river, the middle-aged could not be identified yet #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rent the Runway offers exclusive 50% discount #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30 IPS officers transferred to Telangana, CV Anand appointed as new Police Commissioner of Hyderabad #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The nightmare of deportation freezes the lives of Syrian refugees in Denmark #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“All the dogs on the streets have disappeared and they are not in the kennel either” #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge dump siege in Awobi .. Missed accident #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Gandhi ji ki Pathshala’ also started in Nehru College, students became aware of Gandhi’s thoughts. ‘Gandhi ji ki Pathshala’ also started in Nehru College, students became aware of Gandhi’s thoughts #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Urvarshi Rautela, who landed on the ramp in a 40 crore gold dress, became the first Indian to go to Arab Fashion Week! | Urvarshi Rautela, who landed on the ramp in a 40 crore gold dress, became the first Indian to go to Arab Fashion Week! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Several injured, including policemen, hospitalized in Tamil Nadu’s Jallikattu game #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three policemen suspended, video of them enjoying music while traveling went viral #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crowd of workers gathered to welcome NUSI state president, officer spoke – permission was not taken | Crowd of workers gathered to welcome the state president, the officer said – permission was not taken #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today farmers are fleeing for fertilizer, Maryam Aurangzeb #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuel Rates: What is the latest price of petrol and diesel today? Find out here | Fuel Rates: Petrol-diesel prices remain unchanged on 29th January, check today’s rates in your city. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hampshire shared a video of Muhammad Abbas bowling #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Villagers booked for unleashing dogs on wild boar in Badin #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junagadh: Bhairav’s soon-to-be-climbed Desi Spiderman to the Forest Department #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[36,334 took the examination from Durg to become a supervisor in the Department of Women and Child Development, the social distancing broke down inside and outside the center | 36,334 took the examination from Durg to become a supervisor in the Department… #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Shoaib Akhtar already know about Kohli’s resignation as Test captain? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Punctuality of passenger trains improves by 83 percent in 2021-22 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Babar Azam named ICC ODI Cricket of the Year #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prime Minister Modi on the field for Afghanistan: Together with those five countries #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No change in surname of Dhanush couple in the same hotel even after separation! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BSP’s product can be identified immediately by special tagging in the bundle | Heat proof and bar code will be equipped with ‘Unique Stud Welded’, customers will be able to identify the product and price easily #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[27 drug smugglers killed trying to enter Jordan from Syria #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PTI names new vice presidents, deputy general secretaries #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barcelona signs the Wolverhampton star in his third deal in the winter Mercato (photos) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Messi received a shirt signed by Pope Francis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vishwabandhu of Bhagalpur became the winner in the online chess championship | 60 male and 15 female players selected from 38 districts, selected in state championship #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A terrifying story behind the famous ‘Just Do It’ by Nike! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A History Lesson In A Critical Race Theory-Free America #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burkina Faso’s army officially announces the overthrow of the president 1 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pictures of Yashmi Gul in saree became the adornment of social media #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secretary Health visits THQ hospital #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The process of death is not going to stop, the name: 13 deaths so far | A day earlier, 4 people had drunk liquor lying on the roadside, 3 are still admitted, on January 26, 12 people died #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ashrafi for concerted efforts to promote int’l interfaith harmony #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taslima Nasreen: Taslima Nasreen clarified her tweet about surrogacy, said … – Taslima Nasreen tweet was not related to priyanka chopra #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which bowler did former Indian cricketer Muhammad Azharuddin find difficult to face? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mushtaq Merchant, the legendary actor of Sholay film, passed away #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you turn to a priest to see a marriage .. what did he do ..? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice Ayesha Malik, the first woman judge of the Supreme Court, took oath of office #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Islamabad United’s Official Anthem Release, Talha Anjum’s Voice Brings Four Moons #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One held, FIR registered against four Policemen #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The formation of new districts is a positive development: Tammineni Sitaram #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Punjabi News| Big blow to Aam Aadmi Party ahead of Assembly elections| #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Famous actress Rohi Bano’s third anniversary is being celebrated today #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indian Mission in Pakistan observes 73rd Republic Day by hoisting national flag #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US announces closure of Afghan embassy in Washington #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Islamnagar police was doing vehicle checking, the accused sitting silent about the recovery amount during this time, the treasury opened at midnight | Car rider could not give information about money, case filed for violation of code of conduct #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taliban delegation’s visit to Oslo can set dangerous precedent of legitimising terrorists, says expert #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taliban have started their first official talks in Europe since takeover : NPR #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Occupied Kashmir, Indian troops martyred 5 Kashmiri youth #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The anthem of the seventh edition of PSL has been released #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>