<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Chloe's done amazing things for trans people but she will not be remembered by anyone but people who were directly effected by her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who supports Argentina colonising the Falklands does not deserve a seat in Parliament or a voice in British politics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is what you get for joining a party that prioritises rural middle-class interests and localism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all the cringe overly queer bitches dating each other as God intended #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the fuck was HYPERPOP my fifth most played genre and not R&amp;B. The white gay defeated the black gay in me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# bring back the homophobic version of Picture to Burn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm not going to post it here, but it's a derogatory meme against mixed race people, especially American ones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# fuckin vanilla-flavoured mayo monkey ass streamers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Megan and Cardi B when making WAP's radio edit #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is Kraut so insistent on not being called British while also dragging us for breathing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How?? They're both bad, but apartheid isn't magically a good or ethical thing because of sweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If black-passing biracial people are considered black, white-passing biracial people should be considered white]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just make friends with gays who you specifically don't want to have sex with #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Franklin approaches every take he makes like he's writing a proper article #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They were not liberal. Their detention policies were atrocious, and they expanded govt surveillance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm a transfem femboy who uses she/her pronouns" you're a binary trans girl? that's super heckin valid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting a centre-left majority is more important than stopping bad tweets Luke #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[clapping my cheeks for the NHS if we enter a new lockdown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The modern Diana, letting a man with AIDS touch your baby #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who cares? If you want more American descents of slavery in office, support them when they run if you agree with their stances. Don't drag down mixed race people for clout #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When my RT results in a tweet getting most of its likes, that makes me feel like a god]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[plagiarism is basically victimless. great artists steal baby. if you want to steal this tweet you have my blessing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am extremely disappointed in his widow for promoting this law, that's my take]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Not really, invasion should not be on the cards in modern Europe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mummy issues bf daddy issues nbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes I'm a bimbo (literally can't do maths)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's actually a very accurate video if you watch past this clip #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And those issues are also talked about by better YouTubers who didn't bait the nonbinary community after Contra's scandal about us, support anti-poor housing policies in a country where we very much need new development, and downplay the issues with Corbyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And they're still white, because of mixing with Europeans and, in the UK, living in cooler climates. My aunt was very much a white person, and her GRT ancestry didn't cancel that out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My mum said she was fine with me flirting with Nikolaj and he's 22 now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I seriously doubt the existence of meat that's better than pork]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything I don't like won't exist if the ideology I like runs the world #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm an island gyal (English and Irish)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift has a gorilla grip on my heart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm legit related to several Roma people, but go off sis 😭 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to dunk on a gay man by using the AIDS crisis is disgustingly homophobic #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm actually gonna wait until I lose my V to someone I love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans online will argue to the death about how progressive their country is compared to us in the UK, but you're just as guilty of whitewashing your past as we are #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Honestly so annoying that the NHS is being undermined from within, I really wish there was a clean solution to get rid of anti-science people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mariah and Michaela expecting a bunch of families to order it are going to be so surprised when a bunch of gays and girlies buy up the entire stock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I actually am totally fine with those, I was referring to their treatment of West Africa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is like cutting off your fingernails because they could scratch your body]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JK Rowling is honestly a bad person, not just a misguided feminist or someone who's simply been harassed into GC ideology]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[no one relates to independent women anthems more than gay men]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I know you want my body" so why are you mad that I've kidnapped you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine being a white rapper, them niggas can't even say the special word]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd honestly like Jeremy Corbyn on domestic issues if he weren't such a dunce about antisemitism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best pop vocalist since Mariah, obv #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# get your paws off the men I'm attracted to paddy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know how financially dependent Australia is on China? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vote for #USER#. He's a great writer and will donate to Stonewall. Follow him btw #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Her ass so fat that it would be taxed at 100% under Georgist rule]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Boxing Day to all dysfunctional families]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when Doja Cat said "niggas ain't shit, all up in your fridge, can't pay rent", the Georgism left my body]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# so proud of you, and I'm so glad you feel safe enough to come out to all of us 💖]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am no longer an extra large in men's clothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad will be glad to know that he's not the only black person without a sense of rhythm #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've never seen a gay woman be called a faggot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sleepy's bisexuality includes terrible female heads of government, French tennis players, and Indian actresses with suspiciously light skin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's so good to hear!! We all need more positive energy in 2022 😌💖🎉🎉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one cares if your non-work clothes are ironed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blocking you isn't enough. I want to deport you to Siberia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're an anarchist, I support a system of taxation with literally no downsides, we are not the same #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Kim Petras song, not the exotic plant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find it interesting that some mixed race people think of their brown half's country as their home country, because that is the exact opposite of how I feel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It didn't have half of the commercial and cultural impact of KMM or DL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I'm gonna liquefy Nik soon inshallah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine if Taylor or Ariana threatened to pull their music off Spotify over Rogan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Destiny when he's not allowed to say the n-word #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How you gonna be a sex worker and shame other low income people? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one cares. Seriously. Look at me. No one cares #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People tried to end Michael and Janet Jackson because America is a racist country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry for streaming this two times, I didn't intend to contribute to this disaster #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the Holland pic is fake because the guy in it is cut and that's not a thing here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They oppose banning conversion therapy for trans people and support GC people generally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tell me you hate mixed race people without saying you hate mixed race people #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am literally mixed race and in the north of England how can your blackness be less cool than mine nigga? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you think you can hurt me? I once sang so badly and loudly at night that the dogs started barking for a whole mile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boiling Flask is the defacto authority on Islam.nnI trust the words of him much more than queer theorists atheists who are genetically "Arab" but have no connection to The Arabian Peninsula or it's people.nnReform is cringe.nnWahabis are very cool, &amp; Sunnis or Shias are ok. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's just a fucking ridiculous definition of whiteness you're operating on. Ashkenazi Jews are fully assimilated and seen as white in English-speaking countries, antisemitism doesn't cancel that out #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Y'all niggas think he's joking, he's actually so deranged for a centre-left liberal #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["wanting to fuck femboys and being straight" isn't a sexuality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're the most colonised Indian I know outside of the Tory Party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans trying to own her like Ireland hasn't been terrorised by Catholic institutions until very recently after radical societal changes #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A Tory who isn't a paternalist or delusional libertarian on welfare issues??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britney, Ariana, Taylor, and Madonna are the queens of pop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# He is a known opponent of Maxine Thought, that is a major L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I promise you I'm mixed I just had to admire that word]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lindsay Ellis was the victim of abuse, and I sincerely hope her friends and family are supporting her, and that all the people that work for her get equally good jobs elsewhere. God bless her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wear women's clothes that fit all the time, the sizes are only a minor inconvenience lmao #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, I wish the fearmongering about Labour becoming the British equivalent of the American Democrats in the 90s was true #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The skinny trend from the early 2000s is coming back because bodies are just a trend lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do you hate mixed race people living freely with our families? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting the economic consensus on immigration being good and the lump of labour theory being false is good actually #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A smear campaign is when you refuse to understand how antisemitism works and take accountability for losing the trust of an entire ethnoreligious group #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My seven year old cousin is asking why I have red dots on my face. should I tell them they're adopted or?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# But I think Evan is trying to say that most of his followers would never call themselves fascists or think they would endorse fascism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wwyd if this man came up to you and asked your opinion of Albanian disco singer Dua Lipa #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trans and cis as labels are medical and social terms, they exist to describe what is real]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd be willing to date a 20 year old at the oldest, and a 16 year old at the youngest #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# their arguments are very clearly antiquated, given that the way they talk about the environment at the time is very outdated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new Lady Marmalade with Ariana, Dua, Doja, and Megan is what we need]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And? His children deserve to be brought up in a better environment if he is abusive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I like washing my own clothes everyday, I sweat a lot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oomf was convinced that Jesy Nelson was afro-Carribbean a few weeks ago 😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We gotta start talking to the younger teenagers that hang out with these people, because these spaces desensitise them to really disturbing and abhorrent views #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone made an "I identify as" joke to me today

hurray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I listened to a song on an album that was literally about murdering a guy and the word "fuckery" was bleeped out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I was definitely wrong, and too hopeful about Muslims being liberal. I still stand by my criticisms of new atheism and their major ex-Muslim figures being unhelpful to deradicalisation efforts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# your points are invalid, and waving your ancestry around doesn't make your foreign policy takes any better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to spend more of this year being an adult than being a minor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, slavery resulted in generational trauma for most black people in the Americas, with the effects being felt even today. You haven't really gone through that, so it feels a bit uncomfortable reading your light-hearted tweet, knowing the stories about my ancestors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excuse me, mandatory feminisation of twinks is a perfectly decent position #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me when 14 year olds retweet porn and try to be horny on main #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I forget how many biracial people look totally like one side of their heritage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# So you'd rather exclude Albertans and other rural Canadians from the civil service than just deal with the fact that Canada will never be bilingual outside of some areas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so glad that my parents decided to leave this abusive institution #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taylor needs to redo Bad Blood with Kendrick it could be so much better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is such a good argument against all the anti-mandatory vaccination noise I keep seeing #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wait, as a black Jew, does this mean you have the most valid claim over Israel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ghislaine Maxwell is so bad ugh 😩😩😩

From a moral standpoint]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love to make 30 somethings feel old by reminding them that I was born in 2004 and will be 18 in a few weeks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We need to end COVID as close to completely as possible, and make sure that if it still exists, it's no more serious than the cold or the flu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a white guy on here who bragged to me about being in a majority-minority school and even tho he didn't mean it maliciously, I felt genuinely annoyed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[before Nicki Minaj rapped on Beez in the Trap a hundred mothafuckers could tell me anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're going to fetishise mixed race people, don't fucking openly oppose our rights and let your friends call us ugly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[niggas will post this instead of touching grass #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# To be completely fair, plenty of biracial people are lighter than me, even with more black ancestry. Like Mariah Carey, who's totally white passing, for example]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Building our cities around a virus sounds inadvisable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then they were colonised and oppressed as well, what's your fucking point? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And calling them a terrorist group could damage the peace process in Colombia #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is racism, and I don't want your support if this is how you express support for people of colour #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There are white passing biracial people, like Mariah Carey and Logic, black passing biracial people like Obama, and fully white people who look black, like Sandra Laing. Ethnic features exist, but are not proof of race being real in the way it has been understood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm tired of the "land invasion in Russia" jokes and any war that would happen hadn't even started yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rich being empowered, and the poor stuck on the ground, so true #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A land value tax solves me not having a white bf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It took a long time for me to look in the mirror and like my face and body genuinely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my granddad being racist was especially hurtful because he dated two women of colour (my Irish Catholic grandma and his Scottish girlfriend of over 10 years)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1984: what’s the plot, who cares, BOOORRRINNGGGG

Dystopian YA novels: Interesting, entertaining, good world building #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# honestly just curious you give me 18-20 vibes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pan-Arabism was tried and failed, nice try #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Halsey and Logic aren't PoC, they're just white biracial people, smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm getting a hybrid so I can cause maximum damage to the environment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even though I dislike Keir, I'd rather have a PM that's able to be pushed in a better direction than an actively damaging head of government #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[woman on the supreme court? idk about that :/ what if her period gets in the way of reading]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I gotta be real, I've never met anyone with any opinions on Roma people, outside of my family, because one of my great uncles was a gypsy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having thick thighs and owning skinny jeans is a special privilege]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The German government supports Russia because they decided that anti-nuclear pandering and using natural gas was more important than genuine environmentalism #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Worldwide and the world's most beautiful woman, Jennifer Lopez #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was talking to an organisation run by Jews, not all Jews. This is still concealing the truth #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because they'll absolutely hire a random Brit with a superiority complex who unironically defends blackfishing and blackface #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I never said they did, but if someone wants to celebrate them, I won't judge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I trust members of the South African legislature on what apartheid is more than people on Twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She said absolutely nothing wrong. What happens to mixed race people like me? Do I go live with relatives who don't even speak the same language as me? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a bad way to decide who runs governments #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Honestly, less than 5% for any racial group probably doesn't mean anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes I'm gay, yes I bully gay people #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Low skill workers also offer something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stormzy's verse on Power goes hard af ngl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A lot of it, considering that young Brits are more socially libertarian than our parents and politicians]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Who says he's good? They're probably also poor political observers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would like to see Twitter's reaction to Rihanna and Beyoncé coming out with NFTs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I refuse to believe Tom and Zendaya are dating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The German Greens are very much responsible for their country's pro-Russia stances]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can drink entire bottles of pop without ruining my teeth but metabolism refuses to be that good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# An old friend of mine online and his little friend. They were very weird about my race, one of them accused me of blackfishing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Those signed copies gonna collect dust in Jamie's wine basement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again, we are not one unit, how was I, a Brit, responsible for how your family was treated under Belgian rule? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's why black Americans have such a weird definition of mixed that excludes the mixed children of black/biracial couples]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accounts like this will call me ugly for being a mulatta and then post this #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mum doesn't understand that saying the word "gyp" is just a little racist against Roma people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone should be in therapy because talking about mental struggles with a neutral third party is a very good thing for everyone #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel sorry for mixed race people with straight or plain wavy hair fr. That's the worst place to inherit white genes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Critical Race Theory but it's my criticisms of Drag Race]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He called me North African for talking about how the French education system discriminated against me lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American who shocks their British friend by smoking a fag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# His fans defending him in all tweets about his wedding like he's paying their bills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mariah better drop that new album soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm the queen of rap, young Ariana run pop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justin Timberlake deserves to lose his career]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Second wave feminists got jobs as columnists, lawyers, and politicians, and their views of women's rights grew more cursed with every passing year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exercise has nothing to do with understanding public health #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anarchism is when land governance is based on ethnicity #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of the guys I've flirted with don't exist now omg #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a way i empathize with you being part of a small racial minority, im in the top 0.1% (like socioeconomically) and i often feel left out of society. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a feeling that she's going to try and enter the pop charts again #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# hot but not if it actually makes it hard to breathe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Person who thinks that biracial people are white but that Ashkenazi Jews are people of colour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In the Heights erased afro-Latinos from the story, I can't abide by that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just Look Up was a good movie, Jennifer Lawrence slaughtered her ginger hair, and Ariana Grande should've had a bigger role in it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doja Cat is to gay man what Ryan Reynolds is to straight men]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when I first saw the benefits of a land value tax #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I don't support traffickers, but I do support taking our share of refugees to lighten the load for other countries and potentially boost our own economy with more employable people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never been catcalled, I've never been groped, I've never been sexually threatened. Shut the hell up #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Manchin is pro-union, Sinema is literally and unambiguously right of centre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It very clearly describes your sexual attraction to feminine men, enbies, and women, "Roman Straight" screams "I LACK CONFIDENCE IN MY SEXUALITY". And I know you know what you're into]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Puigdemont deserved it, Belgium should've been sanctioned for not returning him to Spain, and the parties involved in the referendum should've been fined by the Spanish government #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I totally believe that a Palestinian state would be racist against Jewish people and Israelis, but that doesn't excuse the oppression they experience at the hands of the IDF, various Israeli governments, and western allies of Israel who won't cut funding to them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I blocked someone because they were incredibly ignorant of my experience being black yesterday, and a weight was lifted off me. This person fronted like they were my friend, but when difficult conversations emerged, they allowed people to be nasty towards me because of a bad joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MY COCONUTS
WATCH EM BOUNCE UP AND DOWN (BOUNCE UP AND DOWN)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>