<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[$PAYX Small Business Hiring Advances in October; Wage Growth Hits Record High #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$CPER USCF Announces Launch of the USCF Gold Strategy Plus Income Fund (Ticker: GLDX) #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Services #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$CNS Cohen &amp;amp; Steers Limited Duration Preferred and Income Fund, Inc. (LDP) Notification of Sources of Distribution Under Section 19(a) #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$BKD Brookdale Completes $100 Million Refinancing And Prepays Substantially All Remaining 2022 Debt Maturities #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$BB BlackBerry Named to Newsweek's List of the Most Loved Workplaces for 2021 #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$ACB Aurora Cannabis Announces Results of 2021 Annual General Meeting #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$NEWAB#USER# Annual General Meeting of New Wave Group AB (publ) #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American Influencer Council Launches The Career Creator Club A Free Mentorship Community #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Travelocity and Thrifty Car Rental name summer 2021 the official season of family reunions and give away two $25,000 road trips #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# #&amp; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$CUZ COUSINS PROPERTIES ANNOUNCES FULL BUILDING LEASE WITH AMAZON AT DOMAIN 9 DEVELOPMENT IN AUSTIN #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2020 National Wreaths Across America Day Sees the Placement of 1.7 Million Veterans' Wreaths at 2,557 Participating Locations Across the Country #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LNG Bunkering Market Fuels Growth at 42.5% CAGR, to Reach USD 6.97 Bn by 2027, Reports Brandessence Market Research  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LabCentral Appoints Dr. Jo Viney to its Board of Directors #HASHTAG#-related #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$SRI Stoneridge to Present at the Stephens Annual Investment Conference #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Provident Healthcare Partners Advises Family Care Partners In Its Partnership With InnovaCare  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motto Mortgage Premier Choice Now Open #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$EW Edwards Announces Six-month Data From Transcatheter Tricuspid Replacement Program #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Medical #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Floyd Commemorative Concert Announced For May 30th in Houston, TX  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$DELL Dell Technologies Announces Early Results and Increase of Tender Cap and Maximum Tender Amount for Cash Tender Offers for Certain Outstanding Debt Securities #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$FICO FICO Announces Earnings of $3.00 per Share for Fourth Quarter Fiscal 2021 #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$OEG Orbital Energy Group Reports First Quarter 2021 Financial Results #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Howard And Georgeanna Jones Foundation For Reproductive Medicine Announces New Board Members #HASHTAG#-related #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$MAIN Main Street Announces Exit of Portfolio Investment #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$SSNC ALPS REIT DIVIDEND DOGS ETF DECLARES FOURTH QUARTER DISTRIBUTION #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$SO SAVOY, STOKES ELECTED TO ALABAMA POWER BOARD OF DIRECTORS #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fractal is Title Sponsor of Analytics Unite 2021: The Summit for Retail and Consumer Brands #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EVMANN takes under its umbrella two innovative, fast-growing companies #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$ALLY TIME And Ally Financial Honor 47 Dealers #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guiyang Is Applying Big Data to Social Governance Modernization  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$AVTR Avantor® Opens Second European Single-use Facility in the Netherlands; Supports Growing Demand for Bioproduction #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$FLT Archie L. Jones, Jr., is honored by Savoy Magazine as one of their 2021 Most Influential Black Corporate Directors #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# #&amp; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DataTracks, the right ESEF Reporting partner, to get clients across the line without hiccups #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alliance for Women in Media Foundation Announces 45th Gracie Awards Call for Entries Open #HASHTAG#-related #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Increased Racism" and "Missing Black Women and Girls" Are Most Important Issues For Black Women, Finds Zeta Phi Beta's "In the Voices of Black Women" Study #HASHTAG#-related #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$LDI War Heroes on Water Sportfishing Tournament Creates "Josh Miles Award" Honoring Beloved WHOW Collaborator #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$MDP Meredith Corporation Announces Anticipated Distribution Date Of The Previously-Announced Spin-Off In Connection With The Gray Merger #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$ADTX Thinking about buying stock in Altamira Therapeutics, FuelCell Energy, Doximity, Aditxt, or ChargePoint? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$LOW Lowe's Unveils Measure Your Space(Beta), Using LiDAR To Take The Guesswork Out Of Home Improvement #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$MTB M&amp;amp;T Bank Corporation Receives Approval From New York State Department of Financial Services and Connecticut Department of Banking for the Merger of M&amp;amp;T Bank and People's United Bank #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$SFUN Fang Announces the Change of Auditor #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students Flock to STEM and Creative Online Activities, Nord Anglia Data Shows #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# #&amp; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late-Breaking Data at ACC.21 Show XARELTO® (rivaroxaban) Plus Aspirin Significantly Reduced Total Ischemic Events in Peripheral Artery Disease (PAD) Patients After Lower-Extremity Revascularization #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Medical #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$AER AerCap and Safran Sign Joint Venture Agreement for Shannon Engine Support #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genesis Software Innovations Announces FDA 510(k) Clearance For Preview™ 3D Shoulder Arthroplasty Planning Software #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$IP International Paper Announces Cash Tender Offer for up to $500 Million Combined Aggregate Principal Amount of its Outstanding Notes #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$GS Goldman Sachs Asset Management and Ascensus Offer a Retirement Plan Solution for Small and Mid-Sized Businesses #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Match-Day Presence of Celebrities Boosts NRL Merchandise Sales, According to The Stubby Club  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$BHC Bausch + Lomb and Clearside Biomedical Announce FDA Approval of XIPERE™ (triamcinolone acetonide injectable suspension) for Suprachoroidal Use for the Treatment of Macular Edema Associated with Uveitis #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PBS' NATIONAL MEMORIAL DAY CONCERT: A NIGHT OF REMEMBRANCE Returns With Performances And Tributes From Washington, D.C. And Around The Country Honoring All Of Our American Heroes #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$FPI Farmland Partners Purchases More Than 8,000 Acres in Louisiana #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NWEA Launches Season 2 of The Continuing Educator Podcast #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tribute to Veterans of Mayaguez Rescue at National Museum of Military Vehicles #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Greater Women's Business Council Invites Consumers to Buy Women Owned This Holiday Season #HASHTAG#-related #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber partners with GetSetUp to teach older adults to use Uber's services and apps #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Marketing #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Navy Mutual Announces Four New Board Members #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$DGE Industry-first virtual trials to begin on lightweighting glass bottles #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$208340 PharmAbcine Announces Encouraging Non-clinical Data of PMC-403 at the Association for Research in Vision and Ophthalmology (ARVO) 2021 Annual Meeting #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Medical #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$MPLX MPLX LP Announces Quarterly Distribution for Third Quarter of $1.28 per Common Unit, Including an Increase to the Base Distribution Amount and a Special Distribution Amount #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$NEW Puxin Limited to Hold Annual General Meeting on December 20, 2021 #HASHTAG#/Marketing #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital precision farming company OneSoil announces new CEO to strengthen global growth #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$TGI Triumph Group Secures Boeing Interiors Business #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The American Council of Learned Societies Welcomes Three Scholarly Associations to Its Federation of Member Societies #HASHTAG#-related #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tampa General Hospital is Named One of the Best Maternity Hospitals in the United States #HASHTAG#-related #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$AAL Thinking about buying stock in Ardelyx, American Airlines, DiDi Global, Norwegian Cruise Line, or Express? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deep Isolation Announces Agreement with Dominion Engineering, Inc. to Cooperate in Developing Nuclear Waste Disposal Technology #HASHTAG#/Marketing #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soteria Solutions Awarded Coveted Grant From The Office On Violence Against Women's Training And Technical Assistance Initiative #HASHTAG#-related #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wounded Warrior Project Honored as a Top Nonprofit #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$WRN Western Copper and Gold Announces C$25.6 Million Strategic Investment by Rio Tinto #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AxeTrading Integrates ICE's Pricing and Analytics Solutions for Its Quoting and Execution Management System  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honors High School Students Start Online Education Company To Help Students During the Pandemic #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$TAC TransAlta Reports Strong First Quarter 2021 Results led by Exceptional Performance at Alberta Hydro #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["She's Back!" The Newbury Boston, A New Luxury Hotel By Highgate, To Open May 18, 2021  At Boston's Most Celebrated Address  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$VCIF Vertical Capital Income Fund (VCIF) Announces Estimated Sources of November Distribution #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$CB Chubb and Wharton Study Examines Ultra-High-Net-Worth Individuals' Preferences on Financial Advising and Investment Management #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# #&amp; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making Veterans' Issues a Priority in the 2020 Elections #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$SRV Cushing® MLP &amp;amp; Infrastructure Total Return Fund and Cushing® NextGen Infrastructure Income Fund Announce Upcoming Portfolio Manager Retirement #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$069620 Daewoong showed improved performance both sales and earnings in Q1 #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education Cannot Wait New Annual Results Report Highlights Multiplying Education Challenges for Children and Adolescents Living in Emergencies and Crisis Settings Amid The COVID-19 Crisis #HASHTAG#-Related #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will The Courts Permanently Change Procedures Due To The Pandemic? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buttock Augmentation Market Size Worth $6.6 Billion By 2028 | CAGR: 22.0%: Grand View Research, Inc.  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$ONL Arch Street Capital and Orion Announce Single Tenant Office Partnership #HASHTAG#/Marketing #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E-Commerce Logistics Market Records a CAGR of 20.44% by 2025 | Technavio  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$HAE Haemonetics Announces CFO William P. Burke's Retirement for June 2022 #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$CMG Chipotle Sets Science Based Climate Goals To Reduce Its Carbon Emissions 50% By 2030 #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lighting Fixtures Market in Japan 2021 Report, Featuring Profiles of Key Players  Artemide, Arup Japan, Dongmyung, FSL and Koizumi  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$FLURF FluroTest Prepares to Detect SARS-CoV-2 Variants of Concern with High-Throughput COVID-19 Testing Platform #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In-Person Indian Market Returns to Santa Fe This August #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millennium Trust Welcomes Karyn DeFalco as Chief Human Resources Officer #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eagle Merchant Partners Named to Inc.'s List of Best Private Equity Firms for Entrepreneurs and Founders #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$SOLY Soliton to Report First Quarter 2021 Financial Results on May 13, 2021 #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$PEAK Healthpeak Properties Declares Quarterly Cash Dividend on Common Stock #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$KIND Nextdoor to participate in UBS Global TMT Conference on December 6 #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$FLURF FluroTest Provides Clinical Trial Update for High Volume COVID-19 Rapid Antigen Testing System #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Medical #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$TTB According to Total Brain Study: 86% of U.S. Workers Want a Corporate Culture that Embraces Open Mental Health Dialogue #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# #&amp; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four WISE Women of the Year to be Honored at the 26th Annual WISE Awards Luncheon #HASHTAG#-related #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relativity Announces Expanded Cloud Capabilities in India at Relativity Fest #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gaming CEOs Bullish on Future Industry Growth #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# #&amp; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$HPI John Hancock Closed-End Fund Preferred Income Fund Declares Monthly Distribution #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$TUP Tupperware Brands Named by Newsweek as One of America's Most Responsible Companies #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schedule Engine Partners With Rheem® and Ruud® to Deliver Seamless Online Booking Experience #HASHTAG#/Marketing #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$DUK Duke Energy awards $200,000 in grants to support economic development in Florida #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$NEE American Indian Graduate Center unveils NextEra Energy Scholarship Program #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Active Minerals Announces Price Increases #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E-Bike Market worth $79.7 billion by 2026 - Exclusive Report by MarketsandMarkets™  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$EQT EQT Announces Public Offering Of Common Stock By Selling Shareholders #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lydsto R1 Self-emptying Robot Vacuum Allows Users to Cross Vacuuming Off the Chore List #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Services #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analyzing COVID-19 Impact on Air Cargo Market | 3.37% YOY growth expected in 2021 | Technavio  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$TTI TETRA Technologies, Inc. Announces Third Quarter 2021 Income Before Discontinued Operations Of $2.5 Million And Adjusted EBITDA Of $15.0 Million #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$DM SHAREHOLDER ALERT: Levi &amp;amp; Korsinsky, LLP Notifies Shareholders of Desktop Metal, Inc. of a Class Action Lawsuit and a Lead Plaintiff Deadline of February 22, 2022 - DM #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$AMD Thinking about trading options or stock in Mastercard, Netflix, Novavax, Tesla, or Advanced Micro Devices? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$K Kellogg Company Reaches New Tentative Agreement with Union #HASHTAG#/Union #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MESI: Upcoming Effective Medical Assessment Conference to highlight predictive diagnostics as a way forward #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$ORCL Half of US Colleges Surveyed Have Not Started Preparations for New Student Aid Requirements #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# #&amp; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$VZ JumpStart and Verizon Announce Learning Centers to Provide Skill-based STEM Education to Cleveland Residents #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$ERIE Erie Insurance earns 2021 Diversity Impact Awards from the Global ERG Network #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#-American #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orbit Coffee Offers a Triple-Punch Pick-Me-Up #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Services #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$FSLR National Grid Renewables Announces Commercial Operation of 200 MW Prairie Wolf Solar Project in Illinois #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The South African / USA "Adventures of Zizwe" Spiritual "heroines" Animation Series Wins at the Prestigious Accolade Global Film Festival #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High-Growth Frozen Food Brand Real Good Foods Launches Grain-Free, Nutritious Pizza Made with Beyond Meat's Plant-Based Sausage #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Services #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$CCL Caribbean Princess Welcomes Guests Back Onboard for a Season of Cruises to the Tropical Caribbean from Ft. Lauderdale #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Services #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$ALK Un-Belize-able! Alaska Airlines launches first flights to Belize City from SEA and LAX #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Services #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$AON BrainScope and Aon Secure IP-based Deal Funding Full Expansion of Commercial Activities and Pursuit of New Indications for BrainScope's Next-Gen Medical Device Platform #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$SMP Standard Motor Products, Inc. Announces Appointment of New Director #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$TWOU 2U, Inc. to Present at the Needham Technology &amp;amp; Media Conference #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$AER AerCap Completes Acquisition of GE Capital Aviation Services from GE #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chicago Housing Initiative Receives Support from Medical Home Network Accountable Care Organization #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$PLT Poly and Microsoft Teams Rooms Studio Kits Bring Equity and Ease to Hybrid Work for Any Room Size #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Services #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$QLYS Qualys Teams with TD SYNNEX to Deliver Leading Security Solutions Including Vulnerability Management, Detection and Response and Patch Management via the Qualys Cloud Platform #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free Popular Ebooks Provide Sweet Summer Reading Experience for Students #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Services #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Porter Freight Funding Partners with Leading USDOT &amp;amp; FMCSA Compliance Agency (US Compliance Services) #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The American Legion National Commander Congratulates President-Elect Biden #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$IMAX IMAX Corporation to Present at the Wells Fargo 5th Annual Virtual TMT Summit and the UBS Global TMT Virtual Conference #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$TGT Target Announces Fast, Easy Solutions for Last-Minute Holiday Shoppers #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Services #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American Legion assists thousands through Buddy Checks #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$AHT Ashford Trust Amends Corporate Financing #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$ORCL Oracle Opens First Cloud Region in Italy #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$KLR Kaleyra Announces Third Quarter 2021 Results #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$034220 LG Display Unveils Next-Generation OLED TV Display 'OLED EX' #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Services #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$LLY Lilly accelerating baricitinib's availability in India following receipt of permission for restricted emergency use as a COVID-19 therapy via donations and licensing agreements #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$SNX Hyve Solutions Unveils Building Blocks for Hyperscale Infrastructure #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$LEG Leggett &amp;amp; Platt Reports Record 3Q Sales #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wounded Warrior Project Addresses Barriers Faced by Veterans Exposed to Toxicants #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11.04% CAGR in Preschool or Childcare Market in China by 2025 | Rising Demand for Sustained Enrollment to Boost Growth | Technavio  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$AAL Thinking about trading options or stock in American Airlines, Peloton, NVIDIA, Carnival Corp, or Citigroup? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$DAO NetEase Cloud Classroom Introduces Free AWS Digital Training Courses in China #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Services #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$CNPOF PharmHouse Closes Sale of Greenhouse Facility  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smithfield Foods Commits $300,000 to Heritage STEM Camps Foundation to Increase Participation Among Minority Women #HASHTAG#-related #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$MTN Vail Resorts Hospitality Announces Annual Cyber Sale #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Services #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$KTEL KonaTel Subsidiary, Infiniti Mobile, Approved Provider in Emergency Broadband Benefit Program #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Services #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$VVV Valvoline Reports Fourth-Quarter and Fiscal Year 2021 Results; Reiterates Plan to Pursue Separation; Provides Fiscal 2022 Outlook #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$GOL GOL Announces Investor Update #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At 14.6% CAGR, Warehouse Automation Market is Projected to Reach USD 38.23 Bn by 2027, Says Brandessence Market Research  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lung Cancer Research Foundation Raises Awareness of Lung Cancer in Women #HASHTAG#-related #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$LUV Southwest Airlines Announces 15-Year Agreement With Velocys For 219 Million Gallons Of Sustainable Aviation Fuel #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Viant Completes Major Expansion of Orthopedic Implant Manufacturing Facility in Chaumont, France  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chasing Gold providing the means for American athletes to do what they do best: Bring home Olympic medals  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Home Depot Foundation and Habitat for Humanity partner to support safe, affordable housing for U.S. veterans #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$SNX TD SYNNEX Names Sammy Kinlaw SVP of Customer Communities in North America #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$TFC Truist expands Operation HOPE financial coaching to 600 branches #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$MIST Milestone Pharmaceuticals Announces Late-Breaker Oral Presentation of NODE-301 Data at ACC.21 #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Medical #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$CEO CNOOC Limited Announces Liuhua 29-2 Gas Field Commences Production #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$AEO The It Gets Better Project Announces $500K Grant Initiative Benefiting LGBTQ+ Youth with Support from American Eagle and Aerie Brands #HASHTAG#/Gay/Bisexual #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$BRX BRIXMOR PROPERTY GROUP APPOINTS SANDRA A.J. LAWRENCE TO BOARD OF DIRECTORS #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covalent Metrology Announces New Executive Leadership and Positions for Scaled Growth #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$ENVB Enveric Biosciences Announces Artificial Intelligence Platform, PsyAI™, Has Identified Viable Drug Candidates from its 'Psybrary' of Psychedelic Molecular Compounds #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Medical #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National Corporate Housing Expands in Dublin, Ireland #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fintech Wirex Appoints Top Female Talent to Senior Marketing Role #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$RMAX RE/MAX National Housing Report for November 2021 #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# #&amp; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Acronis SCSVets to Graduate 100 Veterans &amp; Military Spouses by End-of-Year #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$APD Air Products, Aramco, ACWA Power, and Air Products Qudra Complete Asset Acquisition and Project Financing Transactions for $12 Billion ASU/Gasification/Power Joint Venture at Jazan, Saudi Arabia #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$1873 Viva Biotech and BioMap Reached a Strategic Collaboration Agreement, To Jointly Accelerate the Early Drug Discovery through AI Technology #HASHTAG#/Marketing #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stand-up Paddleboard Market to grow by $108.21 Million from 2021 to 2025 |Technavio  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At 10.5% CAGR, Vaccine Adjuvants Market Revenue to Cross $ 1400.1 Million by 2027; Brandessence Market Research  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 59 Years, the Families of Flying Tiger Line Flight 739 Receive Closure #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$TDG TransDigm Fourth Quarter Earnings Report and Conference Call Set for Tuesday, November 16, 2021 #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$CP CP and Canpotex enter new long-term agreement #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saban Music Group Declares "Justice" A New Message Of Hope And Equality By Up And Comer Nakkia Gold Ft. Wiz Khalifa, Bob Marley And The Wailers #HASHTAG#-American #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catholic Charities USA and Felician Sisters of North America establish $2 million "CCUSA Francis Fund for Eviction Prevention" #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$CNDA.U Concord Acquisition Corp II Announces the Separate Trading of Its Class A Common Stock and Warrants Commencing on or About October 22, 2021 #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delta Dental launches nationwide effort to advance patient-centered care  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nature's Path Becomes First Canadian Company to make 100% Fairtrade cocoa commitment using the Fairtrade Sourced Ingredient Program #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$ABT Abbott Launches New Initiative to Drive Diversity in Medical Research and Improve Care Among Under-Represented Populations #HASHTAG#-Related #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#-Oriented #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$0945 John Hancock Premium Dividend Fund Notice to Shareholders - Sources of Distribution Under Section 19(a) #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introducing Top Notch Services at The Sterling Group  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$SEAS SeaWorld Proudly Supports Manatee Awareness Month, Providing Essential Role in Manatee Preservation and Completing Nearly 1,300 Rescues, Rehabilitations and Returns #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Polymer Market to Grow With 5.1% CAGR Through 2030, says P&amp;amp;S Intelligence  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gogoro Announces Partnership With DCJ And Yadea To Build Battery Swapping Network In China #HASHTAG#-Related #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Marketing #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Craig Newmark Philanthropies Commits $650K to IWMF's Emergency Support of U.S. Journalists #HASHTAG#-related #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$WD Walker &amp;amp; Dunlop Reinforces Affordable Lending Commitment with Addition of Affordable Housing Chief Production Officer #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Lactose-free Cheese Industry (2020 to 2027) - Market Trajectory &amp;amp; Analytics  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$OMC DDB Latina Strikes All-Year-Round Creative Festivals As Network Of The Year #HASHTAG#-Oriented #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$RKT Rocket Companies to Acquire Truebill, Adding Rapidly Expanding Financial Empowerment FinTech to the Rocket Platform #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Native Computing Foundation Welcomes New Relic to Governing Board as a Platinum Member #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$RFP Resolute Completes Amendment and Extension of Its ABL Credit Facility #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cole Haan Introduces Performance Tennis #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celonis Ushers in the Era of Data Execution #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#/Services #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heropa achieves Microsoft Co-sell Ready Status for Virtual IT Labs #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$BKI Black Knight: 8.8 Million Rate/Term Refinances Over Last 18 Months Have Delivered $14 Billion in Monthly Savings to Homeowners; Refi Incentive Reduced but Still Historically Strong #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# #&amp; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parks Associates: 37% of US SMBs Likely to Purchase Cybersecurity Services in the Next Six Months #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$STLA New Jeep® Wrangler 4xe and All-new Jeep Grand Cherokee Win 'Adventure Vehicle of the Year' Awards from GearJunkie #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>