<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My therapist has made the same observation to me after years of therapy. Kids often withdraw out of safety, which makes sense then. We need to as adults learn to be safe while being a full member of society at the same time. And that's a very, very difficult lesson to learn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good on you. I've grown twice as much hair on my head as last week, so I'm having a really good go of things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, having a burning masks party &amp; now having to suspend activities due to COVID? Hmmm, I wonder if they saw this coming. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There are some USL back lines I would trust more than several of the defenses in MLS era. 2015 was special beyond for sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The wind &amp; rain are random as f**k out in West Gres-ham today, but that hasn't stopped the grounds crew at the school behind our house from running leaf blowers for the past 45 minutes straight. JFC. I loathe them. To no freaking end, I loathe those machines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, it's one of our eight different cup competitions about something or other instead of working to strengthen the presence of USWNT players within their domestic league. I'm overly excited about this. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't even follow their teams &amp; knew this poll would be doomed the minute they clicked Tweet. Wow. You would think they would know better. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah, but there are some huge names on the list that I have seen, so we might be Ok here. Can only lose 1 player if anybody is selected &amp; they can only choose 5 total so I can see where the odds are with us here. It's still unsettling though, but I'm believing beyond reason here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Uh, okay. Pardon me while I fall off my chair laughing hysterically at the ineptitude of this idea. No, really, I think it could work. Really.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure, keep telling yourself this as the COVID cases skyrocket as your state crumbles to keep their footing. Someone really doesn't know much about how things work around here. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# They are throwing potatoes at it. What else do you think they can pull off to help?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Shakey's was a huge staple of my youth in Boise. One of the few restaurants my family could all agree upon going to that didn't involve varying degrees of emotional mayhem (sister was very picky eater, stepdad was a complete jerk, mom just wanted food &amp; peace, I loved pizza).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Match is on FS1 as well, so national audience for the broadcast. Wondering how that will influence things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yup. And while the logical side of me understands that, the emotional side is angry &amp; frustrated at people who instead of doing what is best for everybody decided their choice was more important.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Honestly, I was listening to radio a few days ago &amp; the songs all sounded very tinny &amp; offputting. I thought it was just the radio, as I played them digitally &amp; they were much better. This could explain the whole issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nevada joined "the cool kids" club in terms of voting. Nice work as Nevada Gov. Sisolak signs permanent mail-in voting system into law #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's one of the various cup things to distract fans from the fact that USWNT really doesn't support their own domestic league. It's better if we make our monies from our own tournaments instead. Oh, wait, I said that out loud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But throwing money at it &amp; yelling into the void that we're awesome apparently is much more fun. Yet it's that belief that is ultimately killing off any momentum towards doing exactly what you stated - we accept what we are &amp; work to make it better for the future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pfizer. Shot 1 was a relative breeze with few issues. Shot 2 put me in bed sleeping for most of a day, but once I was up later that day, I was absolutely fine. No soreness at all. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting seriously blows. Thanks for the updates or lack thereof.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe the lesson you should have learned is having empathy for someone suffering during an event many people enjoy. Doesn't mean we aren't upset about the world's issues and working for real change. People can care about several things at once. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Columbia is actually decent for having wide range of sizes in my experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to #USER# for sharing this amazing story about an amazing person. I wished I had met him in person over my years within the TA, but I'm honored to have learned about how truly amazing Kevin is through sharing these stories. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nope. I dig both sports honestly and am looking forward to the upcoming Olympics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess that I am champion level passive aggressive at work because I use plenty of column A. Yet I only use them when absolutely necessary due to timelines or repeated behaviors. And the suggestions come off much worse IMHO. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uh, yellow isn't the color I would expect for this card. Wow. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I don't blame people for not wanting to give MP ticket money, but that means them being replaced by others that don't care nearly as much. We all need to yell in whatever manner necessary whereever that they knew &amp; covered it up, only addressing it when they got caught. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# They must be so proud. Seriously. Who wouldn't want to associate with someone that legendary with such awesome takes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shout out goes to the douches working on their car playing loud rap music at 1 am this morning next to our house. The fact you picked right up at 7:15 AM just adds to the legacy of your being. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would love finding compromise &amp; a solution involving both sides. But when one side has effectively said our role is to prevent your group from doing anything &amp; we're going to do anything we can to do it, there's no room for compromise with that. Hope Senate Dems are listening. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Or it's great to get inspiration to help guide or change your course. It's a big reason why I still hang out in this place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As a person who watches basketball, the box out position was really poor and his feet were in a terrible spot. Needs better coaching to see the floor again. These fundamentals are really bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'd love to be wrong, and I hope the trend continues as I think it's still too soon to judge anything about ATX FC. If this continues for a while &amp; it's still similar to what I saw yesterday, I will be happy to give Austin its due. Anything is better than Flounders. (2/x)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hopefully it's clown free. Well, unless PK is there, which then means all bets are off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And over the years, I've even made that kool-aid joke myself after being desensitized to the original events. Yet I do remember being unsettled as a child hearing what happened for many, many months. It's very odd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Considering she's a tortie with full on catitude, I appreciate the Stewie reference. Quite a lot actually.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# wait, you're more than a soccer guy? wow, I would have never guessed that! Thank you for clarifying that important point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And here I thought it was just done to cause mayhem on social media among people just so they can watch everyone argue about whether it's a sport or not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Don't remember. Too many fart clouds from about to recall, but Jen remembered forming a line to stop people from cutting in front of us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cause freedom. Or stupidity. Or whatever. I don't know, but it's beginning to get very annoying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well, and when you get older, it's easier to hit the CAPS LOCK button on your tablet, laptop or phone. Keith knows not what he does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've worked in banking my entire career &amp; Black Friday is one of the craziest days for us because of all the retail activity. I remember our phone bank being off the charts with people calling about monies. I can't imagine what it was like in stores as I always am working.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# S M R T, I mean S M A R T. I am having the same Monday here, glad I'm not trying to get into an office in this weather mess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Thirdly. One of the most genuine spirits out there, always a great chat with him on the few chances that I get to see him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Applaud you both for this. I understand the need for social media &amp; try to use it for those purposes only, but I will vent from time to time. But I'm much happier when I take walks about my neighborhood safely or work out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LRT: I've worked in the corporate world for 30 plus years &amp; worked many days when I should have taken time off to help me. But I felt guilty about leaving my team in a lurch, but my health &amp; psyche suffered in pushing myself. A day off could have done wonders for me in retrospect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# My wife &amp; I love airports. We seriously walk about as much as we can to take in the sights &amp; sounds, so it's not uncommon for us to be way ahead of our flight time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[uh, that's a pretty sweet free kick. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# For sure. I'm OK with reasonable cost jumps up every year, that just makes sense, but it seemed like the jumps got bigger &amp; bigger with the perks getting less and less until most don't exist anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've reached the point in my work year where it's probably easier to tell me who is in the office versus who is out on vacation. I'm almost ready to put that as my Outlook notification - yes, I'm really here and working. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Timbers player news. He's back. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Only thing I will say is this - if he needs to go, there had better be a viable, available candidate that could replace him. I'm not versed enough to know who that might be, but replacing him doesn't immediately fix our issues IMHO. I do agree that changes need to occur &amp; soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's 2021: Forever Whirling. Cue up the Simpsons thing about whirling about in several directions as we move towards victory or something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm so sorry to hear this. Apparently, the douche factor at the match last night was huge between masking issues &amp; stolen gear per the tweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm already paying a boatload to my cable provider in addition to the other streaming services we have. As much as I want to watch, I can't absorb another service just because. It's bordering on ridiculous the costs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whooo hooo. You get broken, and then you get broken. And then somebody else gets broken. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I remember something like this happening a few times during my youth back in Boise, yet nobody could explain it &amp; many about thought it was hearsay &amp; not true. Glad I'm not imagining things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My current self understands this reality as I'm awaiting word on my new manager. My younger self despised this instability &amp; I think that's why my career stagnated for so long. It's not easy to embrace it, but it does help having the wisdom of many years within work rat race.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow made it look awesome last night, but the power went out about 1:30 am. Still not restored but at least a crew is showing up now to review it. Fun weather times. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, get rid of one of the people that knows what they are doing to help the country? Sure, this sounds like a great idea. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important thread read for the day. You are most welcome. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# IMHO I trust the NWSL stability over the French league right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grover is awesome and I loved Bert and Ernie, but you can't go wrong with someone that lives in a trash can. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck jugging when the schedules overlap &amp; fans complain about missing coverage: ROOT SPORTS is already the home for the  Mariners, Seahawks, Kraken, Seawolves, Gonzaga University, Big Sky Conference &amp; Portland Timbers. Hope Root 2 is happening to help sort this all out. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# So what does this mean for the future of USOC in terms of MLS involvement? I love that selected US teams compete annually for the title of best soccer club. I'm assuming this move means MLS isn't able to play or will essentially play the youth if they are obligated?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[69' Adi with good work to spring Wallace but Rodney gets YC for bumping Melia on shot effort. Simply incredible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I had to stick close to home with several updates happening for work, so I couldn't wander. I support your choice for foods.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why stop lawmakers from making rules when they lack the basic knowledge to understand what it is they are trying to make rules about? What's the worst that could possibly happen? #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Per Timbers stats, we've scored 6 goals twice as Krista mentioned. Last time was 10/07/20  at  LA  Galaxy:  W  6-3. The SJ match was the other instance. So this is now the third such occurance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes. Luxor has one as well if you choose to venture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow, so all of my education in economics could have been summed up in one sentence - lines going up good. That would have saved me a lot of money. Go figure. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yup, same group ran both locations. And Corbett closed a lot sooner than Hawthorne IIRC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I know what Rich is seasoned with after several seasons of watching him go Chara all over the pitch. We could honestly do a lot worse than letting him lace them up. If Keith is anything within the same vein as that, count me in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This thread brought up emotions showing a list of #HASHTAG# supporters who are no longer with us, yet their memories live on. There aren't many days where I don't think of a story involving Howie or Gisele, but I know their spirit will be very present tomorrow, as will many others. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Never been. Had wanted to visit years ago, but now seems like a waste of time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Acid jazz hold music right before our quarterly all hands meeting with the big management. Yeah, that's not ominous or odd at all. And it's cranked up to eleven, too. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Right, because the alphabet network is such an expert on all of the sports they cover. Or pretend to cover. Or ignore on a regular basis. We need more shows on that network where dudes in suits yell at each other!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Can relate. Seems like there is something going on culturally and it's unsettling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here's the insanity of the AL Wild Card race between 4 teams, including the Mariners. Lots and lots of scoreboard watching, because of course, nobody is playing each other. Thank god for everyone starting at 12:00 PM West Coast. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I understand. It's not worth the risks. Not trying to be fearful at all as I have the least severe conditions, but if I went out &amp; got exposed to bring it back to my house, I'd honestly never be able to forgive myself should I infect my wife, MIL or cats. Nothing is worth more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Way to go, Idaho. Putting the dis in dysfunctional for as long as I can remember. Uh, I might have been a teenager when living there, but I don't recall such antics during my time there. Keep doing you!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow. I only wish you were kidding, but I would be asking the same question if I were you. I'm really sorry about this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My company's health care provider has this as part of their mobile app. I just found it moments ago after Jen said something to me about this post. This is really freaking easy to use.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# PTOSC was 06. MP didn't become team president until part way into 07 season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sorry for your loss. I lost my mom back in 05 to lung cancer actually on 9/9. This time of year is always really emotional for me personally. Thank you for sharing your story, it really helped brighten my day. Your mom sounds like an amazing person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to thank the academy for this great honor. It's come with a lot of solid work &amp; effort by everybody, but I think this award speaks for itself in what happens when people work together for a common goal. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# For Giants fans like me, we love stats like this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's the section with the loud people, Kristen. LOL. But yeah, nobody needs to be that drunk they forget where their seats are. Nobody.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IIRC This would leave the Blazers as the only NBA team without an exclusive partnership within the G League. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One of the best sounds at that airport ever is the Wheel Of Fortune yell from those machines. I love Vegas. Glad that you found the lucky machine!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Love reading these stories. Apparently, a lot of people made this trip &amp; have similar experiences. I actually watched their feed versus the Timbers years ago &amp; was struck how awesome the whole experience was at the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I've dealt with this nearly every day in my career &amp; still fight it. It's a daily challenge, but it does get easier when I have co-workers &amp; managers that support me no matter what. And it's getting a lot easier being the true me at the office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They already nearly butchered a rebrand years ago &amp; they are up to something now? I'm frightened.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is bad. Really bad. Please Timbers do better here. Rules are supposed to be enforced. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Back at you all. Enjoy the feast of massive consumption with family gatherings!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Way to make the statement then run away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm still upset about how the game ended, but proud of the Giants &amp; the season they had. I like the future of this group &amp; cannot wait for next year. I also can't figure out what the hell that guy was thinking by laughing at you. Some people are just jerks by nature.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why didn't anybody tell me??????? I'm always the last to know anything!!! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We understand the situation all too well. Jen had to force feed our last couple of kitties when it got to that point. After a month, they really got fussy &amp; tried to bite her. I miss them terribly, but am thankful for every last minutes we had with each of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# University Food Center was the name, but Chad ran the place so that was the nickname. It shared the parking lot with what is now Wolffy's. According to Google Maps, it's now a virtual reality arcade. I see Pete's Pizza is still about as well, thank god.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I'm sure there is a catchy song in there, but I can't think of anything clever right now. I just know my sports teams love to make things as interesting as possible, so of course, we are in a game 5 with our biggest rivals in the Dodgers. Of course we are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'll take annoying as f**k. Or the most passive aggressive way to deal with something. It's not good either way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You might be a jack@$$, but you do have a point here. The software said I had a call &amp; I was presenting something, but honestly, I could have been in the damn void for all I know. Not exactly the way I wanted to start today, but it's never boring when I lead calls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow. You must be so proud to be so smug and sanctimonious. Drawing a line on something so benign when there are far more obvious targets to draw ire at takes a special kind of skill. Keep on keeping on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Exactly. I can't even fathom the rational with this just to save face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Have they tried turning themselves off, then on again? That works for my computer. Just saying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Look, I remember what the building was prior to being a bar, so it's really odd to see it in this format.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's a conundrum that I imagine many are facing today. I know it's been going on for years with Timbers supporters. There are no easy answers here despite what many will say. I just say listen to your head &amp; heart to do what is best for you personally. Screw what others think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Most of my teams are on Central or East time zone, so a majority of my meetings are 7 to 9 AM PT. Luckily, I love coffee, I have control of the mute button &amp; my cats provide amusement since I need to have my camera on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's an opinion that I have had for years. I miss several seasons of greatness but the last episode with Pizza Bots was one of the best I have seen. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sport is a business &amp; is always treated as such, but there is a personal side to any trade. Personally, I'm angry with the Timbers doing this, yet I realize it's probably best for Jebo's long term career to play the 9 &amp; he can do that in San Jose. Just wished he could do it here. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey kids it's the line ride. My absolute favorite thing to do ever! I think I can see the front.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah, I'm having the same issue, too. I'll keep trying because simply put, I will make the time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impressive and important thread for today. Never take the eyes off the prize here. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what we get for keeping the filibuster in place &amp; listening to the GQP about things. Real change isn't going to happen if the other side is allowed to change or delete the paths &amp; programs a huge majority of the country want. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I'm with you all. My wife &amp; I have this debate regularly with both of us having autoimmune conditions. We had the initial bliss but we have withdrawn back to regular COVID standards with deliveries only. It's not worth the risks IMHO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You are probably right, but the situation will be that many STH will be sitting in different places than where they are used to. Better to prepare for that possibility now because it's very, very likely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saw this on social media &amp; thought there was no way this could be real. So imagine my surprise that not only is it true, but they've doubled down on this. Apparently their plan to govern is just to poke holes at the other side's ideas while offering nothing but platitudes. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah, I missed the date thing. Oops. Yes, it is tomorrow. My mad, but I would hope the damn league would know when their games are. Seems like kind of important details.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Take your eyes off the situation for the tiniest moment &amp; it can derail everything. The momentum we had gained was lost by the one simple act &amp; we never came close to recovering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I got angry, but then I just laughed. You can't make up stuff like that &amp; it's probably some intern that just used a photo service to find MLS photos, found this one &amp; thought it was good enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I know plenty in that camp myself. I was disappointed by the situation, but in sitting in plenty of MLS to PDX meetings personally, I know he did a lot to try &amp; keep the team here. He was undone by plenty of people &amp; situations including actions by the current mayor of PDX.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Oh, no, there is a very real border. I had a party down there that actually involved drinking lots on the literal dividing line. Most good parties down there, however, do blend the campuses quite seamlessly. I'm wondering how they actually get any school work done sometimes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My apologies if I took incorrect offense to your statement. You've just posted something similar to this on several occasions when I've put out similar calls like that, so yes, I'm a little sensitive. I'm just trying to do anything I can to amplify the message anywhere I can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How truly "Christian" of you to make such a statement. You must be really proud. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's been this way for as long as I've been following the team, so I'm not expecting any changes anytime soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With all the issues surrounding soccer in the US, this should obviously move to the top of the list because it's so vital. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had retweeted something earlier from the ACLU supporting them suing West Virginia that cut off weird on some forms of Twitter that might make it appear I'm in support of a state trans ban. Suffice to say, that is very, very, very wrong. States shouldn't be doing crap like this. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# 100 percent chance of it being freaking hot with triple digit temperatures in Portland all weekend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Congrats on the new human added to your collective. Best wishes to you &amp; the entire family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We had an attack? Being sarcastic somewhat, but yeah, our offense was offensive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It hasn't been for many years. Part of my issues with the church honestly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Thinking the rules don't apply to you or just doing whatever because it's more important for personal freedom or liberty than doing what helps a larger group. Yeah, that sounds very American as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thank you for sharing, but let's not pretend there isn't a bigger issue here - the Timbers got pushed out due to competition from other teams with similar schedules - Mariners, Kraken, Blazers - and matches would likely move to ROOT+ due to that. This just avoids hassles. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Last picture of my pet. Since you asked nicely. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# FFS. This organization has severely lost its way if they are allowing things like this within the park &amp; not stopping it. It breaks my heart, but hey, they seem to be more interested in massaging the past to avoid accountability than looking at any real change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wow. Simply inexcusable for a media outlet to make such an error.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You could be referring to another team's fan base within the same area here, as it's been obvious for many years there as well. They probably learned it from the Blazers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This makes no sense whatsoever. I am truly stunned by this statement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I would vote the fender bender. You should get checked out if you can just to make sure there isn't anything wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm not sure she could have turned in time. That should be part of the consideration there, could the defender do anything at all? You have to allow for some reaction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Garden Home? Wow, that's a blast from the past for sure, but yeah, that's one hugely meandering bus line.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, apparently the font didn't throw anybody off. I'm expecting big news for some guy that wears the number 8. Apparently he's really good &amp; did great things this year or something. :) #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You are absolutely right that nobody came out looking good in this, as it's been mishandled by all. Over 20 years, you would expect we could have helped build something that would be sustainable under all this, but the fact it crumbled in 3 weeks is troubling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have to get up early for work on weekdays &amp; I respect construction crews greatly for what they do, but you lose all credibility with me if you show up at your site near my house at 6:40 AM with your stereo up so loud it causes our windows to shake &amp; rattle. Seriously f**k off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sure, it's not my first rodeo about here. Still doesn't change how I feel about being insulted &amp; apparently I'm not alone in my disgust right now either. Just sharing my frustration amongst the RCTID crowd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As is now tradition this year, I won't be watching the NCAA brackety thing because you don't mess with a successful streak that works. Yes, I believe in superstitions. Am sending good vibes to the Bulldogs as I'm #HASHTAG#. I hope they keep on dancing until the end. Seriously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I will trade you for some plums straight out of beautiful West Gres-ham. You can just taste the pluminess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good lord. So apparently the baptisms didn't take due to one word being changed. So instead of your soul being cleansed, the clear coat is now plaid colored or there's one less thing on the invincibility scale. FFS. I'm glad I gave up on Catholocism. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've lost track of the number of explosions in my neighborhood &amp; I have 3 very terrified cats wondering what the hell is going on outside. To say I'm frustrated with my fellow humans right now is an understatement. But hey, enjoy your little explosions because you f**king can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Considering I think that's what they do for other markets where they cover teams (Golden Knights, Jazz, etc), I think so. But I'd rather it be more spelled out than assumed at this point. We will see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Or albums. I still have a ton of albums that I got from joining back in the day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We can go back to Sesame Street for the great lesson of what near is and what far is. Near fits the explanation per Grover, who trumps VAR so it stands. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# We have always needed that quality. IMHO Ridgy had the talent &amp; could light up teammates when needed. Seba is only one on current roster with any of that snark. It's needed badly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right because most kids know nothing of bad words. What kind of world do we live in to allow such disrespectful language? I'm going to need a moment to recover from all of this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My initial reaction to this statement as an alum is very much OUCH, but objectively speaking, you are correct based upon our current resume. We will need to finally win one to change that narrative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow. I'm sorry to read this but glad you are on the mend. Best wishes for a great start to the new year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As annoying as that would be, it would be so like MLS to grant them a berth for that very reason just because.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Mariner TV ratings here are still very huge &amp; there is still a sizable contingent of people that travel to games up there. I was looking for some posts on it, but in talking with NBC Sports NW folks months ago, they mentioned Mariner TV ratings here were very substantial.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dude. Ouch. Sending best wishes for a quick recovery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Even if that is true - which is horrible if it is - that still doesn't excuse or justify his actions relating to the players over the years. Just when I thought they couldn't make things worse, they stoop to another lower level.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zero times anything is still zero, unless math is somehow different in the GQP world. Which I don't think it is. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Our old Honda's gas gauge was really accurate until the car started having issues with starting. It got very finicky   before we donated it when it was struggling to start &amp; the gauge would go on and off at random times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I remain in the corporate world where I'm bucking the trend &amp; taking care of me. Honestly, I've not been happier since making this choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thanks for reminding me about that. Someone needs to end that streak and now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is fine. Really. Nothing to see here. This is all good. I mean, I learned how to say this correctly by watching hours &amp; hours of Looney Tunes back in my childhood, but hey, you do you. It's OK, whatever. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Us? Drinking? That's unpossible. Do you even know us?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yes, the WICC controls what happens in the tournament, so they make the rules. Much like when CONCACAF comes to town, they set the match parameters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Apparently in the US or up my butt depending on the various replies that I'm getting. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Uh, okay, sure. I guess me wanting to save some money means putting up with lunacy &amp; idiotic behavior. Guess I should just put up with the stupidity. LOL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So O does come before U in this case?ðŸ˜¬ I got no allegiance on either side, as our TV is watching something else. The game wasn't too insane last I checked. ðŸ˜œðŸ˜ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's the motto of our esteemed local publication. They'll have to find something more appropriate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tell us something we don't know, Rich.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He's not fat, he's big boned. That's what my cat tries to tell me each and every day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I've been reading a lot of the Vegas insider accounts talking about the challenges to keep venues open &amp; staffed. Can't even imagine everything they are trying to do in order to have people there to serve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tell #USER# to stop messing around and getting us all in trouble. This measure twice, cut once philosophy is nothing but trouble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'd be honestly shocked if there wasn't. I've been there a few times in my day and never saw it myself, but take no ownership if this becomes an idea to spawn it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I have been lucky enough to have access to employees store each time I needed jackets, but the Dicks near my house always has wide range of sizes. Good luck in your search.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# FYI - the 150 is AQI, not temperature, although it's 102 and it certainly feels hotter than that outside. It's abjectly terrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you creepy NY robocall person. Your 6:42 AM call to me saying the IRS was coming for me was greatly appreciated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Our cats are the same. It's 3 hours of running about creating havoc as loudly as possible, then eating a bare minimun to then begin begging for food in 30 minutes after being fed. It's the kitty cycle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Fair point. And I am only pointing it out to emphasize how much supporters actually spend supporting their side. Fans IMHO don't spend nearly this much, but I know nothing about economics. Or money. Or soccer âš½ï¸. I can't believe the FO can't or won't understand the impact here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good lord. Just make him stop already. Seriously. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Unsure for now, will let you know if anything changes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's Deadspin. I'm shocked if they write in complete sentences with proper grammar, so the intelligence part is just icing on the cake so to speak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# West Gres-ham would like the trash to stay exactly where it is, simply as we already have our own issues going on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I can't imagine having her as a representative of your state or community. Can't think of anybody that could possibly be worse, especially the not knowing how she will engage from moment to moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I love the Timbers but this is a completely stupid statement to say it never happened. They could have said anything else, but instead chose this language. It's been nagging with me ever since to be honest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Kentucky for keeping this @$$clown in office so he can effectively stop any meaningful changes that are needed within our government to help people that need it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I, for one, love the bots making crap up as our new news leader. And I remind them as a media member myself that I can be used to herd together soccer fans for useless &amp; pointless purposes. Or not. :) #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After waiting 30 minutes on chat for service, my queue time has been quoted as less than 1 minute. For the past 45 minutes. This seems totally fine in terms of customer service I would think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud of this team under the circumstances of 2021. It's going to be a wild one next weekend back at Providence Park when they host MLS Cup. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I hope this gets resolved in the right manner. Supporters sections need to be set aside &amp; treated as such by all teams. I can't fathom a team not making that clear or insisting on it for traveling supporters. Best way to avoid any hassles on game day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not that I want to beat up somebody more than they might already be doing, but hopefully they understood the significance of the banner &amp; won't let something like this happen again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah, we are such terrible people and don't get along with anybody. Now you know the dirty little secret. BWAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!!!!!! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Stay up all night. Or just show up half asleep. Whatever works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My cable provider. If I say their name several times outloud, it conjures up bad spirits, so I shall not invoke the dark side. But it's probably not hard to guess who it it. And yeah, my company's chat has some great response times, so when something is really bad, it stands out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Todd, it was a really big card and they carried it around the entire park.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe in faith &amp; the concept of having a wonderful community that people can belong to. However, any "religion" that can allow such monstrous behavior under the guise of their beliefs can get bent. Don't use a belief in God as a cover for extremely hateful behavior. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Apparently everything has a price tag. (I know the reality, but watching my country be pulled apart piece by piece is sad) #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>