<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Indeed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# LOL ... SO WHAT THE HELL DIED SOCIAL DISTANCING DO THEN? 

HEY #USER# A TRAVEL BAN IS JUST SOCIAL DISTANCING ON A GLOBAL SCALE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I would have to concur.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You should check out the alleged FBI report starting that the attack on the capital was planted well before the presidents speech ... you know ... just for clarity sake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The Biden foundation for a richer Joe Biden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A BIG question on this for me is why is prison a thing for a teenager for rigging a meaningless high school election ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We do not have an independent press.

The intent was to have a press free of government control ... not to have a press that can choose to controlled by whichever side of government they choose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Explain to me how sucker-punching someone is not an act of tyranny ... or breaking onto people's property and threatening to kill them ... you are not standing up against that you are promoting it under the facade that it's legal protesting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# &lt;RAISES HAND&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Daddy can't get him another job pulling down millions ... the access the other countries wanted was to Clinton and Obama ... apparently Joe doesn't have pull od he's not connected to them I guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Everytime you say that the costs of goods and services skyrocket ... that's not better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Because WE ... need to see how wrong here is and his antics with the reporters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Democrats platform according to Joe Biden is to RAISE YOUR taxes, thus taking money out of your pocket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# ISIS ... ISIS is also stronger now ... and I understand that Al Qaeda is surging too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're going to cobra that you lied about being native American to get a gig at an ivy laegue university?  WOW A DEMOCRAT TELLING THE TRUTH FOR ONCE ... THAT WOULD BE HISTORIC!!! GOOD FOR YOU! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# where are you? Who is looking into the arbitrary and capricious decision by SCOTUS ruling that one president cannot undo the executive order of a predecessor? FOLLOW YOUR OATH! DEFEND THE CONSTITUTION OR STEP DOWN.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've always said about CA that aterrorist with a box of matches could do a MASSIVE amount of damage ... i don't imagine Oregon quotidian be much different if they manage forests the same way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You can take the burnt ones at numbers 4 and 5 off the list ... they're burnt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Paul is attempting to paint trump in a bad light ... as he's been doing for thre years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# EVERY day ... is ... bacon day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah - cuz he was all takin money and stuff from the Romans in return for access to Jewish state favors #HASHTAG# ... more like Caiphais IMHO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Your own right hand man said you failed miserably with 68m getting H1N1 ... so if you DID leave a playbook ... im glad we skipped it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hmmm interesting that liberals take government to be an all powerful, omnipotent entity, and God to be a social construct of man. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It won't be considered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Kristi Noem ... she's kicking ass in SD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That should day withdraw AND gave numerous criminal charges ... if this is true and he skates like Hillary did ... we have no justice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Makes sense ... call the tune ... pay the piper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Your premise is massively flawed and idiculous and I reject it ... if a natural disaster wiped out all of the mailboxes it would be ONE DAY ... on top of which such WOULD NOT eliminate the capacity of mail collection

What does the law say? You won't answer will you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Never do anything with a loaded or unloaded gun without clearing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hillary Clinton going to jail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Congrats ... that must feel TERRIFIC!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How long was dinesh in for 20k? .

350m รท 20k = 17500 ... so just to be fair ... whatever dinesh served ร 17500.  Same sentence per 20k allotment in 350m.

Then we can like ... oh ... cut it in half so as to not be cruel and unusual.

Just spitballin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# America does not need the trial and tribulation of a Joe Biden presidency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# WHAT??? BILL IS RUNNING AROUND NAKED?  

BTW ... he's NOT the emperor ... and you missed your coronation in 2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# They'll decriminalize the deviancy and try to make it acceptable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Juan Williams lives in his own private world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They don't view the constitution as a deterrent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So, #USER# how do you feel about elder abuse? To continually promote someone who clearly is experiencing dementia as a presidential nominee is disgusting. He needs help and his "handlers" are shameful worth this charade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It worked for the freedom protests in Hong Kong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# OH MY GOSH ... THAT ... SOUNDS LIKE FREEDOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh ... I don't know ... from the right angle that looks like blue darting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It all really started with the hearts and minds tour of Iraq. 

Once that infection commenced ... the doorway to the slippery slope was wide open.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How about you sponsor a house and Senate pull your heads out of your assess act and quit screwing around with the economy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah ... I keep hearing this.  None of it matters if the big dogs aren't indicted. The underlings are sacrificial. If those in charge of it aren't indicted, they know they can act with impunity and no repercussions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Imagine a future ... where government ideologues are not creaming useless nonsense down your throat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've been thinking about ALL OF the incidents of NFL players abusing women over the years a la Ray Rice knocking his GF out in the elevator ... considering that ... is it ANY surprise they league would back a person accused of sexual assault?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That would be because Biden lacks then mental capacity to be unscripted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Hmm because he let his daughter marry a Jewish  man or maybe because his lawyer is of Jewish descent. hallmarks of white supremacy #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Keep in mind ... THAT is the way Biden treats VOTERS asking him questions ... have you EVER heard Trump speak that way to a VOTER?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nah ... #USER# intentionally threw the olive branch on the fire. Are you surprised?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You better beat in a primary then else you give the seat to the impeachment Democrats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There was also a convention center that was converted by army engineers with over 2k beds space that went unused ... completely ... unused.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She seems to be a REAL GOOD catholic #HASHTAG# ... until it comes to abortion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What an embarrassment ... I'm starting to wonder how many of these Olympic athletes were selected for social justice warriorism than athletic capability.  Our "representation" is largely an embarrassment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# had already fearmongered it ... had "an expert" on who said they've had no success and stopped using it ... cavuto wrapped up by saying basically "you'll die".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That would have been an accurate statement even IF Biden wasn't wired.  His intelligence is very artificial.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not over there ... the taliban has all of those drones now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He'll start a civil war.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Democrat hero for "testifying" again fast Trump.  Wer have no rules of law anymore. Liberals break laws with impunity ... especially those in government and NOTHING happens to them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Of the what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Heh ... I probably spend that much avoiding Walmart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# GOOD JOB MOM!!!!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah ... but guess what it's be if she adopted a black dog instead of a white one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The only ones required to reduce emissions is the US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IMHO ... #HASHTAG# is being prepped to be thrown under the bus by the left ... remember NY is losing a house member ... so ... what do you think of occassio-cortez as the governor of NY?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No matter how much they get paid to be exploited.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# LOL ask her about her HUGE entourage of family members listed as advisors ... like way over 250 including their two MINOR daughters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Joe never had a sense of tact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Joe's bank account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# With CNN mandatorily there. 

Just kidding - they'd botch it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Uhhh ... I don't think viruses fare well in smoke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# HIGHER TAXES!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I like fishing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Worth a shot ... i have to force myself when I have migraines bug ig usually helps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I guess so ... but then despicable behavior is high up on their bucket lists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The Supreme Court if PA creating a new mail in ballot law 2 months prior to the election, outside of the state legislature, at the request of the Gov and AG ... IS shennanigans ... they overstepped their authority which is responsible for the chaos now happening in PA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# THEY WON'T. THEIR POWER IS GOING TO HAVE TO BE TAKEN FROM THEM.  THEY AREN'T GIVING IT UP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I lament that I had to do so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You are not alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah he's so far "above the law" that an entire team of anti-trump, Hillary Clinton donating lawyers, couldn't find a crime to charge him with. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's not her fault ... it's all those guns that come in from across state lines, place themselves in innocent people's hands and force them to pull the trigger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You also CANNOT forget the quantitative easing Obama did and the massive debt the goveenment continues to build ... THOSE things contributed to collapsing economy whizz contributed GREATLY to the rise of the tyrant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They're FINE if China uses coal ... just not U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is that why you had to go to mail in voting without proof of signature?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Don't forget the electricity rationing that cost some lives during the fervent wildfires. I se he neglected to include that in his little commercial.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You cannot have safety when tyranny exists. 

Giving up freedom for security is a misnomer ... you lose the freedom but do not REALLY gain in the safety.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I prefer shock and awe fire crap like this ... it makes a bigger statement and they don't have time to adjust or hide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ahhh ... my pleasure. ALWAYS happy to follow fellow patriots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# YEAH! CUZ WOMEN AT NEVER CORRUPT #HASHTAG# nnHow are you going to tell who is make and female?  What about the other supposed 30+ genders?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did you push some buttons???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# YOUR violatns of the constitution are the stain on this nation.  That you are doing it in the name of "democracy" sets the stain ever deeper into the fabric of society]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah ... as a child I ruined Dionne the one time my mom tried to serve it.  She never made it again after that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You know that massive debt such ad you suggest creates inflation ... meaning the prices of goods and services go up ... meaning your policy will hurt poor people with things like food and healthcare ... you're advocating this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mine was made by the real me ... a statement on the political problem we face in America ... two parties joined at the ass by list for money ... neither one caring for the forgotten people who put them in office from whom they steal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Regardless ... she's celebrating the deaths of the victims ... including those MURDERED by #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Thank you ... our serves well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# All you have to do is look at history.  Tyrants have ALWAYS suppressed people by keeping them from gathering under draconian penalties.  The only tactic used slightly more is to ban those they dislike the use of arms.  

These two factors are WHY the first two ammendments exist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's just one more thing where lebron is trying to ride the coattails of Michael Jordan ... and failing miserably.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# &lt;Raises hand&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There'll be another headline soon about police kneeling before their masters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Or ... 

"Caller ID said spam likely. I'll take a case"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When he auctioned off the letter that Harry Reid sent to Clear Channel to have him removed ... for charity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I spend damn near that much in a single visit to the gas station.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Is she really loved this country she'd not be bad for it, there'd be no reason for her to resign, and she'd be defending the constitution appropriately instead of undermining it ... as it is ... the only thing she loves about this country is the taxpayer money she's been given]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They are assholes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone challenging the  denigrate is a threat to the democratocracy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And what is happening now ... IS NEITHER IGNORANCE NOR INCOMPETENCE. 

AT THE VERY LEAST IT'S GREED.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# By the way ... that was #HASHTAG# for the leftists pushing that ... not directed to you #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if this whole mask thing is nothing more than a way to hide ANTIFA and BLM amongst the populace as they go about terrorizing the nation? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What kind of a moronic quiz is this? #HASHTAG# No, by all means let's not hold politicians accountable for their actions - gotta be kidding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh - I don't know let's build arenas and charge admission, could end up being good theater Nazi vs ANTIFA in Knock down drag out #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did Cuomo's executive order - IN YOUR STATE - ordering long term care facilities to take COVID infected patients, in spite of having TWO 1000 bed temporary facilities accessible, kill people who were vulnerable to the virus?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So is this his confession that he was trying to get a piece of tail?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Only ones who have converted to actual thinking people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Aye. 

And the whole ... wait wait wait ... gotta make sure the battery is fully charged.  

Let's see half a tank of gas vs half a battery load.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't get down on yourself ... sometimes when you are driving past an accident it is hard to NOT look at it ... and the worse it is the harder it can be to divert your attention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I would like to say that she is INCREDIBLY NAIVE ... but alas she is TOO MUCH AN OPPPORTUNIST to be naive and she gives little damn about trauma ... how traumatic is it for someone to rot in jail when exculpatory evidence that would vindicate is suppressed by the DA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# LOL ... minimal test demand ... &lt;chuckle&gt; because ... HEHE ... PEOPLE AREN'T SICK HAHA ... HAHAHA  .... BAHAHAHA!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You won't win ... they'll make sure of that at the voting machine level.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They just think they should have so much influence ... is sad really]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Didn't he abdicate ... doesn't that mean he's no longer ROYAL?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And the suffering and deaths of potentially millions has you thrilled? Because it MIGHT get trump out of office? What the hell is wrong with you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And Louisiana? 

While the rocky mountains that are MILES higher are under water???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She could have stopped at doesn't know a single American.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nope ... snot rag may likely have SOME brain matter ... making its IQ much higher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# WOULDN'T BREAK MY HEART!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# One more thing I'm left constantly wondering about ... why do democrats want to bring people to our horrible, racist country. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Based on his general outlook on life - He was ... being in front if her, he was giving her A LOT of room in back of her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ROFLMAO

DOESN'T SHOW YOU WHAT HE IS MISSING WHEN TOWING THE PROJECTILES ... CAN'T SWING A  SLEDGE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Regardless of whether it was 4 days ago or 5 days ago a week ago or fucking yesterday IS IRRELEVANT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# THEN CUT TAXES SO WE'R CAN AFFORD IT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well ... you know ... providing for the needs of the poor rich pedophiles and all #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The dog i had to have euthanized a few years ago due to bone cancer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ROFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# So ... basically ... all a person has to do ... to avoid any sort of even an investigation into their corruption while in office ... is to run for president as as Democrat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A day after I hit 4k ... looked again and was 3400 ... 600 gone in a day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Amy examination of slavery, MUST include the fact that African tribes participated in the slave trade, selling lesser tribes they defeated in wars in order to take the lands they occupied.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Umm ... IT'S A FREAKING MUGSHOT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How about we just remove the show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What I'm saying is the way it is being bandied about right now in states where it hasn't existed before is inviting a disaster and voter disenfranchisement and fraud.  You HAVE to have a deadline and people must meet it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tis sad to say but unknown GOP at this point is better than KNOWN move to green new deal and communism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And she should be prosecuted ... but I doubt she will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I know ... hence my comment ... it is a discussion that will NEVER take place.  

Gun control is about disarming citizenry so a tyrannical gov. can exert unopposed force upon them.  

I'm offering to "discuss" his proposal ONLY after my condition is met, knowing it won't be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hmmm ... whatever the ending huh?

So #USER# is planning another coup if the count comes out AGAINST biden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Women" are being canceled.

You cannot prove a person's thinking ... thus it will become a mechanism for second class male athletes to get scholarships at the expense of women ... welcome to utopia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# How can a person who, by his own admission, cannot conceive how to bring manufacturing jobs - implement policies that will result in bringing manufacturing jobs?

#USER# literally said those jobs were gone FOREVER and mocked the policies citing the need for a magic wand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sounds fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What about white people who came who were indentured servants?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is St Thomas a non-extradition location?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It is absolutely stunning how many people misunderstand the preamble of the 2nd ammendment 

Basically 

Because a militia is necessary to the preservation of a free state - THE ... RIGHT ... OF ... THE ... PEOPLE ... 

THE RIGHT OF WHOM? THE PEOPLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And the question is not even incredibly difficult to answer ... Is it (the baby) alive? Will it be when you are finished? thus, the answer is you are KILLING it (the baby).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Gotta love the advanced vocabulary of ANTIFA ... they really know how to put out a coherent message #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I thought you said you were taking about the NRA ... you're ACTUALLY describing the Democrat party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It would be perfectly legal to murder that child at 3:46 in new york]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nope. 

The verdict is forever tainted... when it needed to be pristine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ... we're going to bring them all here and let them grow and prosper here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Also ... he's not given anyone healthcare ... they have some insurance ... and if you're paying attention more have lost it than gained it. Several states have only one provider, and contrary to his promises. Costs have sky rocketed, and choice eliminated in many cases.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# WE NEEEEEEEEEEED ... an honest government with representatives who KNOW HOW TO HONOR A FUCKING OATH.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It has to be the privations at the top though ... not just underlings ... I'm talking Hillary and Barry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If you guys don't quit printing money a minimum wage of $50/ hour won't support a family of one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What's ALSO weird is how liberals address white people like this ... then admit that their message is not for those whom they addressed ... THEN brag about how they will take those same - kicking and screaming to "a better society" I can only assume meaning socialism. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And THAT dear children is why everyone is leaving it ... to the point where the GOVERNOR said come on over ... I'll make you dinner if you come and open your business here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So ... is it truth ... or facts that science follows? JOE admitted he takes truth over facts ... just need some clarity ... you know ... so I can follow science and all. 

Oh ... did you know science has shown that CAPITALISM lifts people out of poverty, and socialism doesn't?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What color was the teenage girl that wasn't stabbed by that knife?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If ANY of the current kneeling sycophant NFL players go play there ... I won't watch that one either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# LOL ... you got THAT right. 

So I don't need to pay more for others, right? HAHA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh i don't know ... how many democrat mayors are there?

Probably that many.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm Joe Biden vote for me baby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How's your bail out the terrorists fund going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So ... are THOSE all of those jobs Biden created that he's shooting his mouth off about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If I meet any of them I'd worry more about where I may have ended up than where they did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Really? And just WHAT were the wishes of the American people? 

Oh ... and you know YOU DO NOT REPRESENT THE AMERICAN PEOPLE ... RIGHT??? YOU REPRESENT THE STATE OF NEW YORK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm a medical anomaly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The DCP ... DEMOCRAT COMMUNIST PARTY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# IT SHOULD BE 1 FUCKING DAY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# THey were for Epstein until they were unplugged]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There is ample evidence for them to start looking into it to find the depth of it. They just doing want to find it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That tends to happen when government forces you to take on bad debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The same NY Times with proven bias and that refused to report the holocaust? THAT NY TIMES???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# By now ... Biden HAS NO VISION for America.  

The "vision" he speaks is not his.  It's BLM and ANTIFAs vision ... Marxist Communism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saint.. and what makes it worse is their rhetoric about what they want to do with Trump supporters. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well ... you know ... those Jewish worshippers holding funerals are pretty dangerous ... morality might break out and we can't have THAT.  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How could he get vaccinated when there were no vaccines? 

Oh ... and ... HE CAUGHT THE VIRUS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Oh ... but he DID know what he was doing ... he was NEVER going to have a robust recovery ... here doesn'tit was supposed to be the new normal ... government dependency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Now do your husbands and his crooked financial dealings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# By the way ... that was #HASHTAG# for the leftists pushing that ... not directed to you #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sounds like the problem was the parents ... I have WAY more than two guns in my house and my family isn't scared or worried about them. AT ALL!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# UN ... FREAKING ... BELIEVABLE!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Because the laws YOU VOTED FOR AND PRESIDENTS FROM YOUR PARTY SIGNED INTO LAW ... are driving it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Your highness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# if the federal government continues to give taxpayer funds to colleges and universities that DISALLOW free speech of conservatives, they are funding institutions that violate the first amendment, are thus IN violation of it, and need to be replaced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Or means that I'd the kid follows natural inclination, they'll stop all such activity do the child's doesn't identify with a gender.  In other words ... SCREWING up the child.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I trust statesmen ... I DO NOT trust politicians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Voter ID PROTECTS your vote.  It ensures it remains yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hmmm don't know about you but I won't feel more comfortable being communist ... no matter what it looks like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hmmm the ACTUAL definition of consensual or BILL'S definition of consensual?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah ... he LOOKS like batman #HASHTAG# the bloody hell is going on with batman movie casting?  There are WOMEN who'd make a better batman than he would]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How will a 120 pound woman carry a 230 pound injured man to safety during a fire fight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# the parkland warning signs were not missed... they were ignored or swept under the rug.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# For the sake of argument, IF institutional racism exists,  WHO runs the institution? 

 IT IS NOT THE POLICE DEPARTMENTS - IT'S THE POLITICIANS AT THE TOP, AS IT HAS BEEN THROUGHOUT HISTORY.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>