<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Spain: 2/2 

Aida Chacon Martinez, the mother of a non-binary teenager, said:

"Waiting until you're 14 to be recognised for who you are is very hard."

Amen to that. ðŸ‘âœŠ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Don't delay your booking up folks! Places won't lastðŸ‘ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I reckon they'll be #HASHTAG# testing #HASHTAG# daily now until Monday's court appearance to allow argument he presents no incoming virus threat to Australia. It's in the hands of Mr Djokovic to withdraw and keep his credibility intact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart goes out to Mr #HASHTAG# â¤ï¸ Racism he's been subjected to was woven throughout the 70s in my generation and younger!

Plain wrong #HASHTAG# persists throughout UK now.

It takes leaders setting an example at every level and us on an individual basis to check ourselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No security to let you in then? What about ringing other 'tenants' in there to explain you need to get in. You can show them your card at the door before they open it too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Draft an eloquent letter of resignation! Provide cab fare to the #HASHTAG# they kept a light on too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's them completely gone now:

"Account Doesn't Exist"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# History suggests these people will eventually arrive at all our doors if we permit or encourage them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There was a tic tock video just before Christmas of the two trans men coming out of cubicles in a women's bathroom when two cleaners confronted a third as he walked in. Was highlighting this very difficulty, should their state vote go the way the Lords amendment might have done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Lovely candle powered carousel similar to this but more characterfull restored so the wee lads grandkids can see it's wonders anew! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Now put your hands on your hips, fingers to the front thumbs at your back! Press thumbs in and circle them to massage your kidneys! Helps relaxation too!

This was equivalent to Only Fans in the 80s ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Probably can't take her foot away from the door Andrew is trapped behind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He should be asked to document his reading in preparation for the interview. I'm thinking it'll be nil, The Times or all GC authors. Don't embarrass him to identify five trans folk he's spoken to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thanks for your thread here. This is Dawkins horror and trans folk have no responsibility for what he's pinned his pennant too. May he and his ilk be forever condemned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Very 70s ðŸ¥° would fit right onto the Mystery Machine side! You stop and look!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Minded of the Jaws promo in Back to the Future - I guess we've caught up. Brilliant work ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Aye, that's a fact. ðŸ’– Sorry to hear news of your sad loss. ðŸ’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Tasmania did the research that Australia will benefit from too.

#HASHTAG# arguably best &amp; most recent adopters, great for affirming it's youngsters too!

#URL#

#HASHTAG#

#URL#

#HASHTAG#

#URL#

&amp; subsequently added NB too. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# and finally just to be fair - this picture of former LibDem leader Jo Swinson is best I ever saw. Posed well. It was definitely a photographer who could really see the personality. Good photographers imo are worth their weight in gold; they create the happiest memories. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Bell was listened too and supported on her own journey. She alone knows the ins and outs of her situation. She, as far as I can be aware wasn't subject to Conversion Therapy outwith an NHS setting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# BBC are obliged to observe UK law, chap was walking on eggshells as he came prepared for the one nuance free task &amp; found himself in a field with mines everywhere. Clipping his responses was the only chance of survival. Barnett could have done the same herself a few times too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interview preceded by an interview with a mum who had to have a heavily restricted funeral for a teen child at same time as #HASHTAG# garden soiree (after hard work) - "sorry for your loss, if we can concentrate on the type of funeral you'd have wanted" Sensitivity bypassed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That isn't it, don't know, maybe an older home. Current town property was considered 'at risk' &amp; personally; from an architectural perspective; I'm glad the author invested in its preservation. Hedges, it seems; are a necessary evil these days. I've seen lovely original drawings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# &amp; #USER# Joint Working for a better Wales. A 3 year co-operation agreement "we take another step forward in our collective effort to fulfil that promise of a new politics."

3yrs to extend free school meals to all primary school pupils!

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The #USER# opened this rift proper on 20/06/2019 &amp; it's gotten far worse since then. They declared open season on trans folk, brutally so with Non Binary &amp; the LGBTi+ Community in general. Haters were energised to fill the gap &amp; have done everything possible to poison the well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 2/3 I enjoyed #HASHTAG# the de ageing there had context and it was still the actors bring themselves to the performance and that connection is imo, vital. We revere old classics today because the performances were somehow unique to actor/period/level of technical abilities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thanks too for the provinces. I'll update for next time. ðŸ‘ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We're now in times that dictate your hate by your crowdfunding power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Probably community needs to reach out to independents to work out a GC free programme addressing issues that matter to trans folks overall wellbeing, issues getting uncritical platforming in mainstream media &amp; perhaps examine history behind that. Maybe after the NHS challenge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Manys an Allapa garden hut emitting "Noooooooo!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In fairness to the SNP they really couldn't have been clearer than in that May manifesto. I hope the independence prospectus/proposition follows suit. ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 2/2 &amp;/or 2) Another excuse to delay taking both Bills through parliamentary scrutiny phase until next yr whilst party is in court answering well publicised poor me compensation actions. It's been steady as we go. I don't want goalposts moved. It's a clear SNP deliver or fail now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You are removed from reality. Both of you actually. Young trans folk bullied to the point of withdrawal from interaction with their peers (and that is at best). Imo; you ignore reality from a comfortable distance whilst poisoning a landscape real young people must navigate daily!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# 2/2 The penalties for false declaration apply to those who would for their own reasons would try to make a fool of the reforms and by virtue of that, a fool of the government. Trust has proved fruitful in 20 countries etc so far. Time #HASHTAG# caught up and got on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I thought it good enough to save ðŸ˜Š #HASHTAG# era too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What about himðŸ‘‡from 2019 and still available?

Not so much an apology but perhaps a short essay on the crucial difference as both "went out of their way to feature the address panel" yet one reported to police.

#URL#

Perhaps it was just an anti trans thing? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Aye it's deeply entrenched in the older generation that supped on it originally and it's been given new life by these enablers with an average age circa 67yrs seizing on an opportunity and deploying fascistic techniques to poison as many minds as possible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A significant ðŸ‘‰jury decisionðŸ‘ˆ by decent citizens ðŸ‘ really encouraging and I hope the penalty sticks.nnGreat message to pin up for other institutes, facilities to note. Decent citizens support trans folk living their lives just like everyone else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# In Scotland's weather it pays to evolve to some hybrid! ðŸŠðŸ‰ðŸŽ¿â›¸ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# This is what they have written to Scottish Government who are presenting their very long awaited &amp; twice consulted #HASHTAG# Bill in Scottish Parliament Chamber on 24th February 2022

It's basically UK Government attempting to proxy strongarm #USER#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detecting current #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# is more of his bullshit from his don't think of the worst inflation in recent UK history, our piss on you &amp; your parties! Not an ounce of new information just the rah rah "how great are we!?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# All so very sad and tawdry. Kid will need positive independent support too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas one and all. â¤ï¸ðŸ’ðŸ‘

#HASHTAG#

#HASHTAG# 1975

#URL#

Tempus Fugit ðŸ™‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# one and all.

Starting with a pulse and working my way up! â¤ï¸ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Including politicians and the lord's hangers on mob.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attempts tonight to 'other' trans folk &amp; dress an apartheid style 'solution' to detention of trans offenders, withdrawn "they didn't have the numbers". Seems it was a profile raising 'game' to an unelected unaccountable Baroness in the Lords.nnReal trans folk as collateral damage #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Pretty awful stuff imo with Sackur doing an utter minimum to arm himself with good data. The Stanford report was in the press so little worth as a journalist here! LGB Alliance have something to circulate!

Right of Reply appearance?  Of course two cis folk discussing the trans!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Trans folk always #HASHTAG# &amp; always will. What #HASHTAG# does is sweep away political medicalised gatekeeping designed to add a patina of respectability to deeply entrenched prejudice. No women's rights are affected. That's the propaganda you parrot. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Guess it's best to not open up slightest opportunity for the author to do this with. Publicity garnered can't do any harm for traffic to the profile page at this important time of year. All for a photo op that lasted hours &amp; led to so much hassle. Oh &amp; the worldwide circulation!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I claim nothing more than my own opinion. There is nothing self righteous about condemning violence; as I do, violence to women, in all its forms and given the attrocous fear that some men visit upon women, I don't think it subjective to want that educated out of the population.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[38/ "I'm 100% in favour of that. The UK has the equality act, the GRA I fundamentally agree with that. None of that depends on us saying trans women are women trans men are men - these things have been pushed together by trans activism! But they can be detached!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Seems current thinking is about nine folk ðŸ™„ðŸ‘€ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maggie Chapman was showing impeccable restraint.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Jings are the #HASHTAG# still at that #HASHTAG# game? Last night pretty much typified what show has become. #HASHTAG# member harangued, #HASHTAG# allowed rants with untruths &amp; inexplicably for St Andrews location; a Westminster Labour representative - branch office not good enough..again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

If you've 100 people at a function and ONE has this new variant - data on #HASHTAG# is showing that half the room OR MORE are likely to be infected. 

It's a fast spreading #HASHTAG# variant infections doubling every TWO days - faster than we've ever seen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Running now on fumes!  Coming to the end of the prevarication road on a number of fronts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Trustees must at all time be declared and current on the register. They influence the charity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Smallest print possible : child may not live!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have her working academic rigour 'reins off' on the far right press for the duration of the anti trans culture war - mercenary like. The other option was as a SPAD for associate of Liz Truss - an injection of intelligent life there would be of benefit &amp; birds of a feather etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Core is metabolism. Everything else is accessorising.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# running now on #USER# channel with distinguished actor and activist Mr #USER# â¤ï¸âœŠðŸ’ it really is worth 30mins. I'm so glad we had #HASHTAG# for all it did for acceptance, visibility &amp; ultimately equality. #HASHTAG# reference gave personal perspective.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Currently trans people are routinely left out of conversation. Older non trans folk work on what comforts them. Committee report wasn't kind, it left room for additional delays for further studies/reports, placating more aggressive Lords by offering 'clarifications' opportunity!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Couldn't say, I got Chile from a reply last night &amp; looked into it.  I have a wee scout about ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Website is not working. Reported this last week and tried to telephone the 0800 number abandoned after 15 min wait. Customer care is it, connecting people is it. Those days are long past BT. 1/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Plain fact. Trans folk have shared spaces appropriate to their gender presentation for hundreds of years absolute fact &amp; without significant issue. Some only discovered at death. Propaganda has caused this unrest &amp; political failures since 2018 have added fuel to the bin fire. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Will we see a transcript or is it confidential?

This is a better photo I thought, someone knows a good steady hand graphics person! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I could say where are trans folks voices in all this. That may feature a very genuine &amp; utterly decent Mr Morton. I saw &amp; haven't forgotten his deeply crestfallen &amp; betrayed face at the Pride event when told that Holyrood Magazine had written an awful piece to accompany the day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh #HASHTAG# please give the #HASHTAG# folk a spliff before broadcast. We need chill calm soft tones describing the whims of the wind the chills and that snow ice and high winds.

It's racing greyhound level anxiety just now.

Even "it is what it is (shrug)" would be fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Can't rely on Putin. Passively standing by whilst the country sours (any country) plays right into hands of those who would impose authoritarian regimes or worse by forcing ordinary decent citizens to beg the 'authorities' to put an end to this poisonous culture. Inviting it in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 2/2 Currently:nn#HASHTAG# 20/06/2019nnhttps://t.co/ikNcRb9Ofhnn#HASHTAG# 09/12/2021nnhttps://t.co/jjkAscZnmFnn#HASHTAG# 15/01/2015 (near neighbour &amp; now include non binary)nn#URL# countries and 35 Federal states/autonomous commune - have #HASHTAG# today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I can readily apply that passage to every conversation I've had with GC's on here. I've watched young trans folk and their young allies tire themselves out with GCs who are on auto pilot &amp; as your quote says "amusing themselves" for many of the empty repeaters - it's a wee hobby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Clearly Conor Burns has been watching #USER# for delivery tips!

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pound to a penny #HASHTAG# tried on BBC news 1st of save #HASHTAG# sops to public opinion to see if it flies. Reading into what he said; #HASHTAG# draft report will likely recommend structural change of management at #HASHTAG# bolstering his inane "nobody told him" talk!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[28/ "...wrong to receive treatment as an adolescent or young adult, would it? Can you be sure of that?"
Stock: "Of course it would, Yes, (laughing) (big grins) I mean look, you've got to be clear about what these drugs mean! Like you know, you're permanently rendered different..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #HASHTAG# have allowed themselves to become partisan proxy's for #HASHTAG# who have no legitimate rights to interfere with devolved Scottish #HASHTAG# - they have disgraced themselves, their office &amp; destroyed any credible claim to being independent.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Once moonbase is sorted, earth better watch out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine the upholsterers of the #HASHTAG# sofas to #HASHTAG# cream yellow, will prefer to remain anonymous. After all it's become the 2021 theme.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's all the hurt, division and distress that they generate for the deliberate sake of drawing votes that really gets me to thinking there ought to be fixed points like Roe vs Wade that are not up for debate once agreed, esp so by supreme court. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# quoted, wasn't sure of slight squirm at 'barrister'. Sackur "You are in essence saying some women's rights do not extend to transgender women!" Stock "Yes, I am!"  'Immersive Fiction' phrase getting attention. Sounds awfie like delusion, does it not? Claims 1/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Walking away from process won't assist a tribunal determination. Still, as long as it's burning others money...there's always the "I've been silenced" tour to look forward to.

Sooner this schism is repaired by proper GRA Reform the better. Then they can all lunch in the sewers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There's a gag in the Zero Mostel version of the Producers:

"Hitler, my Hitler was a great painter you know!  A whole apartment, two coats; one afternoon!"

How sad, not though what he'll be remembered for shrugs Mostel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This really ought to become known as the #HASHTAG# and forever shame all who use it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# you do understand meaning of 'proposing'?

GRA Bill includes a witnessed legal declaration confirmation of change of gender and the 'proposition' one intends the change to be for remaining life. The Bill allows we're human &amp; a change of position is built in without penalty. 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The United Kingdom media equivalent of slashing your ambulance tyres.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Try &amp; see Pennan (filmed Local Hero there) Slaines Castle near Cruden Bay said to have inspired Bram Stoker for Dracula. Beach at Balmedie is amazing! Fraserburgh lighthouse well worth a visit.

Great folk with warm hearts up there!

Rare breakfasts too!

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm very wary of this government on this &amp; frankly that keeps this awful schism open wide for those Baronesses and their ilk to supercharge their poisonous efforts. Cauterisation needed the exceptions imo as written are fine except to GCs who still want segregation by any means.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# This is someone for whom, power fixation aside; can make a great living outside politics, really intelligent &amp; very goal focused. Sacking is well affordable, publicity value on the well paying cancellation and silenced tour well known; before the compensation for hurt feelings!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Think you need to sign up. He isn't personally on Social Media.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Wonder if those two #HASHTAG# demonstration's at Broadcasting House get mention!nnSurely, surely BBC realise, trans folk aren't standing in the rain, during a pandemic without genuine longstanding grievance?nnOrdinary folk aren't daft to one sidedness of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ha ha I meant whomever was writing the attachment â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent interview on how the UK apparently got so much more toxic for trans folk (especially online in social media) and the real life dangers this can generate simply trying to live, day to day; your own authentic life! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# So much wrong about this article. #USER# will likely dump it all at the Journalists door, she hasn't helped herself disappearing from Twitter when she could have just gone secure. Very least #HASHTAG# should do is take the awful story down right away &amp; get independent auditors in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The accused wants! Sure to impress the New York judge ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 2/ claims some trans folk find that offensive others agree "that's exactly how I understand myself" suggesting to Sackur he is pressing on her the opposite. You make it sound like it's just about words, but it's not! Sackur "what are these problems?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Look after yourself. Best start to 2022 you could wish for. All best wishes. âœŠðŸ‘ðŸ’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# talk of outrage at #HASHTAG# on the #HASHTAG# with #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# featuring but #USER# excised with no mention at all before moving onto #HASHTAG# update &amp; BBC implied 'disappointment' #USER# predicted 50,000 infections have not been met.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Dearth of #HASHTAG#+ Centres throughout main cities of UK is a real bar to community stories continuity. Those coming up through youth groups are making long &amp; longer term friendships; it may see this sorry state reversed to better protect an increasingly positive community legacy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So much for public service!  Facebook taught them that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 Genuinely could not make up this blatant perception manipulation by a 'national' &amp; well tamed broadcaster sitting within shoving distance of our river Clyde. 10mins in they now return to the Downing Street story. Very much a pro Johnson survival.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# True to her very long form then.  I take virtually no interest in a party as relevant as the waste bin on the computer. As we gain independence it serves to remind us to turn off the lights and pull the flush; one last time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Appreciate that point, thinking about dealing with it without creating martyrs to a false cause allowing endless "I've been silenced" tours. At least one is begging for it. Better I feel; we get #HASHTAG# in per #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# &amp; render them all utterly irrelevant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think he'll go for a sparkling rich pearlescent garnet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The allegedly soon to be Baroness Stock will I sure, remain untroubled. ðŸ˜ Silk purse etc still amazes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Mr Forrester definitely suits that get up! ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Interior Designers everywhere rejoice new opportunities ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They showed I &amp; II recently in the UK on #USER#  well received and repeated. Still grand work ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# and out all the allies pour to defend the trans folk they know and care for as well as those many solid decent people who recognise the touch of fascism stroking the tension.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "ðŸ‘‰All aspects of motion were voted through without objection &amp; speeches introducing it were roundly applauded in council chamber. ðŸ‘ˆ

â€œpast 48 hours we have seen a wave of online abuse following media coverage of this motion that I think illustrates why it is so important."" ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Nobody forces MSPs or MPs into these roles. I'm heartily sick of those who would have us believe, once WE elect THEM they are somehow doing us all a favour! We can't even get rid of the routinely renegade ones, they slink off collecting their salaries until the next election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Too thick to make the connection to relative proportions of trans folk in the world to cis counterparts and maybe allies didn't get enough notice to be there. Bit of time and publicity on here &amp; elsewhere and numbers will be better. ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She made an important point, letters sent to 1922 Committee against a sitting PM remain 'on file' to be added to subsequent submissions to achieve the required minimum for action to be taken. (unless formerly withdrawn). She claimed letters won't be withdrawn on this issue or PM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# and finally, much of the NHS past is being exposed now, their managerial ethos questioned - I expect the worst will gtf with fat pensions this year or next &amp; trans folk are well rid. Imo an inquiry into the methods employed by government &amp; those who led it is also needed. Stinks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sorry that said; if #USER# would do something akin to this, I'll happily put my name to it. ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3/3 #HASHTAG# flew in from America especially to pay tribute on This is your life and #HASHTAG# rated him one of the finest singers of his generation!

Well worth catching the documentary.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# My old Jewish friends, all gone; had anglicised names and all of them the most open, caring of folk.â¤ï¸

We already have a partnership of wellbeing with #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG#

This TED Talk from 2018 imo, came not from scriptwriters but from her heart.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm sorry to hear he's taken you to this. Take care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I agree &amp; would add their lethal approach to the trans community being so very painful to see and hear as part of an apparent link with government direction on reform, other media outlets based on metropolitan London territory &amp; their routinely excluding trans folks voices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Hopeful this is acceptable to youse yin."

Stenographer from east coast mining village and director with a speech impediment. Signed off and only noticed with next days carbons review. Air salty!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was not uncommon for old style Council Directors to have old masters on their office walls. Wondering now if some became leaving/retirement gifts for some 'better connected' sorts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Some folk had to briefly learn about self restraint, adapting &amp;'making the best of it. Bit about 'for the benefit of a whole community' took I think, a bit longer &amp; for some never took. Lots of brief chats on this relate now to doing our best &amp; looking out for 'our' less able.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Be interesting to see how it pans out. Her tweeting suggests she's happy with outcome. Sackur can be pretty robust in his questions &amp; challenging, wouldn't thole a 'poor me, sad eyes' Stock. He'll have expected the professor &amp; gone in at that level. #HASHTAG# grinds on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Poor woman looks miserable! Probably precarious balance and lack of oxygen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You are arguing for apartheid segregation. It was made clear, attacks in the prison estate are a fact of life. Policies that work on the whole work are in place but cannot be 100%. The individual assessment process since 2019 has not failed the estates. Trans folk don't add risk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Reminds me very much of the films:

#HASHTAG#

and

#HASHTAG#

and their depictions of folk just trying to cast a vote!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# There is the segregationist position or the equalities position. Former is heavily funded by charismatic evangelical right of America. Latter in the UK is under sustained attack; made worse by breaking away from Europe.

#URL#

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oddly enough, I imagine a few Alba folk nodding in agreement there ðŸ¤”ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# &amp; Lords naked anti transgender apartheid shots.nnScotland MUST be better than these unelected charlatans kidding folk they're protecting women &amp; girls!nnWe're shaping a new inclusive country, let's be seen to reject these odious repeated attacks on trans folk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Nonsense!

Fear &amp; aye, hatred being driven by UK media, bad faith actors, MPs &amp; sadly MSPs all studiously avoids the plain bleedin obvious ðŸ‘‡

That so many so readily supp with a devil's own propaganda is the real societal question. It's been an exercise in poisoning a people. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It's a hobbyist at play. Simple addition of anti trans and obsessive gender critical's mostly empty repeaters. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The bodies that matter and effectively control practice in the area of psychotherapies are all very clear. It's got nothing to do with this obvious Westminster government partisan arm the EHRC. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That goes way beyond disturbing and #USER# this person has been promoted to your readership in the article that has effectively targeted trans folk on the back of no discernible evidence. You're fully mask of facilitators now. #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 

Saw this on Tumblr - 'Correct way to lift your sausage dog.' ðŸ‘‡ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor #HASHTAG# did nothing to merit being linked to the Johnson deceptions.

He was a decent man, of his time and really loyal to the team of players he'd gathered around him to produce his work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The optics on you trans people trying to get better healthcare aren't good!"nnFuck me, had you the slightest idea of how readily trans folk are abused by UK Government, NHS ðŸ‘‰personal gatekeepersðŸ‘ˆ, distinct creeps in Lords &amp; BBC all fighting against trans folk daily! if only!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Officials, disguised as keepers of peace &amp; masquerading as ministers of justice, disregarded their oaths, set in motion a series of events that forever destroyed these men, their families, &amp; a community, I have not witnessed a more complete breakdown of criminal justice system." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utter madness manufacturer of bus can't be consulted for reasonable adjustments to the driver environment to facilitate safety for all. Worse and inexcusable imo; in a new bus purchase, the existing workforce are not fully assessed as part of the pre-configuration. Not progress!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# In the extras to the utter magnificent #HASHTAG# by Mr #HASHTAG# there is some marvellous stuff on how they rendered authentic street and period traffic scenes. Well worth seeing; I'd be surprised if film students don't already study it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Simple - o t h e r G Cs M O N E Y Â£Â£Â£Â£Â£ effectively risk free organised harassment and huge free media exposure. Winning would be a slimmest of bonuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Enjoyed that, the setting and the closing music too ðŸ‘well done all! ðŸ’ðŸ°ðŸ‘ðŸ‘ðŸ‘âœŠ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The pro sense, pro current working policy, tried &amp; tested prisons assessment of all individuals, their risk to all others &amp; their being housed in most appropriate prison estate section &amp; as it happened the pro trans folk speakers; came armed with ðŸ‘‰the factsðŸ‘ˆ &amp; they triumphed!ðŸ‘Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That sure was a god awful Ghost of Christmas future!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Registered Hate Group (Charity - a first for the UK) LGBAlliance is based in Metropolitan London. In the early days at least, the cross check on IP Addresses suggested many of their 'overseas' branches had location in common with the queen of the hive in London. Uniquely British.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# 

For those unable to download the .pdf it's just these four pages. This is the revised 2019 edition as per the download link.

All the principal psychotherapy institutions are represented by the MoU. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If it was up to the BBC today it would be the apparent disappointment at the First Minister failing to meet her pre Christmas prediction of 50,000 #HASHTAG# infections by now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 16/ "..in the wrong body err there are also high percentages of autistic children in clinics, children with history of trauma, umm so there's complex issues around gender dysphoria in children and we've got to remember this ahhh, if they take a medical route, the effects are...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Media in UK have reached the bottom &amp; long ago began dredging a new low floor, it's been utterly detestable. Any opprobrium UK media face is well earned. Some remain very proud of applying no journalistic rigour preferring as they regularly demonstrate; to take toot &amp; print it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Betrays her own lack of knowledge with that. Understanding is another matter altogether she'll never have that until she talks with trans folk or cracks a decent book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Aye, that last point on the previous chair's comment fair winded her firmly unqualified Gender Critical perspective! Could have pointed out the increasing legal challenges are all crowdfunded GC 'stings' and all are fundamentally failing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Term we use here in Scotland is "What a brass neck!"

They've not driven him to the airport &amp; huckled him on the first available plane home, nope they've added a stay to his deportation. 

Hand wringing in case they've to compensate him to the value of a prize he'd likely win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# rolled back earlier very firm confirmation the #HASHTAG# report will not appear before the Met complete their investigation to avoid compromise. Much softer linkage to delay now used - "..it it isn't clear when the Sue Gray report will be published.." used by Sophie Raworth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I've never had 'deep relationships' with my staff.

I've had professional relationships with all of them and I'm fairly certain, this late on; nothing to fear from any of them in forty odd years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing the Rod Laver Stadium on the Australian story from Melbourne I'm minded of my late mum always following him at Wimbledon and getting ever so routinely flushed in the process! ðŸ˜Š His being a lefty was important to her; they had that in common.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Giant Two Fingers to us all. From them all. (Tories and their funders/pals/soon to be elevated [once the cheques clear] and the tamed BBC)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Imo, eight councils should not be permitted to stop the survey and that in the interests of protecting young people from council's preferring to play politics with their lives, good sexual &amp; mental health as well as general wellbeing. Councils need calling out by residents here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Can't begin to imagine the worry this delay in proper care has caused you. Wishing you good health and the best of professional care in #HASHTAG# âœŠðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep that really was a very tawdry business altogether. Glad it got out in the end, folk make up their own mind; as they should.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yep we've have ac/s of folk saying to neighbours "so when will you be going back then?" in wks following Brexit vote. Similarly we've had Brits abroad in tears as they've had to leave their 2nd homes in #HASHTAG# behind. Tory gov't supports brutalising/coarsening of the population.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Unfortunately this was a non story: an ill advised picture protest by three silent placard bearing folk. It was ably converted to an international propaganda vehicle. No comment on the gushing 2019 'The Potter Collector' video that arrived, filmed the address and named the owner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm none the wiser on the colour really.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Late pal Gladys was definitely 7yrs old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Might have been better making them .pdf documents as most folk can read them easily.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The JK Rowling tweet business was mentioned warmly &amp; sympathetically on the BBC Daily Politics show on the BBC today (naturally). General agreement how tough it's been for her and of "course trans folk should have rights" etc....There was no Trans Person voice present (naturally)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clapped three dogs today!! ðŸ¥°ðŸ¥°ðŸ¥°

Last one tapped my knee with its nose as I paused at an outdoor seating area on Argyle St to let folk pass at the pinch point. "While you're standing there; clap me please!" Style.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Started reports through trusted sources such as Switchboards &amp; LGBT Centres. Patterns became apparent, criminals got targeted, things slowly got safer. With 'the numbers' stats; police saw trans hate crime needed targeted responses. 3rd Party confidential reports common today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER#THINK It's sad seeing this, I cannot imagine a time frame where this will ever come to an end in the USA. Those awful words of five terms former NRA President Mr #HASHTAG# still remain embedded there. "From my cold dead hands!" A mountain of fatalities his dynamic monument still.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 2/2 SNP had trans supporters hemorrhage in relation to many sound reasons of feeling awfie low down priorities whilst high heid yins of the GC persuasion; spouted their acidic bile with impunity. First Minister did a personal plea video, they responded.

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I can well see her argue it's an essential part of her journal. My old pal; a direct contemporary, never once shared her original image, albeit they could be found. She transitioned at the other end of her life's journey so I guess she was focused on everyone sharing her delight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Simply stunningly good filmmaking. What a tale, so beautifully presented. Probably one of the best cross generational A list cast of players ever. They give their all. The soundtrack is fabulous &amp; deployed to great effect. Last role for #HASHTAG# &amp; a belter!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# There was no need for this awful spotlighting. Trans folk have been with us hundreds of years rubbing along fine but being targeted by authorities awful gatekeeping and NHS tortuous deliberate psychological delays to proper healthcare with no power to fight or appeal. It's evil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Medical record is updated. GP practice can give you a note of CIH number that links your records &amp; you can get a paper copy. 

You can request a copy of your vaccination statusÂ by phoning the COVID Status Helpline on 0808 196 8565.Â 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Take care of yourself, that's a long time. All the best. ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Aye that'd very sad, she bonded my old pal Gladys and myself. She taught me very young that difference is okay. Hold your head high in adversity, you've done nothing wrong in being yourself!ðŸ’ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I agree. It should perhaps be confined to the school's estate, pupils, teachers &amp; ancillary workers to have a simple easy paper vote. Those in support get a small grant for bunting etc, a special wee buffet &amp; a professional school photo. I'd imagine junior schools would say aye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cheesed off with Number 10 go to smoke layer #HASHTAG# as he unusually for him unconvincingly tries to sell #HASHTAG# attendance at #HASHTAG# as being motivational events by the PM for a big department working hard. 

Peston "In UK it was unprecedented!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Most definitely is an #HASHTAG#+ ally. Really no question about it, I've met friends of hers &amp; was very proudly principle witness at first equal marriage events in Scotland. She made history leading, walking a full Glasgow Pride march &amp; opening ceremony speech! Politics challenges.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Interesting &amp; very worrying article. Really trying to stand in way of evolution to a better, caring &amp; inclusive society from a nation that remains on high alert of invasion. The kids are alright! #HASHTAG#'s story in linked article was truly heartbreaking; robbed of 'fitting in'. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You can use this #USER# to write to your MP about this even if your in devolved Scotland as this will ultimately impact funding in Scotland too!

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's absolutely figured in. Not well known for error nor chasing 'losing cases' in defence of losers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 Exceeds stated criteria of author

" "carefully positioning themselves to ensure" address was visible." "

BBC "campaigners deleted photo the day after it was posted."

Potter Collector's is still up! Since 2019.

BBC might have asked what's the KEY essential difference?ðŸ¤”ðŸ³ï¸â€âš§ï¸?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Glad to see a positive &amp; very uplifting piece in the Metro.  Hope to see many more. Trans folk need barrier free access to their full healthcare needs; at point of need. Well proven to hurt trans folk; current gatekeeping must end; public opprobrium is essential, simplify paths!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cheers, I started with the Wiki entry and got to the Indian Express article from July saying that intervention had been scrapped in the final draft. 1/2

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Blocked him now. Thanks, I'd already blocked the person to whom he referred. Life's way too short as it is. ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# 24th Feb is the kick off. It's a real test of Scotland's mettle in this imo. I'm watching and I'm sure our partners by the #USER# own stating #HASHTAG# and #HASHTAG# are looking carefully too. We can't be less equal that our partners imo.

#URL#

Wellbeing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He doxxed one of the #USER# team (general area) yesterday and I advised on Twitters new hard line reporting of that behaviour. See I'm blocked just looking the account up now so I've returned the compliment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Detest trade in rape statistics almost as much as any mention of that particular author. Grateful to the police being so forthright with that response. Trans folk are real genuine people. In my experience; they're loving, creative, open, warm, decent &amp; can be very vulnerable too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This shit just stresses how important for Scotland that our #USER# get a move on on #HASHTAG# to head this off at the border. The border many GCs can cross when their 'prize' mirage disappears in a cloud of equality &amp; decency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# announced the three Trans silent protesters accused of #HASHTAG# the author #HASHTAG#'s home address in a photograph have been cleared of any criminality. 

Doubtless a relief to this 2019s  #HASHTAG# too.

 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That looks so very good and exceptionally tasteful work imo. ðŸ‘ðŸ‘ðŸ†]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spent an afternoon with the late Mr #HASHTAG# who has my heart! ðŸ’– #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Story goes, Mr #HASHTAG# was furious that his photo was used on that work without permission. So much of that period was outwith his personal control as he was ruthlessly used to fulfill the creative ambition of others including from within his own family. He survived.ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Integrity of her then message took priority once she saw she was remaining the story. Public health specialist did the right thing for the good of public health.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "But the report also points to something many of us have sensed for some time: that, ðŸ‘‰while popular with a certain class of well-connected media figures and politicians,ðŸ‘ˆ popularity of gender critical-feminism is much more niche than its greatest supporters like to claim."ðŸ‘âœŠ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 It is both shocking that people with law making power can be so clueless yet boldly flaunt that level of idiocy for the public record. nnThis is a segregationists amendment intended as a spearhead to other areas of civic life all aimed at third space apartheid of trans folk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# This egregious falsehood was read into Hansard last night during what was a full scale 'anti trans folk' almost introduce UK trans apartheid 'debate'/assault.nnThese clear facts debunk what rigourous due diligence in Lords ought to have done in advance. nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I read it as a fresh start up fund. For a new 'company' entity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Article deliberately ignores formal legal process built into self ID #HASHTAG# it's important to reinforce that in immediate post reform period to tackle those who would aim to do stunt entries such as that done by the press. These real people hurting real people ought to pay!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 13/ Sackur "hmmm", with no challenge to any of that jumble..

"..can I ask you about young people &amp; body dysphoria, we know a number of children get 'this feeling' they can't identify with the body they've been born with, &amp; increasingly with some, over time they want to change...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# This is propaganda speaking. Since 2019, the rigorous assessment process has worked to ensure the protections these peers argued didn't exist. We also heard prison attacks are a fact of life, no policy will ever be 100%. Trans folk don't add risk by simply being themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They represent the people and there are some fabulously good MP &amp; MSPs. Qualifications bar wouldn't be democratic, folk make their minds up on information &amp; seeing real people. I would want truth checks on any materials at election time - actually all the time. 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Jeezo that's terrible why would #USER# entertain that personal abuse? Locked their account now too!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>