<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Camelot 3000". Nice one, #USER#. Nice one.

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I broke this rule once. I can only assume it was the fact that it happened in church that saved me. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet #HASHTAG# thinks the preamble to the U.S. Constitution begins, "We, the #HASHTAG#, in order to form a more bigoted union...."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Both. And if Bill Clinton had committed sexual harassment in the White House, or Trump on the campaign trail, these would be valid concerns. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Should've stopped at "yes because of disunity." Your "no" section really didn't address *denominational* differences, which are *doctrinal*.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing in the #HASHTAG# suggests forking over all your possessions was necessary to become a #HASHTAG#. Else how could Paul encourage giving? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He took their stuff, not their lives. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unless they know their personal blast radius sucks. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can tell you what one of them was today.

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's fine. At the same time, take the option to legally murder unborn children off the table to give her one less reason to make bad ones. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Just because he's not tearing up doesn't mean that wasn't emotional.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is literally nothing about redistribution of wealth in that chapter. If anything, it says that your property *stays* your property. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Could you please send me a screenshot of what you are seeing? I logged out &amp; looked at my account. Couldn't see your picture; saw the bear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A zygote *is* a whole person. Just because that whole person doesn't look like you or me doesn't make it anything less than a human being. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is now a choice between a man accused of feeling entitled to women &amp; a woman wanting to expand every entitlement known to man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The name Jehovah is in the old manuscripts and scrolls of the Bible *not even once*.

"Jehovah" is an anglicized version of vowelless YHWH. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait until #USER# uses the label "so-called" judge on a judge that *he* appointed. (Maybe #HASHTAG# himself.) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: ANTIFA Debuts Its New Unisex #HASHTAG# Line at Berkeley Fashion Show #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfortunately, we're going to need nothing less than a #HASHTAG# to force government to recognize only male and female genders. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to #USER# run the #HASHTAG# ceremony and I would pay good money to see him do stand-up #HASHTAG# because this guy is *funny*.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# has been advised to "take the high road". #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...so I'm going to #HASHTAG#!"

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, this can only help his case.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day I wake up in a country where half the people insist killing their children is a human right, without a shred of #HASHTAG#. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely! #HASHTAG#'s so badass she went down like #HASHTAG# after a clean shot. That's *exactly* what badass means. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only response to someone transgender who's mad you won't date them because they have their original parts is "No, how about YOU change?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile another 300 babies were put to death today by an organization you just can't give enough shovelfuls of money and praise. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "And when you’re a star, they let you do it. You can do anything." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hebrews 10:25 -- Let us not neglect our meeting together, as some people do, but encourage one another. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.#USER# Real St. Nick may have been dark. #HASHTAG# is if we change #HASHTAG# to match Xtian saint, #HASHTAG# would then demand, "Ban Santa!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When's "'The Confederacy Is History' Month"?

I'll celebrate that. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can take criticism. What I can't take is someone who's sole goal is to pester me w/ things he repeatedly proves not to comprehend himself. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The argument: "He was evil and violent before #HASHTAG#." But Islam co-opts just such tendencies for Allah's use and promises Heaven in return. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's see: The 15-year anniversary of a day where nobody I know died. I think I can get through it. And still stand. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 90% lower UTI risk, 50% lower cancer risk, lower risk of HIV &amp; other STD infections -- all of which outweigh risks, per most recent studies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm liking this just for cleverness. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Congressional Transgender Task Force:

When government absolutely, positively has to know who's wearing the pants in your organization. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way that a lot of independents were ready to vote for *anybody* with credibility &amp; some chance of winning, I think #USER# had a shot. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you saying Book of #HASHTAG#, Doctrines &amp; Covenants, &amp; Pearl of Great Price are *not* works of Joseph Smith? Because I've read them twice. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm more in favor of teaching men not to have sex with women they're not willing to have a family with. That's where it starts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem is that many #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# celebrate the Confederacy, when a traitorous nation of slavers is nothing to be celebrated. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#-Comey-Comey-Comey-Comey Chameleon
You come and go (x2)
Firing you is easy 'cause your colors were never true
Red, white, &amp; blue (x2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't know what #HASHTAG# was trying to prove. No one said a woman has to dress in an attractive fashion to get in the #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what we've established is that your memory doesn't go back to 1996. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to #USER# for visiting Dallas, giving a presentation on #USER#, &amp; signing books at the #USER# flagship store! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# God allowed certain practices He didn't like because the Jews were too hard-hearted to do better at the time. Jesus said so in Matthew 19.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I *knew* there was a reason I check Twitter every ten minutes to see whether a dumpster fire is trending! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't have to know how to best care for the #HASHTAG# to know the homeless shouldn't be murdered. Same goes for unborn children. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.#USER# #HASHTAG# how #HASHTAG# condemn turning #HASHTAG# into sex objects when their pushing sexual liberation is the no. 1 cause of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always wondered why John Byrne's #HASHTAG# wasn't reprinted by #HASHTAG# for #HASHTAG#. Might this be why? Lana Lang here is *14*. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willful blindness, continued.

#HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# (It doesn't, but we should make him think it does.) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I'm just going to leave this here. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did not need to see Hillary's Whoa-face. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not unless they opted for it, or had a living will directing it. (What happened to Terri Schiavo, for example, was a damn travesty.) #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kinda ballsy to visit a Muslim country and give a speech telling them what their religious leaders need to be preaching.
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is that sarcasm? He endorsed Sessions, didn't he?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing non-#HASHTAG# about passing a Constitutional Amendment to protect our national institutions from getting trashed. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 80s grade school, had no love for girls, saw some boys as cute. I'm straight but if today's coercion existed then, probably dead of AIDS. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If two denominations have the same doctrines but different "emphases because of calling" -- whatever that means -- they should be one denom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "You have reached 9-1-1. If this is about the Bill Maher clip, the Cultural Appropriation Police have been notified. Please hang up."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just think of it like being in that #HASHTAG# ad. Except instead of handing the cop a Pepsi, you're handing him ID, and then everything's cool. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect song to heal #HASHTAG# after #HASHTAG#! #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Given there were married apostles, and Paul encouraged both Tim &amp; Titus to ordain marrieds, NOT doing so is weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right, because there's nothing about funding a criminal enterprise that is responsible for mass death and carnage that deserves punishment. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is teaching your kids, "Don't judge!" then taking them to sit in the lap of a fat, old, beaded guy who judges them every year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm four episodes into the original "He-Man" #HASHTAG# and it only just now struck me as implausible that his tiger talks. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Um...no, you haven't even cited *how* they contradict. Which I guess I'll have to dive into since you aren't willing to make the effort....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My white cousin's elderly neighbor told cops my cousin is leader of a death cult because "I know his kind! I'm from the Middle East!" #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, go watch "Chinatown" if it makes you feel better.

(Actually a pretty great movie, notwithstanding who directed it.)

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Suicide Squad" had a few moments, but overall it was a much better movie back when it was called "Ghostbusters".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I totally read that "ANTIFA". #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So is a Jackson Pollock painting. Doesn't make it any less a confused mess trying to represent something it's not. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That #HASHTAG# wants to serve his sentence as a woman is #HASHTAG#, seeing how #HASHTAG# would like to cut his balls off. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a dog walks up to you, sniffs your crotch &amp; butt, then walks away crying, should you take it personally?
...
...
...
Asking for a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember being the TV's remote control. #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, it's not. You pick #HASHTAG#, every time. Because then, if you ever want to stop being Batman, you can settle for being Bruce Wayne rich. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've already stated that I don't believe Genesis 1-11 are literally true. They may bear some relation to reality but I see them as mythical.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Confused about IvX #HASHTAG#. How did Magneto know of Scott's corpse? Havok was told, but IvX #HASHTAG# implies Magneto wasn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the U.S., they have #USER#.

In the U.K., they have #USER#.

How mirror-universe is that??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You and everyone else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The CROWD booed. The actors collectively, AFTER the show was over, read a brief, respectful (though IMO off-base &amp; inappropriate) statement. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["HEY! Missed one!!" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In fact "Once saved always saved" is a belief no Christian church held 800 years ago. Those who adopted that belief *did* change the gospel. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do extremist #HASHTAG# miss the #HASHTAG# that Islam motivates them to kill the immoral by promising they'll be pornstars in Paradise? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Obviously the mixed-gender army. Roughly 3% of the women are bleeding before you ever fire a shot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hey, can a whole lot of people retweet and like this so it gets really popular?"

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Meh. Jury's still out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# veteran needs help after benefits canceled! Can't the #HASHTAG# world do better than this? #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrong Dylan. That's his son who wrote that.

So...Nobel Literature Prize for Biology?

[Please tell me you knew that and were just kidding!] #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's getting so we need a Constitutional Amendment saying, "There is such a thing as #HASHTAG#."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When did "white" become a belief system?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# you notice your #HASHTAG# has randomly dropped an app from its display, and now it looks like your phone has lost a tooth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That would only be true if it were your body being destroyed at the abortion clinic. It isn't. It's someone else's. So it's *not* your call. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not how it's presented, tho. More like:

Us &lt; God by infinity, so us good deeds = infinitely little; us bad = infinite big.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judging from what we've seen of Palestinian kids decked out with guns &amp; suicide vests, the conscience that needs to wake up is Palestine's. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're lucky the news about #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# broke, or this would literally be the dumbest post on #HASHTAG# right now. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gee, thanks for #HASHTAG#. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess I should watch these last two "Leprechaun" movies before my DVR gets sick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need a #HASHTAG# with a Constitutional Amendment guaranteeing the #HASHTAG# of public/private representatives. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of what? God's judgment?

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are people who literally believe that it's better to be put to death in the womb than be born into the world without #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any politician who equates a woman's destroying the body of her child with controlling her own body is mentally incompetent to hold office. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seen on #HASHTAG#:

Are there so few songs about #HASHTAG# because no word rhymes with orange?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# you wait for a particular bathroom &amp; restroom stall to free up because you know you get good reception for websurfing there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# in a nutshell. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But why clog traffic when you can reach your destination, park, and listen while idling?
...
...
...
There's even less road noise that way. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nothing would surprise me. Trump Sr. has been charged for the last 6 months with the crime of fairly &amp; freely winning a democratic election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe that's why they're getting into the transgender hormone therapy business -- to replace the public abortion funding they're gonna lose. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great. Now I'm wondering if my grandfather, who had penile cancer, was circumsized. I'm filing this under "I Know You Meant Well, But...." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Skynet. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- Entitlement Mentality
- Rich Taxpayer's "Fair Share"
- Rainbow of Sexual Confusion
- Maxed-out Minimum Wage
- Ravages of Racial Politics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think that anything #USER# tweets can be taken as "unabashed #HASHTAG#", you are completely and irredeemably out of your mind. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DARN THOSE SNOWFLAKES!!!--oh, wait, an actual snowstorm. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# in Islam: Medina adopted Islam so its tribes would stop killing one another. Now, in #HASHTAG#, the killing is Muslim-on-Muslim.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His version of faith is shared by others who control over 23000 sq miles of land. But they're all just "crazy dudes hiding behind religion". #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The developer next to me has the theme to "Mission Impossible" for his ringtone so I guess that gives you a good idea of our project status.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet things like #HASHTAG# make old people wish they'd died the day before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(That sound you just heard was #USER# losing his mind.) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# New anti-terrorism protocol:

Next time shrapnel comes your way, politely decline.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Still, those 1.4M couples seeking adoption won't be looking to adopt every single year. We got a supply problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there an episode of #USER# that *doesn't* involve questionable #HASHTAG#?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait til pedophilia's classified an immutable, "born this way" sexual orientation just like the others; watch liberal attitudes shift. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# of any kind should always be concerned with rectifying wrongs, not ratifying wrongs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad realizing #HASHTAG# warriors would never permit "Diff'rent Strokes" today because it depicts cross-racial #HASHTAG#. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This literally invented a new KIND of Christianity that never previously existed, which DENIES, "They went out from us, but were not of us."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are rich people on both sides of politics that could fund these "populist" candidates if "campaign finance reform" was repealed. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burkas cover the face. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, great. Looks like #USER# has jacked with its "Notes" editor. Can't single-space my paragraphs there even if I want to. Which I do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please tell me you don't actually *want* martial law. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's important to remember on #HASHTAG# that this is the Left's ideal #HASHTAG#: The ultimate victim, who takes no responsibility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If #HASHTAG# had been elected, these same guys would be staying home and setting up email servers in their bathrooms. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Conclusion "actual reality would have a fixed history" doesn't follow. I couldn't know what happens now, next door, unless someone tells me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I put on my 3-year-old #USER# "BEERKNURD" shirt, turned to the mirror, and learned *today* that KNURD spelled backwards is DRUNK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a very critical point. Nobody minds  tax dollars going to actual #HASHTAG# issues. But making men women or women men?

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then you're effectively saying #HASHTAG# has *no* essential elements -- there is no behavior categorically unacceptable within any marriage. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# that the #HASHTAG# demand for free #HASHTAG# is based in the idea that a #HASHTAG# can't properly function in #HASHTAG# w/o #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ironic, considering the meaning of Christmas isn't about Santa and gifts and being like all other kids. But yeah, the church "stole" that. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another #HASHTAG# shows her stuff. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Not my best work: I just cough a couple times and it's over. They shoulda got Matt Damon. Watch my films! My estate gets paid!" #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would be hilarious is if we later learned those lines are tracking the impressions of the red, yellow, and green Teletubbies. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People laugh when I say we need a #HASHTAG# that, among other things, bans nonhuman marriage.

Then come the validations. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seen on #HASHTAG#:

Q: What's the difference between a #HASHTAG# &amp; a suicide vest?
A: A suicide vest actually DOES something when triggered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't make this up: Driver caused a multi-car pileup running a red light at intersection of #HASHTAG# &amp; Shiloh (= "Peace" in Hebrew). #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then y'all can be the minority party for real! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seen on #HASHTAG#:

Australia Customs Agent: "Have you ever been convicted of a felony?"
Friend: "I didn't know it was still a requirement!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every so often I wonder if there's any money to be made in a hotline that *encourages* suicide, and if I could get the right people to call. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Personally, I thought #HASHTAG# Episode II was so bad it needed *more* Jar-Jar. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heavy flow of love! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Locutus should've been press secretary. Imagine the ratings. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Sure, if I never want to get hired again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Years from now they'll talk about how #HASHTAG# was winning this horse race until she *literally* threw a shoe. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've just launched Tomahawks into #HASHTAG#.

Because now that #HASHTAG# is dead, America insults you with *missles*.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: Michael Flynn Is Cobra Commander and Has Been All Along #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'd like a triple venti half-sweet non-fat caramel machiatto."

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I hear ya, but if the point of the universe is for God to fellowship with beings capable of existing on His level, nobody but us qualifies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did #USER# call #HASHTAG# to concede, or to negotiate the terms of her surrender to law enforcement?

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, but we just because gays can't choose to be straight doesn't mean we must distort #HASHTAG# and the #HASHTAG# ideal to suit their desires. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Are you blocked by her yet? It doesn't take much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't the media who are running away in droves w/ every ridiculous gaffe. It's the voters. The media LOVE gaffes. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All shades drawn. Still feel him.

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Good, but not as good as its earlier namesake. Reminded me more of "Super 8": Once you know what's up, it's over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judging from the #HASHTAG# response, #HASHTAG# were kinda hoping Pence would end up like the first GOP President at his last play. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just pre-ordered "Gosnell: The Untold Story of America’s Most Prolific Serial Killer" at #HASHTAG#! #URL# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep in mind it's only a matter of time before progressives stop complaining about the 1% and start going after the 51%.

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I really have to explain how my calling you a certain piece of posterior anatomy could be both "true" and "not true" at the same time? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# continues #USER#'s longstanding tradition of printing covers that don't describe the contents &amp; don't sell the book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what is the point of #HASHTAG#? Is the idea, "Without the ability to kill our children on demand, we can't be in the workforce?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did I go all my life until now without the wondrous experience of #HASHTAG#? And why couldn't I have gone the rest of my life without it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Fire and brimstone coming down from the skies! Rivers and seas boiling! Forty years of darkness! Earthquakes! Volcanoes!" #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: Top Democrats have invited the cast of #HASHTAG# to #HASHTAG#'s first "State of the Union". To perform. *During* the address.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is that according to Jewish oral tradition, a reason God brought the Flood (then rainbows) was gay #HASHTAG#. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Mary were born in the usual way, had died in the usual way, and decayed in the usual way, no core Xtian teaching changes. #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And Washington apparently did know of them. He has journal entries pertaining to them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He would forgive the girl if she repented and came to realize that she had done the wrong thing, just as he had been telling her on the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Maybe in 2018, not before then. Not while the GOP holds the House. Trump supporters have them on a short leash.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keith Richards? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing more feminist than Islam, I tell ya! #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet #USER# would blow it by telling the moderator, "Performance like this is why u make only 77 cents on the dollar!" #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because Leftists are selective about everything they claim to abhor. Everything. Even cultural appropriation. Go on, appropriate that hijab. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to retweet this now and then for about a week to make sure everyone gets the memo. See you all over at the new account!

5 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even for a #USER# movie, the 1st scene of the original one makes no sense other than to provide a death-by-#HASHTAG# demonstration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, this is good for a chuckle: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To refuse to vote in #HASHTAG# is to confess before God and everyone that none of your convictions matter enough for you to act on them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I decided not to buy something I saw on #HASHTAG# today.
...
...
...
Good to know that part of my brain still works. I was getting worried.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How #HASHTAG# is it that #HASHTAG# now considers it morally outrageous for religious people to object to human sacrifice? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best miniature golf course EVAR. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think it's more a function of erasing *present-day* support for the ideals that a #HASHTAG# embodies, which justified slavery. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I want to take that money that other people earned &amp; use it to do what I think is best for you!" #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#2016 #HASHTAG#Night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reducing the stigma of mental illness (a condition) does not mean we should reduce the stigma of suicide (a decision). #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Was still up last I checked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just 79 signatures till this #HASHTAG# reaches 500 and...and I get to see what happens when a petition reaches 500! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skipped lunch at work today so I could leave early. So hungry now I just ate a #USER# Fire Sauce packet. By itself. No taco. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somebody hurts your feelings, you have a good cry, get it out, &amp; go back to work.

Somebody destroys your car, you can't get to work.

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Careful. According to #USER#, that's how this whole mess started. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Reading the Comey testimony is like finding out J.R. Ewing was really Cliff Barnes all along.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, because reading the Bible and the Quran three times plus commentaries hasn't qualified me at all for a round of "Spot the Differences". #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Try 3 books:

"Endless Forms Most Beautiful" &amp; "Making of the Fittest" -- Sean Carroll

"Relics of Eden" -- Daniel Fairbanks

#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who makes it a point to say every year during the same event, "Look how inconsequential we all are"?

Must be a blast at birthday parties. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# wasn't having a "medical episode". Someone just reminded her today's when #HASHTAG# happened, too. #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>