<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# the big thing is this lil chiweenie is just really possessive, he snapped at my dads friends dog who was sitting on my bed. i think its more the bed then anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# and the other one fondles his balls, cuz these people are sickos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# look im a nerd and i dont give a shit about sports. some ppl just wanna control the world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# nice. i wish my wawa's had a liquor section]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# the obvious answer is "make ass beatings legal and in the spot light"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# bro fucked a towel doll mermaid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# dude i love it. also kinda funny its an enchantment matters set. yea artifacts matter too, but like urzas block was "the enchantment block"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# TBH i'd rather watch you brave performers actually put your life on the line then bitch about how 'fake' wrestling is. how many people have been legit injured from botched moves? way too many.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# 
even the big ones my ex had who tried to smother me with them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# back then i took care of her until she was able to walk, but last august she broke her arm and things went down hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# you have lived in nj. why must you desecrate the sacred pie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# did you play soul edge though? not gatekeeping, wondering if you know that whole loooooong story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Loco says no. Loco says he loves me more then my brother #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# wait, are the x-men trying to be master races now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# shoe has me blocked actually. im blaming on memeing on her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# time for the pizzadare.

or burger king dare :B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# bye bye taiwan, because once russia invades the ukraine, china is attacking taiwan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# mickie james got bray wyatt fired, got]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# might not bro, might be asuka as number 30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# their becoming self aware. its fucking SKYNET FUUUUUUUUCK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# im still friends with one i met in 1999. she writes romance novels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# plus you have knives for defense and totally not something sexual at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# CDC now says vax wont help :^)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# we live in a dumb world. these same people think the orcs from lotr are 'black-coded' meaning they see black ppl as savages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Korn and ben folds five were on a tour, and something happened and so they started beefing. Ben made 'rocking the suburbs' because of korn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# &gt;&gt;falling asleep during evil dead you can do better c'moooooooooooon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# look, we know you have daddy issues, but i aint yo daddy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# he's hollywood. they deity pedos and beaters. fucking Roman Polanski gets applause all the time at the emmys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# im still blocked by shoe lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to get my brother, and the whole apartment complex smells like weed. Like i didnt step in the place and i swear i gotta contact high]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# thats because you keep sitting. stand up your not chained to your computer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# he's scottish. the lucky charms guy is irish. do better and dont be a bigot tipster! &gt;:( #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# lol i too use the ralph troll saying no meme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# rhianna too old for drake, he still trying to get that eleven girl from stranger things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# interesting? twitter loves the damn pedos so much. they needed homeland security to get a kids nudes taken down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# tbf you are a business social media account. you should be shitposting to promote your business and not political bs that businesses should not be in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i would have shit my self. thats my phobia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# he def is a beast. a sex pest beast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He nade a bunch of people disappear, thats a mircale!!!1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# looks kinda like the mom from the shining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i hope he gets some therapy or else he might walk a dark path]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# wait, im cyberbullying you, i thought i was just being a bro busting chops D:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Too much salt can fuck your body up. Im not a medical expert, or chemical but i know too much salt causes high blood pressure so im assuming it affects your body that way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# they kinda look alike. i hope no one confuses them for brother and sister like people did with me and my ex.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# was it the hole in your lip? one time my ex said she spilled a drink and said that, and this was months after she took a lip piercing out and i was like 'wait did that not close?' like she really meant a hole in her lip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mine also. Also have my brothers dog and hes getting spoiled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# look i already gave the catfish that and kept getting calls for ken, who wanted to, and i quote 'ravage my old man boyhole' #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# not my dad!

mom died on the 28th of dec :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# &gt;&gt;she doesnt listen to j-pop metal, viking metal, mexican gangster rap, or video game music FANTASY RUINED! ONLY POP!! REEEEEEEE!!!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# nothing about the cubs winning the world series? THE LIST IS GARBAGE!!!!!11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# did we date the same big tiddy white girl with alcohol problems?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# imagine having a stick far up your ass you cant see how funny this pics are. 

cant be us tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# YAY THE ASS BOYS WITH THIER BEST FRIEND #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hey, now she doesnt have to reach in her pants to play with herself #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Im in the er with my mom since 12pm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 9h man im glad when i open up gamefaqs and look up a walkthrough and its from "ceemoorebootytang69" cuz he is just like me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# it was always a kink. all men want amazons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# your confusing what is real. dont worry your wounds will heal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i too bit others in elementry school then i grew into crying after fights, which had the 4th grade teacher put me into therapy until i was like in 7th grade]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Write me in the will. Im already in my parents. 

And use the 400 for hookeeeeeeers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ever see the video of the gaming journalist who couldnt even get past the tutorial?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "if you dont like the cowboy bebop live action series you are a racist CHUD!" *this video actually exists*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# one time after midnight me and some friends went to an ihop and in the bathroom was filled with vomit.

wait that was a denny's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# give us names OJ, so that we may mock them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# like yahoo had groups where people shared porn, and 'briefcases' which were like online storage. shit was craycrayyyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# front mission remake, earthbound and earthbound beginnings on the console subscription thingy, xenoblade 3, chrono cross remaster, LIVE A LIVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# child sexual abuse is no laughing matter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# get better soon. maybe it was #USER# nipples that attacked your heart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# im part irish and injun! a 7 course dinner to me is a 6 pack and a potato!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i spooned on the first date, i'm a h000000r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# maybe if they stop defending babyfucking then they wont be out of money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i was forced to go one time in 4th grade D:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# so far here in south nj at the shop rite i go to, cat food has been missing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# so far so good. he needs night cuddles, but my moms dog is clingy to me ever since she died and doesnt like the cat too much, so when the poor cat jumps up on the bed, the dog snaps a him, chasing him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# WWE legend Tammy Sytch was arrested this morning for weapons possession and terroristic threats in New Jersey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i remember when i was younger my dad showed me the house of a guy who made some star wars ship to scale and it was pretty big and took up the dudes drive way. it was in a town down the road from our house. let me see if i can it via google]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# so neat story, #USER# grew up not far from me. he saw the ninja turtle movie at the same theater i did, the caldor he talked about in the rental review vids was an actual place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# that's a shit ton of schizo posting holy fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# thats just a link to something saying its true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# wait you dont train in make up? ILLUSION SHATTERED! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# remember when becky lynch dressed up like mtg character chandra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# post on the steam or reddit crying about it. maybe even gamefaqs!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# thor became a girl in the earth x books]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i didnt go, and i had a 'friend' lord that above me. like mofo, you went to community college, bought google glasses and backed might no 9 and *I'M* the dumb ass?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# its def not smtv. that got cancelled after the leak :B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yea bro. my mom died in one yesterday, but you seem better then she was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# all commie graves must be pissed on. let me piss over china]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# overwatch is bad, i should know i have great taste #HASHTAG# i hope bro gets his skin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# wait is that why im tolerated? cuz my man tits are great?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# if WoR is like KM, grease everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# your right though, we're going to be fucked if russia invades the ukraine, because then china is going to attak taiwan and we're going to be dragged into a 2 front war]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# he looks like haley joey osment in that his body got bigger but not his face, his face is the same size from age 14]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# &gt;&gt;that face when we'll never see jimmy pesto again because he was seen in the capitol during the 1/6 dumbshit #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# BUUUT THE GANG IS GOING AFTER STUUUDENT DEBT LOANS WACKINESS IS BAD GANGSTERS GOING AFTER STUDENT LOANS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# what if you re-enable the dislike counter for fans and stop the cryptoscam bullshit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# sony is now ruled by sony of america, which is REALLYYYYY censorious of tiddies, and its pissing off the japanese developers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# we gonna see revolutions man. if ppl werent weak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# my ex wanted to be married FAST. with kids. at a time i was still living at home, and she was living at her friends mothers house. working at a convenience store her aunt got the job for. and i was working with my dad. it was no place for a beta fish much less a child]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# because america dont like the cartoony look]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# imagine caring about what consenting adults do. fuck the haters you and john are a cute couple]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# those messages look like they were faked by a try hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# thanks, im just going to guzzle some bleach now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# thats why im pro second amendment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# &gt;&gt;tiktok as a job jesus fucking christ and i thought being a shitty drama youtuber was bad enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# but we need to normalize kissing the homies good night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# somebody book this. gabby vs leon. hardcore match. winner gets the money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# did anyone in Lenape wash their ass? i went to overbrook :B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "circumcision? YOU ARE CUTTING YOUR JUNK OFF????"
"YOU CUT THE BABIES JUNK OFF?????" 
romans amirite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# trad tattoo :B tattoos are awesome my family have them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# My dad said you couldget in the house via cutting through with a sawzall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I had fun with pathfinder kingmaker. for like 4 months.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# so playstation players cant handle complex rpgs? :^)
btw im AnAngryMarine on psn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# same. ive had kids make fun of me in front of teachers and when i struck back *I* was the one in trouble. like literally, kid was making fun of me misspelling 'cactus jack' and when he asked where 'catcus jack' i said 'doing your mom' the teacher listening in yelled at me 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# good. twiiter think its ok to fuck kids, but it aint.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# old viking excution method. cut the back and pull the lungs out from the holes, so it looks like wings. "blood eagle" was suppose to be for the most serious of offensives like breaking oaths or friendships.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ive been called a big teddy bear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# like i put this dog into his bed and he got off and ran into my room.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# HI IM SHAWN FROM RGT85 AND THIS IS JACKASS! *posts a Jadakiss album cover*

you the longest time I thought Jadakiss because i never got into rap and hip hop and r&amp;b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# a bitch is someone who wont sleep with me. hashtag for the dumb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# IT SAYS ***NEW TITLE ANNOUNCEMENT*** Coming to Blu-ray 4/26 from Scream Factory! Wes Craven’s “Cursed” (2005) 2-Disc Collector’s Edition Blu-ray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# remember when cactus jack and chainsaw charlie started a rumble and were using chairs?
drew needs to use the sword]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# in the thread i linked theres two pics and they look alike my eyes burn from seeing it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i got up and made a sandwhich i dont care about edge vs miz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# hey those are tarot cards. i learnt those from #USER# and the binding of isaac!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#onTV he's still injured though but a great addition to AEW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i have a clip of me blowing up a kkk gathering in rdr 2 and the mc saying 'bunch of rats']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# that part where you get sabin was always confusing to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# thats the game store i go to on saturdays. owner self meds with the marywannas. week before it was kinda funny because we were playing magic and it just hit hard from his office]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i barely talk now as a 38 year old man. one of my brothers friend was like 'he doesnt talk much does he?" 
"noope"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# mental health &gt; twitter. 
are you seeing a therapist? or a dr?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i had a goth chick burn me the soundtrack in high school. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fine enjoy justin castro just trying to help out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL#
is something wrong with my mount in AC Vahalla?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# inmy life we've had a beagle mix, a dobbie, a chiahuahua, a yorkie, a husky, a rotty, a chiweenie(still with us) an american bulldog, a mutt we think is mixed with jack russel, and now my brothers long hair chiahuahua that loves sleeping in my bed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# uh huh. LESBIAN CARD REVOKED! you can only identify as bi or experimenting with men, no inbetween. i dont make the rules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# its the coof Ragin' contagion's got ya #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes because china isnt white so stop crituzing them, BIGOT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# memes are to be shared freely. unlike wealth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# mom's home, she saw her friend(my aunt), my half cooking with aunts help didnt kill any one, today was a good day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i mean, if they were real, people who totally bone pokemon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# cant offend Xinnie the pooh with the Xi variant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt;&gt;ref bump
here comes that wcw bullshit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# snorted it. He could have waited and got a free joe biden crack pipe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# she's doing the samething my cat when i lift him up near the ceiling fan strings, batting them around to play]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# nice! i cant watch right away cuz its dnd night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# they would give him -100000 social credit for his degeneracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "BRO, IT WAS THE 80S! TECHNOLOGY MAKES IT TOTALLY UNABLE TO BE CORRUPT! PHOTOSHOP IS NOT REAL, TECHNOLOGY CANT FAKE THINGS!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# and here i am with a gamecube tat doesnt read discs :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you cant report deaths to Social Security online]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# hispanics are like up there wth asians with racism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ITS LIKE MARIO 3D ALLSTARS, NOT REEEEEEEEEEEEAL! for those dumb enough to think im for real]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i heard they looked into it but where like 'nah fuck that, not worth it']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# HE'S GONNA GO TOY HUNTING WITH #USER# !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# he's about to find out truckers aint like the kids he taught, and that fuck around and find out is not a threat but a pledge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# my parents got hit in the driver side rear in 2010, and my mom braced and broke both her knees. shit was not fun. she never really fully recovered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Im tired, i thought this was about last nights AEW and chris jericho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i wasnt potty trained until i was 3. your doing alright in my book dude, kid aint starving, beaten, or worse. some kids bloom late.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ya'll should be the distraction we need cuz life is shitty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i'm here for the Abadon pics and not in a perverse way. yea get in shape, live the dream!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# their waiting for the super inflation. happened to germany before the nazis came on board.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# time to donate washing machine and dryer combos to the third world nation of Scandinavia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i crashed a go-kart into my dads car trailer in my backyard in 6th grade, breaking my ribs, puncturing my lung and almost killing me. so i know that feel, sis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# megan fox looks like the girl who jumps from toxic relationship to toxic relationship because of a horrible home life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i should check outside its getting close to midnigght]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Forget it Dev, its New Capenna. *movie ends*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# nyla, for awhile i used to think you were actually irl a nice person who is geeky, but now i see damn you are really a heel why you gotta slam that old guy so hard BAW GAWD THAT MAN HAD A FAMILY! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# just a normal one from a guy who gets upset over memes like this #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# it is 21 degrees here, i have 2 dogs in my bed and im shit posting on twitter while watching wrestling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# im single. im choosing pets over kids right now cuz im not ready]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# get him some magic spoon! they cant be bad if they sponsor youtubers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you mean you dont sit around in little clothing doing lewd things? CANCELLED! CANCELLED! CANCELLED!! because someone will think im being for real]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# remember when he wrote a 2 page and a half about a children's orgy, then is surprised when people complain about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Santa baby, forgot to mention one little thing
A ring, I don't mean on the phone
Santa baby, so hurry down the chimney tonight

it popped in my head i swear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# checkmarks are just so we know its ok to bully you. checkmark. how's the weather up there, checkmark?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# why must you ruin my week. it was an ok week, hell we finally got my mom's ashes home but then you had to post this bs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# vampire. being sauve just to get blood? nooooo thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# why was cody not medically cleared to wrestle though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# this is coming from a guy who was on so much coke he does not remember writing cujo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# gotta take you out then friend. im sorry. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# line up boys so that i may give you wedgies you NEEEEEEEEEEERDS #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# onslaught mirrodin affinity/tooth and nail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# UPDATE: watched it and liked it. was damn good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i mean, he did want the release of his sister. there has to be a network in there. sister or someone he called sister. ive been busy yesterday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# im still playing ac valhalla :B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# TBF elbowing something hurts for awhile. tattoos dont hurt like that, and a piercing is fast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# excuse wtf. i know your a comedian but like, really?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# your the guy who wears shorts in winter. damn it now that i thought of that im cold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ive seen cam shows with mom and daughter....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# rip your freezing to death twitter friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My nephew gave me the destroy all humans remake on switch, sweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# even funnier, he barely owned his own shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# wait, youtube started as a dating site??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# it looks like a fake. its not on the nytimes site]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the acclaimed( #USER# #USER# ) def reminds me of the new aged outlaws i love it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# THEQUARTERING SHOWN TO EAT THE WHITE POWER SKITTLES SHOWS HOW RACIST HE IS REE REE REE REEEEEEEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# im learning. family likes butter. a lot of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# does the jersey devil eat the witchs in nj or do they worship him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# as someone who voted trump, you posted cringe bro.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# it was more playing around on her friends couch clothed and she just puts my face in her chest.
h sized breasts man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# wait, you posted nudes of yourself while underaged? ew unless you where coaxed by a greaseball pedo]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>