<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yes. Celsius is bad. That is the most important point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Vac trains with maglev can go 1000 mph.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You’re not buying up suburbs and trading them up, turning them back to nature.

You just want more building and more people.

And your zoning ‘reform’ will be easily squelched by local building, parking, traffic, and utility rules.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# President Lincoln promised President Juárez help when he could and after the war President Grant sent materiel to help Mexicans kick out the French and win their country back.

The French dictator in Mexico, Maximilian, was hanged in 1867.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The people who advocate mass immigration are delighted to know that they're harming Americans. The cruelty is the point with open borders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It would be much better to send them all back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We don’t charge Mexico tariffs to export salad to us in the winter. Why should we tariff California salads?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# So-called native Americans are from east central Africa, not America.

The only way to have anything is to defend it, whether that sounds like slamming the door to you or not. There is nothing the native Americans regret more than failing to keep immigrants out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Since you don’t have any plan to accomplish that, we better close the borders now until you do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# We already had this problem in '76. The GOP veep and Congress refused to accept certified electors chosen in fraudulent elections and instead accepted electoral votes from the electors nominated by the other party.

Justice was done and America is proud. Could happen again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Surely you're not stupid enough to think that is ever a relevant thing to say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You're dead wrong. The demographics of mass immigration guarantee the the population will be majority made up of post-1980 migrants soon, even if we were to close the borders today. The old America is dead and the new arrivals are not capable of running a first world country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They’re not libertarians. They just hate America and want us exterminated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just think how embarrassed the anti-vaxxers would be if they were capable of shame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There used to be a middle column in WSJ where they would find people multiple times a week with the most bizarre problems and examine them from a business perspective. And they did it before you could find people on the internet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Amish people are very good looking. No plumpers or tattoo victims. Let’s do it. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Do you really think it's meaningful to describe every country with at least two people of different races anywhere on its territory as multi-racial? Think it through.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# “neutrality collapsed under Russian pressure”

Yeah, Obama/Biden’s CIA-led coup was just a form of “Russian pressure.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# In France, you should prohibit unmarried couples cohabitating and bearing children with gentle penalties and opprobrium to encourage marriage.nnAnd then use the same laws to prosecute, incarcerate, and deport the half-million Moslem polygamists out of your country permanently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But how will we make people show papers to eat in their home kitchens?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The technology of the 1800s has been lost in this benighted twenty-first century when we cannot imagine the well-documented materials and machines that our forebears made commonplace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Either people will accept the new definition of racism or else people will come to accept racism as normal and natural.

But either way, race based preference will always be necessary and pervasive in a multi-racial democracy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We’re not going to fight to feed their slaves again. Remember last time the slave power just wanted peaceful divorce. We just need to make them want it again. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If we valued life and well being more, we would lock up more criminals for longer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Ordinary working people need an intact nation to keep them safe, alive, prosperous, healthy, &amp; to continue their families &amp; our nation into the future. No billions of dollars can ever replace what membership in a healthy nation gives us. Our first responsibility to our children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Sinema is a patriot who wants our country to be healthy and prosperous. That’s her excuse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Let's add 10000 more cars a day from Treasure Island with zero quality transit connections! Brilliant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Understanding people of different races have different personalities, different average intelligence, different social structures, different language and expression, different talents. Or disapproving of inter-racial marriage. Or pride in being white.nnLots of things are racist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Treasonous anti-America white wokes (not progressives) are a fairly small proportion in American politics but they hold the balance of power because they control most of the racial minority factions. Asian Americans are one of the factions they control, helping undermine America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# No. It would be great for the economy. Wages would rise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Foreigners invading and replacing our nation is the extermination of our people. Ukraine is a fake crisis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Kendi, DiAngelo, and their whole ilk are making millions undermining workers for big business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I was munching at a nice little fonda in Guerrero a few years back after trips to Guanajuato, Morelos, and Nuevo León before. My companion just looked at me and said, “the Mexican food is just never as good as in Mexico City.”

It’s a fact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# They kept it ruined for 45 years afterward with those parking lots. Seems like the Germans liked their city destroyed and take all the blame themselves.

Glad to see they rehabilitated themselves afterwards. I wish America would.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And all it cost was any last hope that we'd be able to leave a livable planet to our grandchildren.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Every election, there's a wide swathe in the east that votes for rapprochement with Russia and a swathe in the west that votes to become another subjugated colony of Germany. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Armenian and Azeri lands within the USSR specifically, but close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Conquered countries may be subject for a decade or a century but the people survive. Unless you become a settler colony, your nation persists. 

Immigration replaces the people in slow motion genocide. It’s total destruction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nobody in SF or Cambridge can build what is legal in Tokyo. And their extreme wide street geometry and car based regional transportation system guarantee that more neighbors will harm their quality of life in ways unimaginable to Tokyo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Who cares how she’s accepted? As a Supreme, she is accountable to no one, has guaranteed power for life, and her power is limited only by her colleagues who often have embarrassing Thomas/Kavanaugh/ACB/Sotomayor appointment stories of their own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just tell her that she’s going to have to study and pass the bar herself just like all the other lawyers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Agreed. If people wanted a libertarian country, they shouldn't have imported so many people of different races. It's too late for that now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And UN data proves that Africans are uniquely resistant to dropping fertility under decadent western influence. The inability to afford families and marriage just doesn’t make African women more reluctant to have lots of babies. And never had in history either. r/K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It’s open borders fools like you trying to kill our nation that we need to escape from.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Doesn’t any representative institution do that to any minority voting block? Libertarians, white liberals, and environmentalists are similarly disenfranchised by the Senate. And by the House.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# After all, Portugal is just the province of Spain where they speak Brazilian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There is nothing moderate about America’s governance. Nor Canada’s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Inertia. The conservatives don’t want to change anything and feel owed something any time anyone else wants things changed. So adding  voter ID, they expect some price in return or they’re going to complain.nnThat’s all. They’ll get used to it eventually.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# What’s clear is that the top people in charge of US government—and whose grip is increasingly immune to public opinion as population and party demographics shift—are salivatingly eager to invade, occupy, punish, or control Russia as a hated and subject people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# There is no excuse for that stupidity. Maybe there was some excuse by segregated elites who had never been exposed to poverty and racial integration back in the 1950s and who therefore didn’t understand the consequences.

But Pruitt-Igoe was already national news in 1961.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Less so if you wear nothing but safe, reliable polyester.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The top priority of the Bush family was always hating and destroying America. They resent being associated with the rabble whose work pays for their privilege.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# 1. The boiling point of water in science labs depends on atmospheric pressure and is never assumed to be 0ºC.

2. Science usually operates in Kelvins anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# IQ isn’t everything. You would still need affirmative action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yggy’s nudes would break the internet. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# 2012-2017, Brady's top performing years, Aaron Rodgers was getting paid 50% more per year than Brady. Rodgers went to zero superbowls. Brady won 3.

And Brady would have won 5 if it weren't for Peyton Manning's Broncos. Rodgers was getting almost 50% more than Manning, too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Yes, they will always be a minority."

Someone doesn't understand how math works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You should tell the victim races about this. They’re going to be very surprised that Democrats are racists! You can be the one to show them the truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Too optimistic. Our population growth policy will eventually get to all the nice places in America. And end them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Your proposal is acceptable. Cars like yours kill 40,000 Americans on our streets every year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Not sure if you are playing dumb or really dumb.nnWe have added 100MM people because of immigration. The children of immigrants are people added to our already disastrous overpopulation regardless of their official on-paper citizenship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wrong. Labor was strong for decades because of the purges of communists. It was mass immigration and Red China that were the hardest challenge for labor and brought it down. The right co-opted anti-racism and anti-imperialism to import cheap labor. Just like Karl Marx said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Resulting from liberal race policies?

That is just a lie.

Lead in gasoline had more effect. And liberal crime policies applied to all races.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Real conservatism was an option in a 85% white country. It will never again be a part of American politics in our new majority minority country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 4. You didn’t mention Korea, but there is a country that really made its own democracy against our guidance. Koreans got a lot of problems but they don’t mind throwing a brick. Good for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The members of the KKK were known. It was all the mayors, congressmen, cops. They were openly proud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Counties.

For instance, LA County in California is larger than any Canadian province. Meanwhile Esmeralda Country in Nevada is smaller than any Canadian province but PEI. 

For example, BC can become Colombia County, Canada. Of course, you need a new 2-letter code: CA is taken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sure, in poverty and misery you can jam on ten times more people. Or you could cut the population down to sustainable levels and we could all live without poverty and with the clean safe space of opportunities we want for our children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Foreign tech workers getting massive visa giveaways to cut wages for American workers with their backwards culture and sexist behavior drove American women out of high tech. Turned the industry into a low prestige hive of cheap coolies.

That’s what ‘vetted’ immigration does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I had a wagyu cheeseburger with a hand made warm from the oven butter brioche bun and caramelized onions and wild mushrooms. Gorgonzola bechamel overflowing around the burger and mushrooms. Fig-arugula side with balsamic reduction. At my cool neighborhood theatre. Thirty dollars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If you let the word racist control your country, you don’t deserve a country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No. Portland? Oslo? Compare some western cities with western populations and not all of east Asia comes out ahead. Manila? Bangkok?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The American people did not consent to being flooded with 100MM immigrants since 1980. Why should we agree to add even more housing so that we can add an additional 100MM more immigrants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# “We will build dense, we will build tall.”

Hahaha, sure you will. It’s easy to build dense and tall. That’s why there is so much abundant housing in California now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Mexico has a fixed blend of FPTP deputies and PR deputies and the constant conclusion of local government and civil society advocates is that the PR deputies (pluris) are an utter waste of flesh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Call me what you want. I’m proud to be a chauvinist in favor of the American people and our lands and natural wildlife.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# We wouldn’t even have Tang to drink. Or that ballpoint space pen that writes upside down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Djokovik shouldn't be allowed out of his house until he's fully vaxxed. Australia should have restrained him and vaxxed him, voluntarily or not, before deporting him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wouldn’t young people just make a lot of bad choices with that much money?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No. It's very easy to cut home prices 3x in California. You just make it legal to build enough homes for everyone in the state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# We can’t colonize the rest of the galaxy. We can’t even remotely colonize subarctic lands much less arctic land or ocean bottoms which are 1000x easier than Mars or outer space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Because time pressure is part of what makes it valid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The lack of fresh water for everyone in the western states. Traffic jams getting into less developed mountainous areas. Endangered species going extinct. The shrinking base of rural jobs and rising expense of farmland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We’re not complaining about roads and sewers. It’s the sick hateful values that the woke have imposed on our nation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The US economy will improve when we don’t depend on Red Chinese investments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# …is a rapidly failing ideology of the past, just like socialism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No. Legal immigration is terrible for America and the flood of sky high immigration rates is wrecking our homeland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Whichever party is in charge of taking from Americans to deliver benefits for free to newly arrived foreign clients is going to win the votes of the post-1980 immigrants forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nobody asked you to come and you’re welcome to go somewhere else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# But seriously, nobody has any idea how to force changes in the structure of family life nor does that structure have any causal effect whatsoever on academic performance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Degrowth makes everyone richer. It’s the opposite of the resources wars you people promote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, it doesn’t. Race blindness was never viable, never serious, &amp; never popular. You can’t have a multi-racial society without judging—in all official important matters—judging and organizing the citizens by race. Race matters.nnOnly autistic libertarians wish it were otherwise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Terrible? With that sibilant-liquid blend and the sharp abrupt Anglo T at the end, slut is a gorgeously sensuous word.

Too bad about the definitions. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You would think Pelosi doesn't have kids, from the way she runs the country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There was no fair election to overturn in America last year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We could improve our old flu vaccine with new tech.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Affirmative action is necessary to sustain a multi-racial democracy. America won’t go on without it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# We're already ruinously overdeveloping all those resources. And 7/8 of the world's population is living lean and over 1/2 is living in poverty that we can never fix unless we reduce our global overpopulation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Make it illegal to build any housing in California that is more than four minutes walk to a rail stop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Using the word socialism but advocating standard centrist policy isn’t the same as advocating socialism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# America was far, far stronger as a world power and won two world wars before mass immigration. Now America is wrecked and well on the way to become the next Brazil or India.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I put the flags of countries I like in my handle. You should try it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's the end of any hope for real universal health care in America. The right wing corporate globalists have finally won decisively against health care reform.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hahaha. In a multi-racial democracy, all politics is identity politics. The future of America is rapidly increasing identity politics as our population gets rapidly more racially diverse.

“Eradicate the cancer”? That is just hilarious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No. It’s not your information, just commerce. It’s a publicly regulated tax and government in the sunlight prevents corruption. And the only ones who benefit from secrecy are big business exploiting workers and consumers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# There are very few smart tech people among our immigrants. The H1-B visas go to mediocrities who can easily be replaced by Americans paid decent wages. Highly qualified EB-1 and O-1 migrants amount to 1% of immigrants and we don’t really need them either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yes, you also have to be a right-wing sellout. SC black voters are as conservatives as SC white voters. They vote D only because they know their white GOP neighbors would repeal the XIIIA if they ever got the chance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Leftist revolutionary Benjamin Franklin, close associate to the literal founders of leftism. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The BBC is funded through a voluntary subscription tax on television sets. It’s pay television in a market system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# First world colonialism is good for the colonies, which finally get to enjoy honest effective European government.

It’s terrible for the colonizers who have to pay for it all and send away their young local talented leaders to civilize the savages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Men are to blame. It’s not the fault of women and children if men govern them badly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They’re all racist. Studying ants is racist and the relationship between society and human biology is the most racist thing of all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When they all say something that’s objectively impossible and do the opposite, believe what they do, not what they say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The more people there are, the more they will compete to get hold of the undeveloped land and develop it to get open space of their own. It’s a constant political struggle now to maintain habitat lands and we will lose more fights the more people are crowded in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nope. Santa Fe and the San Luis Valley’s deep Spanish roots form the single best Mexican food culture north of the border in New Mexico and Colorado.

The rest of you have never tasted the real salsa verde. What does LA have? Burritos?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# America’s schools do much more than .15 sigma better than any other school system in the world. So we’re doing something right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It’s brutally nasty to force kids to take 3-5 extra bus rides per day, mostly on unreliable schedules.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wrong. It belongs to Israel. Christians are mostly allowed to visit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They're not counting all non-whites as illegal aliens yet?nnHalf the babies born in America this year are illegal aliens!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Every president since Nixon has been to the right of Nixon on most issues. Nixon was the leftiest president ever, aside from the criminal conspiracy against the Constitution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Seattle is a horrible environment and nobody wants to live there unless he enjoys wet skin rot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# How about we cut out all the spending for recreational wars overseas and spend it on health care for all Americans.

P.S. Taxpayers can just write a check now or even fill out an ACH without ever using paper. No rape involved anymore!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Coin flip says Mahomes victory is inevitable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# With a bizarre exception for industrialized Oak Creek Canyon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# People who care about Black Rock and want to protect it should be working for BLM or environmental advocates or tourism. Not industrial development on fragile desert habitat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Fake again! Handle in Japanese, but words in Chinese. 

Proves you’re nothing but a weeb. Enjoy your waifu pillow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# West Valley City official motto: It’s not as bad as you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Haven’t failed in China and Japan.

But I agree. We’re going to have to send 100MM Reagan era new arrivals and their children back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That’s niche advice from vegans and other extremists. Cheese, milk, whole grains, nuts, lentils, and beans have nice protein content without that highly processed soy.nnAlso—if you’re not body building or pregnant—protein needs are overrated. Healthy humans do not need 50g daily.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And furthermore, immigration of the biggest threat to the Social Security system as immigrants take out a lot more than they pay in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Trump is pro-affirmative action. He did everything to reconcile with black American voters. They weren’t interested. At all.

Even with Biden campaigning to impoverish and disenfranchise black America with open border mass immigration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The vast majority of the genetic diversity of humankind lies in a couple million Bushmen and Pygmies in Africa. The vast majority of black Africans are Bantus with little diversity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The replacement of people who don’t really like or want children with people who do is good.

The only problem here is that our overcrowded homeland is being invaded by masses of foreigners while our own fertility is low.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Rothbard was a radical. Sometimes silly. But not completely stupid like modern libertarians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Those all (for now) have solid racial majorities. They’re not multi-racial democracies.

And Australia has pervasive affirmative action. Canada, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Also poisonous infections grow in corpses and they pollute water if they’re too close to your water source.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Progressive agenda requires legislation subject to filibuster. GOP agenda is just right wing judges and tax cuts for millionaires, neither of which can be filibustered.

Therefore filibustering blocks only progress, not regress, and ending it is good even under a GOP Senate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# These right wing open borders fanatics don’t care about health care and a safety net for Americans because they hate workers having any decent quality of life and they hate Americans. Destroying our people and our nation is a big positive side effect for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Too late. You right wingers elected Reagan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# She doesn’t even speak the language that cocoanut girl flirted in and she lives far away. So I really doubt that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# We can’t get good government reforms like that done in America anymore because we have tens of millions of immigrants voting from nations where corruption is normal, like Indians, among others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Of course they can survive apart. Both countries would have over 50MM people, far larger than most other countries.

And no. We cannot coexist each under our own rules. Immigration alone makes that impossible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Real is good for trips of under 500 km. Maybe 800 maximum  in a pinch. Cost to cost is 4000+km.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Thurmond wasn’t elected to the Senate as a Republican. He was a solid Democrat as governor and later as senator.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Mark Kelly’s career is over in 11 months. Sinema can be a senator as long as she wishes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Who exactly do you think is ruling Europe today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And the rep who got primaried wasn’t even one of the bad ones, just didn’t get along with Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No irony here. There is nothing in this world indians wish and dream of more than that their ancestors had got their act together and defended their borders.

Our posterity will look on us the same way. We are betraying them with our loose borders. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Asian students in America outperform every Asian country. Latino students in America outperform every Latino country. White Americans kids come in nearly first among white countries. And black America kids come in ahead of every black country.

#HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG#, nearly #HASHTAG#, &amp; #HASHTAG#

USA is #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trillions. It's one of the top spending items in national account, though it's mostly off budget because it's mostly mandates on private land owners. And that's just the equivalent rent of mandated free parking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I love clips. It’s the clipless lycra people who are just playing games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Gross and ugly. Terrible to live in. Imagine the noise and view destruction of all those flying cars. No place for people at all. This is a sprawl burb with more glass. Pruitt-Igoe with helicopters. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Hilarious. Immigrants are almost never a net positive for any economy. The '40s and '50s economy was created by low immigration driving up worker power and making it possible to demand education, benefits, and high pay.

Sorry about your fact-free self-published fantasties.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Great news for the barren. Those of us with children and grandchildren have to care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If Biden hadn't stolen the election with his pro-Corona policies because he owes billions to China, it would have disappeared by now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nope. In 1996 we already were forced by greed-head Republicans to put the Grand Staircase-Escalante National Monument under BLM management. We already know how to handle this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# “The designers never saw a real black person?”

Probably…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Directly elected senators are literally the problem right now. They’re not supposed to be directly elected for a reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Those places have high net emigration because of their terrible economies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Playing dumb? Globalists imported 100MM foreigners since 1980, replacing half the American population. None of the past decade of elections would have come out anywhere like what they did if only Americans were voting (Except Obama’s wins).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sinema has always been a progressive. Indeed used to be a Green partier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# MD and VA should have their statehood revoked for the same reasons that our founders didn’t want DC to have the vote or be an independent state of its own. As commuting technology expands, they’re both dominated by the sprawl of DC corruption.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Trump was more progressive on climate than Biden or Obama.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# In Massachusetts?! Remember that when JFK chose the Democratic Party, Massachusetts was a red state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's conservatives like you who imported over a hundred million cheap labor immigrants since Reagan opened the border that have usurped our democracy. It's no longer possible for Americans to elect a government in our own homeland because of the foreigners you have voting here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No. Legal immigration is nearly always bad in the short run.

And it’s easy to find places that suffer in the long run:

France. America. Canada.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# We have been having both for years. All the most successful multi-racial democracies have extensive affirmative action: Brazil. India. Malaysia. Every multi-racial democracy in the world has affirmative action.

Because you can’t have multi-racial democracy without it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# America would be lucky to trade from Biden to Lula or to Bolsonaro. Either would be a big upgrade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Her blood is American indian, one part in two (thousand-forty-eight ).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They eliminate the black ones 25 years ago when they added back the reds. Just another example of communists ignoring the needs of minorities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Australian aborigines are far more genetically related to Swedes than any two random African tribes are to each other. And the Swedes and Aborigines are far closer to each other than either is to any Africans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Japan is an ecological disaster, not a model to follow. They’re voluntarily reducing their own population rapidly because of overcrowding.

And Japan isn’t out of water, unlike California,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, Biden could just quit NATO like he quit Afghanistan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Plenty of Appalachian doctors and more qualified who get their spots taken by immigrants. But every Indian doctor in America means one less American gets a chance.

There is a national cap on doctors so each foreigner means one less American doctor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Rural American houses are not a part of human history but just a fake lifestyle forced on us by bad planning in DC. Real rural people always lived in dense villages with open land around them, not isolated farmhouses until the screwed up incentives of land homestead rules.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# England is an environmental sacrifice zone and we—as a global community of living things—can’t afford to do that to California, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Hahaha. LA has pure Mexican food? That wheat-based northern creole California cuisine?

You need to spend some time in Puebla and Mexico or even Guerrero and Oaxaca and see what the real Mexican food is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The solution for this is that people who have forty year old bladders should not go see children's movies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Salt Lake City, Vegas, Portland, &amp;c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Have you looked at an electoral map? The less segregation and the more that people of different races interact, the more likely white people are to vote Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The purpose of a country isn't to jam in as many people as possible. Our nation is a land and a people and that land is overdeveloped and badly lacking in wilderness and natural habitat already.

We're in a global mass extinction crisis from overpopulation. And we need to stop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You can’t depend on polls like that. There is too much bias; revealed preference would be much more informative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It should be free because it makes human life better and because young people don’t have a lot of money. A lot of people will miss out if they have to pay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That is a dumb theory. It led people to assume that turning a unified nation into a multi-racial minority-majority agglomeration wouldn’t destroy America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Pelosi is 80-something and about to retire next year. She doesn’t care if the state floods or America collapses entirely before 2030 because she won’t be around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# City housing is a tiny fraction of all the land a person depends on. You need 100x that land outside the city for food, fiber, clean water, fuel, metals, wood, parks, railroads and airports, and natural habitats to conserve biodiversity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Slow Boring wants property developers to be able to build whatever they want, a classic conservative goal.

Open borders was a Reagan-Bush policy originally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The majority of white women voted for Trump. White suburban women increased their Trump vote share from ‘16 to ‘20, opposite white suburban men.nnBlaming AWFLs for the state of America is not entirely fair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Did you learn nothing at all from Iraq and Afghanistan? And Syria and Libya. And Vietnam.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# For Okies, that was lavish wealth. They even had ambitions of rabbit ownership.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The Republican candidate was the most center-left Republican ever nominated. Not much room for the Dems to pick up support on issues against that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fewer cars is a direct improvement in standard of living. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We just need courage to rebuild the temple instead of dreaming about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The future of life on Earth, if we’re going to survive the crisis at all, it’s going to require hard work and decisions. It isn’t always going to be whatever is easiest or what makes you feel good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# No, executive order is not how a president would accomplish any of that. That is just a misunderstanding of how presidential power works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It was May. I didn’t win a permit in the lottery for summer in the wilderness section with the big rapids, so I went at the end of the rainy season. Had 71 solid hours of hard rain before the sun came back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wrong. Dems drove out Reagan’s next nominee through character assassination without even a hearing. It’s only when Reagan put up a centrist as his third nominee that he was confirmed. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hart-Cellar did not significantly change immigration policy. It put limits on Latin American immigration which were hardly ever met and eliminated limits on Asian immigration that were already very weak. It did nothing about illegals. And it was repealed entirely by 1990.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The America of Red Dawn—defeated as it was—was far, far better off than America today. At least the American people weren’t replaced by aliens in their own homeland in Red Dawn.

Plus, they probably all get health care under the Cuban occupation. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Second largest contributor is that facilities have gotten a lot nicer. Better swimming pools, weight rooms, fancier food services, nice finishes and natural light in services buildings that would have been dank basements when I was in school.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>