<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Josh Wardle, a software engineer in Brooklyn, knew his partner loved word games and created a guessing game for the two of them called Wordle. Just over two months after releasing it to the rest of the world, the once-a-day game has over 300,000 players. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the deadline for 2022 coverage fast approaching, sign-ups for Obamacare health insurance plans continue to break records. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kimberly Potter, the former police officer who fatally shot Daunte Wright in a Minneapolis suburb after seeming to mistake her gun for her Taser, was convicted on two counts of manslaughter on Thursday. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Behind the wildly popular Trump coin — merch that features the former president's face in gold — lies an entire disinformation supply chain. Complete with fake social media profiles and fake news, it all exists to help someone, somewhere, make a buck. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a recent episode of "And Just Like That," Carrie Bradshaw buys an outfit for a Diwali party. She visits what she calls a "sari shop," but ultimately buys a very different three-piece garment called a lehenga. The mistake didn't go unnoticed. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The march of terrible news in New York has felt dizzying. In dozens of interviews around the city, New Yorkers described a new and deep unease at what looks like an erosion of the sense of security they felt before the pandemic. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Archdiocese of New York has asked the Vatican to consider the social activist for sainthood. Her supporters worry that Catholic hierarchy may dilute her message even as it considers elevating her.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eating or giving fruit is a beloved Lunar New Year tradition in many Asian cultures, expressing love and thought to bring good luck. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ingrid Betancourt, a former congresswoman, will run for president in Colombia, a person close to her campaign said. She was kidnapped in 2002 and held by the country's largest guerrilla force for more than six years. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Texas man pleaded guilty on Tuesday to attempting to smuggle two men into the U.S. in a flag-draped coffin. The crime was uncovered by two Border Patrol employees who happened to be military veterans and sensed that something was amiss, prosecutors said. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Metropolitan Opera is back to its four-operas-in-under-48-hours weekend marathons, featuring "Rigoletto," "Le Nozze di Figaro," "Tosca" and "La Bohème," as virus cases rise in New York City. Here is our critic's marathon at the Met to see them all. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Medical advisers to the Israeli government have recommended offering fourth coronavirus vaccine doses to people age 18 and over, citing what they suggested were early signs of the effectiveness of an additional shot in helping prevent serious illness.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Carnival Cruise Line ship returned to Miami on Sunday after multiple people onboard tested positive for the coronavirus, the cruise line said. It was the latest Florida-based cruise to be disrupted as the Omicron variant drives up cases. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia has a history of beginning military action with an operation of disguise or misdirection to sow confusion. As tension builds on the borders of Ukraine, the country’s soldiers are facing a nerve-racking guessing game about what might happen next.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three members of BTS have tested positive for the coronavirus after returning to South Korea from the U.S., according to the K-pop group’s management company. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Philippines Commission on Elections threw out a petition to disqualify Ferdinand Marcos Jr., the son of the country’s former dictator, from the presidential election. He is leading in the polls despite several efforts to keep him off the ballot. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Air fryer vs. convection toaster oven: #USER# weighs in on the debate that has divided American kitchens. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Animal rights advocates decry the hunting practices, and conservationists say loosening restrictions would be ruinous for the environment. But others argue Indigenous people have been caretakers of Taiwan’s wildlife for thousands of years and their expertise should be respected. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Biden on Thursday denounced Donald Trump for spreading lies about the 2020 election. "I’ll allow no one to place a dagger at the throat of democracy," Biden said. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French fries, made with a lot less oil, may be one of the main reasons that air fryers were invented. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Districts are made up of 15 adjacent tiles. Draw a district with at least eight of your party’s tiles to secure your party’s advantage. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Documentaries about the Beatles, Billie Eilish and the 1969 Harlem Cultural Festival were about reclaiming and rethinking memory, about unexpected echoes across decades, about transparency and the mysteries of artistic production. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask the people who know Penélope Cruz best to describe her, and one adjective always comes up. "All my life, I’ve been hearing how stubborn I am," she said, then paused. "I don’t know if it’s because I’m a Taurus." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Novak Djokovic, the top player in men’s tennis and its leading vaccine skeptic, has had his visa canceled for the second time by the government of Australia.

Here’s a look at how the standoff has unfolded: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking News: The WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange can appeal a decision to allow his extradition to the U.S. to face charges under the Espionage Act in connection with obtaining and publishing secret government documents, a British court ruled.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which Covid test should you get? When should you get tested, and what if you can’t find one? We’ve got answers for you here. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFL stars like Odell Beckham Jr. are wearing customized T-shirts designed by Bruce Thompson, a New Orleans native like Beckham, to show love to one another during pregame warm-ups. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lisala Folau, 57, survived 26 hours floating in the sea after an underwater volcanic eruption sent a tsunami crashing through his home.

“It’s one of these miracles that happens,” said New Zealand’s acting high commissioner in Tonga. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The U.S. Supreme Court passed up a chance to issue its first major Second Amendment ruling in a decade, to the relief of gun control advocates #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are 12 new books recommended by critics and editors at The New York Times. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ben Smith, the media columnist for The New York Times, is leaving the paper to start a new global news organization with Justin Smith, who is stepping down as chief executive of Bloomberg Media. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most affordable U.S. cities for singles to rent studios: Wichita, Kansas; Columbus, Ohio; and Albuquerque. 
The least affordable: Miami, New York and New Orleans. 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omicron causes less severe disease than other coronavirus variants, according to a new study of nearly 70,000 Covid patients in California. The research aligns with similar findings from South Africa, Britain and Denmark. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2021 was the fifth warmest year by a slight margin over 2015 and 2018, according to a ranking from Copernicus Climate Change Service, a European Union program. The hottest years on record are 2016 and 2020, in a virtual tie. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brussels sprouts are quite possibly the best vegetable you can make in an air fryer. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Passing," the new drama from Rebecca Hall, "reminds us of the need for movies to get us past the surface — of skin and sight — and revel in the worlds that Black women create for themselves beyond the gaze of others," our critic writes. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In an unusual joint statement on Wednesday, Justices Sonia Sotomayor and Neil Gorsuch sought to rebut reports that Gorsuch’s refusal to wear a mask at Supreme Court arguments has created tensions between them. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gov. Kathy Hochul of New York said Wednesday that she would propose spending $10 billion to help rebuild a health care work force exhausted and depleted by the pandemic. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the new “West Side Story,” Justin Peck’s dances have a life of their own. But they’re less a part of the show’s fabric than an escape.  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The slip from genetics to eugenics is one that can happen quite easily." For decades, geneticists collected blood from the Roma people and deposited their DNA in public databases. Their research was rife with ethical issues, a new analysis reveals. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least 10 people were injured after a bridge collapsed in Pittsburgh on Friday morning, hours before President Biden visited the city to discuss infrastructure. None of the injuries were life-threatening and no one was killed, officials said. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a recap of what's happened with Djokovic's standoff in Australia so far. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An air fryer can form a crispy shell on chicken Parmesan while keeping the meat inside juicy. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. officials vow to unleash searing economic measures if Russia invades Ukraine, including sanctions on its largest banks and financial institutions, that could cause severe inflation, a stock market crash and other forms of financial panic. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Guatemalan court sentenced five former paramilitary members to 30 years in prison for the rape of Indigenous women during the country's civil war. The women were "treated like animals, sexually violated and subjected to sexual slavery,” a judge said. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three federal judges threw out Alabama’s congressional map and ordered state lawmakers to redraw the lines. “Black voters have less opportunity than other Alabamians to elect candidates of their choice to Congress,” the panel of judges wrote. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africa’s government, buoyed by data showing that infections from the Omicron variant aren’t as severe, has dropped quarantine restrictions for all but symptomatic people. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new clinic is changing prostate cancer treatment for gay and bisexual men, a process long geared to the relationship needs of straight men. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a statement filed in court, an FBI agent said that the passenger refused to wear a mask despite being asked to do so “dozens” of times and threw an empty beverage can, hitting another passenger in the head.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coffee gets people moving in the morning — in more ways than one. Here's why.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NSO offered the FBI a workaround: a new system called Phantom. Israel granted a special license to NSO that permitted Phantom to attack U.S. numbers. The license allowed for only one type of client: U.S. government agencies. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inflation is higher than it has been in decades. What does it mean for you? #USER# will pose reader questions to #USER#, president of the Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco, on Friday at 11 a.m. ET. Join us for the conversation. #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech companies are lining up to sell devices that let people into the metaverse, an immersive digital world, and control their experiences once they are inside it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The New York Times obtained a brochure put together by NSO for potential customers, which says that Phantom allows American law enforcement and spy agencies to get intelligence “by extracting and monitoring crucial data from mobile devices.” #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Families in Detroit, Michigan's largest school district, were told on Dec. 31 that classes would be canceled, with no remote option, from Monday to Wednesday, to ensure all of its nearly 8,000 employees get tested before classes start again. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain's NHS plans to erect temporary field hospitals in response to a steep rise in coronavirus hospitalizations nationally. The Omicron variant's dramatic impact on UK medical services is a bellwether for the challenges to come in places like the U.S. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Chinese government says its planned overhaul of a women’s rights law shows its dedication to gender equality. At the same time, it’s censoring and detaining feminist activists. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans quit their jobs at record rates this year, in what was labeled “The Great Resignation” or the “Big Quit.” Some suggested a collective life-or-death experience caused people to reassess their options. Others see a new anti-work era emerging. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Modern Love: "I am a deaf person. For the past 10 years, since I turned 18, hearing men have flirted with me and taken me out on dates. The only thing they have in common is the promise they all make: 'I’ll learn sign language for you.'" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A proposal by NYC to ban fur sales has polarized New Yorkers, pitting animal rights advocates against black ministers and other opponents #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Novak Djokovic had received a medical exemption to Australia’s vaccine requirements, a move which stirred anger in the country. Then he was stopped at the border.

Here’s a look at how the standoff has unfolded. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: President Emmanuel Macron of France, determined to engage with Russia and facing a national election in April, is putting himself at the fulcrum of crisis diplomacy on Europe's future. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After chaotic back-room negotiations, Italian lawmakers said Saturday that they had reached a consensus to keep the status quo in place and would ask the country’s current president, Sergio Mattarella, to serve another seven-year term. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Private insurers will soon have to cover the cost of eight at-home coronavirus tests per member per month, the Biden administration said Monday. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Kurdish-led militia that has been battling Islamic State fighters for control of a prison in Syria retook the entire complex, a spokesman for the militia said.

More than 100 people have been killed since ISIS fighters stormed the facility on Thursday.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last two months were supposed to be uplifting. But the Omicron variant added another speed bump in New York City’s road back to normalcy and deepened the city's stark economic divide. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Making me appear ridiculous was the chosen way to marginalize my message.” Marianne Williamson, the hard-to-define former presidential candidate, still keeps an ear to the ground in Washington as she ponders what’s next. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The U.S. Transportation Department plans to tackle rising traffic fatalities using new funding in the $1 trillion infrastructure law. It aims to address issues ranging from speed limits and street lighting to emergency medical care. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inflation in the eurozone climbed to an annual rate of 5% in December, a second consecutive record, according to the initial estimate of the EU’s statistics office. But analysts say there are signs that it’s turning a corner. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At 90, Michel Butros al-Jisri, one of the last Christians in the Syrian city of Idlib, is a relic of a once-vibrant community now teetering on the brink of extinction because of war and persecution. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The S&amp;P 500 rallied 2.4%, its biggest jump since June 2020, avoiding a fourth consecutive week of losses. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“In salmon terms: I had been swimming upstream in heels and skinny pants,” Rachel Stevens writes. “When it was time for a baby, and the river told me I had to let go of all of that and my old self had to die a hard death, I was one shocked fish.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahead of talks with the Kremlin, the Biden administration detailed punishing financial, technology and military sanctions should Russia invade Ukraine. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gov. Kathy Hochul of New York moved a step closer to realizing her vision for a link that would fill gaps in New York’s Manhattan-focused transit system and provide easier, faster travel to hundreds of thousands of low-income residents and people of color. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jean-Marc Vallée, the Oscar-nominated director known for the critically acclaimed “Dallas Buyers Club” and TV’s “Big Little Lies,” is dead at 58. 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The head of a comet often glows green; the tail mostly does not. A team of scientists have now come up with a detailed explanation for why. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardy Kruger, the first German actor to become a Hollywood star after World War II, died on Wednesday. He was 93. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A four-foot tsunami wave was reported to have hit Tonga’s capital on Saturday, sending people rushing to higher ground. The U.S. National Tsunami Warning Center issued a tsunami advisory for the Washington and Oregon coast on Saturday morning Pacific time. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans have started to receive free coronavirus tests from the U.S. government in the mail after it began accepting orders on Tuesday.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Hexapolis, you are an elected legislator for either the Purple Party or the Yellow Party. You are in charge of redrawing Hexapolis’s districts in your party’s favor. 

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Israel weighs whether to approve a fourth Covid vaccine dose, some scientists warn that too many shots might actually harm the body’s ability to fight the coronavirus. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The type of animal slaughter used to render meat kosher or halal is now illegal in Belgium. The ban was pushed by both animal rights advocates and right-wing nationalists. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking to upgrade your medical mask? Here’s a guide for picking a quality N95, KN95 or KF94. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All Los Angeles Unified School District students and employees will need to show a negative Covid test to enter school on Jan. 11, the district said. “We don’t know what we’re going to see when we come back,” Pilar Montalvo, a parent in Los Angeles, said. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world is still beautiful — and in many places, things are changing for the better. Our "52 Places" list in 2022 is here to take you on a journey. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Draw your own map to learn more about how gerrymandering works and see how you stack up against other Times readers.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How should Christian schools, which advocate abstinence until marriage, treat pregnant teenagers? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Opinion

“The most serious attempt to overthrow the American constitutional system since the Civil War would not have been feasible without the influence of America’s Christian nationalist movement,” writes Katherine Stewart, an author, in a guest essay.#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To find a durable skillet that heats evenly and meets the demands of professional chefs and home cooks alike, #USER# sought help from kitchen and cookware experts. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesters in Kazakhstan stormed government buildings and captured police vehicles on a fourth day of demonstrations driven by outrage over surging gas prices. Anger has swelled despite some government concessions and a strict state of emergency.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Opinion

“No one talks about the sadness of gifts,” writes Tim Kreider. “I’m thinking of the adult, multilayered and tangled sadness of failed efforts to please you from people who love you, and whom you love.”
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands of protesters flooded the streets of several cities in Sudan on Saturday, activists said, denouncing the October military coup that imperiled the nation’s attempt at a democratic transition after decades of military rule. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thirty-one people were seriously injured on Sunday morning as a five-alarm fire tore through a high-rise apartment building in the Bronx, officials said. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Astronomers around the world will be watching (and perhaps biting their nails) as the Webb telescope undergoes a $10 billion, monthlong game of origami. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a major pivot for the Biden administration, 8,500 American troops have been put on “high alert” for possible deployment to Eastern Europe, the Pentagon said on Monday, as NATO and the U.S. brace for a possible Russian invasion of Ukraine. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Committing to regular exercise is often easier said than done. Here’s how to get started. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.#USER#’s last issue of the year always honors the artists, innovators and thinkers we lost over the past twelve months.

These are The Lives They Lived. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A strong winter storm is expected to bring snow and freezing rain across parts of the South and into the Northeast beginning Saturday, potentially creating hazardous travel conditions and deepening supply-chain problems in the regions. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This may become your new favorite chocolate chip cookie recipe, if it isn’t already. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking News: The Jan. 6 panel has subpoenaed 14 people who acted as fake electors for Donald Trump in the 2020 election. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Johnson &amp; Johnson’s booster shot offered strong protection against Omicron and reduced the risk of hospitalization, a clinical trial found. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Opinion: “I used to have a lot of trouble falling asleep; now I lie down, breathe in and out in a slow rhythm and focus on letting all tension flow out of my limbs. I usually fall asleep within 20 minutes,” #USER# writes. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Omicron variant is blazing around the world, but fears of its rapid spread are tempered by early evidence that the variant causes milder symptoms, with vaccinations and boosters helping prevent serious illness and death. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prime Minister Boris Johnson's political future is in doubt after he admitted to attending a party during a strict coronavirus lockdown. Here's a guide on what could happen next. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Michigan school superintendent debunked a rumor that students who identify as furries used litter boxes in school bathrooms. “It is unconscionable that this afternoon I am sending this communication,” the superintendent wrote in an email to parents. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharp manicures, bejeweled cages, and thick white eyeliner. Here are otherworldly beauty looks that stood out at Paris Couture Week. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Omicron variant has fueled a rise in Covid-19 cases across the United States. Here’s what you need to know if you get infected. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Jan. 11, 2002, a sailor photographed 20 men in orange uniforms and on their knees at Guantánamo Bay. The image became one of the most enduring, damning photos of U.S. detention policy post the Sept. 11 attacks. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Opinionnn“Again and again, we have heard conservatives argue that even if you believe that Donald Trump is flawed and the MAGA movement is worrisome, the left is much more dangerous,” Jonathan Rauch and Peter Wehner say in a guest essay. “We disagree.”n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kazakhstan’s long-serving former president, Nursultan Nazarbayev, posted a video on Tuesday with his first public comments since violence in the country erupted, expressing support for the country’s leader and the economic reforms he has proposed. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opposition to pet vaccines has grown in recent years, fueled by an anti-vaccination movement in humans that has spilled over to animals. Here’s what you need to know about keeping your pet safe. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, tech companies did some good this year. Here’s our columnist’s annual list of the handful of projects that improved the world. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We found 40 words that can be spelled with these seven letters. How many can you make?

Don’t forget, your words must include the center letter.
#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michel Butros al-Jisri, 90, is one of only three known Christians who remain in the Syrian city of Idlib. The once-vibrant Christian community, like many of others in the Middle East, appears headed for extinction. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Tampa Bay Buccaneers have cut Antonio Brown, terminating his $3.1 million contract. It is the receiver’s fourth departure from an NFL team in four seasons, and possibly the end to his career. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This recipe shows the potential of an air fryer and the creativity of cooks who seem willing to try making anything in it, even cheesecake. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands of flights have been disrupted over the last month. Here’s what you need to know if yours is one of them. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking News: Bill de Blasio, the former mayor of New York City, said he would not run for governor of New York, as he had been widely expected to do.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scorned, Animal Rights Advocates in France Intensify Guerrilla Tactics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Max Julien, the sultry, soft-voiced actor and screenwriter who rose to pop-culture prominence with his starring role in the 1973 film “The Mack,” died on Jan. 1 at a hospital in Los Angeles. He was 88. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Lunar New Year approaching, now is the time for homemade dumplings. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The UN human rights chief urged nations to root out systemic racism against people of African descent on Monday, as she released a report calling for measures to dismantle discrimination and for sweeping changes to policing, as well as reparations. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People of African descent are reclaiming lost traditions among the waves. Contemporary surfing derives from Polynesians who settled Hawaii. But, historians say, African wave riding, on boards or in canoes, evolved independently along the West African coast. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ronnie Spector, the lead singer of the Ronettes, the 1960s vocal trio that gave a passionate edge to pop’s girl-group sound with hits like “Be My Baby” and “Baby, I Love You,” died on Wednesday. She was 78. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With shootings surging in many U.S. cities, calls to redirect money to policing are rising. But other anti-crime measures might be more effective, experts say, and avoid the downsides of policing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For some parents, jewelry made from breast milk can be a way to cope with loss. Others have such pieces made after experiencing difficulty nursing, one store owner said. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands of flights were canceled as a winter storm was expected to pummel the U.S. Northeast with blizzard conditions. 

Here’s the latest. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYPD Officer Jason Rivera's interest in law enforcement came early in life and spilled over into everything he did. “My brother had a lot of fears,” Jeffrey Rivera said at the funeral on Friday. "But he wasn’t afraid to die to wear that uniform.” #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To find reliable tools that can help drivers through bitter cold snaps and record snowfalls, #USER# tested ice scrapers at the same facility where Ford tests vehicles for extreme conditions. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If urologists "do not understand the role of the prostate in sexual pleasure, it’s rarely a priority discussion."nnThese doctors saw the need for a clinic that focused on prostate cancer treatment specifically for gay and bisexual men.  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a recent session in the House, two Republican lawmakers from Georgia, Marjorie Taylor Greene and Andrew Clyde, sat in full view of TV cameras. Neither was wearing a mask.

To date, the two have incurred more than $100,000 combined in fines. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberal activists noticed which 2020 candidates swiftly called out President Trump's attack on Rep. Ilhan Omar. And they noticed who lagged behind. “Black folks are watching. Muslim folks are watching. Brown folks are watching." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bronx building that was the scene of a deadly fire on Sunday did not have sprinklers in most areas of the building, a spokesperson for the owners said. Residents said the smoke alarms went off all the time, leading them to often ignore the signals. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Italy, a proposal to include a female philosopher, Cornaro Piscopia, in a monument whose 78 sculptures are all men has spurred debate. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our editors handpicked 11 stories for you to enjoy. Welcome to The Weekender. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The artist Melvin Van Peebles filled his “Blue Room” with scenes from everyday life and turned them into sculptures, #USER# writes. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Moscow correspondent, Valerie Hopkins, visited Nur-Sultan to understand why Kazakhstan erupted in violent protests. "The protests started over fuel prices, but it became clear that the deeper anger was over economic inequality," she writes. 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bells of Archbishop Desmond Tutu’s former church will toll for 10 minutes at noon every day this week, until his funeral mass on Jan. 1, at the same cathedral. The service will be limited to 100 people because of the coronavirus pandemic. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Safety experts offer advice on how to stay safe and keep warm if you get stranded on the road in a snowstorm. Their top tip? Be prepared. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a storm pushes north in the U.S., more than 1,400 flights have been canceled and thousands of people have been left without power. Most of the New York City area is under a coastal flood warning or advisory, the Weather Service said. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A snowstorm shut down a 50-mile stretch of Interstate 95 south of Washington, D.C., trapping motorists overnight in freezing conditions. Senator Tim Kaine was among the drivers stranded for more than 12 hours. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When contentious new Covid protocols for French schools were announced this month, the local news media reported, France’s education minister was vacationing in Ibiza. “I regret the symbolism,” he told lawmakers. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are people in the U.S. thinking about the pandemic, and how ready in the nation to discuss living with the virus? A poll, commissioned by The New York Times, tried to find out.

Listen to Part 1 of The Daily's look at what the poll revealed.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking News: More than 4.5 million people in the U.S. quit their jobs in November, the most in two decades of tracking, as openings remained near a record. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alarming levels of toxic mercury have been found in the leaves of trees and the feathers of birds in the Amazon forest of southeastern Peru, a new study says. The mercury is released into the air by miners searching for gold along nearby riverbanks. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Individually, books are frequently useful or delightful, but it is when books are displayed en masse that they really work wonders. Covering the walls of a room and exuding the breath of generations, they nourish the senses, slay boredom and relieve stress.#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A grizzly bear named Arthur was sedated before a helicopter flight back into the wilderness this June. Researchers are tracking orphan cubs reared in a shelter to see whether they can thrive after “rewilding.” 

See more from the year in pictures: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is hard to find these days. New podcasts let listeners eavesdrop on singles in search of connection. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most at-home tests use substances that change color after a chemical reaction. Advocates for the blind believe new science could employ temperature or smell changes to make coronavirus tests more accessible. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Social Security Administration now allows gay men and lesbians to receive survivor’s benefits if they can show that they were in a committed relationship and would have married had that been possible. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking News: The CDC has lowered its estimate of Omicron’s prevalence in the U.S. — Delta, not Omicron, was the dominant variant during the week ending in Dec. 18. The update shows how poorly the agency has communicated its uncertainty, experts say. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avoid drawing districts with boundaries that stretch across the map. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new study of a cluster of Covid cases in one household in early December suggests that Omicron may have a shorter incubation period than previous variants: about 72 hours. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe is experiencing record daily coronavirus infections as Omicron spreads at an unprecedented pace compared with the first two years of the pandemic. People across the continent and Britain are scrambling for tests and businesses are short of staff. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A second New York prosecutor decided not to pursue criminal charges against former Gov. Andrew Cuomo over sexual harassment allegations that helped prompt his resignation. The prosecutor called the allegations credible but said his conduct wasn't criminal. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A severe outbreak of avian flu in Israel has led to a mass culling of infected poultry and caused the deaths of about 5,000 migratory cranes. It's "one of the worst blows to wildlife in Israel’s history," the minister of environmental protection said. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Omicron variant, which has proved capable of bypassing vaccines, has infected tens of thousands of people in New York, ruining countless holiday plans. Still, New Yorkers brimmed with determination to salvage what they could of Christmas. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael K. Williams was a window into the lives of men we rarely choose to see, Reginald Dwayne Betts writes. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Novak Djokovic was told to leave Australia on Thursday following a 10-hour standoff with government officials at a Melbourne airport, ending his chance to defend his Australian Open title. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The prime minister of the Bahamas, Philip Davis, has ordered Bahamian flags in the country and at its embassies around the globe to be lowered to half-staff in tribute to Sidney Poitier. “Our country is in mourning,” he said. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A former police officer in Tulsa, Oklahoma, was sentenced to 25 years in prison for the 2014 killing of his daughter’s boyfriend after a jury found him guilty of second-degree murder in his fifth trial in the case.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Republican-led states have passed laws that would allow workers to receive unemployment benefits if they were fired for refusing a Covid-19 vaccine. Many were among the first to end some or all federal unemployment benefits early several months ago. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taliban fighters are no longer insurgents, avoiding airstrikes and planning ambushes. Instead, they are policing the streets of Kabul.

Our journalists spent 12 days with a police unit in the city. Can the Taliban secure the peace after winning the war? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sticky, fiery and impossible to stop eating, these air-fried chicken wings are easier and less messy than deep-fried wings. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Opinionnn“How can it be that in this era of heightened sensitivity to every kind of hatred,” Bret Stephens writes, “there’s so much caviling, caveating and outright denying when it comes to calling out bias aimed at Jews?” #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Giants chose Brian Daboll, the former Bills offensive coordinator, as their next head coach, the team announced on Friday evening. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“This case is a disaster for the rule of law and a grave disservice to women in Texas, who have a right to control their own bodies,” Justice Sonia Sotomayor wrote in dissent. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We have a big problem." Makers of gruyère cheese in Switzerland and France are not happy that a federal judge sided with U.S. cheese producers and said the cheese — named for the Swiss town where it's been made for centuries — could be produced anywhere. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Divers enlisted to search a Texas lake for the remains of a missing man instead discovered 13 sunken vehicles, the authorities said. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Sassoli, the president of the European Parliament, has died at 65. No cause of death was immediately available, but he had been hospitalized in Italy because his immune system was not functioning normally. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In England, many parents, politicians and school administrators are desperate to keep schools open after two years of chaotic openings and closures. But the variant is raising questions about those hopes, at least in the short term. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The U.S.'s blood supply had dipped to levels that the Red Cross has not seen in 10 years. “This is the biggest challenge that I’ve seen in my 30 years in the business,” said Chris Hrouda, the president of biomedical services at the American Red Cross. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaders of the U.S.’s largest air carriers said that thousands of flights could be grounded by interference from 5G technology. The warning comes two days before Verizon and AT&amp;T plan to deploy more segments of the new mobile service. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The danger in the wild popularity of the Trump coin, experts say, is how harmless the merch might seem. But behind its success is an entire supply chain of disinformation pushing the trinket for the low, low price of $0. (Plus $9.99 shipping and handling.) #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have to make a quick getaway in the event of a wildfire, hurricane, flood or any number of other emergencies, #USER# recommends that you pack light, reliable and versatile tools that could be easily carried in a backpack. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Yorkers are making their yearly trips to see dazzling holiday lights, and visitors should expect crowds, spectacular displays and some new Covid safety precautions. 

Here's where to find them in full force, in all five boroughs. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Julian Fellowes chased his new series, “The Gilded Age,” for a decade. Call it his white whale. "Beginning Monday on HBO, you can watch it drag him and a large, talented cast beneath the waves," #USER# writes.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newly released body camera and surveillance footage shows a man attacking shoppers at a Los Angeles store last week and police officers opening fire, killing him and a 14-year-old girl in a dressing room. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia is investigating whether Novak Djokovic could be charged with making a false statement about his travel history on his visa entry form, immigration authorities said. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The FBI is treating the attack on a suburban Fort Worth synagogue on Saturday as “an act of terrorism targeting the Jewish community,” contrary to the agency’s initial statement, the bureau's director said. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Like Iceland itself, Sjón’s books are simultaneously tiny and huge, weird and normal, ancient and modern," #USER# writes about the Icelandic novelist, whose wide-ranging work carries a whiff of the unreal. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two decades ago, “Sex and the City” set the standard for many shows to come. With “And Just Like That …,” the series reintroduces itself to a genre that has evolved beyond it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Opinion

"My journey into homelessness was traumatic, but it was also incredibly expensive, and that’s what I want to focus on here," Lori Teresa Yearwood writes in a guest essay. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sharp rise in Covid cases in the U.S. from the Omicron variant will peak by mid-January, scientists are projecting. "It’s shocking. It’s disturbing," said a Columbia University epidemiologist who led the data modeling. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The academy has plenty of Oscar-worthy contenders with crowd-pleasing appeal this year, like “West Side Story” and “Belfast.” The only problem is that the crowds haven’t shown up for them. Will that help “Spider-Man” make a case for best picture?
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New studies on animals suggest why Omicron is less severe than earlier variants: It seems to cause much less damage to the lungs.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Austria’s lower house of Parliament voted on Thursday to make Covid vaccines mandatory for almost everyone 18 and over, putting it on the path to be the first European country with such a mandate. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a first, a man receives a heart from a genetically altered pig #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a eulogy for Officer Jason Rivera, who was shot and killed last week, Mayor Eric Adams pledged to work with officials to provide the New York City Police Department with the resources it needs to do its job and “keep the people of this city safe.” #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In an effort to keep classrooms open, five million rapid coronavirus tests will be made available to schools across the U.S., the Biden administration said, but states will have to apply for them. The first shipments could arrive as early as this month. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The number of Americans hospitalized with Covid-19 is higher than last winter’s peak as Omicron tears through the U.S. and overwhelms hospitals. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Activision has faced accusations of sexual harassment and discrimination that senior executives ignored. The game maker’s shares have fallen 27% since California sued the company in July over the matter.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope Benedict XVI said he had been at a 1980 meeting about a priest accused of pedophilia, contradicting a previous statement he made to a law firm investigating how allegations of clerical sexual abuse had been handled when he was an archbishop.n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new musical "Black No More" is an expansive, Afrofuturistic take on race relations in the U.S. — set against an equally vast arrangement of jazz, gospel, R&amp;B, hip-hop and reggae meant to connect the past and present. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's how to make your bathroom less gross, according to the cleaning experts at #USER#. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For 50 years, Francisco Luis Ramírez has been the go-to guy for instrument repairs in Mexico, a nation that reveres the accordion. Now it’s a family business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A container collapse at sea may have sent tens of thousands of hotly anticipated cookbooks into the sea.  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prenatal tests initially looked for Down syndrome and worked very well. But as manufacturers tried to outsell each other, they began offering additional screenings for increasingly rare conditions — and often got it wrong. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor Eric Adams won New Yorkers' votes on a platform of bringing down crime. The killing of a police officer on Friday in Harlem has increased pressure on him to do something substantive to improve public safety. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The CDC on Thursday shortened isolation periods for health care workers who contract Covid-19, recommending that workers who are asymptomatic return to work after seven days and a negative test. #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>