<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# i'm guilty of doing that during the years i expected a refund. LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# that could be said for any artist that drew for any animated film or TV series ever made. Why's he special? ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# it's true. Black people are victims. Everything bad that happens to us is because someone is keeping us down. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm sorry for the loss of your cat. She looks just like my 14yo calico Amber. Also a senior. ðŸ˜¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# we hate Trump. we don't want the man to die.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ðŸ˜ **sigh** alright. that's your right to do so. I'm diehard  #HASHTAG# but we're still cool regardless. ðŸŒ·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# everyday nonstop. Black folks can't seem to stop being kind to one another. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# gun control will make the ghetto a safe place for black people to live around each other #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# more pizza for us, chicken wings for #USER#, soup for #USER# and seafood for #USER#. just to name a few. LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# according to liberals black people cannot be racist. So we're all good. We get a free pass. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Jimmy Swaggart would've loved Cicero Avenue ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You just low-key defended the orange retard in chief! ðŸ¤¡ LOL ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ðŸŽµIt was all a dream/
You used to read People magazine ðŸŽ¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# **sweats**]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# TRACY MORGAN!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I'll bring the punch bowl and the punch...and my flask of cognacðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Ah. I thought I was being attacked by a Trumper but I see she's #HASHTAG# too. We're on the same side. ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# every once in a while i meet a woman who doesn't mind. But usually these broads are stuck up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# because black folks need more abortions and handouts.n#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# a meteorological Spring TECH. that means come December you get a meteorological Winter TECH. ðŸ¤•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# HAWKS WIN!!!!

dedicated to Uncle Joe!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 
#HASHTAG#
ðŸ–¤Chicago Hope*

*yeah, yeah i know there was a show with that title in the 90s. still witty though. ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm listening to Reunion - Life Is a Rock (But The Radio Rolled Me) - 104.3 K-Hits Chicago 
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# it must be good to be naturally in an upbeat mood. one of the many reasons why Grumpy Shaun likes you. :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# a poignant season with the death of Mr. Ilitch. ðŸ˜¢ and I hate that corporate name for the new stadium. LOL #HASHTAG# ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# no such thing as fair play in politics. Gorsuch is cool but the GOP would have done the same to Garland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I'm not into moons. Unless she's not wearing anything under her jeans. ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# because all black women are queens and can do no wrong. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yay Obama! Yay Quinn! #HASHTAG# rock! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm ok at the moment. Hru? How's your son doing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# i hope so! that would be a funny hashtag! LOL

#HASHTAG# the saccharin of airlines ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#
Mariah Carey as Maria von Trapp in "The Sound of Music"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# you're obtuse asf if you really think that meeting a famous person or following news stories about them equates to KNOWING them. ðŸ™„

i'll bet you don't have Ingraham's personal phone number.

but since you women like to have the last word, i'll allow you do the predictable and...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# 
I deleted the bitch's number years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# hey John! i'm not as far right as i was 2 years or even a year ago but i still maintain many conservative sensibilities with a dose of pragmatism. Artman is the most pragmatic progressive i know. 

yet we still have respectful, spirited disagreements.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Kimmy is good Pisces!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# but, but, but...I thought the #HASHTAG# loved black folks #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i disgaree. LOL this is 2017. paying for porn is played out. ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm still Conservative. but no longer far right. The far right has been co- opted by Trumptards and white nationalists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We'll hold off for now. I gotta read up on Gerald Rivers. Never heard of any allegations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Uncle Joe? You're on the Trump Train now? ðŸ˜ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Shittt, I'm ready for hockey PRESEASON!!! ðŸ’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# all in fun. LOL kudos to you for being consistent with your libertarianism. ðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 1:40am...and I just heard more gunshots. The rewards of living around black people in Chicago. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# hello Shauna. ðŸ’ I'm Shaun. ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you are so funny! lemme stop flirting before i begin making you think i'm obsessed. don't wanna scare my buddy off. ðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yup. 2012 was the precursor to 2016. losing Don Cornelius, Whitney Houston, Dick Clark, Donna Summer and Sherman Hemsley in a 5 month span.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm listening to Billy Joel - Big Shot - 104.3 K-Hits Chicago 
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# those weren't the thongs i was talking about but ok HAHA ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yes they sure have! press "0" and the message repeats. pinche comemierdas!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i thought Republicans were about less government intrusion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# with the exception of death threats I'll never defend Trump. He's not one of us. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 
Deplorables vs. deplorables. makes me hungry for pizza! ðŸ•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER#
#USER# 
#HASHTAG# Brothers!!!

Let's FILET DEM FISH!!!! #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# IJS if i'm gonna watch a fine woman enjoy the D i'd like to HEAR her enjoying the D. ðŸ‘¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 
"Chizza" sounds like the next weird celebrity baby name. ðŸ¤¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# happy belated birthday. i usually don't tweet celebs but just wanted you to know that DJH and DH were important parts of my childhood. ðŸ‘ŒðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# this is a good thing, right? ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Jordans, Playstations, weaves, rims, iPhones, iPads, etc. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# hey. you never responded to my DM from yesterday. ðŸ˜‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I didn't know TVs had that capability nowadays. Wow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don is a no for me then as well. 

no ban. no TECH. still creepy even by 1970s standards but he remains one of our old school icons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# i like thongs too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Crockett is/was our boy. but we may have to consider ban. we banned Ted Nugent for similar reasons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you're a Trump supporter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# not sure how often but for a while they were overdoing it with "Bohemian Rhapsody" too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i wanted to see the vote happen and see it FAIL so that Trump is humiliated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This ancient mofo? ðŸ˜†ðŸ˜…

Although I'm not a Democrat, I agree his running would risk gifting them that coveted seat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i'm cynical too. i haven't attended church in 8 years. if i ever go back it'll be just to meet women. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#
Dirty Dancing Machine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# how did I miss this one? ðŸ˜ I live in South Shore. I appreciate your prayers for my neighborhood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# you're free to not use whatever language as you see fit on your Twitter page.

on my Twitter page, i speak as i like.

thank you...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Ex-GOP like a mofo ðŸ˜  well you warned me. I'll do my best to prepare for the orange shit to hit the fan ðŸ˜”ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# 3-0 #HASHTAG#. Since it's just the preseason I'm gonna go ahead and say it: one more goal and I'm calling it! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you know typical black people. we're supposed to hate the rich because we're so oppressed. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I thought liberals were against bullying #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# that's too much to sit through just to meet single women ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I envy you ðŸ˜„ although you weren't old enough to enjoy the disco nightlife like Tony,  you still caught the kids edition of "Fever"!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# my Conservative princess. even if i found her she'd be a Trumptard by now anyway. ðŸ’”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 
P.S. i wasn't flirting or anything, just giving a well-deserved compliment. ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# somebody got shot a couple blocks away as usual. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# 
I don't think I should drink another liter of #USER# today.

#HASHTAG# ðŸ’ŠðŸ’‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#
Off-duty sheriff's deputy fatally shoots robbery suspect at Englewood salon #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS!!!!!!!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# you supported him too? not gonna diss ya or anything. just wondered because we talk cats more than politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm so glad you're back. I thought you had left permanently. Did someone attack you on here? ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ðŸ˜”

Happy Thanksgiving and see y'all Saturday when we MAUL DEM PANTHERS ðŸ± (maybe)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# seriously, black people in the inner city are so benevolent and peaceful. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Ok the #HASHTAG# took a 4-0 lead before surrendering a goal.

Technically that's a 4 goal rule occurence. So I'm calling it for the good guysðŸ˜ðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 
Sheriff Rosco P. Coltrane is more qualified than this clown. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# about 8 or 9 inches here in the Ghetto on South Shore Drive â˜»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# the next time I go on a date I'll spit on her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "but, but, but Conservatives can't be racist!"n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#
Who's That Liberian Girl?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# black people destroying their own neighborhood. That'll bring #HASHTAG# back from the dead. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Muslim who once was a spokesman for St. Ides malt liquor. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# on second thought today's college chicks would be young enough to be my daughters. nevermind. i'll bang the cafeteria ladies ðŸ‘µðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# **hands shotgun to Deebs** time to set up a perimeter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# darned nails. ðŸ˜¦well the blue looks great on ya ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i'd rather be killed by a white person because people will actually care enough to give me a hashtag. #HASHTAG# LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# your mom should be raped for birthing you, inbred Trumptard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# oh my. ðŸ™
i've put this off because i've had the exact workup done before w/ a different doc and know what's gonna happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm so glad i never followed this guy. to those of you that do, move away from this ASAP. he epitomizes the #HASHTAG#. ðŸ‘ŽðŸ¾ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#
Beat It Street]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tell us how you really feel, Six LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ðŸ˜¢ oh I'm sorry about your cousin. It can be difficult for some of us to manage .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i hope you have a wet dream about Bill Clinton and Barney Frank...in G-STRINGS!!!!

#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# for now. i'll be sick and off of Twitter again in a few weeks though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# one day we will indulge in Jell-o shots.

I was horrible at drawing as a kid yet always enjoyed those large crayon collections]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yup that's how my visit with Santa ended in 1983 when I mentioned cute feets. ðŸ˜„ðŸ˜†ðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# damn! a lady gets away to the Orgeon coast to clear her mind and gets sick. :-( so unfair!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# God bless Woodie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# if #HASHTAG#'s name wasnBerkisha Perkins, she would be. you know black people can do no wrong #HASHTAG##HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# GOP = Grand Ole Pedophile (in his case)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# YOU. ARE. CRAZY. LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ðŸ˜‡ poor Phil Hartman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 
my East Texas Princess is (or was, depending on when you see this tweet) trending in Chicago!â£ðŸ’“ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 

Chicago Shaun vs. Lizzy From The Bay: Strictly Business!!!! 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# damn skippy. we grown. it's SHIT FUCK MOTHERFUCK all day, everyday! LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i still get goosebumps watching that. it's amazing how theme songs or jingles can trigger fond memories]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# my rep and both us senators are Dems. Chicago gonna Chicago. ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# are already up 4-0 in the 2nd period. 

So everyone gets the night off! ðŸ˜„ðŸ˜ƒ I'm calling it!!! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i'm the Cat Whisperer. ðŸ±ðŸ‘…and if you drink solo hopefully you take some pics. so we can see you in your tipsy glory!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I try. ðŸŽ© Although I must warn you sometimes my tweets are a bit raunchy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# you didn't care for Wendy's old fries? before they switched to the seasalted skin-on fries they have now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# we've got the #HASHTAG#/#HASHTAG# at some point. Screw the #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# hi neighbor. ðŸ˜Š I hope you're having a good weekend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I also hate the new name for White Sox park. Guaranteed Rate Field. ðŸ˜£ðŸ‘Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm maintaining. Can't complain. I'm still waiting on an act of Congress or an act of God to take out Trump. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# good for them. good for her. i'm still not moved. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# DISCLAIMER: Chicago Shaun Is Not Into Anal Sex In Real-Life. Never Tried It. Never Will. But He Enjoys Making Nasty Jokes About It. ðŸ¤£ðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yikes. LOL 

Another one that people don't realize is a goof is "butt naked". It's actually "buck naked".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# what i should or shouldn't eat. 
then again, i eat the wrong stuff so perhaps i need a reminder.

#HASHTAG# ðŸ’ŠðŸ’‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# they are gorgeous!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# some people are just insensitive or don't realize their words are insensitive. to me "someone has it worse than you" = "get over it". ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm writing in Professional Massage as an option for Alika Hope's Day Off. 

You work hard everyday. #HASHTAG# ðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# duly noted. i will not poke fun at your religion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She's too young for the list! ðŸ˜‚ I may as well add Drake ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤£ðŸ˜†]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I saw your tweet about Utah. How da hell y'all go from 80 degrees to SNOW in 24 hours!!!!!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lizzy!!! â£wow that really hit me in my fuzzy warm spot in my chest!!!ðŸ’‹ðŸ’‹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# black women think about George W. Bush when their partners impregnate them. Yep. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i thought democrats were tolerant and caring people. #HASHTAG# i avoid wearing my anti-Obama tees now for fear of being shot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# but I thought the Democrats cared about the little people #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# WHOA! SAY WHUT!!!? How did Beck go from being a Trump critic to a Bannonite? ðŸ˜¯ðŸ˜®ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# dumbass still thinks I'm a liberal ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i'd leave...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# even when you tweet about the smell of your balls? LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It'd be very embarrassing too. Worse than hitting your shirt. I cringe whenever a flock of geese or birds fly over my head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# and subsequent primary and general election wins. I took stock of the bonds broken &amp; realized that wasn't the place for me any longer  (2/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 dead, 4 shot on South Side...way to go, black folks #HASHTAG#://t.co/HXOHenuHn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Which means that the remaining few do.

I just don't want to jump on any bandwagons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Severe Thunderstorm Warning for Northeastern Illinois tonighy. And I have no one to snuggle up with. Argh.

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it safe to ummute the football fans or should I give it a day or two?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 
#HASHTAG#
Cicely Tyson
Aretha Franklin
Stevie Wonder
Harry Belafonte
Sidney Pointier
James Earl Jones
Al Jarreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I thought liberals cared about black people. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# that if u don't "talk black" or "act black", you'll make only a few friends &amp; have fewer girls interested in you. â˜¹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# we know 2017 will pick up where 2016 leaves off. we just need a break. ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 

lick-spittle sounds like...nevermind I'll be good ðŸ˜‡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#
Christmas Day 1986. #HASHTAG# everywhere!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# other than my monthly illness, nothing is going on. however when i'm sick i don't have the energy to communicate and that's when ppl worry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# aaaaaw you are sweet. I'm hanging in there. Hru?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The IT department was monitoring what websites i visited. Even after hours off the clock. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm listening to Cheap Trick - Surrender - The Drive 97.1FM on The Drive 97.1FM with TuneIn. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if "PP" stands for "Pretty Pussy", then #HASHTAG# 
otherwise...no ðŸ–•ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm listening to Tears for Fears - Head Over Heels - 104.3 K-Hits Chicago
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# 
"Be the change you wish to see in the world." - Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# my cats are seniors. ðŸ˜» they are stuck with me til I die or they die. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ok cool i'll keep that in mind. truthfully i would like to adopt a male so Sterling has someone to do "guy cat stuff" with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ok. understood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm always learning new stuff about Mom. She was #HASHTAG# before it was in style! ðŸ‘¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Ku Klux Klan is shooting black folks in the ghetto again huh?n#HASHTAG# n#HASHTAG##HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I love Whitney but she wasn't in chronic pain like the others. She was a functioning addict who zigged instead of zagged one time too many and UNsafelisted herself

Birthday tribute coming in August. Get those raw jokes ready. ðŸš«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# go to bed! and put some swears on ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i respect your feelings on the matter. i coudn't be a Dem because of how they treated me over Obama in 2008. but i understand your choice. ðŸ’™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# what's that supposed to mean? trying to say black people don't taste good!? RACIST!!!! UNGH!!!!!! *LMAO* #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# one of these days I'll kick-off another game. meh...

have a good weekend guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# WHAT!!!!!!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# i just reported that guy for harassing you. why do you follow this guy? he is very disrespectful. typical of a Trumptard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# that's where i bought my current old ass PC during the last days of the Bush Administration. LOL i like #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i billed this last night as The Sellout vs. The Fossil. either way, something's gonna give. LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# oh yeah that's going WAY WAY back. i love my birthplace but it's rough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# i think it's too late. there's no going back with the GOP and Trumpism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you still watch #USER# huh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#
Say, Say, Say Anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# right...because black people are so loving &amp; kind to each other as it is.n#HASHTAG##HASHTAG# n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# consider the source. a nigga that ain't combed his hair since Truman was President. fuck hoe ass Don King.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# if i wanted to be a poltical sheep i would have supported Obama years ago. i became Conservative to escape that only to...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ALIKA!!!!!!!? you just said a bad word!!! **GASP**

P.S. some of us males like big lips **clears throat** #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# the Sally Jessy Raphael look is en vogue for 2017. ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# we've put THE BAND back together! ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# let's get back in the swing of things!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#
Janie's Got A Red Ryder BB Gun ðŸŽ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm listening to The Goâ€Goâ€™s - We Got the Beat - 104.3 K-Hits Chicago 
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# amen sista! next time that happens to you, you should key their vehicle. LMAO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# is your deal with McDonalds exclusive or are there possibilities of partnerships with Burger King, White Castle, etc.?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# 

**waves at #USER#**]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ðŸ˜„ðŸ˜„thanks Lisa! I guess with a Santa hat on I look less mean ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# it happens to the best of us. i'm sure you're doing 3 other things at once while tweeting so it's one of those things. ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# understood. well it goes without saying that i want all of our furballs to find new homes. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# watching my George Foreman grill gather dust 

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>