<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe I'm being weird, but I can't read about all white couples anymore. I can read Black/White couples and Black Interracial couples? But a whole white couple? NOPE!nnAnd isn't the authors fault. Its mine! After a lifetime reading all white couples I can't do it anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a white artist draws a Black person but clearly just changed the colors to brown and called it a good old day. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, it can.  Just because it's opinion doesn't mean it's factual or it's beyond criticism.  Now, I am going to pour myself two drinks and you can further tell your readers that they can't feel safe enough to leave honest reviews on products they paid hard-earned money for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They are times when I read a book, that the book is so good that it makes me doubt my own ability as writer. What's the point if I'll never be that good? But the thing is, I don't need to be. All I have to do is try to tell the best story I can &amp; someone will find value in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am so jealous that I can't afford to pay an artist to do art for my books. I hate being poor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way they are writers out there that hate to read books is a paradoxical mindfuck that I will never understand. You don't have to be a bookworm but to not read at all? Especially in your own genres? That is a mindset I will never understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Honestly, purity culture bullshit just fucks over teenagers and makes them less able to make healthy sexual and romantic choices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still struggle with imposter syndrome. It's kind of hard not to when you know so many great authors. You have to remember that I was too scared to even DREAM of being a writer. When you are disabled having the course to DREAM about something like that seems impossible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Just to clarify: When using an umbrella term to refer to first nation folks, is the word Indigenous a better term to use to be inclusive?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Sorry, I became obsessed for a while so I have done tons of research on him. So I can babble a lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Honestly, I don't believe in talking shit to readers (unless they are really out of pocket) in fanfic. But a lot of these authors really think that writing is above the law of business: You do not piss off your customers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The best hashtag for this #HASHTAG# but I have found just outright asking for recs is the best way to not only give marginalized authors a chance to advertise their books but it gives you a whole bunch of recs. Honestly, this is why I don't depend on twitter alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I get the biggest imposter syndrome when I'm writing anything SFF. I think why I have been dragging my feet with any longer stories. Because I keep hearing my high school dude bro "friends" telling me I was too unintelligent to get DnD and fantasy books.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[NSFW] I thought that Korean BDSM drama was risque but no Thailand always got to show up and show out. This is a M/M BDSM drama and I'm going to die from a heat stroke. ðŸ¥µ#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me clear things up. I do not agree with the anti-human sentiment in fantasy. I was mostly venting about the vampire/normal human trope. Because I can count on one finger that the times I actually don't find the human boring af.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Are you serious? Tristan and Isolde? Talk about REACHING.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I'm writing the Patreon extra shorts for Joneses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, I agree and I got so much pushback. You need to study the genre and see what works and what doesn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaking on trends: if you ever wanted to write short fiction? There has never been a better time. The popularity of novellas and short serialized books in general is just going to rise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is best nicely worded professional "fuck you, I do what I want" I have ever read. How they are not dropping members like flies is a mystery to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to get mad just scroll through the op's comments. They are people actually defending the Nazis in this the OPs comments.  #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# SERIOUSLY.  I would be mad as hell if I paid all that money to fly out there for you to give me some motivational speaking and you are dressed like you are about to go shoot some hoops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And some First nation folks like to pretend like some of ya'll ancestors didn't enslave some of our ancestors. Ya'll also likes to pretend that black native folks don't exist.  Yet, beyond that, some of you are still thinking with a colonizer's mindset.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi, am the only one who has been FURIOUS since the pandemic began, and since you can't start wh*pping anti-vaxxers asses in the streets all you can do is let that shit just fester to the point that it is fucking with your mental health?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First of all, this has to be said: sex work is work. And I'm asexual but would I give a blow job for millions of dollars? Yes. Because the 5 mins of discomfort would be worth not having to live in poverty and providing generational wealth for my family. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The answer to this question really depends if you are Indie or trad, what you can physically and mentally handle, and what your goals are within publishing. 
I'm going for 4 books this year. I published 2 last year. Now, will accomplish my goal? Who knows?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to say the same I said about Matrix 4 that I said about sense8. The plot only makes sense to Lana and that is typical of her work. The true gems of her style as a filmmaker are the characters.  If you not here for character arcs you going to dislike Lana's work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know what January means? Author brand audit. 

Lord help me. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently France is banning Halal and Kosher meats to really make Muslims and Jewish folks choose between breaking the core tenants of their faiths or starve. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a nervous wreck today. I got a 1k of writing  in and I'm going be glad I got even that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes! I can't be John Oliver but I can burn it still.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I actually like it but that is because I know Lana's style very well and her plots only sense to her in her head (see Jupiter Ascending). If you just watch it for the entertainment value and for the characters its enjoyable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have been reading 'Newslettet Ninja' by Tammi L. Labrecque. And the one thing I learned is that I have been treating my newsletter like a writing journal/book notification thing. I should be treating it more like another social media platform/networking tool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hunty, what an abelist talking point! Also, if you would know do 10 mins of research body shape or size does not automatically make someone unhealthy.  The BMI is a fucking scam, and y'all could care less about skinny folks living the most unhealthy lifestyle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So we cut to a crowded convention center in Vegas and filled  to the brim with white cis presenting women. And yeah, in age of omricon: no and hell no!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That is such a sweet deal. Honestly, you are so lucy. I have been saving like a mofo for my novella.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing that keeps me going back to Rachel and Dave Hollis is that a picture perfect example of the rich white privilege and the fallacies of white feminism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could be an author for a lifetime and still learn something new. The learning curve never stops twisting, my friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sex in Joneses is goddamn hot that its giving 'The Devil's Bargain' a run for its money. I nearly had a heart attack writing these sex scenes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, I think people worry so much about trying to get an agent and a contact that they don't focus on what comes after. And that is one of the reasons authors should not be looking at getting an agent and a contract as a sign of social status with the book comm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to thank everyone who signed up for my giveaway. I randomly picked a winner and I will be emailing them soon.  Thank you all so much for your support. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks at my upcoming Death god monstefucking romance and cackles. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ San Antonio, Texas #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Chile, I remember getting shit for reading romance in high school from my geek dudebro friends and they were reading Forbidden Realms books.  The hypocrisy never ends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Awwww thank you! I'm working really hard on my new books and I can't wait to share them with you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If you want some hot monsterfucking erotica? Then you should read my debut erotica 'The Devil's Bargain'
ðŸ˜ˆ Black MC.
ðŸ”¥Demons
ðŸ˜ˆDubious Consent
ðŸ”¥Informal D/s
ðŸ˜ˆBad BDSM Etiquette
ðŸ”¥Implied Mpreg
ðŸ˜ˆBreeding Kink
ðŸ”¥Tail Kink

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I usually buy my clothes online so I am not all that worried about it.  But I have a heavy-ass bariatric wheelchair and I'm worried about having to squeeze my big fat but there is no real rep on youtube or hell in the wheelchair community for fat folks and I'm frustrated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm not going to lie, I love dragging the really offensive bad romance takes like that TIME article on Monday. But also, pointing out a legitimate flaw in the genre is not a bad thing and but apparently you have to be a long term Romance reader to give legitimate criticism. ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Your welcome. Its seems every high fantasy show I watch has a racism and colonism allegory. And we BIPOC folks are tired and I can't not imagine how Jewish and Roma people must feel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queerbaiting only refers to non-canon couples. If a couple is canonically queer, it's not queerbaiting. But yes, what Witcher is doing absolutely queerbaiting. The show is absolutely using queer fans enthusiasm over Geraskier while at the same denying that Queer people exist. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I need to do more off Twitter networking and I'm working on that right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also if you are Black MCU fan and you were outraged at the anti-blackness exhibited in this fandom this BMH but yall are quiet about the harassment Roma people are getting for speaking out on the whitewashing of their culture then you are part of the problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two white women getting high and talking about how their mental illness is a super power. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, I totally agree! It pretty much ignores the romance and talks about the historical part.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think it can be both. For example, I am aesthetically attracted to nightcrawler from X-men and The dark lord from the movie Legend. But also my own trauma has feed a lot into my interest into monsterfucking. It doesn't help I'm a myth nerd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The movie 'Friday' was such staple in so many Black households that I could probably drop a line from it with no context in any Black american household and they would immediately get it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# NTA! Nat really is the type of person that I can't stand. Will do all the performative shit in the world but when it's time to take a step back and listen (which is what real allies do) she stomps her feet and get her Karen on. The OP did the right thing by dumping her!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I had a very good source who works with computers find his real name and history. They did not dox them to me, but they did very good outline of Damon and his husband's real history. So I do have a lot context to his rise to power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look, I believe in giving queer couples all the pets.  Cat, dogs, bearded dragon? Yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My kids are playing in the same room and I will be reading the raunchiest shit.  I used to feel bad about it but idgaf anymore. Besides, I keep my kindle password protected for a reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have quiet a lot of mutuals following her and honestly I'm too tired to unfollow them one by one. I would be here all day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun fact: Calling black people colonizers or settlers is anti-black as hell and is erasing all the afro-indigenous people out there. Also American black folks are the descendants  of indigenous African folks that were kidnapped from their land and brought here in chains.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll go first! Brenda Jackson, Jayce Ellis, Meka James, Aveda Vice, Anne Rice, Kelly Armstrong, L.A. Banks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They really set an example on how to be in a relationship but also how to end it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I said it once and I'll say it again: Most writing advice is written by neurotypicals for neurotypicals. Don't get frustrated if some writing advice doesn't work for you. Just take what you can use and discard the rest. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a trash monarch and I was wondering what best-selling author Rachel Hollis was doing. Apparently, she just had another RISE conference and she is wearing a flannel shirt over a t-shirt, basketball shorts, and some Jordans like she is a teenage boy from the 90s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly I'm a bit mixed with the Matrix. I love the first movie, was meh about the 2nd movie, and hated the last one. I'm not taking it too seriously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly, I have the best mutuals in the world and I am blessed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aisha Tyler narrated this and this makes me feel some type of way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh, trans misgyonists are so unoriginal and weak sauce. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# To the playlist? The tweet is mostly a headcanon that I probably never going to write.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Thank you so much! I'm going to check it out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I also find this hilarious because I know quite a few married folks whose entire job is to write about and look at attractive men all day. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's just really telling when authors who think their shit don't stink and is dismissive of the genres they belong to are put on pedestals. The moral of the story is read more widely and read your intended genres, please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I plan on eating my weight in Christmas cookies and reading Witcher smut? Yes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I was like ooh cheap affordable housing. But I thought about the pandemic and being trapped there for lockdown. And nooooo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You would not know Black atheists, Pagans, Jewish folks, Muslims, and every other religion exists. We all must be Christan (and in particular protestant Christan) or we are not Black enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I watched the behind the scenes featurette for season 2 and everyone is talking about Geralt's grief but no one is addressing the queer elephant in the room.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey indigenous folks. I tend to not get in y'alls business. But this shit with Reservations Dogs and cultural appropriation is becoming Black business.nnSo if I see yall being anti-Black or ignoring how Black Indigenous peoples thoughts and feelings about this?nnBLOCKED.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The way that Harry looks at Meghan with full hearts in eyes. Like she hung the entire moon? And then you see this shit. Chile, talk about reaching!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing hotter than a hot Black man in a tuxedo. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And before y'all start on my typos and grammar fails: I'm dyslexic.  And this forced font is hell on my writing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's very telling that its white folks (in particular white women) who are getting up in arms about this. Who are condescending to me like I haven't run a business before. They are so used to sliding in on priviledge alone that they don't realize a lot of us got to work for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Books that she had obvious distaste for. And I still want to hulk out and smash everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The goal of my patreon is to get enough money where I can cover the bills of my author business so I won't be paying out pocket. If I can get over $100 a month hump that will be a big help in covering editing and advertising costs. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Question: You know that mom and pop store down the street from you. The people who saved up and worked and scrapped together every penny just to open a store. Do you approve of stealing from those stores? Would you rob those stores? if the answer is no then you are hypocrite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$500 and up to simply put a tarp on a 1700 square foot roof? Lol, repair people are tripping!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It maybe sexier but I rather not get caught by the po-po.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1) The way y'all treat QTBIP0C folks in the community is quiet frankly disgusting. You are either performative af or you actively erase us. 
2) Romance is for women by women bullshit needs to DIAF. 
3) The way cis women and their entitlement in m/m spaces. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You would never know if you talked to white Australians or by their media. Hell, Indigenous folks barely get a mention and the mention they get is insulting at best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SPOILERS FOR WITCHER SEASON 2
I really want fanfic where Geralt is raising Ciri from the beginning. Can you imagine big hulking Geralt with tiny baby Ciri?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have been reading romances off and on for 20 years and they are so many anti-woman anti-feminist bs that has been peddled in books since the genre's origins. And intersectional wise, there is the blatant racism and bio essentialism that excludes trans and non-binary folks. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I keep to a routine, write what I am truly passionate about, and have regularly scheduled breakdowns. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 2020s is looking like it's going to be a long slog. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nah, y'all can keep that because after the first roll down the stairs, I'm done. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the way, unlike the Cullens. This fictional version of the Quileute tribe has a very real reason for this dislike of vampires.  A vampire tried to massacre the entire tribe simply because one of the wolves killed his mate.  I'm not even kidding you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My muse told me to go fuck myself when I started to work on Death God Summoning so I'm quitting and working on writing the extras stories for Patreon and my subscribers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm almost done with the prep for the last draft of 'Keeping Up With The Joneses' and whew ya'll not ready for the hotness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why I am not surprised? Honestly, I have little hope that queerness even exist in that universe. I'm just going to lean hard its VERY queer fanfic and keep it rolling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will recommend that you compile a media kit similar to what bloggers and influencers use. This should absolutely include all the information you want the press to know about you, your headshots, info about your books, and your social media information. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The thing is no one ever consults from someone who has publishing experience. They just pull shit right out of their asses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The illustration for the romance scenes are awful. I mean I know budget is an issue but my god.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I think you should find out what social media networks work for you and do it. I also keep my notifications and comment settings pretty strict.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think a lot of new age gurus got the law of attraction and manifestation wrong. Magic is not like a magic wand. Magic is not %100 guarantee.  Its just stacking the deck in your favor. It's not your fault if you don't get results. It just wasn't mean't to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am TIRED. I expect this shit from white folks but to get this shit from your skin folk? Its disheartening. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way that Scarlet Witch stans are shitting on Roma people upset at the butchering of their culture is disgusting. You say, "They say this every week." But have you ever thought that they have been saying it so many times because yall refuse to listen. Yall racist ass hell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the seed of everything is anti-blackness and colorism. LGBTQ spaces both in the book community and out have anti-blackness problem. There is reason why the very little Black rep we get with covers are light skinned Black folks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nah, that ruin all the fun.  I like giving my readers ton to choose from.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I could concentrate on one project for longer than 2 weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minorities all across the board but especially Black, Asian, and Jewish folks are just so fucking exhausted right now. We want to just live in peace without a fucking bigot running roughshod over our peace of mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one thing I am doing differently this year is to really have better work/life boundaries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not really. He's a mediocre white boy with delusions of grandeur. ðŸ¤·ðŸ¾â€â™‚ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way that Latinx folks fear the wrath of the Chancla will never stop being funny. I know I'm Black and pot and kettle over here but y'all moms be throwing Chancla like boomerangs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm done with all shorts for 'Keeping Up With The Joneses' and on Monday I start on Death God Summoning.  I'm super excited! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Aww thank you! You are a sweet heart. I'm at a point where it makes me uncomfortable to even look at a LINK of a review for my own books. I retweet because I appreciate it and because it's good promo. But I tend to stay out of reader spaces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# NTA! This is not about the luggage. This is about Ted not putting your first and not snipping his mother's behavior in the bud. Honestly, Ted can't take accountability for himself or hold his family accountable. You need to get out now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silas twisted and turned, fighting against the control, though his body wanted to submit.

â€œStay,â€ the creature growled. The rush of arousal got sharper, clouding his thoughts.

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#+
#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I know a lot of ADHDers who have high book counts (I'm just not one of them) but yeah teachers really need to learn that shit is ableism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because most authors both trad and indie authors are just small businesses. Indies in particular got to put their own money into their small business. And what you are essentially doing is robbing from a small business. DRM content is nuanced issue but supporting...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White women in this community are so used to doing less than the bare minimum and then getting accolades and book sales on white privilege alone and it shows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm trying to find the article and it might have been taken down but I'm about %80 sure that this actually happened and it Anita was the author of that article.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm sorry but if your story takes that long to be good? Then your story is not good. ðŸ¤·ðŸ¾â€â™‚ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Honestly, I do well with small contained spaces so I never wanted a sprawling home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[bell hooks books are really expensive even in ebook form and I think her publisher needs to actually try to make those books more accessible for poor folks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I never knew that horror and romance came from the same place. I know about Gothic horror but it never occured to me that the genres have the same origin in literature.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So there this tiktok video of someone taking their white friend to an all Black thanksgiving and that dude is legit slurping chitlins like its spaghetti. ðŸ¤¢ðŸ¤£ 

It couldn't be me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you are complaining about a WOC being snow white because it's too PC?  Yeah, I'm going to unfriend you and block you. Transcript: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also these are all christian women and no Jewish folks? No Muslims? No pagans? No atheists? You are talking about religious pressure but talking to only Christian's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Goddamn shame. Service people ain't like they used to. I can't even count how many times a mechanic has done a terrible job on a car and expected tons of money for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current Word Count: (Death God Summoning) 5041 / 10000 (50.41%) My kids are home from school and they cut into my writing.  I should have gotten up at 6am and wrote but that is the breaks.  Anyway, I'll make this up on Saturday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People: We are going to rec the top 10 romances of the year.
Me: Arent those same 10 romances you read last year and they are all trad YA/NA romances? 
People: Yes????!
Me: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wait! They let Letitia go but is still giving Crispy Rat voice jobs. ðŸ‘€. I'm not mad at them firing Letitia but I want the same thing for Crispy Rat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I totally will let you know once I got something that is actually readable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh, I can understand that. Not from being biracial Black but from the stand point not feeling Black enough. You don't speak Black enough, you don't dress Black enough, you got interests in things that are not Black. I have been there and it's not a nice place to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would like to do some cross promotion events with some other authors this year. Not a lot but maybe 3 or 4.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I just stopped a draft and switched over to a new project because I know it all needs to be scrapped and rewritten.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ALERT: Someone is trying to impersonate me. They copied everything down even down to my username. My PayPal is theimperialpurple#USER#.com. I think I have been Blocked by this imposter but can y'all please go down this thread and report this person for fraud. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read fanfic. I have learned that if there is a will, fanfic writers will find a way! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't know! I never read the books and I haven't played the games. But my guess that it isnt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As for the rest. BIPOC are not a monolith. I am personally leery of white folks writing BIPOC POV characters. They are very few white authors I trust to do it right. Some, BIPOC don't have a problem with it. But at the end of the day, the biggest things is the reason why.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# small businesses should no brainer. If you have beef with the DRM stuff  you should be taking  that up with Amazon and government local representatives because they are the only ones that can change that. But authors have zero control over that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not going to read this but I just had to let TIME know how much this pisses me off.  You couldn't save these hottakes for February? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not just a criticism of the Witchers but to all fantasy tv shows. It's really telling that you can have incest, sex work, orgies, rape, and all type of sexual things. Somethings that are taboo but the one thing you won't have is queer or trans folks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The smug look on Geralt's face is sending me. He legit gets to fuck a rockstar and the most powerful mage on the continent. 

The lucky bastard. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Whew, I think the whole RWA in 2020 gave me a false idea of what publishing did during December because now I'm like where is everyone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fall Into You for All Love and The Devils Bargain for Dark Erotica and Fantasy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah, you gave me something to think about with next years sales.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could write an essay on why monster romance took off during the pandemic and in many cases it's a direction reaction to the fear and trauma that we are living with right now. It's a fear that we can control and in a lot of ways overcome and make into something positive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is monsterfuckingfriday a new thing because I have a new hashtag to follow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jaskier's rakish makeover is giving me Captain Jack Sparrow vibes and also I want his jacket and waistcoat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2023, I really need to buckle down and publish ruin you. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching the first matrix movie is such a time capsule.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh my fucking god! I can't even.. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That sounds beautiful.  I always loved nature-themed weddings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[Chapter 1] The Devilâ€™s Bargain By Rian Fox #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am always glad to help and I am looking forward to seeing what you create next.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I cringed so much because I just saw the photos of them together on your thread and Kate looked like she was plotting his slow demise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spoilers: #HASHTAG#
This skinny dipping scene seems hella wlw to me. Not gonna lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a natural voyeur so this works well for me. I don't want to participate, I just wanna watch. ðŸ¤·ðŸ¿â€â™€ï¸ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah white people are always so fucking predictable. Death threats are not okay but you act like her fans weren't giving death threats to Austitic people as well. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Barbie got a better house than the rest of us. ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I just heard this argument about doing sales on Facebook. And it doesn't make sense to me. If I'm on a fence about a book, nothing will make me buy it quicker if it goes on sale.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Geralt was going to take Ciri the day of before the invasion and had even warned them. Queen Calanthe was really the worst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Person: Let me tell you how sold thousands of books a month on Amazon on autopilot. 
Me: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Geralt was so terrified of fatherhood but it turns out that he is the best father.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I give you the highest of high fives! I think for me I'm going to stick to 2-3 per project. I think that is doable for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, I am ready for the shit storm my femdom romance is going get. This why I love I don't read reviews because my tran man character in that book is going to be unapologetically trans. And if they have problem with it they can kiss my entire ass. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The pandemic did and still does have a choke hold on my productivity. I write a lot but also I have take breaks because I'm end up always breaking down. I wrote over 150 words but only published two short stories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really wanted to hear Roma people's perspective on all this and wow Marvel basically drained all SW's race, culture, and ethnicity.  I am not really surprised they really mishandled her character from the get-go. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks so much! Its priviledge being on a list with so many awesome authors. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I was kind of skeptical because it's so old school but it really works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I would freak out tbh. Especially since my books lean more to the raunchier side of things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look like someone's gay eccentric aunt, today. And honestly, I love that for me. ðŸ¥° #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With every episode my polyam feelings grow even stronger. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Omg, thank you! I will be buying these come pay day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2022 is truly cursed because he is doing exactly what I knew he would do. He's trying to crawl his way into Romancelandia's good graces. I bet you 10 to 1 this jackass is writing a new book too. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yall someone with a BLM fist in their bio said that Greece has dealt with its colonial past and racism. Like they didnt throw African refugees into the ocean and leave them dead. White Europeans are a trip.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have personally known indie film makers who have their own libraries of movies that they watch so they study them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is it me or is the symbrock vibes off the chain with this trailer. It very much feels like two old married folks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing advice is mostly given from a Neurotypical person's perspective and it is largely ineffective for ND people. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The answer to someone being unemployed or poor is not start your own business. - signed a failed business owner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am able to do what I do with the support to follow my dreams because I have a partner in parenting and tons of help from the older kids. We all pitch in to help each other, to keep the household running. Nuclear families, the wives have all of that responsibility by themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll probably start the editing process for Keeping Up With The Jones in Febuary-March.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oops! I'm so sorry I could have sworn they said it was you and I should have doubled checked that FB post.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't DM your advertising. If you can't advertise through your own feed, reels, and stories then just give it up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hill I die on is that Drag Me Up by R.M. Virtues is the best indie romance book of the year, peridot. I'm not just saying this because he's a friend. I'm saying it because it was OUTSTANDING and it should have gotten a lot more accolades than it did. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was a lesson I had to learn the hard way this year. In the end, a lot of discourses is just pointless. They are some  things I refuse to stay silent about (bigotry for example) but for everything else I block and mute and keep it rolling. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Especially not with her scarlet o'hara style shower curtain Cape.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The African American Baby Book by Tetesa Norman. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spoilers for Matrix 4:
They saved the cat. Can imagine Neo and Trinty just living their lives with their cat Deja Vue. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tried to read the golden compass and chile the racist tropes especially towards the Roma people.  I'm not even surprised. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi. I thought it was high time to bring back this thread. Instead of trying to police who gets to write or consume queer stories. How about y'all tackle the known cishet people within the book community who commit REAL harm on the LGBTQ+ community? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They use a saw.  Sometimes a manual saw, sometimes a chain saw.  I just watched a video and I was shooketh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit to #USER# for bringing this up but I always side eye people who say "Romances should not end with marriage or with having kids."  

You have to understand for queer people the right to marry is very new and in many places non-existent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He's to be fun and then he started feeling himself way too much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If you want to known when the pre-order links drop make sure to subscribe to my email list. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm the starting the year off with some horror books.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think non-authors don't get that the process of publishing a book is literally you writing the same story over and over again until you get to the best possible version of that book. 

This is why a lot of writers don't make it to the publishing stage. It's exhausting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It be your own people. I know you got bills to pay but so do I. ðŸ¤·ðŸ¾â€â™‚ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is what our tax dollars are going to? Seriously, the department of education needs their ass whopped.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>