<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I hear there's plenty of stuff from Ivanka's line left over they can wear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's like saying let's forget Michael Vick used to be involved in dog fighting because he advocates against it now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Sir, why are you stalking me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I literally just said I wasn't a fan of the outfit choices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Some people voted for him because they thought he would legalize it. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You've seen the interview where he said that? I know I heard it &amp; others say they have too but a video can't be found anywhere. It's weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# He did say congrats. Watch the video and look at the soldier's face. You can tell he's uncomfortable. Trump's comment was inappropriate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# all out on Twitter. (2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ Pence wouldn't have to pound the pavement if Trump wasn't such garbage. Biden was lucky. Barack knew how to sell himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# when he became #USER#, that still doesn't explain this: #URL# (2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# (Insert whiny conservatives who were so sure Le Putin would win) ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Were you abused? Is that why you turn to marijuana to ease your pain? ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Everything Trump related is making Obama more popular.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If only you actually cared that he was murdered and not just about who you could pin it on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Be sure to thank the immigrant groundskeepers and housekeepers for keeping it that way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I'm an American citizen and Daniel is right. Trump has been raking it in since he took office. The presidential salary is peanuts compared]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# When coal fumes are better for your lungs than clean air, let me know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He's still trying to making "bigly" happen? ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Maybe something other than an ill-timed photo. Hearing "grab them by the pussy" straight from Trump's mouth wasn't enough for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I wonder if Trump will even try to strong arm Macron again or if he learned his lesson last time. ðŸ¤”ðŸ˜‚ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mental health isn't taken seriously. It won't get any better with cuts to mental healthcare. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# America needs to fire Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Pope Francis is closer to god than Trump could ever hope to be. God doesn't like pussy grabbers, Lynette.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You have copies of their immigration documents? Cool, let me see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well this is a fun little thread of projection/deflection. But Obama, but Hillary, but Susan Rice waaaaaaaaah! ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No, you're specifically ignoring the facts I've given you while demanding more when we both know nothing will be good enough for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is the second time I've seen this and I still don't feel sorry for her. Â¯_(ãƒ„)_/Â¯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# citizens or green card holders? (2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Damn those Muslims again! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There are multiple scenarios that statement could be applied to and they're all equally ridiculous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# be honest, you only welcomed them because they're white.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Further confirmation that our government couldn't care less about us. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Exactly. ðŸ˜‚ #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So Trump isn't worried about Jr perjuring himself. When you've gone your whole life without any kind of consequences, it's not surprising.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You care? That conflicts with your "build the wall" mantra. Besides, I thought you people were all about free guns for everyone. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I thought Trump was the Russian ambassador. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Oh right, those pesky bone spurs that didn't prohibit him from playing sports. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# lol no, you just can't come up with anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I heard about a boy a few years ago who was accepted to all 8. Can't remember what state he was from.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Anyone who has been appointed by Trump should be fired by the new administration. Â¯_(ãƒ„)_/Â¯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# even so, you know the Trump lifestyle hasn't changed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You have refused to release your tax returns numerous times. What are YOU hiding? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# no consent = rape. That's the last I'm going to say. Have a nice day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't worry, Anthony. Nobody thinks Huckabee is attractive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# who cares? They're just muslims. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I thought Republicans didn't like PC. ðŸ¤” The GOP is the party of hypocrites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# he broke the law. Funny how the law only matters if you're anyone but a republican official.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Two boys who will grow up thinking they are entitled to a woman's body because mommy voted for President Pussygrabber.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wait, I thought immigrants didn't work but instead lived freely off of the government. You're saying they have jobs!? ðŸ˜³ #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, out of all of the religious YouTube channels, Google singled his out for being religious. ðŸ˜‚ Sesame Street is more educational than Fox.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# When's the last time a republican took any personal responsibility? ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# since you love his candor so much, you should ask him what he thinks about your appearance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Are you really expecting compassion from Fox viewers? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# They hate being called out on their bullshit. Just one of the many sad reasons they relate to Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So if I show up to a drug deal to purchase weed but I'm sold a bag of oregano instead, did I not still commit a crime? Yes, still a crime. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yesterday, I saw someone defend Trump walking into the Miss USA dressing room while the girls were changing. These people have no morals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# lol okay this is just getting pathetic now. âœŒðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No punctuation either. Grammar is hard? ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I can imagine some annoyed juniors and seniors who wished they'd known a few years ago what they know now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No disagreement here. I just don't believe Trump's heart is in the right place where Syrians are concerned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# They would take our silence as a victory. Hell, they take losing as a victory, as long as he's in the Oval.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# If you don't see a problem with Mike's tweet, then you are a problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Lol Heisenberg is a badass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The lack of maturity and class this administration has is phenomenal. Petulant children are running our country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nah I bet it was a Muslim. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# and if it were a democrat in the same position, you'd be flipping your shit. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Just out of curiosity, do you think the women who accused Cosby are lying too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# In their day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He received more votes than the republicans. But then again, we see what that gets you in this country now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Can you imagine what kind of word we would live in if everyone had that kind of attitude? It would be a much sadder place than it already is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Still cutting Medicaid, though. Oh, and don't think you're safe just because you have a job. BCRA repeals employer mandate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# how many people in the crowd were married and related?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# When has Trump ever taken responsibility for anything? ðŸ¤” it's always Obama this, Hillary that, Democrats blah blah blah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ Sue me. Please try. Really. I'd get a kick out of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# then why do you follow them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# yeah but they're muslim so who cares? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Do you even know anyone who's Muslim?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Stop trying to make Bernie happen, he's not going to happen. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# My comment wasn't even about your appearance, it was about your maturity level. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# game. It's our lives. He just isn't the right guy for the job. (2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There's a person there? All I see are police kneeling on the ground... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# because he didn't win the popular vote. (2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# to do business, maybe he's not the right guy for the job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Right, I'm sure you were ready for the Benghazi investigation to be wrapped up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# They're only upset that they're not getting their wall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ you blindly follow Trump as if he were Manson but okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Has France learned from our mistakes? Probably not. Good luck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Good for Andrew. Everyone knows now. About time his wife left him, too. If you're expecting me to defend him because he's a dem, it's not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He gave $110B worth of weaponry to a country he claimed was responsible for 9/11 though. How does that make sense?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Jr's twitter war will only hurt him in the end. I hope Kushner goes down with the rest of them, but as far as optics, he's stayed bts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Does Ivanka make lingerie? Her cheap China-made shit should be highly flammable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I'm sure she doesn't. She took a lot of heat during her husband's 8 years but I never saw it phase her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# lol the only difference is I feel bad for the hamster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# lol fucking cry about it. She has no problem with her daddy disrespecting women. Speaks to her character.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#
Oh the wonderful magic of the internet ðŸ™ŒðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# what everyone really wants to know is: was he Muslim? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Excuse me if "grab em by the pussy" and mocking the disabled don't get a free pass. He's not just a bad president, he's a bad person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# products are made overseas. (2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# that's his "hmph" face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Fox could live air Trump defecating on his desk and his followers would set their DVRs like #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# these people have no compassion. It's disgusting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Happy Birthday to one of the best presidents we've ever had. A true leader, loving husband &amp; father. Here's to many more, sir. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I saw a Trumpster profile that had "atheist" in their bio. I thought I was in the twilight zone. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You people always redirect to the same thing. ðŸ˜‚ No valid answer for Lori so you revert back to your illusion of winning. Sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# none of his supporters can defend this so all we hear are crickets from the right. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# by assuming they're all terrorists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Why is no one talking about this? I'd never heard about it until just now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Trump will be impeached before you ever see a vagina in person. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# have you seen his approval rating? This is the truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# oh please, Pence is just biding his time until he can become number 46.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Give it a rest, Ryan. You're even more untrustworthy than Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why is this so funny? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Babies love being born unwanted and uncared for. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're more upset at Ken for leaving you than you are about the people who died in Charlottesville. This is who you are. Not fit to be prez.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Ivanka seems the strongest of the bunch. Poke the rest with a stick and they'd squeal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# No one has been talking about Clinton in this thread but thanks for bringing him in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There has been an attack at a black church because, you know, white supremacy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# maybe if my dad had a million bucks laying around that I could borrow, but he didn't. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ okay that was funny, you win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ðŸš¨ Russian troll alert ðŸš¨]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He's disappointed that they're not all little pawns on the chess board he calls his presidency. 

Assuming he knows how to play chess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Is that a question? Usually there's a question mark at the end of a question. It's okay, Wendy. I know grammar isn't your strong suit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Or inflicted by another Trump supporter. Starving rats in a cage will start to eat each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# How do you defend that? He's had time to retract and he hasn't. He's never shown remorse for any of his behavior. And yes, he did mock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# When is it this administration's turn?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That would mean admitting parts of the ACA do work and you know they aren't going to do that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been a week and this is what you come back with? ðŸ˜‚ I'm not perfect, Marion. I'm educated. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TIME 1. You're not a woman
2. You're not black

You wouldn't understand how difficult it is to find makeup suited for a dark skin tone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Someone should explain to Jr what actually happen. A "I tried to fuck her but she was married" analogy comes to mind. Not enough characters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Google found one incident 7 years ago. What do you have?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I like how he jumped to the racism by assuming she watches The Real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tHaT's BeCaUsE tHe MaJoRiTy Of AmErIcAnS aRe StUpId. KiNdA lIkE yOu (insert retarded Spongebob) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# isn't impeached first. (2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Like father, like son? So your dad lets people die on his watch, too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# lol you were triggered by a word.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Woah there, Dan. Criticizing the police is a quick way to get kicked off the Trump train.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Leave it to Faux News to give Kellyanne "alternative facts" Conway screen time. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# How will you explain to your children that you voted for a man who bragged about sexually assaulting women? Just curious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well your original statement sounds eerily similar to Trump's statement about rape in the military.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's buddy, Jeff Epstein, gets away with raping a child. But you won't see MSM reporting about it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# His rose comes with a side of domestic assault. You don't want it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And Pearl Harbor was just an extension of Call of Duty. This administration sure loves our military. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Don Jr had attempted to rob a gas station but the safe had just been emptied, did he commit a crime?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# because everything is muslims fault, right? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# When you say something they can't argue with, their hardware malfunctions and they need reprogramming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# there are a lot of reasons victims don't come forward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Trump made it relevant when he claimed to "know more than the generals".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It was a slap in the face to our Navy seals when Trump blamed Ryan Owen's death on them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Awh, poor Jeff. He really thought Trump cared about anyone but himself and Ivanka. Bless his heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Saying he has sex in common with his daughter = creepy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# maybe if you ask, they'll put body cameras on ICE officers and broadcast it for your comedy hour. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# All I see if you continuing to attack Obama and Clinton while having no defense of Trump. ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If only this country believed everyone deserved an equal opportunity in education.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# We weren't talking about you. We were talking about the woman who claimed Trump had one of the highest IQs of our presidents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ You win Twitter tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That ripple guy blocked me so one less bot to deal with. ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ okay, act like you know me. It's worked so well for others. Lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The rapture could not come soon enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Would you still believe it if they claimed a lower rating or would you cry fake news?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Barron is 10 or 11, yeah? I'm surprised they only have one. Then again, have to wonder if Trump is really the dad because of his age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# nah, I was saying you used those words, I didn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It's likely the ones so against trans have never even met one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸš¨ Russian troll alert ðŸš¨ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# He needs time to fabricate evidence. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Who are you to decide how a family should mourn a loved one? You're no one. Take a seat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Obviously she doesn't understand too well or she would have told daddy the travel ban was a bad idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# One day, the Trump administration is going to bite you in the ass. Whether directly or indirectly. I promise I'll try not to laugh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Princess Sweatshop desperately trying to find a life jacket on this sinking ship. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not one person, who I directed this question to, can or will answer it. ðŸ˜‚ #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yes, Eric, please help. Drugs are only illegal if the person using/selling is here illegally. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# And yet, no accusations against Joe either. ðŸ¤”ðŸ˜‚ Nice try, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# so you're saying there wouldn't be any rape without illegals?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# but only Muslims and Mexicans are bad... #HASHTAG# Russia is not and will never be our friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# what does he have planned for the rapist who were born here? (2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are legal gun owners so afraid of stricter gun laws? ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Trump loves the poorly educated. Lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I pray this woman survives the character assassination that's coming her way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Your retweets say otherwise but anyway, have a good night. ðŸ¤—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Obama was not born rich so please tell me how he worked his way up to presidency by never working a day in his life. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If you watch the video, he pulls his fist back before she goes for his throat. Not defending either one but it looked like self defense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Without space suits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Remember the days when Fox was the most reliable place to get your news from? Me either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# that little boy at the town hall meeting saw this coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# even if you believe it's just talk, how can you stand behind a man who would even say those things? Grab them by the (1)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think I paid the electric bill. I guess that means I did. Hey, where did the lights go!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# There's nothing humorous about the ignorance of today's adults but I still get a laugh out of you people sometimes. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How sad that he still has to appeal to his supporters by giving Obama the finger at every turn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Last time I checked, no one was gassing our homeless people. Just stabbing them to death with a sword in NYC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How about Eric Trump saying Democrats "aren't even people"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# not even remotely the same thing but nice try.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# can you tell Trump that? Thanks. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# BREAKING NEWS: Trump Jr, Manafort, Kushner given opportunity to perjure themselves with zero consequences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sessions granddaughter was born in Hawaii? She must be Muslim! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We are gathered here today to mourn the death of democracy.*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# blame when the outcome is less than spectacular. (2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yes, your comeback is weak. But it's okay, I didn't expect you to have a valid reply.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# shouldn't that be something you ask yourself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Like clockwork.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's easy to tell which side a person has chosen by looking at their retweets. None of us knows what happened to Seth but thanks for /1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah, us liberals are big fans of "alternative facts". ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #HASHTAG#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>