<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["No such broad conflict exists among today’s nobility. They are unified in their progressive outlook on all things…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["5. A decrease in scheduled activities for kids" #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Promoting competition—rather than regulating content moderation—will reduce the power of any one firm to influence…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Although it might seem like there is a cabal of liberals purposefully trying to infiltrate the last few…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["“The actions that your administration is taking to target federal employees who have applied for a religious…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This split has been acrimonious at times. The culture warriors have been fiercely hostile toward the…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In essence, Western governments have initiated a silent campaign to "find and replace" freedom with democracy in…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Former Secretary of State Mike Pompeo said that people’s responses to religious liberty threats demonstrated that…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Coercion is becoming ubiquitous in medicine. It’s not just vaccine mandates. Doctors, nurses, and pharmacists who…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it is not offensive, it is probably not worth believing.

—Pr. Larry Peters
Pastoral Meanderings (October 30, 2021)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden Nominates Pro-Abortion Advocate as Papal Ambassador: Today’s Read #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Religious Liberty Initiative interim director Nicole Stelle Garnett, the John P. Murphy Foundation Professor of…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Cultivating a Christian mind requires a basic understanding of knowledge. David S. Dockery suggests that “the…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I n recent years, George Will has been writing columns on contentious cultural issues that have, to put it mildly,…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Today, thanks to me, National Review will be one of those outlets, to relate a development from the world of…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CDC Says Men Can Now Safely Use The Urinal Right Next To Another Guy’s Urinal #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A few years ago on ABC’s The View, Star Parker and Michael Moore had an instructive exchange. To justify…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whether or not Trotsky put it that pithily—opinions differ—there is an analogous truth that many self-identified…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Attacks on Christians are becoming commonplace in the West:" #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Associate professor at Yale University Joe Fischel echoed this sentiment in his article “Keep Pride Nude” where he…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This has been a long-term project of the Left. It's not going to be defeated overnight. But parents, take heart.…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Alas for the usually factually fastidious Will, much of what he has written in these columns is false or, at best,…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I’m generous with my notes. According to evidence, the more notes you take, the more information you can remember.…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Thankfully, state legislators have responded by introducing Government Nondiscrimination Acts (GNDAs) in 18 states…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Now, sure, there may be a few good ones out there and I’m all in favor of starting more of them as soon as…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Deliberately placing two new members on the Kansas Department of Agriculture's Pet Animal Advisory Board who are…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Similar laws exist all over Europe. These laws are vigorously used—not against everyone all the time, of course,…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The major shock in Dolezal’s book is that he establishes that it was not only liberal theologians, such as those…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The doctrine of a divinely ordained natural law, accessible to everyone and demanding our obedience, informs the…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In an essay, you need to show how each of your ideas relate to each other to build your argument. If you just make…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As a theory, CRT descends from European and North American philosophical traditions, particularly Marxism and…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Is Christianity saying that every other religion is just completely wrong? Actually, no. C.S. Lewis once wrote,…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Western canon sets out all the important intellectual questions, problems, and issues not of the day but of…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["1. Different Source—Where does the message come from?" #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is commendable that the European Commission in October 2021 announced it was presenting the first-ever strategy…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Paradoxically, the concerted effort on college campuses to increase faculty and student diversity has encouraged…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In the California case, the hospital said it does not discriminate against transgender patients, but does not…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I will dare to say, based on many years of study and teaching about Christianity, that the center, the essence, of…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Assign tags by thinking about topics you’re working on, not by looking at the note in isolation. By using helpful…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It took time, but when CNN’s number of viewers dropped below the number of people listening to taxicab dispatchers…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The quixotic goal of ridding the world of racism is as unattainable and wrought with unintended consequences. Yes,…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The CFC claims to be a “nonprofit organization that lifts up the voices of the majority of Catholics who believe…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whereas conversion therapy causes harm to society because, among other things, it is based on and propagates myths…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["From this foundation, multiple subsidiary branches grow. While its proponents will defend CRT as only teaching…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["One of the big reasons some of them say they turned up at an Orthodox parish was the conviction that persecution…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In the near term, the oligarchs will likely accrue ever more power, particularly given their connections with the…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The message of the Gospel of Jesus Christ is clear. We are not called to cancel anybody…no matter the…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It’s also based on postmodern nonsense. A “healthy public conversation” must include all perspectives so the…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Again, I ask you this: do we believe God and his Word, or do we side with popular preachers and teachers who…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Most people who call themselves progressive Christians do not fit the liberal profile from the father of liberal…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To be clear, there is no question that God in Scripture has a heart for the genuinely oppressed and destitute, and…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Breyer’s commitment to pragmatism means that he sees the role of the judge as a solver of problems and a force for…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["cond, by recognizing how we are being formed, we can seek to counter that transformation through cultivating…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Polling data on these restrictions are limited, but last year the Kaiser Family Foundation found that 69 percent…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Multiculturalism holds no culture better than any other. Under multi­culturalism, culture generally can be likened…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In a nutshell, the state must take freedom of conscience seriously. Governments, administrative decision-makers…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The importance of a Biblical worldview in the personal worldview of any given person is the degree to which that…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The reality is that judges in California—whom voters elect—have always been prepared to handle bail without…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Say, for example, I want to know everything about how God supernaturally guided the early church, or what Proverbs…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The “Tags” are crucial for your Zettelkasten’s quality. As stated in the core principles, a note is only as…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Remember, when you paraphrase an original text, you must still credit the source of that original text. Changing a…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There are two prevailing myths when it comes to religion and science.nnScientists don’t believe in God and/or are…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I believe that critical race theory hurts black America. Critical race theory is a cancer in our society. It is a…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It isn’t hard to identify the same trend in the modern incarnations of transgenderism and adjacent movements. Here…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There never is anything benign about government redistribution of wealth. Money that goes out always has strings…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Naturally, some Christians see the Mark of the Beast. In a sane world, the idea of having your hand chipped to…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When I arrived in America for the first time in 1964, as a naive young European, I was struck at both how…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We’re deeply alarmed at today’s decision by the U.S. State Department to end the designation of Nigeria as a…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Taking from this extensive vocabulary, one lesson in the brochure informs that “structural racism . . . is the…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["An embryo is a fertilized egg complete with a biological sex and full DNA code including eye color, personality…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Since dismantling the current state of racism has become such a fundamental pillar to the Democrat Party,…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["While Mr. Maguire revised a children’s fantasy, CRT is revising facts and replacing them with Marxism and CRT.…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In 2009, Pohjola was awarded the theological journal Gottesdienst’s Sabre of Boldness Award, which is granted “for…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Meanwhile, the mainline denominations in their seminaries were jettisoning virtually every Christian teaching. The…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As many recent news accounts have noted, critical race theory began in law schools in the late 1970s to explain…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["So, how to answer all these late-game questions? The answer is simple. You don’t answer any late-game questions…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To make that plain, I am convinced many within the broader church have been pressed into the mold of a system of…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In Roe v. Wade seven members of the Supreme Court of the United States imposed their moral belief that women have…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["So freedom of religion keeps the United State of America’s federal government and every state and local government…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Money also used his stature as a prominent academic to defend pedophilia. The pedophilic organization North…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Marriage is on the rocks in America, and redefining it only seems to be hastening its decline. The redefinition of…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In the classic New Testament passage on civil government we are informed that rulers are a terror to those who do…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nor are the punishments “disproportionately harsh.” When misdemeanor cases citywide were arraigned — that is,…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Under Islam, Christianity’s fortunes ebbed and flowed. Islam granted Christians, along with Jews, a protective…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We have no liberty under authoritarianism, of course. But we also have no liberty in a state of anarchy. We are…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Chelsea Greene Publishing is suing Massachusetts Sen. Elizabeth Warren for allegedly abusing her political…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["“We recognize that often what is being canceled and corrected are perspectives rooted in Christian beliefs — about…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As Black Lives Matter (ironically awarded the Nobel Peace prize of 2021) ultimately shows, the controversy over…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Republican members of Congress are accusing President Joe Biden of targeting Americans seeking religious…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Colossians 3:8 leaves many believers hesitant to merge the worlds of philosophy and Christianity:nnSee to it that…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This is extremely sad, considering the fact that the consciousness of the Creator entered the consciousness of…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The point I’m trying to make here is that it is easy for me to get why Danté Stewart felt alien in that…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["On March 8, 2021, President Biden issued an executive order establishing a White House Gender Policy Council. The…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Is there any “essence of Christianity” that helps bring some unity to authentic Christianity in spite of…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Thus, following Aristotle, we need to set aside cheery talk of “innovation” and ask what changes we might make in…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Senator Joe Manchin (D., W. Va.) says he’s done with President Biden’s Build Back Better legislation. And if…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you want to add more than one inline tag to a highlight, simply separate each keyword or category with a space…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He explains: “Paul is not saying that whoever occupies some position of governmental authority does so because God…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The culture warriors had a fundamentalist sensibility, and often came from that tradition. Jerry Falwell and…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Third, this challenge is an ad hominem attack. Ad hominem is a Latin term for the logical mistake made when…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["But if you’ve never adopted a child, does this disqualify you from speaking out against abortion? Although this is…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Point to 2 Peter 2:1 the next time you meet someone hiding behind this excuse." #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["However, it is historically undeniable that the ramifications of the deconstruction of macro-narratives can be…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Modern liberalism has adopted the Jacobin spirit. Having dispensed with traditional moral norms, liberals have…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The various attacks on the Western canon do so under the banner of multiculturalism. In this it is amply supported…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["By contrast, forbidding platforms from censoring user speech would require them to facilitate speech with which…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Last year I taught a class in historical method at Grove City College. One of our texts was ­Marsden’s The…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What must be understood is that CRT has its roots in Critical Theory (CT), which is the original thought of…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["But those speed bumps aside, in principle we possess the technological capacity (and the will, given some time) to…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Liquidation is highly visible in abortion, which is an attack on life at its vulnerable beginning, and euthanasia,…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["That’s precisely the outcome pro-life advocates hope for and what pro-abortionists dread. Given what’s at stake,…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["That’s how we learn, and that is how God intends for us to learn. Sure, not everyone is called to go to university…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People who insisted same-sex marriage would have no effect on the rest of us now want to punish dissenters who…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The function view’s inequality problem

A second difficulty is that functional criteria are a matter of degree.…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The best way to avoid the posthumanist fate, though, is to recommit to the virtue of religion: giving God His due.…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Biden administration has quietly accelerated its assault on religious freedom.

Just before we all sat down to…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hanania is right: the culture war is the key to all of this. Yesterday I was interviewed by a couple of…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Therefore, the measures that “tamed” the excesses of laissez-faire capitalism prevented the communist revolution…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The U.S. Departments of Justice, Homeland Security, and Health and Human Services are considering payments that…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The devil’s deceptions—Paul calls “schemes” in Ephesians 6:11—are sophisticated strategies he uses to gain a…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As the conservative writer Jack Butler characterized the growing unease: “We’re in the battle at the end of time,…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Bancel’s Thursday comments echo December remarks by Pfizer CEO Albert Bourla, who told CNBC’s Squawk Box that…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Thus, whenever a government violates human rights, it is acceptable for other governments to use persuasion and…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Third, this kind of person handles the truth with precision. The person who commits to diligent study is in a…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["These expert refutations, however essential, will not touch the 1619 Project’s central thesis: that racial…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Apologetics can also help unbelievers. It is truly loving for an apologist to knock down lies that have propped up…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Science continued to advance, especially in our knowledge of how and when our nerves and other tissues form as we…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["God became a Man that Man might become like God. Surely that’s more than enough." #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To violate the fundamental right to life of the innocent unborn child is against God’s law. What Pelosi calls a…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To the person who rejects any doctrine of prosperity, this passage presents a problem. Its context is singular –…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Marriage is being remade to fit a culture that encourages people to live as atomized consumers cut off from the…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Let me first clear away some underbrush. Whatever the essence of Christianity is, it is not simply what people who…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Teleology has a second implication. If body parts have an intended function, then using them in a way that…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When we look at what has happened in our country just these last two short years, we ask...

How is it that a…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Brownback said that with respect to domestic religious freedom, “this is a growing concern.” He said that…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["With the precedent established that speech can cause “harm” and that the primary role of government is to protect…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["At Villanova, where half of the players have been leaving the court during the anthem, Wright likewise emphasized…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Law360 (October 19, 2021, 7:10 PM EDT) -- A group of Christian businesses urged a North Dakota federal court…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Google went on to claim that “beyond protecting users from medical harm, our policies do not distinguish between…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Regardless of whether we’re in a watershed moment, the world is, and always was, utterly broken. If it’s not…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Calling traditional grading practices "racist" and a manifestation of
"white privilege," an Arizona State…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Democrats in Congress are pushing forward with an extreme pro-abortion bill that pro-life advocates say would go…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sam Brownback, formerly U.S. Ambassador at Large for International Religious Freedom under the Trump…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The American experiment was built on four vital columns of steel. They were Faith, Family, Freedom, and the…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is worth noting that there is nothing at all about what might be in the best interests of a future child" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is only one Word of God, and that is Jesus himself. John 1:1-14," #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The bill passed the House mainly along party lines, 218-211, with one Democrat voting with Republicans. The vote…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we are to experience the fullness of that ­newness in culture, society, and politics, we must first restrain…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["1. Identity
Our identity might be one the biggest idols worshiped today. We have largely abandoned who we are in…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I am a Christian and a professional philosopher. But sometimes Christians wonder if followers of Jesus should be…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This implies one may be considered a terrorist by virtue of being within geographical distance of what terrorists…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The first book to be aware of is The End of Gender by Dr Debra Soh. In this very significant book Soh – who has a…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The religious right culture warriors took a highly combative stance toward the emerging secular culture. By and…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In the show, Justin Brierley mentioned that evangelical leaders may be victims of their own success. High profile…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Canada is among the latest countries to ban conversion therapy. The French Parliament voted on Dec. 14 to ban the…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Bible recognizes unborn babies as valuable human beings in Luke 1:41, Genesis 25:21-22, Psalm 22:10-11 and…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The bill’s name elides what would be its true impact: creating a federal law ensuring abortion on demand at any…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Where to begin? First, people who commit assisted suicide are very rarely in intractable pain. Rather, the reasons…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Democrats claim these trillion-dollar proposals are free – they’re “taxing the rich” to pay for them." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["But such folks are simply kidding themselves. Any deprecation or minimisation of the mind, of the intellect, and…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you’re writing a research-based essay or article, why not just quote word-for-word and put quotation marks…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Christians were asked whether non-Christians can also go to Heaven. “Yes,” say 44% of all Christians. That breaks…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Reading slowly at the start of every day became a daily practice. I have always needed to read before falling…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["CRT is a movement of admitted far-left scholars who wish to challenge power structures represented in the American…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A study of Acts 17 shows Paul using philosophical reasoning with the philosophers, although he knows that…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Roy Austin, vice president of civil rights for Facebook parent company Meta, pledged to crack down on…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sadly, when the focus of a ministry is maintaining a brand, then the one being branded gets neglected." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["nd while we frown in disgust at countries like Iceland, ridding their population of people with Down Syndrome…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For more than a decade, leftist billionaire Warren Buffett, a self-described agnostic who was raised Presbyterian,…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It also wasn’t the only stupid argument by Justice Sotomayor. She argued that access to abortion is essential…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Miles, Lucas, The Christian Left: How Liberal Thought Has Hijacked the Church. BroadStreet, 2021." #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I also have a unit on the Harlem Renaissance. We read a number of poems and short stories; some are comparatively…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Calling this abuse doesn’t encapsulate the full extent of the damage. It is a culturally bolstered, politically…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Big Government aligned with left-leaning Big Business, the permanent Administrative State, the mainstream media,…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["4. But the main controversy today regards sexual morality. The Orthodox Church always has, and always will, teach…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Last year we heard the continual refrain, even from the highest levels of government, that CRT is needed for K-12…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Paul explains therein about “the resurrection of the dead. What is sown is perishable, what is raised is…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["chool choice is the civil-rights issue of the 21st century. Choosing the right school opens opportunity, it shapes…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some of those who willingly participate in this flagrant subversion of the truth include President Joe Biden and…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Not too long ago the left was all about freedom, individual choice, resistance to authority and the State, and…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To make sure I don’t forget to work with my highlights, I customized my Readwise to Roam integration like…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Well before the Court agreed to hear Dobbs, blue states had already begun to prepare for the possibility that the…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The religious Right, libertarians, and even the moderate Left are already being drawn together by their refusal to…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Yet not all compelled speech is unconstitutional. The most obvious example is that the government may require…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The CFC uses this money that it receives from non-Catholic or Catholic doctrine-denying donors to join forces with…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The whole article is a disaster, but the most controversial passage reads:

“Critical race theory, Guelzo says, is…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Yes, the U.S. and the other illogical leftists throughout the West and the other parts of the world bought into…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["2. Orthodox theology is taught through worship. Many of the early Christians were poor and illiterate, so the…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In an interview with the National Catholic Register, Bishop Thomas Paprocki of Springfield, Illinois, said the…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Though it is not being directly litigated, Carson also raises questions about the conflict between religious…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["WTVO 17 News reports a judge agreed Wednesday that Sandra Mendoza Rojas, of Rockford, should not have been fired…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["But how is the infidel to know which Muslim is and isn’t “misusing the principle of taqiyyah,” particularly since…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Today’s sexual constitution, abetted by easy access to contraception and abortion, disconnects female sexual…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABC Omits Obama’s Criticism of ‘Open Borders’ from Televised Interview #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Although Protestants could be as intolerant of dissent as their Catholic counterparts, the Reformation set the…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["400 Years Later, Americans Try Communism Again" #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["One such organization is the Humane Society of the United States, an organization that makes no bones about its…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As Scruton reminds us, while we are not incorrect to resist “too much government” or “a political class that can…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The New Normal Is Total Digitalization
For people with any sense at all, the notion of having a microchip jabbed…" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The push for childhood transgenderism is predicated on a perverse and extreme individualistic sentiment,…" #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>