<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Spooky’ object beaming out energy discovered in Milky Way #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Argentine singer Verdaguer dies of COVID-19 complications #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Light snow around today; tracking a warmup #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prices of newly built houses in Toronto soared nearly 40 per cent last year. Will they go higher? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Cameron describes Saville Inquiry as “one of the most shocking things” he ever read #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Responders Warn Dog Owners About Dangers Of Thin Ice #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 priests, 2 lay people to be beatified in El Salvador #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dallas Cowboys Defensive Coordinator Dan Quinn Says He’s Staying With The Team For 2022 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LACKIE: Homeowners should be prepared for pending interest rate rise #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russell Westbrook Scores 35, But Hornets Hold Off Lakers 117-114 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rafael Nadal reaches Australian Open final, will play for 21st Grand Slam title #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syrian refugees face yet another struggle as heavy rains flood displacement camp #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CervicalCheck Tribunal deadline for claims extended for second time #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“We have had conflicting reports”: Colorado Board of Education denies Adams 14’s request for a new manager #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taliban more welcoming than New Zealand?: Unmarried, pregnant Kiwi journalist gets refuge in Kabul after being rejected at home #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can former Scientologists take the church to court? Or are religious tribunals the only recourse? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State failing to protect sex workers – Amnesty #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People say they want COVID-19 to become ‘endemic.’ But what does that really mean? | CBC News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Ending ‘Zombie Licenses’ for Nursing Homes Moves Forward in California Legislature #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liddell Leads Buckeyes Past Gophers, 75-64 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Republican Party’s Anti-Vaxx Wing Is Too Big to Fail #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honduras: Chaos in congress as politicians brawl over election of new president #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covid-19: Active cases at border hit record highs of more than 700 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driver Airlifted To Hospital After Colliding With Semi Near Duluth #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghanistan’s Taliban have started their first talks in Europe since takeover #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AirAsia renamed Capital A to show it’s more than an airline #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Katarzyna Kobro, Functionalist Sculptor, Is Honored in Today’s Google Doodle #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘You Are Not Alone’: Domestic Violence Interventionists Highlight Resources After Women Murdered In St. Paul #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italian Drug Ring’s Wine Caper | Wine-Searcher News &amp; Features #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Authorities investigating fatal shooting in San Gabriel #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lack of supply—not lack of demand—keeps city’s industrial leasing low #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newly Restored Pink Floyd Footage Shows The Band At A Haunting Turning Point #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland’s restrictions on blood donation by gay and bisexual men to be eased from next year #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloomington Man Charged With Arson After Allegedly Threatening Ex-Girlfriend, Starting Fire In Her Garage #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murderer, 17, led sinister ‘cuckooing’ drug gang that raked in £7,000 a week #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covid-hit Lions tour delivers on the bottom line #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Oakland County Priest Pleads Guilty In Sex Abuse Cases, Sentenced Up To 15 Years #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grandmother Sues NBC Universal For Injuries That Occurred While Waiting In Line For Harry Potter Ride #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Diego first responders, others sue city over vaccine mandate #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic Bag Store makes Chicago debut #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Around 114,500 people believed to have had or will get long Covid | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-abortion group condemns white supremacists’ presence at DC rally #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MLB Owners Propose CBA That Offers Players College Credit In Lieu Of Salary #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | While Indigenous and Black people are killed for speaking up, white supremacists get a free pass in Canada. Just look at the convoy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phoenix officers save man from burning car #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Covid Pill “Active” Against Omicron: Merck #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canucks Game Night: Old friends and foes reunited with Flames fest #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stanford Completes Season Sweep Of No. 15 USC, 64-61 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduates in England hit by higher loan repayments #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ski Club with Chicago Roots Sends Three Ski Jumpers to Winter Olympics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayer and Prostitutes: Redeeming Love Tackles Faith-Based Romance – LA Weekly #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rantz: Seattle Judge releases homeless, prolific shoplifter caught stealing 70-inch TV #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia-Ukraine tensions: UK to deploy troops across Europe as fears grow Putin will choose ‘path of bloodshed and destruction’ by invading Ukraine #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New ownership renovates and reopens once dangerous Christian Park bar #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer In Contract To Sell Malibu Assemblage With $51.5M ask #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard O’Halloran: Irish businessman held against his will in China for three years reunited with ‘unbelievably happy’ family #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alleged Police Beating Victim Poised for $700K Settlement, Judge Not Buying Cop’s Claim That Boudin Buried Evidence #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live Snow Updates: Nor’Easter Blankets New York As Parts Of Long Island Brace For Two Feet Of Snow #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joseph Gordon-Levitt Gets a One-Star Rating for Yelling in Super Pumped Trailer #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Denver weather: Mild weekend before another round of snow early next week #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Abbott Elementary’ quadruples initial ratings after airing of premiere episode #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guide for public on reasons for sentences published by body for State’s judges #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maple Leafs at Red Wings Game Night #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Dakota Man Sentenced 5 Years For Shooting St. Paul Man In Face #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kansas woman accused of leading all-female battalion of Isis fighters #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Ku Klux Klan Hall In Fort Worth Being Turned Into ‘Arts And Community Healing’ Space #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kidnapper who left teenager, 19, brain damaged to have ‘soft’ sentence reviewed #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are Asian women the target of xenophobia? – The San Francisco Examiner #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefighters Battle Commercial Building Blaze In Downtown LA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who’s who in the Prince Andrew sex assault case? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dori: Seattle K9 killed in line of duty mourned; loss triggers memories for dog owners #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden stands by pledge to nominate Black woman to Supreme Court, White House says #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghan activists demand information on missing women from Taliban #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Georgetown law dean blasts tweets by incoming prof about race, gender test for Biden SCOTUS pick #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gay’s 30-yard FG Lifts Rams Over Brady, Buccaneers 30-27 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ithaca Grocer Admits to Food Stamp Fraud #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heavy storm lashes states on East Coast #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-NY Ranger defends Sarah Palin when photographer questions her vaccination status at Upper East Side eatery #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Diego bikers to collect blankets for homeless folks and veterans – #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Best Redhead OnlyFans (Top Only Fans Red Heads)  – LA Weekly #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Brutal attack’: Video shows man shoot wounded victim again with 911 on the line #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farm Laborer Wage Board recommends lowering overtime threshold to 40 hours per week in New York State #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British Sign Language to get legal status as part of bill backed by Strictly Come Dancing star #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vatican defends Pope Benedict XVI over fighting clergy sexual abuse #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police open inquiry into sexual assault allegations against Albert Fritz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emma Raducanu ‘creeped out’ by stalker visits #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennessee school board bans Holocaust graphic novel Maus #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tim Roth walks the beach in 'Sundow #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex in Norway: Norwegian Sex Habits Revealed in New Study – Life in Norway #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Weather: CBS2 1/26 Nightly Forecast at 11PM #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blizzard conditions headed to East Coast, Boston mayor declares snow emergency #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pittsburgh bridge collapses ahead of Biden’s visit to discuss infrastructure #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elite Selective Hospital Only Accepts 9% Of ICU Applicants #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotty snow showers today; brighter weekend ahead #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seattle Sticker Patrol: A New Diet (Ass) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the pandemic’s unequal toll on people of color underlines U.S. health inequities – and why solving them is so critical #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michigan High School Students Participating In Safe Driving Campaign #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot Air Balloon Crashes West of Sonoma, No Injuries Reported #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiheke ferry terminal among latest Auckland locations of interest #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lamar and Yuma schools cling to Savages and Tribe after being told to drop Native American mascots #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘My life as I knew it ended when my father’s life ended’- daughter of murdered DJ Bobby ‘Mr Moonlight’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late layup by Thompson carries Butler over Georgetown #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: Odell Beckham Jr. warned friend, edge rusher Von Miller against coming to Browns #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[City To Conduct Annual Count Of Chicago’s Homeless, And Expects To See Pandemic Spike In Their Population #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IRS issues several tips to avoid tax season fraud #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covid Live Updates: Moderna Studies a Booster Aimed at Omicron #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Symphonic Exploration of That Time the US Kidnapped and Imprisoned More Than 100,000 Japanese Americans #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Humans of Daniel Arnold’s New York #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Prioritizing Antiviral Pills for ‘Non-White’ People #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police Search For 2 In $7300 Theft Of Necklaces At National Western Complex #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Niners fans invade Los Angeles. Sourdough Sam declared king – The San Francisco Examiner #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Carville says Kyrsten Sinema won’t win a Democratic primary against Ruben Gallego if she runs for reelection in 2024 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six arrested after investigation into robberies targeting Asian women in San Jose #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Illinois prisoners wrongly used to wash cars, shine shoes, for IDOC employee fund, says government watchdog #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keith Cradle aims to teach kids: Black people camp and hike, too #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mystery animal pulls off elaborate escape from Pennsylvania rescue facility #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Houston eviction courts are packed again as numbers return to pre-COVID levels | Houston Public Media #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TMD resolving issues with Texas National Guardsmen deployed with Operation Lone Star #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schumer Vows to Pass Federal LGBTQ Non-Discrimination Bill #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus Christ Starts Rival Eternal Paradise After Family Rift #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gilbert homebuilder snags vacant land with plans to build 246 homes in Arizona's fastest-growing city #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Shannon High School Student In Birdville ISD Showed Symptoms Of Overdose, 1 Taken To Hospital #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘I don’t fall into male or female’: AFLW player Tori Groves-Little on coming out as non-binary #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFL hosts program to collect donations for children in L.A. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xcel Energy will no longer route its massive Power Pathway project near the Sand Creek massacre site #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engines of Our Ingenuity 2743: Book Club | Houston Public Media #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No restrictions: Pubs prepped for ‘big weekend’ with 80,000 kegs delivered | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man charged after dead body of pensioner brought to post office in Ireland #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California settlement limits ICE from re-detaining immigrants freed because of COVID #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ailing Whale Found Near Athens Returns To Deeper Waters #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women’s Ashes Test match, day three: Australia v England – live! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philadelphians Flock To Grocery Stores For Winter Storm Essentials #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Manchin isn’t ruling out supporting a Supreme Court nominee who’s more liberal than he is.  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot Marner looking to run goal streak to five games as Maple Leafs take on Red Wings #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Memo: Austin Samsung facility spilled up to 763K gallons of sulfuric acid waste into tributary #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Savannah mayor vows to stop drunkenness and include minorities in Saint Pats Parade #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climbing program helps Afghan women adjust to new life #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Albany PD: Man suffers stab wound after domestic incident #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saskatchewan commuters facing highway closures, extreme winter driving | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kazakh President Tokayev replaces predecessor as ruling party leader #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live: Ash Barty wins first set, but Collins fights back in historic Australian Open final #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Europe is already a great space power”, says Thierry Breton #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gauteng school placements: Online application system to be reviewed, says Lesufi | News24 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotify to remove Neil Young music after singer objects to COVID-19 misinformation on Joe Rogan podcast | CBC News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daily Lotto results: Thursday 27 January 2022 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thieves in SUV Smash Their Way Into Escondido Jewelry Store, Loot It #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covid-19: Lindisfarne College student tests positive after attending Soundsplash festival #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to set up an Amazon Echo smart speaker | CNN Underscored #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US weather: ‘Life-threatening’ conditions in New York as ‘historic’ winter blizzards dump deep snow across East Coast #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: Two-meter Anaconda on the loose in Phoenix! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish American John Travolta lands private plane at Shannon, County Clare #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stranger Suggests: Four Art Shows to Wander Through This Weekend #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man shot, killed on city’s west side #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London Irish come from behind to beat Exeter #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s Time for a Guaranteed Basic Income in Washington State #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mariners sign eight more during 2022 international signing period #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security concerns raised after near riot and ambush at new Marion County Adult Detention Center #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[49ers Playoffs: Health Expert Urges Safety For NFC Championship Gatherings #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghanske Hoda Khamosh: – Jeg ante ikke at jeg skulle møte Taliban i Oslo #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents livid after 9-year-old girl left locked outside New Jersey school in cold #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keeler: Can Broncos coach Nathaniel Hackett win without Aaron Rodgers? Yeah. Can he win a brutal AFC West? “I wouldn’t count him out.” #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reserve Bank lifts rates again as high inflation takes its toll #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tribal eviction plan pits Native American authority vs. civil rights #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalist denied entry into New Zealand opts for Taliban help #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyclists accuse drivers of being ‘ignorant’ of new rules tell bikers to ride in the middle of lanes #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A young nurse investigates murders in 18th century China in ‘The Red Palace’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘I remember’: B.C. residential school survivor speaks following discovery of possible burial sites | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Art Basel Hong Kong Has Been Postponed from March to May #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Virginia governor uses dog’s butt to rebut Bette Midler #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saturday Sport: All-Ireland Club semi-finals, National Football League kicks-off | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despondent Buffalo Fan Wonders If Day Will Ever Come When He Too Blackout Drunk To Remember Bills Super Bowl Victory #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Houston police officers shot, suspect on the run #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[103 new community cases, another Covid death #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philadelphia Weather: More Than A Foot Of Snow Expected For Jersey Shore As Nor’easter Approaches #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Widow delivers heart-wrenching eulogy for NYPD Detective Jason Rivera #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Mom’s Javi Marroquin praised as ‘the best dad’ after sharing video of son Lincoln, 8, crying over Christmas gift #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A second version of omicron is spreading. Here’s why scientists are on alert #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 highly-traveled bridges in Cook, DuPage among thousands in IL deemed ‘structurally deficient’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fire tears through North County nursing home #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 Lunar New Year Recipes for Good Times Ahead #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. researcher shows how Syrian refugees settling in Vancouver adapt #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My View: Here's to Arizona’s newest export – global, educational transformation #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police investigating two North Denver shootings #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cardi B awarded $1.25 million in defamation lawsuit against YouTuber #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Diego Unified approves redistricting map meant to increase racial minorities’ representation #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RATs shortage forces aged care provider to only test some staff as outbreaks grow #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYC To Send COVID Test Kits Home With Every K-12 Student Ahead Of Midwinter Break In February #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Southeastern Colorado struggles to attract home builders. Now federal stimulus will help add 127 homes. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Party Politics: Justice Breyer Exits Stage Left | Houston Public Media #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ontario Man Killed in Car Crash #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should Delaware allow terminally ill patients to end their life? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 women killed in head-on crash at construction site in Montgomery County, police say #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New year means new rules for cannabis industry #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Denton Black Film Festival Goes Virtual, Packed With Entertainment #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rallies gather in Canadian cities in support of Ottawa trucker protest – National | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adams to NYPD’s 35,000 Cops: ‘I’m Here for You … New Yorkers Are Here for You’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jury Finds Former Rock Hill Police Officer Not Guilty In Assault Trial – WCCB Charlotte’s CW #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP candidates for governor claim they can win #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 injured in Pittsburgh bridge collapse; Human chain formed to help rescue people from bus | LIVE #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China warns of risk of military conflict with US over Taiwan #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>