<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[China PCR test orders soared before first confirmed COVID case #URL# 
This is about the same time as large stocks of test and personal protection orders were recommended in the US.  In the US they were ignored.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texts Show Kimberly Guilfoyle Bragged About Raising Millions for Rally That Fueled Capitol Riot #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I see a battle between supply shortages (inflationary) and debt deflation pressures.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jessie Diggins Is Out to Make Olympic History (Again) #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Addictionary of Violence - #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important large sample study (479, 178 children).
 In this nationwide cohort study of Danish children, maternal exposure to #HASHTAG# analgesia during labor was not significantly associated with #HASHTAG# spectrum disorder in offspring.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does the term "kitchen cabinet" refer to the fact that many politicians think of fiscal policy in terms of household finance?n#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Good thread."

And, yes, most in the public are oblivious to the mutation threat. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sidney “Release The Kraken” Powell Is Secretly Funding The Legal Defense Of Oath Keepers #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Dominant are Big US Corporations?
by #USER# 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A former Trump official explains why Russia found America ripe for meddling #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["lazy non-scientific work" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weight Stigma Is A Burden Around The World And Has Negative Consequences Everywhere
by Rebecca Puhl
from #USER# 

#URL#

"Known as weight stigma, these attitudes result in many Americans being blamed, teased, bullied, mistreated and discriminated against." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. preparing to withdraw all personnel from Ukraine capital within 48 hours, sources say #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Also, the research publically reported from Prof. Cole July last year was contradicted by a research paper from Prof. Bennett, also from FAU, in April 2021.  Cole has made no comment or published further.  Looks like the question is completely unresolved at present.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If my understanding is correct, this is a basis for disbarment. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alaska Native villages band together to keep the Yukon River’s wild salmon afloat #URL# via #USER# 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# is everywhere.  Here's a story of an attempt to control and hopefully reverse one depletion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should one millionaire senator really be able to send millions of children back into poverty? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Smile!" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["underrated" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID: why some people with symptoms don't get tested #URL# 
by #USER# from #USER# 
via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["like it’s some sort of skin rash" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I mentioned the efficiency of blockchain somewhere in this thread.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congressional Doctors Lead Bipartisan Revolt Over Policy on Surprise Medical Bills #URL# 
via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I have done similar comparisons for how the White House aged George W Bush and Barack Obama.  I think it is instructive to understand how the public spotlight has great stress and it shows for many people.  Some who aged well:  Harry Truman, Dwight Eisenhower, and Bill Clinton.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Of course I know that.  But those Republicans didn't question the outcome of the election on Nov. 5, the day after the election.  They are an extremely small minority of the party.
And you suggest that the winner of an election should not be in court if the result is challenged?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Workers Are Using ‘Mouse Movers’ So They Can Use the Bathroom in Peace #URL# 
via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colder weather impacts #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exquisitely-preserved mammoth tusk found 10,000 feet underwater #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A parenting expert shares the 5 toxic mistakes that can make kids more 'selfish and entitled' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread.
(Wait for the end.) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow long-term trend or short-term?
Long-duration (growth) stocks’ relative performance is highly sensitive to rates. 
“Reopening” stocks have moved in tandem with 10-year Treasury yield over the past year (relative to COVID “winners”).
from #USER# 
#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good discussion about #HASHTAG# by #USER#.
Can inflation continue when the yield curve inverts?
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["laughable"nMaybe not if the U.S. is planning to repeat its military campaign of 1812.  #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Clinton was impeached for a similar uncertainty about the meaning of a very simple word.  ("is") #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chicago Boys’ 100% Private Pension System in Chile Is in Big Trouble
by Nick Corbishly #USER# 
#URL#
High fund commissions, no employer contributions have led to "just over one out of every three pesos invested actually got paid back"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Happens to Women Who Are Denied Abortion? Check the Stats. #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Ways Biden Can Help Rural America Thrive And Bridge The Rural-Urban Divide
by #USER#  from #USER# 
and #USER#  from #USER# 
and #USER# from #USER# 

#URL#

It's simple.  Give rural people some tools to make their lives better. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science knowledge does not improve Republicans' intelligence or makes Democrats dumber.  Sounds logical to me based on Pew data. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Va. attorney general overturns 58 historic legal opinions that perpetuated racism #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I was wrong!!!

Vaccines create the conditions that enable vaccine resistant variants to BECOME ESTABLISHED.

"to be created" is WRONG.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you think this poll would turn out in the US? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, those radical lefties.  #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does a Past COVID Infection Protect Just as Well as Vaccines? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# nBut Stevenson, Nixon, Humphrey, Kerry, and McCain weren't women.  #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["communication skills" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently related to a huge $2.7 billion defamation suit against Fox.  Also named besides #USER# are #USER# #USER#
 #USER#  Sidney Powell

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing how #HASHTAG# has become one of the most popular #HASHTAG# sports. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Fed's fault (of course aided and abetted by the Deep State, Barack Obama, Hillary Clinton, and Antifa ... among a host of others).  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL#
Research:  Existence of antibodies from "natural" immunization found up to 20 months post-infection.  Effectiveness against new variants was not determined.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fossil fuel industry gets subsidies of $11m a minute, IMF finds #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Democrats shut down the government!  #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The graphic says, "first surgeon on earth".  I haven't researched to verify.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farmers' protests in India end.

After year-long protest, farmers bid adieu to Singhu #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boosted in US 97x Less Likely to Die of COVID Than Unvaccinated #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#
Mysterious Fast Radio Bursts Are Finally Coming into Focus
by #USER# 
#URL#
Twenty years after their initial detection, enigmatic blasts from the sky are starting to deliver tentative answers, as well as plenty of science"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Germany’s Effort to Leave Coal Behind Can Teach the U.S. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pandemic Takes Its Toll; 23% of HCWs Likely to Leave Industry #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Vaccine Timeline Stretches To 2023
by #USER#  #USER# 

#URL#

With such a long rollout schedule, how many mutations will develop that vaccines don't cover? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Death rates fall - Because those getting COVID now are younger and healthier? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Delta plus' is 'not a problem': Everything to know about the subvariant and why experts aren't worried, yet #URL# 

However, the longer large numbers of unvaccinated help continue pandemic, the greater the probability a vaccine resistant variant will develop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hospitals Recruit International Nurses to Fill Pandemic Shortages #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why The British Abandoned Impeachment And What The US Congress Might Do Next
by #USER# 
from #USER# 

#URL#

"the Constitution’s bulwark against presidential malfeasance could become yet another mechanism of minority government." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I moved from the US to Ireland. Here are 11 things that surprised me most. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confederate symbols falling faster as U.S. wakes up to past wrongs - report #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UN Climate Report: 'Atlas of Human Suffering' Worse, Bigger | #URL# #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Black poverty rate declines continued after overall population minimum in 1974 (seen in the previous graph). Rate of decline was less than before 1970.  Cause for the change can be debated. (Unions vs War on Poverty)  Maybe declines &lt;30%  harder to get? 
#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biggest US failure with #HASHTAG# - lack of #HASHTAG#.  Close second is lack of a testing plan.  #HASHTAG# stated if there were no testing there would be less #HASHTAG# and #HASHTAG# acted like he agreed
COVID hawks and doves can agree: We need more tests #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If something is true, it is by necessity valid (although maybe not explainable).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True size of Africa

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In many dynamic systems not in collapse or rapid growth show instances of apparent equilibrium.  Problem with much neoclassical economic modeling is this circumstance is assumed permanent &amp; used in models.  This is a primary reason that modeling does not predict the future well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Black Kids - Shut Out From The Whitewashed World Of Children's Literature - Took Matters Into Their Own Hands
by #USER# 
from #USER# 

#URL#

This makes you think about what has happened over the last 100 years...
.
.
and what hasn't happened. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reason?
Politics, not logic. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hasn't Kelly Ann Conway discovered some 'under-reported' terrorist attacks on her own?  #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dozens of people followed me and 6 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accept It: COVID Will Be an Endemic Virus #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Don't pick on my friends in Toronto. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Expert On Search And Rescue Robots Explains The Technologies Used In Disasters Like The Florida Condo Collapse
by #USER# 
from #USER# 

#URL#

For someone who remembers 9/11/2001 like it was yesterday, today's S&amp;R technology is a revolutionary change. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India Emerges As The World's COVID-19 Hotspot
from #USER# 

#URL#

Until recently India appeared to be escaping the worst ravages of the pandemic.  But since early March infections and deaths have been growing exponentially. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is it formulated sufficiently to be worth a Twitter thread?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think piece result:  White men are exceptional.  #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why bring up this trivial matter when the Democrats are forcing him to separate mothers and young children at the border?  nhttps://t.co/aDnePOricZn#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You have come across as someone who was lecturing me.
Done without data presented.
Done without reference links.
Presentation, presentation, presentation.
I have gladly accepted information from those who disagree with something I have tweeted when evidence was presented.
-more-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And on an irregular path through some 20+ other state capitals. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unnatural alliance. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Saving democracy from Russian rage” #URL#, 
by John West #USER# 
via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paper tiger?  How about Paper Quad?
"cringeworthy “shared values” Quad nonsense" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You'll tweet when your plan fails?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One in four U.S. senators still hold fossil fuel investments — even as world burns #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Russian propaganda tweet from tweeter with zero followers and following nobody.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact Check: Remdesivir Isn't Killing People #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buttcoin Pops and Other Boils Coming To A Head
by  #USER# 
#URL#
Another foully-worded irreverent take on Wall Street madness.  Enjoy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preserving Coal Country

#URL#

United Mine Workers union supports the transition to renewable energy, provided .... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Has a veterinarian examined the cats? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prior Covid-19 infection decreases chance of breakthrough COVID-19 following vaccination.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overthrowing Ukraine government is not our goal, says Russia   #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cash-strapped Ukraine is using war bonds to keep fighting. This is what they are. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They might have been fighters if not for the rampant corruption of their officers.  Most of them had little or nothing to fight for.  This must have been evident to our military advisors and should have been made known to the Pentagon.  Our communication must be examined here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID Vaccine Makers Prepare for a Variant Worse Than Delta
by #USER#  from #USER# 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slower used car price gains point to a somewhat smaller core CPI increase in January, according to Nomura.
from #USER# 
#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have found an earlier source for the commodity super-cycle graphic (1805-2045):
#URL#
Are we entering the next commodities supercycle?
by Daniel Sullivan  #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.#USER# 
Do you know #USER# ?
You two should be talking.

#URL#

#URL#

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Behavior of attorney representing man accused of killing Arbery shows systemic racism in court #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Case Study of Fossil-Fuel Depletion
by #USER# 
#URL#

Whatcha gonna do when the well runs dry?

A thorough study of potential #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 8 Percent Of CEOs At Fortune 500 Companies Are Female
by #USER#  #USER# 

#URL#

Glass ceilings. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colin Powell dead at 84 from COVID-19 complications #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brain Changes Seen After Mild COVID Infection #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humans have installed 1 terawatt of solar capacity, generated over 1 petawatt of solar electricity in 2021 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Recession Is Different: Corporate Profits Boom
by #USER# 

#URL#

Another bizarre result of this recession.  Only happened before twice since WW II - both times when inflation was raging BEFORE the recession started. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Black Cartographers Put Racism On The Map Of America
by #USER#  from #USER# 
and #USER#  from  #USER# 

#URL#

"The precariousness of Black life - and the exclusion of Black stories from American history - remains an unresolved issue today" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia 'will not capture' any of Ukraine's cities, Ukrainian defense minister says #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comprehensive survey/discussion new Covid variant as of am 26 Nov.  Probably still has more info than found elsewere.
by #USER# #USER# 
Probable Vaccine-Escaping Covid Variant Sequenced in Gauteng, South Africa and Spreading Rapidly; Press Underplaying Downside Risk #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How can it seem that potential output is lower in 2021 than it was in 2019?  That appears to be the premise here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Last, Best Chance To Save Atlantic Salmon
by #USER# 
from #USER# 

#URL#

"The best place for salmon recovery is in Maine’s two largest watersheds."

Removal of just some dams would help.  Major hydroelectric producers could remain. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia's Lavrov Warns WW3 Can 'Only Be Nuclear' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Carolina School Board Loses Second Member to COVID—but Won’t Make Kids Wear Masks #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I failed to keep track of the link but I saw some talk recently about a 20-foot seawall-dike for south Florida a la Netherlands.  Seems to me that wouldn't buy much time to  avoid future hurricane storm swells which are likely to overtop 20 feet within a few decades if not sooner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Super-Rich Are Forming A New Exclusive Club #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did someone just blink? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This data is undoubtedly too low.  Reported cases are only those confirmed by testing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America's Scariest Charts Updated 02Apr 2021: U.S. Employment Situation
by #USER# 

#URL#

Discontinuities in U.S. employment data in this recession are unprecedented in the last 75 years. How long will the recovery take and what will be the long-term damages? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We know that rape and abuse is essential to protecting women's rights."  #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ukraine: how the global fertiliser shortage is going to affect food #URL# 
by #USER# 
and #USER# 
from #USER# 
via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Federal Report Warns of Accelerating Impacts From Sea Level Rise #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In every place surveyed, more people see racial, ethnic discrimination as a problem in the U.S. than at home
#URL#
by #USER# from #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Adding salt to anything is not recommended for most western diets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin gets a new card to play in standoff with the West over Ukraine #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Main Street economy slips a little in February.

#URL#

"March 2021 Economic Forecast - A Small Step Back"
"consumers do not yet seem to be prepared to spend"
by Steven Hansen #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Perhaps once a repetitive cheater, always a cheater.  
I know many who strayed once and never again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is one Mexican border resident's description of the border crisis:

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scammer Convinced Instagram That Its Top Executive Was Dead #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On The Limits Of 'Mediation Analysis' And 'Statistical Causality'
by #USER# 

#URL#

"Causality in social sciences - and economics - can never solely be a question of statistical inference."

"requires theory to really explain social phenomena in depth" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s DNA, but not deposition, sought in defamation suit #URL# 
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good short (ca 6 minutes) video on science, history, and determination of causation. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | Tracing a Killer's Path to Mass Shooting 
by Christine M. Sarteschi, PhD, LCSW #USER#
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Lindell says he has 'enough evidence' to put '300 million' Americans in jail for election fraud #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive-Punishing Putin: How Biden could cut Russia off from world tech #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Predictions 2021: Energy Sector
by #USER# 

#URL#

Relative price stability and reduced American oil production are among the predictions. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI Seizes Items From Laredo, Texas, Home of Congressman Henry Cuellar #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cold weather is taking its toll.

6 states account for more than half of the country’s recent Covid hospitalizations #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antimicrobial resistance now causes more deaths than HIV/AIDS and malaria worldwide – new study #URL# 
by #USER#  from #USER# 
via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Added note:  You are correct, banks do have capital requirements.  These are nominally higher after the GFC (Dodd-Frank) but some think the stress tests are just smoke and mirrors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["three Democrats have tested positive after sheltering with maskless Republicans"nnPurely circumstantial, I'm sure.  nn#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beijing Says China and Russia Are Not Allies #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden administration asks Supreme Court to hear 'Remain in Mexico' case #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Andrew Cuomo's Job Is More Vulnerable To Scandal Than Donald Trump's Was
by Monika L. McDermott
from #USER# 

#URL#

Is this a double standard situation?
Yes and no, as the author explains. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do you consider the weight of evidence, or to satisfy you must all technology be deflationary, not just a preponderance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm Fully Vaccinated But Feel Sick. Should I Get Tested For COVID-19?
by #USER# 
from #USER# 

#URL#

Opinion:  Yes. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fatty Liver Disease a Long-COVID Symptom After Severe Cases? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Were Feynman's lectures on physics really too difficult for Caltech students back in the 1960s?
by Peter Clark
B.S. in Physics, California Institute of Technology (Caltech) (Graduated 1965)
#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bannon’s Lawyers Defect After Batshit Call for Fauci Beheadingnn#URL# happened to literary license?  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Most Profitable Companies In The World
by #USER#  #USER# 

#URL#

According to the Forbes Global 2000 published May 14 these were the most profitable companies in the world in 2020: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Groan!!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not by accident SCOTUS is letting an unconstitutional law stand. It's by design. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freeing Britney Requires Reconsidering How Society Thinks About Decision-Making Capacity
by Elyn Saks
from #USER# 

#URL#

 "The inability to make one kind of decision means an inability to make any kind of decision" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millennials are creating housing communes with friends because it's too expensive to buy a home as a single person #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does watching thousands of Muslims celebrate in New Jersy count?  #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Constitution
14th Amendment
Section 3

From Wikipedia  #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Southeast Asia's Success Story For COVID-19 Is Fading

#URL#

Dan Steinbock reports from the eye of Southeast Asia's COVID-19 surge.  
Below:  Daily new confirmed COVID-19 cases per million people #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PolitiFact - What do we really know about COVID-19 vaccine effectiveness? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is still some #HASHTAG# out there ... but it is fenced in.

Wild horses, buffalo and the politics of belonging #URL# via #USER# 

#HASHTAG#  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You are absolutely correct about elections, where 51-49 is very common.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, Bonds Aren't Overvalued. They're A Warning Sign.
by #USER# 

#URL#

If you buy a bond you know exactly what the return is to maturity.

For stocks, the expectations of rising rates &amp; economic expansion are "overly optimistic". #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are Stocks Cheap, Or Just Another Rationalization?
by #USER# 

#URL#

"valuations are not only high by historical standards but will remain high in future as prices rise along with economic and earnings growth."

"substantially lower long-term returns" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dark-Money Group Paid Former Trump AG to Ask for Pardons—and He Never Registered as a Lobbyist #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Okay.  
Of course, you are entitled to your opinion.  
We can disagree without beating this horse until it is dead. 
And I have been up since midnight and need to catch some shut-eye. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one of the most troubling cases that most have never heard of. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Viruses unleashed into a woman's wound to slay superbug in her leg #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wild TikTok Video Shows Unarmed Ukrainians Attack Russian Vehicle #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet they couldn't find 11,000 some odd ballots in Georgia.  #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this is correct, the prosecutors are even more incompetent than the defense. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16 people followed me and 4 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incitement To Violence Is Rarely Explicit - Here Are Some Techniques People Use To Breed Hate
by #USER# 
from #USER# 

#URL#

"The United Nations reports the proliferation of dangerous speech online represents a “new era" in conflict." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found these 5 brief interviews extremely enjoyable and stimulating.  #USER#  #USER#  #USER#  #USER#  #USER#  #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is He using bleach? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Wildfire Lessons For Forest Towns As Dixie Fire Destroys Historic Greenville, California
by Bart Johnson from #USER# 
&amp; David Hulse from #USER# 

#URL#

emergence of extreme fires, resulting devastation shows communities need better means to anticipate dangers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The entire question of correlation and causation is circular philosophically.  Resolution essentially requires time sequence observations which are difficult in economics because so much of the theory is based on assumed equilibrium conditions. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frankincense and myrrh have been revered since ancient times – but now they're under threat #URL# 
by #USER#   from #USER#
via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Efforts to decimate Russian economy threaten to boomerang #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I sometimes do, but not because I expect to use it as a citation.  I am curious about various "spins".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four reasons your fibre internet could be slow – and five tips to speed it up #URL# 
by Omprakash Kaiwartya #USER# 
and #USER# 
from #USER# 
via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About Three-in-Ten U.S. Adults Are Now Religiously Unaffiliated #URL# 
There is a trend toward secularism in the U.S. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NATO Countries Pour Weapons Into Ukraine, Risking Conflict With Russia #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["spammed by a bunch of bots and/or people who dislike my research." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read this tweet and the reply #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER#  Must be one of those criminals or rapists.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Remarkable:” South Australia reached 100 pct renewables nearly every day in October #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL# 
Outrage?  
Sometimes justified and sometimes not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["policymakers chose narratives, lies and expensive policies" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Student organizer of statewide protest against Florida ‘don’t say gay’ bill suspended for handing out pride flags: report #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["all times and places." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where Europeans Get To Work From Home
by #USER#   #USER# 

#URL#

Over the past decade, work-from-home has been hovering at around five percent in Europe.  The pandemic has seen it rise to 12.3 percent with Finland and Ireland topping the list (over 20%). #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The obstructionist Democrats will be blamed for causing the downturn and Obama setting it up.  So much winning!nnJust in case anyone is confused:nn#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That changed your world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nearly 28,000 miles of Pennsylvania's streams are impaired by pollution, report finds #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The EU Wants A Carbon Tax On Imports But Would It Be The Climate Solution Officials Expect?
by Timothy Hamilton
from #USER# 

#URL#

Carbon tax on imports will probably reduce global emissions but the effects will be less than hoped. #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>