<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Cue to those who think Neo-Marxist ideologies that use Jesus' name in vain and that ugly churches and liturgical egalitarianism inspires anyone, especially the youth.

A religion that requires nothing gets nothing in return.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I spoke with a former CIA case officer who investigated a major bombing in Southeast Asia. He said that's always the case. The terrorists he targeted were linked with political Islamists who never conducted a bombing. nnKinda like Al Capone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Spiritually corrupt is something that fits Liberal Catholics better because Liberal Catholic theology is about being self-serving instead of serving God.nnReturning to a "single Roman rite" is a novelty because there never was a single Roman rite that applied to all RCs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah. It's a catechetical tool. Here's the traditional Roman rite in English at an Anglican church. I'm for applying some of the recommendations of Sacrosanctum Concilium to the 1962 Missal. Liturgical reform needs a do-over. 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tell me about it. I typically go shooting with several friends to keep my cost down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You misspelled Modernist theologian. Liberal Catholics are the tumor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bla bla bla. All you learned in school were lies. The Nazis, Internalize were two sides of the same coin.

German philosophy has only brought evil to the world.

You can fill books with what you Germans don't learn in school. 

The truth pisses off ignorant people like you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They don't know much of anything. ANTIFA supporters are the most ignorant people on the planet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I doubt Vladimir Putin fears sanctions. He's got China behind him. Obama's sanctions against Russia helped forge the alliance with China in the first place. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Your views on papal authority are worthless and not Catholic. Truth is truth in of itself, not because of who is in authority. Your appeals to authority don't make what you or Pope Francis say true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I spent 2 weeks with Covid with my family. It's all fear mongering. I have had colds that were worse. The Moderna jab was worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My pastor talks about it in his homily from last Sunday.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maybe Antifa supporters might want to move to Afghanistan now. They'd fit right in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Trains Polish Forces in M1A2 SEPv3 Tank Warfare via #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I think I could handle the way it's done in the Coptic, Syriac, or Armenian rites, not the social gathering mentality found at your average Novus Ordo. 

I hate it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And a similar project could be in the offing in Taiwan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cults of personality are never a good thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The man who rails against clericalism and talks about listening prefers iron-fisted clericalism in practice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turkey may be forced to take sides over Russia-Ukraine conflict - analysts | Ahval - #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No council is ecumenical without the assent of the assent of the Eastern patriarchs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Personally, I would prefer the preconciliar liturgy in the vernacular. It's hated because it reminds people of their sins and that modern philosophy's belief that human beings are perfectible by their own effort is false.

Modernity must be challenged.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If you look at the world in a Left-wing, Right-wing context then you aren't a Catholic. There's only Orthodoxy and Heterodoxy. nnOrthodox Catholics just want Vatican II read in continuity with the prior 1965 years of Catholic Tradition.nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deterrence and strength in the face of bullying is how you prevent a war. They said Ronald Reagan would cause WWIII. His military buildup caused the Soviets to back down. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Liberal Catholicism is what is spiritually corrupt because it's an exercise in self-absorbed self-righteousness. It's always self-serving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I wouldn't be terribly surprised if the FSB did the same stuff in the 2020 election with Antifa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Many Eastern Catholics never adopted Mass facing the people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Masking is a religion. It's proven useless to stop the spread. My girlfriend is a masker. She still got COVID.

It's an excuse for smug self-righteousness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Show love for your flock by revoking your ban on the traditional sacraments using your power to dispense from general norms under canon law. You are a successor of the Apostles, not a branch manager for Abp. Roche.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ollie told me that my sister's father in law saved his life in 'Nam.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The Church's worship upheld by the past two Popes. Actually, does that include Latin-rite Catholics choosing to attend Eastern-rite Catholic parishes?nnDo you work hard at clericalism? It sounds that way.nnLiturgical uniformity is a novel doctrine, padre.n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Democrats spent 5 years casting Trump as "Putin's puppet." In less than a year these same Democrats have positioned themselves as doing everything to enhance Putin's power. Obama should have put the screws to Putin after Georgia in 2009. But they appeased him.

Hypocrisy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You should talk with Orthodox bishops, clergy and laity how they do it. The Orthodox patriarchs reminded Pope Pius IX in 1848 that the people are as much the guarantors of orthodoxy as Popes.

I see this as valid now. Restore Western Orthodoxy. 
#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My friends got Covid before the vaccine was available. Their symptoms were not any worse than mine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Divine Liturgy in the Russian usage of the Byzantine rite at St. Andrew Russian Catholic Church in El Segundo, Calif. (Roman Catholic Archdiocese of Los Angeles) (Liturgical divisiveness?)
#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My professor in college said that Belarus had the least separate identity from Russia among the ex-Soviet republics and said it might cease to exist someday. That was 1994. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# By cutting off funds based on viewpoint discrimination you Stalinist scumbag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wish I knew anymore. The Church of Rome is in eclipse and is occupied by the enemy. The reason I became Catholic was the constant witness of orthodoxy from Rome.

Now Rome is embracing the same errors that caused me to leave the Lutheran church.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Greek Catholics practice the primitive canonical forms. Deaconesses have never served outside of women's monasteries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Communist Manifesto Chapter 2. Abolish the Patriarchal family structure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I want a firm stance with China that stops short of a first strike, namely via military, economic, and political deterrence.

Nuclear war is something I fear and I don't want to fire the first shot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The Pope plans to abolish those vocations sadly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# If you want to talk about errors grab a mirror. Your understanding of the papacy is distorted. A Pope can be a material heretic who can be resisted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian Aerospace Forces complete transfer of Armenian CSTO forces to Kazakhstan - Russia - #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Self-absorption is the essence of a subjectivist worldview because it says there's nothing true outside of the self.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia unveiled new nuc-subs armed with Zircon, Caliber, air defense - Bulgarian Military - #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't forget my cousin St. Bridget of Sweden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# With the exception of the Melkites, the Slav Byzantine-rite Catholics are still fairly Latinized due to the reaction to the 20th-century married priest schisms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Globalists are what we used to call One Worlders. It's the crux of Marxian Socialism. One World Government under their control.nnOckham's Razor. The simplest answer usually is the correct one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Objectively speaking your arguments are Neo-Puritan. I doubt you've studied Puritanism, so you lack an objective frame of reference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nope. The Pope actually is a Liberal Protestant. You clearly have a distorted understanding of papal authority and episcopal power.

We're Liberal bishops who ignored Humanae Vitae Protestants?

You know squat about your religion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More people have been murdered in the name of progress and egalitarianism than any other ideology]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No. Liturgies with patrimonies of over 200 years were exempted. The purpose was to keep local bishops from introducing Protestant ideas into their local liturgies.

The Sarum use, Lyons use, and the French uses were exempted. What Paul VI did was to suppress the Roman rite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Catholics in your archdiocese should jump ship and join Eastern Catholic parishes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Traditionis Custodes was totally unnecessary. The vast majority of Roman Catholics who preferred the Old Rite were in harmony with their local bishops and dioceses. nnLiberal Catholics are the real problem in the Church. Such toxic people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Such as? Returning to our ancient liturgy and removing the Jesuit-inspired mangling of our liturgy. Our relations with the Orthodox are a return to a status quo ante found in the 18th century. n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse - Like A Hurricane - Live 1986 #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donetsk Republic head confirms US Javelin anti-tank missiles present in Donbass - World - TASS - #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[N. Korea hints at lifting moratorium on ICBM, nuclear tests, citing US 'hostile policy' - #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The Pope is not the Church and the Church is not the Pope. If you agree with Pope Francis then you are a Liberal Protestant too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Novus Ordo is symptomatic of the faulty experiment with Existentialism and Roman Catholic theology condemned by Pius XII in Humani Generis. Instead of an objective service of God as kind and creator. Existentialism flips the script and makes it about the emotions in the pews.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Another counterargument is that if there is no TLM available attend an Eastern Catholic Divine Liturgy if it's available.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Modernists and secular Leftists always like their empty doublespeak, and their meaningless buzzwords. 

"Synodal spirit" is another one of those.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia begins mass production of the Zircon hypersonic missile (PHOTO) - Russia Beyond #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey ANTIFA supporters, here's a great book on the history of ANTIFA. It's amazing how it murdered people trying to escape East Berlin and how ANTIFA engaged in the psychological torture of opponents. nnYou have a lot to be proud of. Cheers!n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And you have ad hominem attacks that show you know a lot about Protestantism and not a whole lot about  Catholicism. Liberal Catholics are not educated people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taiwan is Preparing to Sink Chinese Carriers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lost to History or Possibly Just Lost, Meet the "Suitcase Nukes" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The theology that led up to Vatican II was heavily influenced by Existentialism at least in academic circles. It resulted in the disastrous liturgical movement and the Novus Ordo.

Mass facing the people started in the 1920s in some places.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I like your application of Postmodern deconstructionism to words, just like all Leftists/Modernists do.

Faulty ecclesiology. The Pope is the servant of Tradition, not its master. 

As Benedict XVI reminded us. 
 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# And they engineered the deposition of Pope Benedict XVI.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is why the faithful in the Eastern Church called themselves "Orthodox" to distinguish themselves from the Monophysites, Monotheletes, Arians, etc. Right-believing Catholics should refer to themselves as orthodox in contrast with the Modernists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I was referring to the inculturation among the Orthodox compared with the failure in the Roman Church. It's been accomplished with iconoclasm or the wholesale destruction of the integrity of the Byzantine rite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The promulgation of the post-Vatican II rite wasn't an act of the Pope as Supreme Pontiff. It only was him acting as Patriarch of the West at the command of a General Synod of the Western Church as Melkite Abp. Elias Zoghby notes: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Oriental Congregation gave this liturgical recommendation to Eastern Catholics in the 1990s that said Ad Orientem is Apostolic Tradition.
#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Look at the trajectory of Roman Catholic theology prior to Vatican II with the rise of the Nouvelle Theologie and its delving into Existentialist philosophy that made on liturgy and theology. Pius XII condemned it in 1950. 
#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# So you much harmonize A with B. St. Irenaeus of Lyon condemned Pope St. Victor I for rashly excommunicating the Churches of Asia Minor. 

Ultramontane ecclesiology is unbalanced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# In other words they are promoting apostasy. New Ways Ministry is heretical.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Whatever!

Sorry. It's not. The Roman rite is not universal, nor is it in any sense superior to the Byzantine rite or any other rite. It's not the normative rite of Catholicism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wish I could be there having a drink with you my friend. I love South Florida. Kelsie says hi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# International Leftists and National Leftists. Kinda like the Crips v Bloods or the Hatfields and the McCoys. 

Two rival gangs based in hatred and Jealousy. They just differed who they hated. They were on the same side until Barbarossa. #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Neo-Marxist critical theory isn't even a Christian concept. Eurocentrism. Third Worldism, etc., leave it be. 

Your concepts are Eurocentric in of themselves as Arthur Schlesinger reminded us 30 years ago in his book "The Disuniting of America."

The Jesuits evangelize no one. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Color and sex, not competence. No doubt a Woke Socialist. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What would Biden do if Russian Spetznaz seized Little Diomede Island, Alaska?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Christianity has become lukewarm. Look at the fervor of Muslims in comparison. They're confident in their beliefs. Most professed Western Christians aren't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He used to send me emails out of the blue thanking me for my work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I challenged a Modernist once on early Church fasting and got blocked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Vatican II also reiterates the point in the article about the hierarchical nature of the Church. Roche isn't following Vatican II. He's following the ideology of Neo-Lutheran theologians. Call them such.
#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# In the 17th century, Orthodox and Catholics in the Near East shared intercommunion. Roman Catholic priests and Orthodox clergy intercommuned. That continued until 1729. n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# RC Modernists always cite Lumen Gentium, but they avoid Vatican II's Decree on the Eastern Churches that exclusively associates the Mystical Body of Christ with the Catholic Church. It was done AFTER Lumen Gentium.
#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As long as the Curia is occupied territory, there's not much of a chance for reform. Return selection of bishops to the local dioceses. As late as the 19th century, many European dioceses elected their bishops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Catholics in Chicago should attend Eastern Catholic parishes outside of your jurisdiction. (Ruthenian, Ukrainian, Melkite, Malankara, Malabar, Chaldean, Maronite, etc.) 

They should boycott parishes of the Archdiocese of Chicago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Is my attendance at the Divine Liturgy of St John Chrysostom exclusively a refusal of communion? You are a silly man, Timothy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm tired of the propaganda. I probably have better immunity from having had COVID than from the dumb booster shot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clearly an astroturf group created by the Left to slime conservatives. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When Russian naval infantry lands on Little Diomede.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The Roman rite is always Eurocentric. Neo-Marxist analysis is always European. The trouble with your analysis is that imposing it onto theology and liturgy is artificial and misses the point of Christianity.

St Paul was influenced by Platonism as were the Gospel writers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I find it interesting that a Brit was responsible for the founding of the city of Donetsk. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Glenn, my entire family got COVID at Christmas despite being twice and thrice jabbe. The vax is completely ineffective at preventing the spread.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus didn't found a political movement either. If you base your theology in Hegelian and Neo-Marxist categories you aren't going to get Jesus. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wonder when he's going to ban the Sunday of Orthodoxy for Byzantine-rite Catholics?n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My former Byzantine Catholic pastor kept telling me that things would improve around 2040 when the orthodox younger generation of priests rises into the episcopate and papacy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He talks Jesus when he actually means Niccolo Machiavelli and Karl Marx.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Church Fathers and the martyrs died defending doctrine from mad heretics and tyrants. Pope Francis spits in their faces with his heterodox pietism.nnThe Byzantine liturgy used by Catholics and Orthodox reminds the faithful of this.n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Tradition doesn't mean every papal utterance that contradicts his predecessors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch me at 5:45 p.m. Eastern on the Chris Salcedo Show on #USER# as I discuss the Fort Worth kidnapper's extreme jihad connection. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If you change the services you change the faith. Look where we're at. Many Catholics don't know the difference between a Roman Catholic Mass and a Protestant service and treat them as interchangeable.

More Catholics have become Protestant since Vatican II than the other way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Orthodox Catholic bishops must organize and declare him a heretic and organize a rump conclave to elect a new Pope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will be on Newsmax tomorrow afternoon on John Bachmann's program.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A true Synodal journey would give TLM Catholics a voice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Nihilists hate cultural traditions because they interfere with their effort to create a homogenized McHumanity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia-UAE Likely To Co-Produce SU 75 Checkmate Stealth Fighter l Why This Is A Blow To US - #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think that I will be canonically switching to the Melkite Church thanks to our unmerciful Lord.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Jesus never said that the Gates of Hell would not prevail against the Latin Church. The Mass of Paul VI is not the CATHOLIC Mass. 

The Byzantine liturgy is unchanged. If the Latin Church apostatized we would be THE Church.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am playing Mr. Mom with my niece and nephew for the next few days for the first time. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The Latin Mass or the Gregorian rite goes back in its essence to the time of St. Gregory the Great 1000 years before the Council of Trent. 

Latin is the liturgical language of the Latin Church. Vatican II affirmed this.

The language Jesus used is irrelevant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# What I posted is from my eparchial website. There are 7 ecumenical councils, and the councils of the second millennium are General Councils of the Western Church. There's no Catholicity without the East. The West isn't universal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only this bunch understood how to do diplomacy. It's more of a fingerwagging or a yapping poodle. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Divine Liturgy of St John Chrysostom also violates his ecclesiology.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Nope. It's how you wage an insurgency. The Synods in the Orthodox Church serve to defend the faith and hinder innovations. I get your trepidations, but if we don't fight we lose. We may still lose but fighting makes it painful for the other side.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's not nostalgia for things that those of under 50 never grew up with. It's a work of the Holy Spirit to restore the Mass and the faith of our ancestors. 

Boomer Catholicism must die along with your ideology after you are gone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# For gosh sake this is a real Mass offered by a Dominican priest in Sweden using a Missal that's 100 years older than Trent.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hegelian Neo-Marxists in the Church can't handle resistance to their Gramscian culture war. Nice projection. The lions of Orthodoxy should never sleep. 

St. Nicholas punched Arius. He's an inspiration. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ugly art fit for Communists. That's what he means.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do a series on the Desert Fathers and St John Cassian on pride. It could help people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time has come for a nonmilitary equivalent to NATO to face the growing threat from China - Washington Times #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# George Wallace repented of his segregationist and racist politics and worked for racial reconciliation in his later years. Leftism doesn't believe in repentance or redemption.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You have to go at the heart of the matter, which is the use of non-Christian philosophical concepts that divorce the essence of the faith from the faith itself.

We call that heresy. Liberation theology isn't theology. It's heresy. Its supporters are apostates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The Jesuits and the followers of Aleister Crowley have a lot in common. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BLM and ANTIFA supporters have serious issues with mental illness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There are too many ignorant white wumao out there who will take him seriously. His ilk speaks for all Muslims as much as Jim Jones spoke for all Christians. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When cultures collide. Michael Jackson meets Bollywood. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He's the Vicar of Machiavelli, not the Vicar of Christ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was laid off today from my role as Senior Analyst for Defense Policy at the Center for Security Policy for budgetary reasons. If you know of job leads let me know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traditional Catholics should work to reconcile with the Orthodox to help bring balance to the Catholic Church against the Modernists.n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Don't blame him. Blame the ignorant Modernists who twisted his words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I love it. Tradition is for the young. My Melkite parish benefits from the same crop of young people. #USER# I am sure you would agree about Holy T.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# So an ugly bare wall is as beautiful as iconography from floor to ceiling?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This isn't the first time Blumenthal has sided with insane totalitarians. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A saint against papal over reach Patriarch Gregory II of the Melkites.
#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Catholics in Chicago should find Byzantine-rite Catholic parishes and escape his jurisdiction. There are Melkite, Ruthenian, and Ukrainian parishes in the archdiocese.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Liberal Catholics like #USER#  are today's Gnostics, and orthodox traditional Roman Catholics are akin to modern followers of St. Irenaeus of Lyon in the 2nd century.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The problem here is that words mean things. The framework you use is artificial. The Jesuits are the apostates who traded Catholicism for Marxist kitsch.

Forgive me for refusing to treat the ideology of the Jesuits as anything other than a corruption.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ukraine plans to buy AH-64 Apache helicopters #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My friend was a member. He is an Air Force vet. He quit because of their lame standards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am curious about the influence of the Existentialist movement on the liturgical revolution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's why they don't come to church. They see nothing special about it and no difference between it any the secular world. People crave authenticity. 

The 1960s-1980s are over. The experiment was a disaster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Most people probably get Covid from family members and friends. My family did. This BS never ends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# God forbid you refute them, they will say "I know you are but what am I."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pastor Aeternus also results in the conflation of the Roman Church and the Roman rite with the Universal Church in practice and in the minds of the faithful, if not in the letter.

It also results in what you complain about in your original post.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Thankfully Vatican II is ignored in my Melkite parish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Liberal Catholicism is a form of Protestantism. It's what those who are insecure about their Catholicism turn to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Calling the Jesuits Catholics in 2022 is a stretch. They're Liberal Protestants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So the Western Patriarchate went 850 years without any notion of annulments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeremiah 14:13-17 pretty much sums up Social Justice Christians and their Liberation "Theology."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Jesuits have become a largely Neo-Marxist order. I wish there was a traditional Jesuit order along the lines of some of the trad Dominican, Franciscan, and Carmelite communities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The ecumenicity of the Councils since the 9th century is open for debate. They're General Councils of the Western Church, not on par with Nicaea I-Nicaea II. Sorry. Latinism and Catholicism aren't the same thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Honestly, I haven't studied the history of 2014 an Maidan close enough. I know the Russians accuse the Ukrainians of being Neo-Nazis and have used it as an excuse to manipulate Antifa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It took 45 years to resolve the Cold War and the Soviet occupation of Eastern Europe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pope Nicholas I erroneously said baptism was in the name of Jesus only.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I didn't say so, and I wouldn't want them to. If Russians invade Poland or the Baltics, game on. I'm Polish on my Mom's side.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That's not a liturgy. Sorry. Liberal Catholics are obsessed with an imagined past that never existed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Have you ever heard Father that the King can do no wrong? Jesus is God. Where is the theocentrism in your Christology? 

Liberation "Theology" is essentially neo-Arian. Jesus wasn't JUST a man. He is the Theanthropos. The God-Man. 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's funny how I get blocked by ANTIFA supporters when I turn their memes on their heads. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thanks. Buom Natale to you in the land of my ancestors m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I know two Roman Catholic priests who changed rites after Vatican II to escape the rot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The trouble is that the good Archbishop's claim that Vatican II created new ecclesiology and theology of the Mass isn't supported by the documents of Vatican II.nnIf it did then it's news to Byzantine and Armenian Catholics, who retain preconciliar forms. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# St. John the Baptist Melkite Church in Northlake is an option for Roman Catholics who want traditional worship.n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# T-72s and armored personnel carriers being moved via train to an area near the #HASHTAG# border. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Big Tech Cartel needs to be regulated as a utility and made subject to the 1st and 14th amendments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian soldiers told to 'prepare for war' and mass within striking distance of Kiev as ... - #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Existentialism taints their thinking. They've rejected the natural law thinking of prior pontificates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The only Schismatic tendency is on the part of people like yourself Massimo and the the Jesuits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think the fact Byzantine-rite Catholics haven't changed our liturgies and theology since Vatican II offers a control group. Our priests by and large are solidly orthodox. 

They've been formed using Byzantine theology instead of Modernist stuff. It's night and day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Whatever St. Justin the Martyr had to say about the liturgy of his era has very little to do with the liturgy of the 21st century. 

Thankfully, the Divine Liturgy of St. John Chrysostom hasn't been touched by Puritans like yourself. Read up on iconoclasm &amp; Nicaea II.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If World War III happens call it "Joe Biden's War"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If you look at Church history, it's a lot messier than Scholasticism makes it out to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Putin can be expected to lash out, because he worries the same thing could happen in Russia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Catholic doesn't equal being Latin as Vatican II says. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They also don't care what Nicaea II said in its condemnation of iconoclasm. The Byzantine Church went through this in the 9th century. We commemorate the restoration of the icons on the first Sunday of Lent. 

They're heretics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something is up. My source was possibly onto something.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why aren't we bringing good right-wing African refugees to this country? Hmmm, Dems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Or the uncanonical SSPX. Those Catholics also deny the validity of Holy Orders conferred under the post-Vatican II books. From their perspective Pope Francis is a layman like the Abp. of Canterbury.

Many SSPXers are in this camp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's not nostalgia. Latin Mass Catholicism grew from 200 sites in 2005 to almost 700 this year.

The Novus Ordo is 1960s nostalgia. It's failed to keep adherents in Europe and the Americas.

If it's irrelevant, why the urgency to crush it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update:My sister's friend's house survived the night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mr. President the booster is ineffective at preventing transmission of COVID and at keeping people from getting sick. My parents got COVID despite being boosted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Sorry. Vatican II isn't the issue. Why do you care if Catholics use the old rite. It harms you how exactly?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Practices not in taking with Vatican II like the congregation participating in the liturgy? That's the norm at TLMs in the Arlington Diocese. 

Read Sacrosanctum Concilium, buddy. Liberal Catholics reject what Vatican II actually said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The young don't care about the wet dreams of elderly Neo-Marxists. Orthodox Catholics must get engaged and organized in this Synod of Robbers and restore the faith. As the Orthodox Patriarchs reminded Pope Pius IX in 1848, it is up to the laity to fight innovations from high.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They don't want to listen to Orthodox Catholics. Listening is a joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They recovered. My other boosted family members got it too. I don't know if my uncle was boosted when he got it.

I'm not getting the booster because I don't see any value.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We have the same stuff at Holy Transfiguration Melkite Church. Long fasts. A monastic type of worship. Asceticism. etc. 

Holy Transfiguration has services every night during Great Lent. And we're not into felt-banner Modernism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Something like Operation Storm 333 in #HASHTAG# back in 1979.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Just another example of Pope Francis' hypocrisy. Those rigid Eastern Orthodox holding onto their ancient traditions.

At least they don't have an Astroturf liturgy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He blocked me after I cited St. John Henry Newman against papal tyranny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I sang that in my public school choir 30 years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vietnamese New Year celebration at the Eden Center in Falls Church VA. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Watch me on Newsmax at 5:45 today talking about him on the Chris Salcedo Show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's like Roman Catholics adopting the "No Popery" arguments of the anti-Ritualist party of the Anglican Church amid the rise of Anglo-Catholicism in the 19th century.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Thanks for the thought, Bob. I'm looking for inspiration for my next column.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please consider giving for Christmas. My friend's 9 year old cousin is fighting for his life and the doctor bills are piling up. Consider donating to help his family give him a healthy Christmas.

#URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>