<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nope, we need to dissolve the police state, and start from scratch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You mean like, your campaign contributors?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Western Media Losing Enthusiasm for Failing Coup in Venezuela #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stumbling over the text, Mr Trump allegedly blamed people in the room for his mistakes and complained: “It’s like a foreign language.” #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poll: Nearly 70 percent of Americans say impeachment trial should include new witnesses #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An interesting read, even if the NYT failed to recognize that the unemployment rate doesn't have a lot of meaning any more, since Bush the lesser changed how they calculate that particular statistic. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tens of thousands of women march in Brazil against Bolsonaro #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Post op-ed accuses Trump of betraying his oath of office “by threatening to order members of the U.S. military to violate the rights of their fellow Americans.”
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic candidates demand the US prepare to fight the “wars of the future” #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Racism in St. Charles? Gee, shocker. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US-Iran Tensions: Impact on China-Iran Ties #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# those democrats who are blocking Biden's agenda are not centrists or moderates, they're corrupt corporate pawns. But hey, your advertisers don't want you to say that, do they?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘National shame’: Missouri leads U.S. in rate of black homicide victims — again #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's what all those protesters outside the white house think, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Solution to the Homelessness Crisis: Deregulation and Criminalization #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nah, this isn't the act of a guilty man. Not at all.n#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Krassner, Anarchist, Prankster and a Yippies Founder, Dies at 87 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Clinton’s Act of Terrorism #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This isn't protecting people's rights, it's violating them.
Welcome to the empire folks. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Talks tough with Journalists but Lets Strongmen like Turkey's Erdogan Walk all over Him #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign Our Letter to Speaker Pelosi #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you know anything about the culture of the left in this country, you know that it is pacifist by nature. All Trump is doing is painting a bullseye on people who couldn't hurt a fly.
#HASHTAG# is aiding and abetting this. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders is a climate champion #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know, it would be a damn shame if #HASHTAG# had a difficult time getting his motorcade back to the white house today, wouldn't it? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Why, so they can fuck me over again with another atrocious trade deal or yet more media mergers? Or maybe another war in the middle East! Gee, that would be swell!
Or even better, recruit another Jeff Van Drew!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘No cameras, no C-Span, no coverage.’ Rules will limit access during Trump’s trial #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nah, this won't be an inquisition. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, Trump wants to earn that trip to the guillotine. Fine by me. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pumpkin Spice Latte Calls Cops on Black Cold Brew #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amber Guyger sentenced to 10 years for murdering neighbor in his apartment #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Centene Corp. called 'callous' by U.S. senator over accusations of denied care - St. Louis Business Journal #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh look, here's #USER# making excuses for her failure to accept $1.8T when she had the chance.
Science ain't paying my bills, Nancy.
I have $50 to my name because you were "worried about the language".
As a tactician, YOU SUCK.
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Which of Trump's policies AREN'T sickening?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep, she's like a deer in the headlights.
Pathetic. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US sanctions 'suffocating' ordinary Venezuelans #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[William Barr Is Neck-Deep in Extremist Catholic Institutions #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, this is what Democrats should do; embrace war criminals. Brilliant. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a crock of shit. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Is Lord buckethead the guillotine operator?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pathetic. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, there's a bunch a reasons to not be a part of your fascist death cult.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queen's Guitarist Calls for New Live Aid Concert to Fight Climate Change #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're headed for 'climate apartheid,' in which the poor will suffer while the rich save themselves, warns a chilling UN report #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Bullshit. Fascism and religion are intertwined until they become so intertwined that the religion becomes a part of the fascist infrastructure. Fascism cannot exist without it. Ergo, fascism becomes the religion, and the religion is enforced at the end of the sword-Convert or die]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh sure, systematically dismantle the environmental regulations, even though Greenland' s permafrost has melted 70 years before it was predicted to.
This fucker is going to kill us all. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think Peter Weller should sue. LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Media Like Best About Elizabeth Warren: She’s Not Bernie Sanders #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't figured this out already... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dreamed that Blue Duck reconstituted itself, and I went back to them.
Then everyone freaked out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Trump just made #HASHTAG# the official religion of the United States, and he's the head priest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lowe's Fires Thousands of Workers Despite Getting $1 Billion from Trump Tax Cuts #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gee, no shit! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This article is chock full of centrist delusion. First, Pelosi says socialism isn't going to win electoral votes, then it goes on to talk about how democrats failed... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even after years of evangelicals selling this garbage to their herds, I'm still amazed they buy it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI Director Christopher Wray: 'Majority' of domestic terrorism cases are white supremacy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MSNBC's Chris Hayes wants Trump to release proof that Iran was planning imminent attack #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Unveils Plans For Its Own Cryptocurrency #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN's Debate Performance Was Villainous and Shameful #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, lookie here. The suspense deepens... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bullshit. Bernie, you're being gullible. Biden is a proven liar who won't change shit once he's in office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here we go.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beto Wears Bad Brains Tee at Debate to Impress Cory Booker - The Hard Times #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: U.S. cedes Syrian city to Russia in battlefield "handover" as Turkey tries to take it #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[82nd Airborne Division preparing for deployment amid unrest in Baghdad #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Reviews? THE PRESIDENCY IS NOT A FUCKING REALITY SHOW, YOU DUMB TWAT!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barr And Pence Now Implicated As Suspects In House Impeachment Investigation #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Bolton Urges War Against The Sun After Uncovering Evidence It Has Nuclear Capabilities #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fuck off, "entreprenuer".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernie and Jeremy both face the same bias. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carjacker on meth abducts man and his pet goat from Missouri adult store, cops say #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Actually, no. Clinton lost Missouri by 20 points.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you need to change the name of #USER# to "let's try and rehabilitate the reputation of the bat shit crazy fascist criminal organization also known as the GOP", because that's what it looks like you're up to every Sunday.
Bonus: it just rolls off the tounge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Church sign in Virginia says "America: Love or Leave It." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And there it is. The "compromise". #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And even if you do, you could still be ruled by fools. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whistleblower’s attorney says team now representing ‘multiple’ officials #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Feline commits federal offense. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real estate values in Davos and Monaco about to skyrocket. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Says U.S. Economy Is 'Best It Has Ever Been,' But Facts Tell A Different Story #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much for McGrath. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Translation: the democratic establishment is complicit in the Palestinian genocide currently being perpetrated by Israel.
Especially Biden. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Atheists are not antichrists. The antichrist is one clearly defined figure, a description that Trump matches in revelations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Biden; corporate tool. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And frequent judge on "the gong show". #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And of course, since it's a district attorney race, those that have committed election fraud won't be prosecuted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Wanted to Cut Social Security. Then Bernie Sanders Happened. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The inquisition continues... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Koch brothers are funding Facebook’s newest fact-checking partner #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernie Is the Best Chance We Have on Climate #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And yet, Congress still exists. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The money we WASTE on the endless wars could pay for #HASHTAG#, the #HASHTAG# and #HASHTAG#. Wars that actually create more emissions that'll destroy the environment because they're burning fossil fuels to keep the oil based... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ellen DeGeneres and George W. Bush bravely find common ground as rich white people #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orange is the New Black is taking on Trump's immigration policies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would add "clean water" to this. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[St. Louis County NAACP Names New President #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Televangelist Acton Bowen Pleads Guilty To Sexually Abusing Multiple Children #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh good, ANOTHER way the US military is committing genocide in multiple countries! Aren't we so proud!n#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India's sixth largest city 'runs out of water' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jewish students and faculty oppose Trump’s Executive Order #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile in India, #HASHTAG#'s buddy #HASHTAG# is having his own little genocide. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faster pace of climate change is 'scary' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Step one: STOP RUNNING LAME CENTRISTS. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jewish Labour supporters protest against BBC bias #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ocasio-Cortez to campaign with Bernie Sanders in Kansas #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Greatest Threat To Mankind Is Democratic Party's Cowardice,' Says Ocasio-Cortez's Spokesman #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously, what is wrong with Pelosi? Is she senile, stupid, or what? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graham discussed Trump in call with Russian pranksters #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tear gas+COVID 19= zombie apocalypse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Bombshell Evidence Reveals Trump Has Known Arrested Giuliani Associates For 5 Years #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Joe Biden is basically a Republican, and probably senile to boot.
He will lose to Trump if he's the nominee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Trump and the "religious freedom" crowd are actually talking about is social engineering by killing off those deemed "heretical" in their eyes.
In other words, crimes against humanity. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But but but only white liberals are backing Bernie Sanders!!!! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the First Time, Majority of US Wants the Senate to Remove Trump From Office #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# An apt nickname for my theocratic man child senator WHO DOESN'T EVEN LIVE IN THE STATE HE REPRESENTS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Naked Photos Have Surfaced In The Bizarre Jerry Falwell Jr.-Miami Beach 'Pool Boy' Scandal: Report #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks Like GOP Might Run With the "Moron Defense" for Trump #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marianne Williamson Materializes On Stage In Cloud Of Purple Smoke With Message That DNC Polling Requirements No Match For Power Of Positive Thinking #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christianity in Europe during WWII #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not to downplay your question, but why should we believe this report at all? How do you end up with +2.5m when 1st time filers were averaging 2 to 3 million each week of May?
Something smells here, and it's not just his malevolent indifference to POC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh great, another crazy old white guy with stupid hair that'll help destroy the global economy. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indonesia's capital city isn't the only one sinking #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Media elites and professional pundits have tried repeatedly to dismiss this campaign, and yet working-class Americans keep saying loudly and clearly that they want a political revolution," Shakir said. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure, go after gay people, but not pedophiles! nMakes perfect sense! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's right, the guy you really wanted to die, and yet, McClain inexplicably tried to save his life.
Then he died, and it was satisfying. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Only fascists use fashion in a political argument.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Mike Pence’s Office Meddled In Foreign Aid To Reroute Money To Favored Christian Groups #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16 Mississippi beaches now closed due to toxic algae #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oooo, a whole percentage point? Yeah, you're rolling NOW!
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politics is a messy business at the best of times, and these are not the best of times. But Pelosi’s leadership is damaging the Democratic Party. By catering... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gee, #HASHTAG# establishment Democrats are red baiting Bernie? GEE, THAT NEVER HAPPENS. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Republicans can't condemn Trump's racist tweets, they are as racist as he is #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Biden is a piece of shit. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Panicky Trump Orders Dozen New Sharpies Before Releasing Ukraine Phone Transcript #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sanders Shines and Biden Crumbles During Epic Town Hall on Climate Crisis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats Against Impeachment Invite Autocracy and a Loss in 2020 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This trade war segment is being framed in imperialist terms. It's kinda ugly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not good. Not good at all. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QUOTE: The reason is that nominating centrist Democrats who don't speak to class issues will result in a great swathe of voters simply not voting. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe ridership is low because it was an INCREDIBLY STUPID IDEA TO BEGIN WITH. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brett Kavanaugh Wrote That Hiding Evidence From Congress Is an Impeachable Offense #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homelessness a 'Symptom of Greed' by the Rich, Says Bernie Sanders, Not a Crime by the Poor #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sabre is located in Fenton, on the St. Louis county border with Jefferson county. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe Trump could be deported? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course she did. They put her at the kiddie table. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remembering when bankers tried to overthrow FDR and install a fascist dictator #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You mean, the same politics of fear he used to get elected?
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump booed at UFC event in New York City #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evo Morales has proved that socialism doesn’t damage economies | Ellie Mae O’Hagan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When a billionaire presidential candidate comes out for term limits, I imagine this standing army of lobbyists, waiting in line with their hands out, and said billionaire passing checks down the line.
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, those Montana jews are a real problem for this country. All 4 of them. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry about the Aryan nation, it's those Syrian refugees that are scary!nRiiiiiiight. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yeah, that reminds me; why did every single member of your St. Louis Blues go to visit Trump? Are they all assholes?
This kind of shit is why I don't give one single fuck about pro sports. Fucking jocks... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Will Americans Realize We're Not the Good Guys? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But climate change is a hoax. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now that Trump has started a war with #HASHTAG#, how long until he tries to clamp down on free speech with the espionage act?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's truly a sad day. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jack White to join Bernie Sanders, Rashida Tlaib at rally in Detroit #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh look, one of the banksters who helped crash the economy in 2008 is whining.
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nancy Pelosi's Dem Socialist Challenger Shahid Buttar: "We're Gonna Win" | Full Interview #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because military marching through the streets is never a sign of an oppressed society. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's really a shame that people care more about packaging than policy.
THANKS, TELEVISION! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's that, #USER#? The Democrats took the urban vote for granted? That NEVER HAPPENS! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dozens of dead whales found beached in Iceland #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reports on China ‘organ harvesting’ derive from front groups of far-right cult Falun Gong #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren Predicts Another Economic Downturn #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernie Talks Like a Jewish Man from Brooklyn and You Need to Get Over It #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And her name... is Karen. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Assassination Of Top Iranian Military Official May Ignite World War #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's really amazing is that Hillary has actually helped Tulsi with her campaign by floating this... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not even a law degree and a supreme court seat can fix stupid. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sanders unveils comprehensive $16.3 trillion Green New Deal plan amid climate crisis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernie Should Declare Housing a Human Right #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The debate is over; for profit health insurance is a complete failure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's right, #HASHTAG#, let's get beyond just beating Trump!
Talk about the #HASHTAG#!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The GOP has been a criminal organization for my entire life, yet there are those people within the democratic party (like Biden and... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pompeo: Trump sent by God to save Israel #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It looks like Chris Wallace wants to get fired, too. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# continues his crusade to be yet another centrist dem that endeavors to snatch defeat from the jaws of victory.
I've seen this movie before. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Won’t These Democrats Reject Fossil Fuel Money? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bias from #HASHTAG# owned #HASHTAG# is vile. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There goes Kamala, laying on the bullshit again... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Word.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nancy is a collaborator, pure and simple.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I was born here, fascist. That's all that matters in the eyes of the law. Or are you contradicting your dear leader and are against #HASHTAG#? Not that Trump cares about the law, that fucking crook.
#URL#
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump praises Republicans as ‘tough, smart’ for storming impeachment hearing room in likely security breach #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orange President Blames Light Bulbs for Making Him Orange #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Gross Inequality of Death in America #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because men are never wrong in the eyes of god. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2nd whistleblower comes forward after speaking with IG: Attorney #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're only interested in saving your own ass from a long and deserved prison sentence. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The remarks came in an interview with CNBC‘s Joe Kernen in Davos, and although the news outlet did not report them in their initial write-up of the exchange, they were captured in the transcript. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["American businessman". Right. This guy screams mobster.
Giuliani did work organized crime, you know. Remember John Gotti? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To all you people who groused about impeachment being a waste of time, you've just been proven wrong. Impeachment has cost McConnell political... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# FUCK THE BUSINESD LOANS. GIVE THE PEOPLE'S MONEY TO THE PEOPLE! WE KEEP THE ECONOMY RUNNING, NOT BUSINESSES!
MORON.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was probably the Tory plan all along. Use Brexit as an excuse to attack individual rights. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kamala Harris Fails to Explain Why She Didn’t Prosecute Steven Mnuchin’s Bank #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'll be sure to ignore that show, too. I mean, it's not like CNN has ever been a bastion of journalistic integrity. It's only slightly better than Fox.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Area 51 photos leaked; BLACK MERMAIDS! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christian Dominionists Meet at Trump's Washington Hotel to Answer the "Divine Call to War" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Begins Christmas Season With Ceremonial Lighting Of Cross #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>