<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's good one, #USER#. How do you do it and live with yourself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Far worse than Biden’s withdrawal: mainstream coverage of Afghanistan for over forty years.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine that. Mandates to fight a pandemic can be legal. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No justification. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Amongst the issues with EVs — environmental cost of mining; geopolitics of the rare earths; inadequate charging; inadequate charging network; range anxiety — there’s the conundrum that for range, you have to buy bigger, that is, maybe more vehicle than you want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can explain what kind of monarch worthy of the title allows this shit show?
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Corporate profits in the United States climbed 10.5% to a record high of USD 2.44 trillion in the second quarter of 2021, after rising 4.5% in the previous period…”
And they cry about being unable to hire people at shitty pay for shitty jobs…
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't quite trust the government's position here.
OTOH, it's awesome for these people to get abused the same way the people they hate are abused as a matter of course.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not so much the ads as the targeting. Or maybe I’m the problem that this is a problem for me.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Always great to see the opposition party choosing not to oppose what needs opposition.
BTW, he’s also encouraging apathy among POC. No reason for them not to sit out 2022 or any other election — more given that #USER# essentially supports restrictions on POC voters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a surprise. It’s a direct result of five decades of extraction. And getting worse.
Anyone want to justify it?
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“If the Association of Flight Attendants, the International Longshoremen’s Association, the ‘Big Four’ railroad brotherhoods, and of course the Teamsters had wished to… #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“‘African Americans counted 100 percent towards representation in Congress and towards electoral votes, but they still could not vote. That gave white Southerners substantially more influence…’”
Anti-democratic from the start. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder to me: When I note how the US' practice is to shit on other nations, I tend to start with the CIA from its birth following WWII.
Actually, though, starting with the Spanish-American war would be more accurate and the ur-event... #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[”[T]rying to bring to life their anti-New Deal monopoly-tolerant union-busting economic policy agenda by white racism and supremacy… was a very important part and remains a very important part of that shift away from economics… 
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the kind of nation we actually are.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hate to appear to defend Tailkisser Ted but what good can he do either way although, sure, running to Cancun now because (allegedly) a 10 and 12 year old ask is what a piece of shit does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...qualification for Times editor will no longer be just someone the publisher likes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's our nation! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Other nations may be racist. But the US was founded (in part) on racism. So, you know, heritage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“It's gotten to the point where I find myself occasionally not being able to parse entire lines of dialogue when I see a movie in a theater, and when I watch things at home, I've defaulted to turning the subtitles on to make sure I don't miss anything crucial to the plot.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 1/2
So wrong.
First Q: what was the basis economically for saying $800b was the amount needed? Legit fact-based criticism came during the push for the bill. Was there really any incentive to check that number for accuracy?
The mishandling of mortgage disaster is indefensible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“…voters fault him for failing to secure bipartisan cooperation.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too soon…
But surely if there’s an afterlife… #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black and a woman so no need for us to have known about her, right?
Preceding was a shot of illegal #HASHTAG#.
#HASHTAG#
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Being &gt;1%er means not paying your fair share of taxes. It’s one of those inalienable rights we have in the US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's so shithole nation stuff there. Then again more likely than not the US is a failed state so this makes perfect sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knowing that it was a nearly complete refusal to act properly by Donnie and his #USER# is enough of an explanation for me. And enough solution is just to vote the party out of power. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stupidity rules. The success of this prank shouldn’t be surprising. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe it's less a matter that public assistance "paying" people not to work but employers choosing not to make offers workers can't refuse. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia’s heritage is suffering even more than our conservative masses believe in.
But I think a post-nuclear war would be even worse for them than they can imagine. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’d think it should be, but clearly we’re in the minority on that. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Global capitalism has gotten us too entwined with adversaries to be able to respond with force when warranted.
How a system like that can be justified…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SCOTUS will overturn Sullivan then all will be resolved.
Can’t wait for the flood of libel suits Trump would bring.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a great nation. By which I mean fucking disgraceful, to say the least.  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[❤️that headline. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way the world work.
 #URL# by #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If #USER# remains in power, our kids’ future will be killed. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The ridiculous notion that Biden’s window for legislating is closing less than ten months into his four-year presidency is primarily, of course, a reflection of America’s ridiculous political system, but it’s surely the press’s job now…
 #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, I know, satire. Q stands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What Zero Covid doesn’t do, however, is make the rich much, much richer while everyone else suffers." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's their right to block people who use their platforms to kill people (Trump promoting his Covid response) and to promote the subverting and ultimate overthrow of an election.
Takes a disgusting person to post those tweets, #USER#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Word. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now, if you want to consider the harm domestic conservatives have done to the nation, then sure, the 9/11 fall short by many, many magnitudes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think fast: Will the mainstream both-siderism do the job or exacerbate the problem?
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As long as special interests got an undeserved windfall, who can complain? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing on the wall appeared in the dicta of Masterpiece Cake if not earlier. Just for the record. #URL# Follow #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But query: Wouldn’t a Black version of a white actually be more an exacerbation and less a solution given that the problem is or comes from white civilization?
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for the #HASHTAG# to start getting ready to do their thing. Let’s flood the platform with a shit ton of facts and truths.
 #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given global leadership, it’s already too late. Plan accordingly, don’t plan on your leaders doing anywhere enough. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who gave themselves up to die of Covid willingly or by other bad choices.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tell that this is written by a hack is that he has no good answer after (implicitly) admitting #USER# did nothing while failing to appreciate the threat. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News from the trenches. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As #USER# noted, the huge tell for the conservatives is their willingness to allow in Afghan refugees, which is ~nil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny how once the mainstream media commit to a storyline, it never changes no matter the facts. (JK; not funny; actually harmful.)
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Correct as far as it goes. Overlooked is establishment media bias.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[…where the existence of tat kind of poverty is in any way acceptable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Was St. Ronnie a Democrat?
Sim., when Clarence Thomas was nominated. His complete lack of relevant qualifications was to all intents completely ignored by the media.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo, Percy; can't you take some better shots??
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# On one hand, she feels compelled to act like an idiot in public, OTOH isn’t that the official #USER# position on every Black woman Biden would nominate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irony: Before the trans-Atlantic slave trade, Slavs weren’t even white enough for the rest of Europe.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The road to terminal collapse. We can stop it if we want to do the work but far from enough of us do.
Via #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Switching to renewables and as quickly as possible is a legit global security issue full stop.
And it’s something we can do. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER#’s not unusual in this regard. Not even close.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(The kind of nation we are.
$SPY defined here: #URL#) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The other half is mainstream media’s willingness in echoing the lies instead of calling exposing them.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the ambitious jerk’s defense, I know a former patient (with a relatively serious issue) that swore by him.
Didja know? Few things in life are actually black and white.
But query: Why do so many of #USER#’s protege’s turn out to be sketchy?
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Civilized, right. #HASHTAG# n #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No surprise. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful legacy. #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“These results suggest that religion’s role in contemporary right-wing violence is embedded with non-religious factors…”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“It's always interesting when the public is strongly in one camp on an issue (over 60%) which is completely at odds with the dominant views of the press coverage, especially at a very loud one-sided moment such as this.”
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This, FWIW:
“I thought for a moment of how incredibly disturbing it would be to learn that your child had been evacuated from her second-grade class because a madman in the immediate vicinity was raving about going on about shooting up a school.” #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great state. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So the #USER# was making it clear what was expected from ACB? Doing her a favor ensuring that she’d know that she’ll be doing the party a solid?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actual good news.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never forget.
Donnie couldn’t have murdered like this without the full support of his party, #USER#, and establishment media.
#URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“‘Trump offered himself as its instrument. Declaring his presidential candidacy in his golden tower, he asked, “When was the last time the U.S. won at anything?”’”
Well, we elect Republicans and allow #USER# domination, a fine definition of loser.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What passes for progress. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*sigh*
Competent reporting should be the rule, not the exception.
The piece discussed here is he latter. #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s a hell of a lot of cancelling of conservatives by #USER#. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See? Not a racist nation at all. We’ve evolved. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The racists are cool with this because it’s not birth control, just racist control of Black bodies which, of course, is their heritage.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# is now an extremist far right party that hasn’t cared about the wellbeing of the nation of its people since the 1980s. Most recently: Covid; climate change; race (still!); and impoverishment through an extractive, hollowed out economy — just for a start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually not so much captured as willingly, deliberately corrupted by #USER#. #USER# was already committed to putting Big Business first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overdue, essential for civilizations progress.
Via #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what are the odds we would have learned about her sooner if she was a man? #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If one believes in a functional republic that provides for the wellbeing of its people, by definition no Republican is a moderate. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Epic burn. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a surprise. #HASHTAG# #URL# by #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What kind of nation is this when a Black woman refuses to abused by white elitists? #HASHTAG#
Congrats to Hannah-Jones. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if the ruling class promotes strife between people, that left on their own, people would be nice to each other? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The majority who voted against him will be infuriated.”
We aren’t a people who get infuriated as a rule. We go turn on the flat screen or scroll Facebook. We would accept what ⁦#USER#⁩ describes here sorry. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Satire, yet not. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One would think a developed nation would be able handle this competently. That it doesn’t, maybe can’t, says a lot, all bad. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My favorite Jesus: Heavily armed and Aryan.
Great thing about the religion is that even heretics get an image of god that they can like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Punchline: 9/11 was made possible by Saudis -- had zero effect on West/Saudi relations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad that was clarified.
Of course, if he really was, it was the first time in his public life he ever spoke figuratively. He doesn’t even know what the word means.
Via #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second best news today. (1st is #USER# releasing my $timulu$ $$.) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A... poll found that... 52 percent[] of those polled even knew what cancel culture was and those who did know what it was were mostly 'self-described liberals, people with college degrees and those who say they regularly follow politics...'
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a nasty man, calling out a liar. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still love #USER#'s love for this nation. Nothing says love like restricting the ability to vote, supporting an extractive, impoverishing economy and letting a couple hundred thousand people die.
No party can be better than that.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something to think about.
Me, I think for most things there’s a minimum size needed for a screen and that’s approximately a phone screen.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investing in freedom is phrase that can make me hot. Dunno that it does that under these circumstances here, though. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTF, #USER#?
"Notably, there have been 5 million Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccines administered in the United States, with only six cases of blood clots." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...the truth of which he's neither a genius, well informed or the innovation his obscene wealth came from was extorting OEMs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[”Because he was exonerated without DNA evidence, Mr. Strickland is not entitled to compensation from the state, his lawyer said. He will also need help getting an identification card, a bank account and clothing.”
How about a lawsuit?
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Donnie left ~330,000,000 Americans he hasn’t killed, although he ensured that Republicans would be disproportionately sickened and killed by Covid — the latter is a plus. More great policies: the Big Lie, trashing the economy, sadism-based policies and supporting racism.
U c^nt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Five decades of an impoverishing, extractive economy.
Six decades of electing unfit politicians.
Being a failed state that can’t even handle a pandemic with full competence.
Life under a pathological, sociopathic leadership class.
The ignorance and passivity of the masses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting back and forth, except disagreement ends in the same place: The Senate is fucked up and a hair thin majority doesn’t help.
But soon, none of it will matter.
 #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Disgusting yet not surprising.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“One day somebody will explain to me why it is that, at a time when science has never been wiser, or the truth more stark, or human knowledge more available, populists and liars are in such pressing demand.” — John Le Carre
 #URL# # via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who’d’ve guessed?
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FWIW, I thought one of the alleged pluses for crypto was the lack of centralized control.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Again, so unfair responding to conservatives with facts when facts are nearly never on their side.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing all they can to hide the scope of corruption does us no good.
Time to learn the truth about Brett. But the press rather hide it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I started to pass on Zionism for the most part when the victims of the Nazis became something of the successors to their abusers.
All of Israel's denialism re this is complete bullshit. Pegasus is essentially an Israeli intel operation. 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Know your enemy.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can someone as smart as Donnie done something like this? #HASHTAG#  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too true.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I CANNOT WAIT TO GET ON TRUTH SOCIAL!!!
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s your long time dominant, controlling political party there. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another thing I have to tweet because the press should be reporting tis but is mostly ignoring it for, uh, continued fear stories about the vaccines. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truth. Amazing how much we hate our kids…
Via #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The need to let’s say just turn it off for a bit. Turning down the volume would also be good. Maybe even slowing down…
 #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will lead to absolutely nothing.
Easier yet also not going to happen: Making it easier for people and businesses to wean themselves off the Big Oil teat. Would also be good for national security. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why does a star writer at a prestigious publication not know the answer to the question?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, they’re in full sync with #USER#.
Via #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...the car and that it burst into flames immediately.
[snip]
"Authorities... used 32,000 gallons of water to extinguish the flames because the... batteries kept reigniting."
Buggy software and shit build quality. Thank god TSLA's not a mass product. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mystery for 2022: The stuff being reversed was implemented to benefit #USER#. So with the new restrictions, who's really getting hurt more? TWT. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When ones too lazy to figure out a problem, one can always blame #HASHTAG#. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truth.
Via #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1968; Tricky Dick Nixon arguably commits treason for political gain.
Wouldn't argue that that's not when #USER#'s war against America began. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: Owners of businesses with shitty jobs offering shitty pay failing to find workers should just work out a deal to employ prisoners JFC.
To paraphrase Abe Lincoln, a house built on a foundation of bullshit cannot long stand.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know that comrade artist can make a fortune selling these.
Via #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again raising the question of how it's possible to libel a documented piece of shit like #USER# (who's stupid enough to sue a cow -- #USER# -- for hurting his feefees).
 #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I’ve been contemplating this line from The Twilight Zone, rolling it around in my head like a koan: ‘We love a rose because it will soon be gone. Whoever loved a stone?’”
Raising the question: Why not a stone?
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Who in their right mind would expect any better from him or any other Republican? Haven’t they don’t enough for y’all to have a clue?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The failure of leadership corruption buys.
When #HASHTAG# is subsumed by Russia, one wonders whether things will be significantly worse for Ukrainians than this kind of leadership. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate’s awesome, right? Made the nation what it is.
 #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# again.
Spoiler: this bullshit has not helped Intel’s investor as vigorous R&amp;D spending would have done. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest democracy the world has ever known.
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# 
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Donnie: Always attracting the worst people. And the kids are the imbecilic offspring of a huge moron. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are mourning and Classy Donnie decides to flash photos of naked women.
What a piece of shit. Ditto for the submissive, dysfunctional people who support him. #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# is doing the absolute minimum any honest news outlet should be doing. It's possible to provide a lot of context with just a sentence or less. Of course, the establishment media aren't interested in providing truth. Still.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no alternative to unpriced capitalism, so this idiocy. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’d bet he’s right.
And remember that those warning about inflation have vested interests. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Election's less than 18 months away and #USER#'s all in on vote rigging and election stealing.
Good news: If #USER# gets Congress, it's game over for the last dregs of democracy; elections won't matter beyond the local level.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“…that highlights poor management and toxic workplace environments in explaining why workers perceive paid work as useless.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Have we ever seen a group of people who hate America and have worked for decades to turn the US into a failed state #USER# has done?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A complicated issue in need of addressing maybe. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If there wasn't a video of the entire killing, how do you think it would have played out?
Ignored by #USER# and his cohort for one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dividend that only existed as a hypothetical or line of bullshit but never in reality? That one?
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We can breathe where they can't. But we need to use that breath for something more than sighs of relief."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Donnie had his chance to help in 2019 but chose to screw Zelensky for choosing not to support Trump2020.
Great knowing that he can be elected in 2024.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corrected:
"US is Enemy of All Democracy and All States not Wall Street-Compliant Since 1945, Maybe 1918" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's your #HASHTAG#. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What part of "extractive" so difficult to comprehend?
This isn't accidental but what was planned.
 #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silver lining, maybe: The dominance of this is why real, longterm harmful inflation is very, very far away. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If ACAB, then CO’s are worse, so this idiocy, sure, they’re that small and petty.
 #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On one hand, I’m not convinced that BBBA is dead, and I believe passing it closer to the 2022 election is better.
That said, I’m with #USER# that there’s a better way than the BBBA.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A nearly complete scam. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Never mind that most of these options would do little to relieve the backup at the ports. They would, however, undermine newly passed state labor laws and fulfill their enduring goal of eviscerating the groundbreaking California Environmental Quality Act.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The state made Limbaugh possible.
The great flaw of liberalism: Assuming the opposition acts in any sort of good faith.
(And add to the linked piece: The elimination of the Fairness Doctrine.) 
 #URL# by #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like satire, isn't. #URL# by #USER#, #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mmm…nIf generals are focused on selling out on retirement then that can’t possibly skew their policy decisions, right? #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rising death rate and it being ignored by the establishment. #USER#-loving media: Neither a surprise.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dunno if interesting is quite the word. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Making anodyne comments about how vaccines are good becoming a firing offense tells you exactly where evangelicals are right now…”
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe these are posted in offices throughout the nation, no?
Via #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education in this country is an obscene shit show.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great moment in white-American history.
 #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to think that swing voters would see this as frightening insanity and be revolted, but who knows? Their track record is pretty bad. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How a failed state rolls. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too amused. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Punchline: the piece ran as an op-ed piece. The news side couldn’t have any reporter do this because, ⁦#USER#⁩? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I learned something.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Rainbow took me seven weeks to plow through while unemployed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s Porky’s nature. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read it; weep; see dateline; weep more.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Much to ponder here.
That the Ukraine matter is los-lose for the US won’t affect our leaders’ thinking probably.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Halsted had crossed the thin line from confidence to overconfidence and couldn’t go back.
* *
“[P]eople with the right amount of confidence share the credit when they succeed, but more importantly, accept the responsibility when they fail.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This bullshit cracks me up. It shouldn’t but it does. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lost in the waves of time, as it were. I remember her from the old days. Your turn. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American justice.
Straight from a failed state shithole. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If they do it but don't call it cancellation, then it isn't even if it is. What they call cancellation is cancellation no matter what the act they're referencing actually is.
No one's more honest than a conservative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This would be a great solution for the nation of ammosexuals. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can we get greater than this?? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Says everything about our times that a joke like this is possible. (That said, admitted: I was amused.)
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So men didn’t do it all. #HASHTAG# to the point of revisionism, so much history is about riding, not revealing.n #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate him for being on Team Obama, hate him for being a charter school grifter. He covers the spectrum! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I’ll bite: All those openings and people reassessing work/life: how many are shitty jobs and/or jobs not offering a living wage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And he’s not pushing for a theocratic US, right? Case closed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given Republicans' support, shouldn't the US be purple of something other than blue? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The funnies I tweet tend not to be actually funny but JFC this is probably the most depressing one yet. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, without resolving this, the problems at the border can't be fixed in any meaningful way.
Spoiler: Not happening, at least till the capitalist parasites allow it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know I feel safer because cops like these.n#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Appropriate thoughts and prayers.
Mostly around karma coming a’calling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The conservative/neoliberal/Republican response to Covid was literally murderous.
Hate to see how dysfunctional the nation has to get before enough people realize that the entire #USER# is unfit for office — if it’s not already too late (likely).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, nooo, not successful enough by a couple of magnitudes. They've earned a Sodom and Gomorrah moment. 
#URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>