<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[In 10 charts: State of Indian economy ahead of Union Budget 2022  #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obscene Comments against Muslim Women: Delhi Police Asks Clubhouse App About Chat Organiser's Details This comes days after hundreds of Muslim women were listed for auction on the Bulli Bai mobile application with photogr... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bhutan mourns rare Covid death, PM says it felt like a bullet-hit  #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's Valentine's Day, this must be Goa For more such web stories, click on the ET icon below. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CG Consumer shares  gain  1.92% as Sensex  rises On the technical charts, the RSI of the stock stood at 42.21. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From 'moonwalk' to dressing up as 'Yamraj', traffic cops get creative to spread road safety awareness Sandeep Singh from Gurgaon traffic police dressed up as Yamraj, the Lord of Death in Hindu mythology, to send across a... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chola Inv Finance shares  gain  0.08% as Sensex  rises A total of 86,810 shares changed hands on the counter till 01:30PM (IST) #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weddings solemnised in front of closed Tamil Nadu temple on lockdown day As many as 91 weddings were solemnised by priests on roads in front of the popular temple in this northern coastal district on Sunday, temple Execut... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Church Victims Push To Expand Lawsuit Window In Nebraska Victims of sexual abuse at the hands of Catholic priests urged Nebraska lawmakers on Friday to pass a law that would let people who were abused decades ago file law... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decoded: Will Air India have a successful take off under the Tatas?  #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Myanmar's year of turmoil: From coup to jailing of Suu Kyi  #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omicron in 79% of samples from Delhi sequenced in January, shows data The Omicron variant of coronavirus has been found in 79 per cent of the samples from Delhi sequenced between January 1 and January 23, data showed #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kotak Mahindra Bank Q3 Preview: Double-digit profit growth, flattish margin likely Analysts said Kotak should see a reduction in stress but the behaviour of the ECLGS lending pool &amp; restructured portfolio coupled with the... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mansukh Mandaviya to review Covid situation in 8 states, UTs on Friday Union Health Minister Mansukh Mandaviya will on Friday review the Covid situation and the public health preparedness to tackle the omicron spread #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daniil Medvedev not that disappointed by loss It was the second time Nadal had denied Medvedev in a Grand Slam decider #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr Reddy's Q3 Result: Profit declines 29% sequentially to Rs 707 crore, revenue down to Rs 5,320 crore We delivered a steady performance in Q3 with healthy EBITDA and strong cash generation, while continuing to invest in... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tatas to ensure smartly dressed cabin crew, better on-time performance, enhanced meals at Air India Cabin crew members have been instructed to address all passengers as "guests" and cabin crew supervisor will have to ensu... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IMF warns China's property stress poses spillover risk The International Monetary Fund's report comes as property firms in the world's second-biggest economy struggle with liquidity problems as Beijing looks to curb exces... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IAF Aircraft Makes Emergency Landing in Bihar Field, Both Pilots Safe The two-seater aircraft M-102 was being used by the Air Force Station of Gaya for training purposes. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stock market update: Stocks that hit 52-week lows on NSE Maruti Suzuki,  Power Grid,  HDFC Bank,  SBI and  HUL were among the top losers on NSE. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boston ties snow record as 'bomb cyclone' batters eastern US  #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mysterious Island With Hollow Centre Goes Viral, Sparks Curiosity Among Netizens Some Reddit users thought that the island was censored by Google Maps, citing a few examples of locations that are censored by the navigation... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran qualify for 2022 World Cup finals with 1-0 win over Iraq Iran confirmed their spot in the 2022 World Cup finals in Qatar, with a 1-0 victory over Iraq at the Azadi Stadium in Tehran on Thursday. It was Team Melli's s... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adani Total Gas wins 14 out of 52 city gas licences, Indian Oil Corp 8 Hyderabad-based Megha Engineering and Infrastructure Ltd (MEIL) won 13 GAs #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Azam Khan's son Abdullah Azam, says don't trust anyone, 'police can shoot me'  #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heavy Rains Cause Landslides And Flooding In So Paulo, Killing 18 Landslides and flooding from heavy rains in Sao Paulo state have killed at least 18 people since Friday, including seven children, public safety officials... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mahindra Group donates 500 LPM Oxygen Plant to Govt hospital in Telangana Ruzbeh Irani, President - Group Human Resources and Communications, said: "Intending to emerge stronger from the pandemic, we at Mahindra have part... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will China dominate the world of semiconductors? America and its allies are crafting rules to try to prevent it #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indias strategic partnership with France is a visible partnership: Jaishankar These comments by Jaishankar were made at a virtual event titled "The French Presidency: EU-India Partnership in the Indo Pacific" in the prese... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prospects of stable long-term growth, cheer on Budget hopes positive for markets The earnings season has just started, and the results are expected to be more or less in line with expectations, except for the ones where t... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manipur Elections 2022: BJP to contest on all 60 seats, CM Biren Singh to fight from Heingang  #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New virus rules put Djokovic at risk of missing French Open France is tightening its vaccination rules in a way that could put Novak Djokovic at risk of missing the French Open. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sensex tanks 884 points from high, ends 77 pts lower; Nifty holds 17,100 level  #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Southern states account for nearly half of India's total Covid infections One in 5 Covid infections originated from southern states until a fortnight ago, shows data #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fino Payments Bank Q3 net profit doubles to Rs 14 crore It had posted net profit of Rs 6.52 crore in quarter ended December 2020. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 bank and infra stocks to bet on now: Dipan Mehta We are on thin ice but investors should not get too perturbed. We just have to ride out this wave of selling pressure and volatility and focus on good quality companies.... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caught in the crossfire, power corporation NTPC urges railways to rename rail tests The Railway exams have been in the news for the last week over large-scale protests over certain irregularities in its screening process.... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maha govt, FDA crack down on oil manufacturers to check on adulteration The Maharashtra food, civil supplies and consumer protection department and the Food and Drug Administration (FDA) conducted a series of raids at edi... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Louisiana: Conditions After Ida Killed 280M Fish Inland Conditions after Hurricane Ida last summer killed about 280 million fish in inland waters  about 40% more than died in Louisiana waters after Hurricane Andrew in 199... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia's risky options following Ukraine attack Russia, which is seeking a pledge that NATO won't expand to include Ukraine, has options it could pursue short of a full-blown invasion, and other ways to lash out at the U.... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greek PM Survives Censure Motion Tabled Over Snowstorm Greek Prime Minister Kyriakos Mitsotakis on Sunday won a confidence vote called by the main opposition over his government's handling of a snowstorm last week that st... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chalet Hotels posts revenues of Rs 164 cr for December quarter, losses at Rs 14.3 cr The company posted losses of Rs 14.3 crore compared to Rs 31 crore in the quarter ended December 31, 2020. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budget 2022-23: FPIs bat for equal taxation on dividends and buybacks Experts say current situation can lead to double taxation #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UP Elections 2022: Amit Shah holds door-to-door campaign in Muzaffarnagar  #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The World Outside: The Ukraine Crisis is Closer Home for India than You Think With an increased tussle between Indias comprehensive strategic partner, the US, and special and privileged strategic partner, Russia, articula... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[69-year-old 'wrong step' of nationalisation of private airlines has been corrected: Jyotiraditya Scindia The government formally handed over the airline to Tata Group at a ceremony held in the national capital on Thursday... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Share market update: Most active stocks on D-Street today in terms of volume The NSE Nifty index was trading 208.45 points  up  at 17318.6 #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad bank starts rolling, to take up Rs 50,000 cr of accounts While the assets will be on the books of NARCL an entity controlled by public sector banks, its resolution will be managed by Indian Debt Resolution Co Ltd (IDR... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[21 Employees Served 'Show Cause' In JK's Kishtwar For Being Absent During Duty Hours Authorities served show cause' notices to 21 employees who were found absent during a surprise visit at government offices in Kishtwar d... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Karnataka Edu Min Calls Wearing Hijab 'Indiscipline', Dubs Muslim Women's Protest 'Political' as Students Stand Firm Eight students of the college have been protesting for months in the college campus for being denied ent... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Love Story on Netflix Aims to Show There Is More to Afghanistan Than War Three Songs for Benazir tries to avoid politics even as the Taliban takeover of Afghanistan looms over the film. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nifty February futures trade at premium Bharti Airtel, Infosys and Reliance Industries (RIL) most active in futures segment. #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singhu border lynching: Accused sent to police remand for a week The body of Lakhbir Singh, a labourer from Punjab's Tarn Taran district, was found on Friday tied to a barricade at the Delhi-Haryana border where the anti-fa... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agri Picks Report: Geojit According to Geojit , Prices of natural rubber in India have been on a fall after hitting an eight-year high in November and are likely to remain weak for the next few weeks due to bearish fundam... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foreign exodus from India stocks threatens to reduce key support Foreign institutional investors have been net sellers every month since September, dumping $7.9 billion worth of local shares since #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# Standard #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 60% kids aged 15-18 years received first dose of COVID-19 vaccine: Health minister "Congratulations to all my young friends who have got vaccinated. Over 60 per cent children aged 15-18 years have received their firs... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nine entities settle case of alleged AIF rules violations with Sebi The adjudication proceedings initiated against the nine entities under the show cause notice issued in March 2021 have been disposed of, Sebi said #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# Standard #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Open final: Rafael Nadal edges Medvedev in five-set thriller  #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG#Line #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning Digest | Pakistan sends India a plea by Hindu body for air pilgrimage; Houses of Parliament to work in shifts, and more A select list of stories to read before you start your day #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man Tries Out Raw Meat Experiment to See if Survival is Possible on Uncooked Food As part of his experiment, the man has also opened an Instagram page Raw Meat Experiment where he posts his daily update of eating raw meat... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Map Captures Only One Foot in Photo, Reddit Users Have a Good Laugh Truly, technology can spring the best laughs from time to time! #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shanti Educatio Standalone December 2021 Net Sales at Rs 1.01 crore, up 464.5% Y-o-Y NULL #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congress ducks Twitter reply to Rahul Gandhi, targets Centre After the Twitter responded to Gandhi on Thursday - a day after international media reported about Gandhi's month-old letter to Twitter chief Parag Aggarwal - t... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alleged Maduro co-conspirator says CIA knew about coup plans Cliver Alcals attorneys believe his activities were communicated at the highest levels of a number of U.S. government agencies including the CIA, Treasury and J... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Success Has No Age Limit': 66-year-old Man from Udupi Swims with Hands, Legs Tied Gangadhar Kadekar from Udupi entered the Golden Book of World Records by swimming 3.5 km like a dolphin i.e. with his hands and legs chain... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video of African Women Injecting Chicken Stock In Butts to Make Them Bigger is Viral Again The injection was easily accessible and a lot cheaper than any plastic or any other surgery. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BJP brought development to Goa, raised budget from 432 to 2,567 cr: Amit Shah  #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soaking Up the Sun: Delhi's Day Temperature Rises to 20.6 Degree Celsius It was after 19 days that the mercury crossed the 20 degree-Celsius mark in Delhi. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How alternative financing is empowering small businesses growth  #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US economy grows at annualised 6.9% in the fourth quarter of 2021 The US economy grew at an annual rate of 6.9% in the fourth quarter of 2021 amid a surge in inventories, the Commerce Department reported. #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buy SBI Life Insurance Company, target price Rs 1250:  Kotak Securities SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd., incorporated in the year 2000, is a Large Cap company (having a market cap of Rs 121199.33 Crore) operating in Finan... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arjun Erigaisi wins Tata Steel Challengers with a round to spare Grandmaster Arjun Erigaisi became the fourth Indian player after P Harikrishna, B Adhiban and Vidit Gujrathi to win the Tata Steel Challengers event at Wijk... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla beats on profit but no Cybertruck, new vehicles this year The automaker, headquartered in Texas, reported fourth-quarter earnings of $2.88 billion #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amid chill in relations, new PLA history returns spotlight to 1962 war The downturn in ties has coincided with greater interest in China in the 1962 war, which hasnt been covered as extensively in the media as Korean War... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quebec Major Junior Hockey League To Resume Thursday The Quebec Major Junior Hockey League will resume activities Thursday following a weekslong break because of COVID19 complications. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A historic moment Air India privatisation is a milestone in India's reforms #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Rahul Dravid the coach, the honeymoon period is over NULL #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netaji Subhas Chandra Bose's statue should reflect grandeur of his personality, says Kin Chandra Bose has written a letter to the PM urging him to discuss the statue-related details through a virtual meeting for "the stat... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Bengal: Constitutional duties hasn't been performed by CM Mamata Banerjee, alleges Guv Dhankhar  #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homophobic UK Couple Refuses to Sell House to Gay Men Citing the Bible The Christian couple refused to show or sell the place to the gay partners citing a verse from the Bible. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What CEOs Are Saying About Inflation Leaders from Apple, McDonalds, Southwest and other companies share what they are seeing and doing about rising prices. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UP Polls 2022: Congress leader Maulana Tauqeer Raza's daughter-in-law Nida Khan joins BJP  #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officials ID Indian Family Who Died Trying To Cross Into US Officials in Ottawa said Thursday they have confirmed the identities of four Indian nationals whose bodies were found frozen in Manitoba near the CanadaU. S. bor... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barty and Djokovic keep No.1 ranking; Collins into top 10 Novak Djokovic, with 20 grand slam titles, will continue as No. 1 despite missing the Australian Open #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking a sneak peek at new CEA V Anantha Nageswaran's thoughts Here are his commentaries on a few key issues #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# : Google reports soaring attrition among Black women : Civil rights groups and activist investors are pressuring Silicon Valley companies such as Google to bring more women and racial minorities into leadership, conten... by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Renault-Nissan to ally more in $26 bn EV bet The two-decade old alliance, which also includes Mitsubishi Motors, said it would increase the number of common platforms for electric vehicles (EV) to five from four. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Pa. Dems To Miss Biden Visit, Cite Scheduling Conflicts President Joe Biden will appear in Pittsburgh on Friday as an opening step in a broader campaign to promote the White House's achievements in key states ahead of... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China: UN Council Should Try To Avoid Civil War On Myanmar Chinas U.N. ambassador said Friday the U.N. Security Councils primary goal in strifetorn Myanmar should be to avoid more violence and a civil war. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gay's 30-yard FG Lifts Rams Over Brady, Buccaneers 30-27 Matthew Stafford threw for 366 yards and two touchdowns and Matt Gays 30yard field goal as time expired lifted the Los Angeles Rams to a 3027 divisional playoff vic... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government settles over Rs 61,000 crore Air India debt, other liabilities before transfer to Tatas The airline had a total debt of Rs 61,562 crore as of August 31, 2021. Of this, the Tata Group took over Rs 15,300 crore a... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LIC to list on bourses by March 31, says DIPAM Secretary 'LIC disinvestment amount will be included in this year's (Budget) because we aim to list it before March 31,' says Tuhin Kanta Pandey #HASHTAG# Stories by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laffans Petro Standalone December 2021 Net Sales at Rs 7.47 crore, up 65.89% Y-o-Y NULL #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal Bank shares  rise  2.05% as Nifty  gains The stock quoted a 52-week high price of Rs 107.65 and a 52-week low of Rs 69.0. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curefoods merges with rival Maverix to create cloud-kitchen giant Following the merger with Maverix, which operates over 50 outlets across Delhi, Mumbai, and Bengaluru, Curefoods will have 125 kitchens across 12 cities, m... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[H1-B Visa Registration for FY 2023 to Start from March 1: USCIS The H-1B visa is a non-immigrant visa that allows US companies to employ foreign workers in speciality occupations that require theoretical or technical expe... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taliban hold first talks in Europe since Afghan takeover  #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tax when you want to spend Raise the tax-GDP ratio to finance rising revenue expenditure #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Page Industries stock price  up  3.89 per cent as Sensex  climbs As of 31-Dec-2021, promoters held 0.0 per cent stake in the company, while FIIs held 25.07 per cent and domestic institutional investors had 12.68 per cent. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crypto: currencies, assets, or nothing? The tale of Indian regulators and cryptocurrencies goes back many years. We can perhaps peg its beginning somewhere in the summer of 2018 when Bitcoin first made global headlines. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Priyanka Gandhi speaks to protesting railway job aspirants "Don't get afraid. Ensure that elections are held on your issues of your employment. The government did not give you job but commit atrocities on you and suppress... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super sub Kiyan Nassiri powers ATK MB past SC EB Performs a hat-trick, helps his side climb into the top four #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FIR against Shweta Tiwari for hurting religious sentiments with 'bra' comment  #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep Fighting: Netizens Ask Suicidal 23-Year-Old Not To Give Up On Life Reddit users got together to motivate this 23-year-old and urged him to be positive in life and keep fighting. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 75% of India's adult population fully vaccinated against COVID-19 In a remarkable achievement for India, over 75 per cent of the country's adult population are now fully vaccinated against COVID-19, Union Health Mini... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Remain friends' despite no tie-up with NCP-Shiv Sena in Goa, says P Chidambaram Chidambaram, who is the Congress' senior election observer for the Goa Assembly polls, also hit out at the TMC for its barbs at the Congress... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon, UPS, Exxon Are on Deck to Report Earnings in Coming Week Other heavyweights set to report quarterly results in the week ahead include techs Alphabet and Meta Platforms, and auto makers GM and Ford. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawmaker Who Made Anti-Asian Slur Is Resigning, Cites Health A Delaware lawmaker who came under fire last year for using a racist and sexist slur to refer to sex workers is resigning, House Democratic officials said Frida... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India to host slew of Oman's defence teams &amp; joint exercises to bolster military ties amid China Indian Ocean forays Dr. Mohammed Bin Nasser Bin Ali AL Zaabi, Secretary General of the Ministry of Defence of Oman will visi... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banks in talks with NESL to set up loan registry, information utility "The aim is to increase the efficiency in exchange of information in the consortium arrangement," said a senior bank executive aware of the development... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Karnataka Man Robs Bank to Arrange Money for Own Wedding, Gets Caught After Dramatic Chase by Cops A cash reward of Rs 25,000 has been announced for both the policemen who helped catch the robber. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amid defections playing key role, states head for Assembly polls SP had poached backward caste leaders Lalji Verma and Ram Achal Rajbhar from BSP a few months back. They now figure in the SP list with Verma from Katehari... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch | India's only athlete at the 2022 Winter Olympics A video profile on alpine skier Arif Khan who will represent India in the Winter Olympics #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UP Polls 2022: Several SP, BSP and Congress leaders join BJP in Lucknow  #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eoin Morgan to miss rest of T20 series vs West Indies England skipper Eoin Morgan has been ruled out of the final two Twenty20 matches against the West Indies due to a quadriceps injury. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French Left Runs Divided, Weakened In Presidential Race Paris, Jan 30 (AP) The French left is running divided and weakened in this year's presidential race as at least five mainstream presidential candidates have rejected... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Invests $1 Billion In Airtel For Shaping India's Digital Ecosystem, Takes 1.28% Stake The two companies will also focus on shaping and growing the cloud ecosystem in India to accelerate their digital transformation... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kane Asks Fans To Keep An Open Mind As He Joins Oilers Evander Kane knows he will not be universally loved by by fans of the Edmonton Oilers. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Street View Camera Catches Man Squatting on Top of Car; Reddit Users React The man still got his pants on. Seems like hes just making adjustments to tie bikes on top of the car, said a user. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raiders To Go Patriot Way With New GM, Possibly Coach The Las Vegas Raiders are trying to build their team the Patriot Way. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[106 Deaths in Delhi in January Due to Cold, Claims NGO; Officials Deny Officers of the Delhi Police however acknowledged that the number of deaths among homeless people suffering from medical issues goes up during winters... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amarjothi Spinning Mills standalone net profit declines 3.79% in the December 2021 quarter Sales rise 22.17% to Rs 50.37 crore #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CSC, Infosys to upskill 6 cr. rural people They will impart digital skills to students aged 10 to 22 #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[B2B ecommerce startup Moglix valued at $2.6 billion after $250 million of funding Founded in 2015,  Moglix works with manufacturing and infrastructure companies to help streamline their end-to-end supply chain, from procu... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mexican TV Host Lashes Out at Anti-vaxxers, Calls Them 'Moron' in On-air Rant Leonardo Schwebel, in his on-air rant, called the anti-vaxxers 'morons' and asked them to wear a mask while clutching one in his hand. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Native American Tribe, New Mexico Ink Water Leasing Deal A Native American tribe has agreed to lease more of its water to help address dwindling supplies in the Colorado River Basin, officials announced Thursday. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hyderabad Race Club ex secretary Nari Reddy passes away He was the longest serving secretary of HRC #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[49ers All-Pro LT Trent Williams Questionable For Title Game San Francisco 49ers AllPro left tackle Trent Williams is questionable for the NFC championship after missing practice all week with a sprained ankle. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bridge collapses, drops city bus into Pittsburgh ravine A 50-year-old bridge collapsed in Pittsburgh early Friday, requiring rescuers to rappel nearly 150 feet (46 meters) and form a human chain to reach occupants of a bu... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[June sentence set for Ghislaine Maxwell in sex traffic case Ghislaine Maxwell was convicted after a month-long trial in which prosecutors maintained that she recruited and groomed teenage girls for Jeffrey Epstein to sexu... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dairy Farmers Making Chocolates, Competing With World-class Companies, Says Andhra CM Jagan Reddy The State Government has signed two MoUs with Amul for the purchase of Milk for Balamrutham and Anganwadi kids, in the pres... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soon, no fuel without valid pollution-under-check certificate in Delhi The city government will put a draft policy in this regard in the public domain #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Share market update: Most active stocks in today's market in terms of volume The NSE Nifty index closed 8.2 points  down  at 17101.95 #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All educational institutions in Telangana to reopen from February 1 Education Minister P Sabita Indra Reddy said COVID-19 norms should be followed strictly in the educational institutions. She said school managements, tea... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long Covid: Mild infections can lead to hidden lung damage People with even mild Covid infections are likely to have hidden damage to their lungs after an initial bout of illness, a small pilot study in the UK has shown #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SpiceJet gets 3 weeks to settle Credit Suisse dispute The BSE-listed SpiceJet has challenged the Madras High Court order of January 11, allowing the winding-up petition filed by Credit Suisse against the company for defau... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McGusty Helps Carry ACC-leader Miami To 73-62 Win Kameron McGusty scored 20 points and ACCleader Miami held off a late Georgia Tech run for a 7362 win on Saturday. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# : Living on margins, Hungary's Roma feel especially exposed to coronavirus, Leaders of Hungary's Roma people said on Tuesday the coronavirus pandemic posed a grave threat to the already precarious status of the marginalised minority... by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From encouraging startups to making healthcare accessible: Dr Rana Mehta's budget recommendations  #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buy RBL Bank, target price Rs 200:  CLSA RBL Bank Ltd., incorporated in the year 1943, is a banking company (having a market cap of Rs 9009.74 Crore). #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NDMC clears proposals for transfer of lands for Delhi Metro Ph-4 projects The NDMC cleared multiple proposals for transfer of plots of land for projects under the Phase-4 of the Delhi Metro, officials said. #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sabally Scores 23, No. 19 Oregon Rolls Past USC 80-48 Nyara Sabally scored 23 points  on 9of12 shooting and No. 19 Oregon rolled to an 8048 win over USC on Sunday. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK PM Johnson Has Not Been Interviewed by Police Over Party Investigation -spokesman Boris Johnsons office has not yet received civil servant Sue Grays report into the possible lockdown breaches. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No peace in Myanmar 1 year after military takeover The army takeover in Myanmar a year ago that ousted Aung San Suu Kyi not only unexpectedly aborted the country's fledgling return to democracy: It also brought a surprisi... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tamilisai Soundararajan Slams Trolls Body Shaming Sai Pallavi, Says Such 'Mockery Hurts' After Shyam Singha Roy release, trolls had targeted and body shamed actor Sai Pallavi. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aces Sportsman of the year nominees Neeraj, Ravi and Pramod make it to the Sportstar Awards shortlist #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghanistan's Taliban Battle Rebellion by Ethnic Minority Fighters Some Uzbeks have taken up arms in the countrys north, complaining of discrimination amid economic collapse. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mumbai's COVID-19 cases drop to 1,384; 12 die, active tally below 20,000 Mumbai on Thursday recorded 1,384 fresh cases of COVID-19, down from 1,858 a day ago, while 12 more people died due to complications related to the... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mercedes with Rs 2.5 Lakh 'Unaccounted Cash' Impounded in Greater Noida The seizure was made in Greater Noida's Bisrakh area on Thursday, a day after the police in adjoining Noida impounded a Porsche car in a similar case... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Pics: Nadal comes from two sets down to make history with 21st Slam  #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bishop Lifts George Washington Over Fordham 64-55 James Bishop had 25 points as George Washington got past Fordham 6455 on Sunday. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# : Nigerian police free children, pregnant teens from 'baby factory', Police in southeastern Nigeria raided a child trafficking facility holding at least 23 children and four pregnant teenagers, a police spokesman said on Thursday. by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sufficient provisions under existing laws to stop forcible conversions, says Kejriwal The BJP has been targeting the AAP over the issue. The BJP-ruled Uttar Pradesh had earlier passed a bill aimed at curbing religious con... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Catalyst hires Anand Chandrasekaran for its India play In his role as a General Catalysts partner and investor, Anand Chandrasekaran will focus on startup investments in India and the US. As an angel investor, he... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Zero capitulation in equity positioning' despite selloff, says BofA "Note zero capitulation in equity positioning", the research note read, adding that year-to-date, $84 billion has poured into markets and only 2 out of... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budget 2022-23: Clarity on PSB privatisation is expected, say brokerages Some clarity on the privatisation of two public sector banks, announced in last year's Budget, is expected #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sensex  rises! But these  stocks are down 5% or more on BSE In the Nifty pack, 47 stocks were trading in the green, while 3 stocks were trading in the red. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massner Leads W. Illinois Past St. Thomas (MN) 81-52 Trenton Massner had 20 points as Western Illinois romped past St. Thomas (MN) 8152 on Saturday. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UN says Lebanon's economic crisis blights Syrian refugees More than 1 million Syrian refugees in crisis-hit Lebanon are experiencing deteriorating conditions that have left nine out of ten of them in extreme #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All you didn't know about Union Budget For more such web stories, click on the ET icon below #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sensex, Nifty turn range bound; breadth strong The benchmark indices traded in a range during mid-morning trade. All the sectoral indices on the NSE were in the green. The Nifty continued to hover above 17,300 level. #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USISPF recommends urgent action to address distortions and inefficiencies in the banking sector Washington DC-based USISPF, which represents leading Fortune 500 companies, in a set of recommendations argued that to improv... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Portuguese Parties Wrap Up Campaign; Sunday Election Wide Open Waving colourful flags and shouting political slogans, hundreds of people took to Lisbon's streets on Friday to support candidates as they wrapped up two week... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pharmaceuticals firm Laurus Labs Q3 net drops 43% to Rs 155 crore Pharmaceuticals firm Laurus Labs said its consolidated net profit declined by 43 per cent to Rs 154.97 crore for the third quarter ended December 31, 2021. #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At The Pegasus, Life Is Good Runs Away From Knicks Go Life Is Good went to the lead right away and stayed there, winning the $3 million Pegasus World Cup with ease Saturday and denying Knicks Go what would have been a sto... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Federal Reserve's inflation measure hits nearly 40-year high A key inflation measure closely watched by the US Federal Reserve rose at the fastest pace in nearly 40 years in December 2021 #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vatican Website Gives Space To Group Demanding Female Priesthood The Vatican has given space on its website to a Catholic group that demands the ordination of women priests during consultations ahead of a key meeting next... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India's wheat shipment to Afghanistan via Pakistani soil to begin in early February: Report India has been pitching for providing unimpeded humanitarian aid to Afghanistan to address the unfolding humanitarian crisis in t... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gehri dosti says Israel PM about ties with India Countries mark 30 years of diplomatic relations #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stock market update: Nifty Bank index  advances  0.63% in  an upbeat  market The Nifty Bank index was trading 0.63 per cent  up  at 38221.6. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adar Poonawalla wants booster gap to be cut to 6 months Pune-based SII's Covishield and Bharat Biotech's Covaxin were granted conditional market authorisation by India's drug regulator on Thursday. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to teach children about climate change, inspire hope and take action to change the future When young people perceive that adults are not taking substantial action on climate change and when their voices go unheard, th... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Memorial Announced For 3 Firefighters Killed In Collapse Fire officials in Baltimore announced plans Friday for a memorial for three firefighters who died earlier this week after a vacant rowhome partially collapsed, trap... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Naorem Roshan does it for Bengaluru FC against Kerala Blasters Win takes Bengaluru side to joint third #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All eyes on Union Budget, to be key market driver next week Analysts foresee a growth-friendly budget but also expect the government to lay out a path for fiscal consolidation #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[View: Fed action has implications for Indias budget, like GoIs borrowing costs going up Tantrums could mean some more selling pressure in stock and bond markets, and some cooling off in the seemingly overheated commodity... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best of BS Opinion: Win-win indeed, Modi's truths &amp; govt's credibility Here are the top BS Opinion articles of the day #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['No Need to Panic': Experts Allay Fears as NeoCoV is Old Virus, Not Dangerous to Humans in Current Form Experts say that the virus does not pose threat as of now and regular surveillance of such viruses are essential in u... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lydia Ko Holds Off Danielle Kang To Win At Boca Rio On LPGA Lydia Ko pulled ahead with a birdie on the 15th hole and matched scores with Danielle Kang the rest of the way, closing with a 3under 69 for a oneshot victory on... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chiefs Release NFL Player Damon Arnette After Vegas Arrest NFL cornerback Damon Arnette was arrested in Las Vegas on suspicion of weapons and drug offenses, prompting him to be released by his latest team, the Kansas City... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apollo Hospital shares  up  4.29% as Nifty  gains A total of 13,058 shares changed hands on the counter till 10:00AM (IST). #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bharat Biotech Gets Nod for Phase-3 Trials of Covid-19 Intra-Nasal Vaccine The trials will evaluate BBV154 nasal vaccine for both the two-dose primary schedule and booster dose schedule. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buy Astec Lifesciences; target of Rs 2120: ICICI Direct ICICI Direct is bullish on Astec Lifesciences recommended buy rating on the stock with a target price of Rs 2120 in its research report dated January 26, 2022. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty sets out to break Russian 'propaganda wall' The West has repeatedly accused Russia of spreading disinformation to justify its cause, while Russia says the Western view of the crisis is d... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspired by 'Drishyam', a Family Planned the Perfect Crime, but They Ignored a Vital Detail The Bengaluru family fooled police once by staging a gold robbery. But they lucked out during the second time when police looked... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alden Hedge Fund Appeals To Investors In News Publisher Lee The Alden Global Capital hedge fund is sending its own appeal to shareholders of newspaper publisher Lee Enterprises as part of its campaign to acquire the compa... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Akuchie Powers Youngstown State Past Milwaukee 86-72 Michael Akuchie scored a careerhigh 33 points to propel Youngstown State to an 8672 victory over Milwaukee on Saturday. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dollar Gains As Wall Street Retreats On Future Fed Hikes U.S. stocks retreated on Thursday after a solid opening, while the dollar gained as investors prepared for future rate hikes from the Federal Reserve. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USD 426 Million Mega Millions Lottery Ticket Sold In California Los Angeles (AP) A single ticket sold in Southern California matched all six numbers and was the lucky winner of the USD 426 million Mega Millions jackpot pr... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India's Ather targets 1 million electric scooters a year as demand soars By Aditi Shah #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magnitude 6.6 quake strikes Kermadec Islands region - USGS  #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Louisville's Pegues Set For Challenge, 'Not My First Rodeo' A relaxed-looking Mike Pegues said he is ready for the challenge ahead as Louisvilles interim mens basketball coach, noting Friday with a laugh that this isnt my... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man United player Mason Greenwood arrested on suspicion of rape Manchester United player Mason Greenwood was arrested on suspicion of rape and assault on Sunday after a woman posted visual and audio allegations on social... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Move Over, Meme Stocks: Retail Investors Go Back to Blue Chips Individual investors have returned to favoring broad market funds and shares of the biggest U.S. companies. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decks cleared for setting up of Bad Bank, SBI chairman says all approvals received The National Asset Restructuring Company (NARCL) or what is popularly called a bad bank will help lenders in cleaning up their books by ac... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budget to hold the reins on raising import duties, sources say A slowly stabilizing trade deficit has given the government room to put off raising import duties at the moment, sources say. #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rakesh Tikait slams govt, says farmers would observe 'Betrayal Day' on Monday The movement was suspended on the basis of a letter given by the government on December 9 but those promises have not been fulfilled," Tikait s... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 Hindu bodies seek to intervene as parties in SC in PIL alleging hate speeches against Muslims Two Hindu organisations, 'Hindu Sena' and Hindu Front for Justice, have moved the Supreme Court seeking to intervene as parti... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delhi records 4,044 Covid cases, 25 deaths; positivity rate down to 8.60% The national capital's case count increased to 176,441 #HASHTAG# News by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daily Voice | Even if no reforms are announced, it will still be a good budget, says Anuj Jain of Green Portfolio Budget 2022 | Manufacturing is one of the sectors that will be in the limelight again. Further, Renewable e... #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>