<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC &amp; Celebs are telling lies. 

Your license fee pays only for 'technical' broadcasting. All the talent, creative assets and content is owned by a shell game of mysterious private sector companies  which are not wholly owned by BBC. 

It's already structured for privatization. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He won't be trusted by any, and having betrayed them a recall petition surely needs to be launched.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One simple question, how? 10 000 Spanish workers work in Gib, the adjacent region of Spain relies entirely on Gib for it's prosperity. 

So, are the EU going to throw part of Spain under the Blue Bus just to try and look clever? 

Spexit here we come!

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another fake headline, it's only about Ireland not overall UK booming trade figures. This is how the disenguous media work. Misleading headlines in hope you wouldn't read the article. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# For people who voted leave not having a clue I'd say the evidence is somewhat more to contrary. Your assertion just reveals none of the remainers ever, ever, 'got it'. We're good thanks, so, that's it. You lost, can't imagine how shit you feel baby. Well, I can actually, lovely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today Keir Starmer accused the PM of being under personal criminal investigation, Starmer said to the House that was happening and that the investigation constituted proof of criminal wrongdoing by virtue of being carried out. No evidence of any of it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You didn't even listen to Dick did you. They work closely with the Cabinet office, have stepped in at request of Cabinet office (Gray) to assess findings. MET already excluded several No10 events as not breaching laws. Investigating others across Whitehall. So ignorant of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ian, explain logic of NSII, buying more gas from Russia which plays energy politics, EU wants conflict with, constantly agitating. All the reasons gas is currently volatile. You want more of that lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Had billions more than that. Next dim wit. Even  Court said it wasn't lies and totally true. That was years ago, see how your cut paste is all out of date.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just bullshit. They are now perpetuating and reinventing the lefties fake narrative of Tory rebellion. Just make up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yo are confused, rules you point to don't apply in workplaces where distancing wasn't always possible. These are not households mixing. See what an idiot you made of yourself using an extract of the wrong rules. Pretty stupid just posting what others tell you to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So in other words she knows sweet FA because of course Police report daily to scribblers about ongoing investigations #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Still inhabiting the delusional SNP echo chamber, get out into the real world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Remainers have raised second rate Tories up to create a coven to attack from. I thought 1922 was supposed to be seasoned operators not fecking children sacked as Ministers for incompetence and stay behind 34 year old remainers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I can tell the stupid ones joined SNP - Independence will shatter your economy, no trade deals, like Truss gets done. Be worse than Greece when it crashed. No currencies, no trade partners, no central bank. Slave state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labour are looking more like the Nazi Party. Has anyone else noticed their first response to their own MPs taking alternate stance on women's safe spaces or any opposition figure is to hound, dehumanize and demonize with 100% unrelenting and pure hatred. It's what the Nazis did. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real reason Meghan Markle wants HER private security in UK not Palace security is to prevent Harry refusing to return to US and staying in UK with the kids she holds hostage. 

WAKE UP

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard core bed wetting from main stream media, it's getting delicious. I can feel the sense of panic from them. Having called Gray a whitewash and demanding MET Police act they are now in meltdown having realized Police response will shut down party gate. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minster of lies, sacked for telling lies, MP #USER# got a £700 an hour job doing something she had no relevant skills or domain expertise to do. 

Opposition silent about sacked Minister who lied to parliament getting £60k bung for influence! 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# zzzzzzzzz only since she heard Boris likely to do the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Read the article it deals with the flight for animals, not the British and other staff. Really is a good idea to actually read something before you make assertions about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bloody hell, you really are a bed wetting idiot, look at your pathetic ranting, yet again you see a platform you tried to trespass on collapsing. You are Ebola to any cause you try to attach yourself to, It dies shortly after.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have yet to see advert with a white male and BAME partner, why do all mixed race couple have BAME male and white females? Haven't seen a BAME same sex couple either or Muslim same couple. Is that discrimination against LGBGT?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are we really supposed to believe that interests rates rising from a quarter of a percent is unusual or having rates in low single figures is bad?  

Near zero rates are unsustainable, disaster for savers and pensions, unrealistic in the extreme. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Anothe ridiot, German flag, Germany has ID cards, di wit. But we do know you just make it because you are a pro EU loser in the Brexit debate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BORIS SAVES EUROPE 

#USER# said Boris had  paralyzed Govt, but here we are, Boris is off to Ukraine to meet Putin and Truss heading to Moscow. 

Russia only takes Boris seriously, no one else in Europe or EU lickspittles. Press talk of letters!

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Empty words form the Chinese SPY party. A party full of anti-Semites, a party which shields pedophiles for votes. Do you all seriously believe anyone who matters falls for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labour have been trying to brans Tories Islamophobic ever since they got proven to be hostile to Jews and to harbor many, many anti-Semites. It's jus ta fake narrative o try and alienate Muslim voters and others of different faiths or colour form the Conservative Party. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ZZZZZZZZ when real people vote not fake polling sample groups, always different story. And, voter ID so much more secure elections to come. Keir is out anyway. Boris stays Labour will boot Starmer out for Rayner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# MET boss confirmed many of the events at No10 have bene ruled out of the investigation.  S no rule breaking. They are looking at other events across Whitehall estate so that will be remainer lefty Civil Servants in the line of fire. That's you twisted narrative done isn't it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz

May is a traitor who betrayed the British nation to EU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Which means sweet FA, and you 'understand' so you have no idea do you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 14 followers in 8yrs, repurposed profile for lefties to circulate left wing politically motivated independent sage nonsense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hate begets hate . . ever thus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did you see the Dick interview? Confirmed several No10 events ruled out from inquiry. Confirmed investigating several other events 'across Whitehall'. 

Looks very bad for leaky Civil Servants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pathetic Labour councilor claiming over 30 Tory MPs called for Boris to go yet even Scum Media report it as just 6. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just tell them if they are correct people will still pay by choice not compulsion so to stop being such drama queens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reality check, no way will Labour allow an Indy Ref. They are desperate for Labour Scots MPs in Westminster. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And it goes on, the anti-Semite stance of extremist Sultana revealed. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on folks, get your tweets on to our glorious PM. Everyday! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Not Brexit we voted for? Ballot was leave EU, we left. That's what it said. You have had to much Irn Bru Army cut paste propaganda. Come up with something original - can't can you and you are unable to support your EU Indy argument either. Did SNP not give you a cut paste.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not to mention their entire failure over ventilators, vaccines and Covid politics, blackmailing poor nations with vaccines while UK got them out to the world. Thieving products, means of production, even threatening to thieve away patents. Some pharma firms refused to supply EU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because they settled and invested money here, treat same as any others with major investments to make, any others from anywhere in the whole world. SO, as you can see, UK attracts massive investment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to Fire Up the Jumbo. 

Left will be bed wetting again as both Boris and Truss are overseas next week saving Europe from war again. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# What photos I have seen him sitting in Garden, groups of workers in social distanced clusters. No evidence of a party. It's part of workplace. Harrison you rely on lies and look like a brainwashed idiot. Show me a picture of a party, go on. Yu can't can you. Lies are all you have]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The real division is simply hard left linking up, student thugs and those who want a ruck. Notice when Lab in doesn't happen, that's because grown up Tories don't riot like idiots and respect democracy, the left doesn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It needs to be answered. These peopel will destroy our freedoms in a jot without any respect for democracy or due process. They will exploit anyone, any crises, demonize others without remorse. Just look how they operate. Hatred, demonization of others, endless personal attacks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remainers all denying return to normal, nothing unusual in that. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Ignorant of you, being there distanced, garden of his office and home doesn't make it a party or mean he partied. He was at a legal gathering alleged to be a party that is alleged to have broke rules so your statement is incorrect. It might already be cleared of breaking rules.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maybe we need an inquiry into your expenses and hate tweeting against leavers which you were sanctioned for just a few months ago and forced to remove the abusive tweets. Look to your own immoral and disingenuous conduct before attacking others. 
#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Well, you will be sh*t out of luck, he will lose his job before Boris. No evidence to suggest there will be a leadership contest in Tories, if so, Boris would likely win it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What about CCP agents, 'hey we don't like Boris, don't care who else is in No10, no other motivation, you don't like him, make a few quid, set up a scandal, who get hurt, just Boris, nasty Tory, no harm to UK if you already beleive he is the wrong guy . . ']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yeh more shit that never happened, did you explain the EU has several offshore corporate tax havens . . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# so many of them banging on about how its a trusted institution, if so let them give up some wages if they love it so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wouldn't be surprised if much that so called journalists get from inside the Tory Party is fed to them to keep Labour running around and looking like playground politicians not to mention to feed Starmer's last chance to secure his leadership. Setting the idiot up for a fall. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# MET will have their new powers - peopel will demand action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turns on Tory MP who had some second job income that called his independence to doubt, mock his wife's suicide, this is Rayner smirk the moment it was mentioned. 

Yet noone resigned over taking near £1000000 from the Chinese laundry. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Repurposed fake profile with 29 followers in 10 years . .typical of the profiles perpetuate the lies about photo ID, you won't debate will you because you know the Bill provided for local authorities to provide photo ID free of charge where required. Sultana's fake followers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# threads backed up by these fake followers, like this one 8 yr old profile, 9 followers and history redacted. Scribblers like Dan rely on these fakes. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# maybe you are just stupid and think they were, no evidence to support you idiocy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You like the BBC - you pay for it. Nice to see lefties bed wetting as party gate flops and Starmer looks like the one who'll be gone soon. Suck it up losers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Ewen, Ghani was sacked for telling lies to parliament, after due process and independent investigation. She's a proven liar simply making up allegations to try and cleanse her reputation. We Tory members just laugh at her lies. She hasn't any credibility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have no sympathy for rabid left who lost people, they chortled and wished death on Boris when he had Covid or refused to condemn those of their ilk who did. Same over old people and Brexit, Prince Phillips death. I always said careful what you all wish for. They should reflect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Doing so much better than Italy though, G7 leading economy, less deaths per head than Italy, full employment. Worlds leading vax discovery and deployment, so where did it go wrong, oh, nowhere, you just hate Brexit. Yet you wrap yourself in the dead to pretend you are bothered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Labour MP and Acid threat. Respect! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More nonsense, what, farmers going to knock down and plough up listed monuments lol  Give me a break. No surprise anti Brexit rhetoric and scare mongering is back is it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So lets wait and see you demand sick lefties jailed for blocking ambulances.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just media speculation, trying to get MPs looking over their shoulders, there was no red wall rebellion. One traitor who was left plant all along.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Khalid Mahmood is another extremist and anti-Semite. Why do you platform these hate mongering people. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Dream on lol You are so deluded. Come see what happens after 3pm, Starmer will be first to resign, I give him 8 weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another fake narrative - rebellion of the 12 failed, no MPs are challenging Boris because they never were. Gutless Gnasher and Dirty Wragge didn't have to nuts to so pretending others should have. No one serious wanted to join their playground rebellion. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lefties are not liking MET Police involvement are they. Having squealed for Police to investigate because Gray report would be a whitewash now they will have nowhere to go. The 6-12 tory rebels must be bed wetting now, nowhere to hide as many a leaky civil servant will be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Maybe because the claim is utter nonsense and no crimes were committed. See how dim wit media has dug a big dark hole for itself. All the bed wetting over nothing Tim, we will enjoy how pathetic media look when the hate campaign fails.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Behold FEMI, Behold STOOOOOOOOOOOOPID

Translation 'I hate Boris Johnson so will post a profoundly disingenuous and divisive tweet insulting voters, while complaining about people saying divisive things'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fake narrative rolls along - the last resort of 'racism' and 'islamophobia' has been made. Why, because the left think it's a denouncement that ends all things, it doesn't, it's just a play before she crosses the house. Let em blow. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So as your pathetic party gate is about to fail you all suddenly say, oh we missed one lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is #USER# or #USER# being interviewed anywhere today, I doubt it since car crash Starmer yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labour's outstanding achievement of the week #USER# Shows Labour live in a perverse echo chamber. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Truss is of to Moscow to meet trade counterparts, Boris is heading for Ukraine and invited face to face even on the other side of the border with Putin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stand out achievements of #USER# tenure as DPP. Plus add the London Bridge murder he did a soft plea bargain with that enabled him to be released ad MURDER two people. Oh and, tried to protect Islamic Asian organized trafficking pedo gangs to save Labour votes. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Oh look record exports lol thanks to UK trade deals that Scotland will lose access to. Blows your remoaning out the water doesn't it. See how your England hating lies fail.  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Labour are trying to re write Covid history and blame Boris for their own mess in Wales and in England for trying to undermine the Govts, now proven successful, Covid response - they want want someone to blame, it's all so very 'Soviet'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No worries, noisy, they give ear plugs. Bit like sticking your head in a dustbin (if examining head and neck, if not you just slide through on a table. Little claustrophobic if just head and shoulders, but they give specs with mirror so you can what going on. Piece of cake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Getting desperate for middle class Champaign socialists isn't it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Matthew, you need to get out of the echo chamber and talk to real people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No evidence he parties, is there, see, you got all twiggered and still you don't know what happened. Just twiggered idiots on the left screaming it out. When Gray and MET police prove no rules broken you'll scream conspiracy because lies are all you have. You are so brainwashed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BORIS ACTS. EU NOT. 3000 anti tank weapons sent to Ukraine by UK. A significant counter to Putin's massed Amour. 3000 men/women/even children able to singlehandedly destroy an Russian MBT. Russian Sagger hammered  Israeli armour back in the day, modern equivalents are deadly. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Must be a lot of that China money going around from Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LABOUR HATE THE HOMELESSnnStarmer's Labour warns a Labour councilor against working, mid Pandemic, with local Tories and other volunteers to feed homeless people. So much hatred from Labour, against homeless of all people.nn#HASHTAG# nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You chose the one who hates Jews, do you hate Jews Ian, a lot of people in Labour do. It's just you promote Corbyn, who loved harboring anti-Semites. As for Boris, your hatred is simply because he went to a school with rich people. Hating people because they are different. Sick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She's a liar, all live long day. 

Here is #USER# telling lots of lies. 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proof Boris is getting it right - the sheer hatred and petty sneering lefties bottom feeders are up to today while Starmer is missing in action since his car crash interviews yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fair to say we are back in a war between hard/pro EU Lib left, media and those who supported Brexit. The same hatred, lies, false narratives and vicious attacks are underway. The false line now is on No10 drinks, when one fails another story emerges. Same as Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reality check, Alistair Graham is always attacking Tories, any questions arise he immediately announces they need sacking or investigating, ex, a former and another has been with personal vendetta. He has no access to evidence at all. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Every tank Putin has at the border is facing 3-4 man portable light anti armour weapons. With more prepared to surge in. Putin would have to turn Ukraine into another Chechnya. Politically, Putin couldn't sustain that or the high level Russian casualties.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's not true Linda, we just don't care about Liberals bed wetting and remoaning and calling for Boris to go. 

Your views are simply not important, funny, hysterical but no, not important to us. It's you and your few in your spiteful little echo chamber. That's all you have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Bene announced Weds, maybe Tuesday, Coats is just lost for anything intelligent to publish and shitting himself over being humiliated by it now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You have to sober to remember Alastair, anyway, apart from you, who is in your house, they all left when you became an drunk and intolerable bore. nnHere, just dial, help is near to hand. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Source, same pic as you, which doesn't show a party, shows workplace Garden, No10 garden. Your rule cut paste refers to Households not workplaces dim wit. I used your evidence to destroy your argument. It says Household sin the text dim wit, You didn't read it did you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get it form the horses mouth folks, not from second hand journo's who are stuck for something to write or misrepresent what was said. 

Police been in the wings all along. This is about locking down the outcomes press were poised to call out as a whitewash. 

Boris is clear! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Another pathetic, egotistical back bencher, one of a dozen who covert Boris majority. They really do not like being reminded who the big dog in charge is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She left NHS for private work over half a decade ago, just a Champaign socialist and Covid grifter making a few quid, sells masks, lefty pamphlets all sorts of shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I never said sh was still Lab MP I said why did Socialist Labour For Corbyn MPs still list her as  member. Learn to read fool. Got yourself all twiggered up eh little lefty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a reminder folks, a smart journo pointed out in 2019 that the Boris Brexit deal was brilliant work to actually get Brexit done then undo the NI Protocol and then move to no deal in 2-3 years once over the speed bumps. It's all happening as predicted. Boris had to get us OUT. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# awwww you got it bad loser. The desperate delusions of the FBPE. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State of this one, Scots fascists are a strange bunch #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why should journalists not be held accountable for lies? As usual a lefty or liberal wants press free to to tell lies for political advantage. If journo's not accountable then how can you demand any other person should be?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# EU did it to itself, EU wanted a war, EU interfered in Ukraine and started agitating. Let them sort their own shit out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many repurposed fake profiles, Boris detractors, every Labour MP or activist or lefty journo, half the supporters of their threads of 5-10 yr old profiles with barely any history and dozen or few followers. That's it, that's half their followers, fakes run by the other half.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Girl Friends Matter

Kneeling to a violent Islamo Marxist hate movement that declares white people be treat to a lower standard than others, then beats up his white girlfriend. 

When did he decide his white girlfriend was deserving of mistreatment a colored person wasn't? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Brexit'y Birthday Everyone. 

#HASHTAG# How ya doing remoaners? Come on, was all good fun, we won, you lost, time for you all to get out the echo chamber, burning EU regs this week, Boris and Truss of in the jet. More trade deal near. Saving Europe from Russia. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She's telling lies again, this is why Labour desperate to stop progress of legislation, they see their little world slipping through their hands and Boris getting more and more populare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He threatened to take HO to Court for not paying for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two sides of the same coin;

Failed leadership candidates coveting Boris' majority. Brexit substantively sorted, Covid success and booming economy they see the platforms they leveraged slipping away. Desperate to appear 'relevant' but simply not anymore. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking News

Tracey Emin requested return of artworks donated to Govt. Govt spokesman said;

'Regretfully No10 cleaners accidently disposed off Tracey's work follow excessive staff partying' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexit first birthday party tomorrow, lets celebrate huge gains already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Cry all you like lefties . . no laws or rules broken. However, how doe sit stack against Labour having near ONE MILLION QUID of laundered Chinese spy funds to do the bidding of China CCP in UK Parliament. Now that is illegal and accounting for it unavoidable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boris ain't going anywhere, suck it up lefties and pro EU losers. It' just going to go harder and faster now and we Tory voters love it. We love it. nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I suspect Labour, pro EU and Tory traitors, and media, will be exposed as shamelessly manipulating the narrative and exploiting the grieving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The hard core Marxist left will use any shield, any excuse to attack our political freedoms and democracy. Even to extent of creating hatred against a democratically elected leader and Govt. Why would I be silent why they try to demonize the PM and Govt using Covid as an excuse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Not at all, why do you think so? Police decide what to investigate, not Govt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Its the truth, hard core left will stoop to anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The judge is basically OK'ing pedophiles to use defence of 'didn't know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starmer own goal!
Boris would have done this anyway. Party Gate and ensuing media and opposition hate campaign has simply focused Tory MPs minds to accelerate existing policy intentions. Majority pressure on MP's is not for Boris to go but quicker change. 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh Howard, you do spin a story line for time to time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Remainers bed wetting over lies form Guardian comic - priceless, look at the state of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What you going to do, talk, having agitated for confrontation now others will have to pay the price and step up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Biden was one who did pulled out without warning. You lot on the left are really rather pathetic, none will debate or defend their assertions, just childish cowards who know their rhetoric falls apart, lies, hate, targeting idiots is all left has, terrified of intelligent voters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I cannot believe you FBPE and lefty sorts all so stupid you fall for these media stories that have no basis in fact. All of you bed wetting, as always yo do what you did since 2016, it just makes you all look stupid, unthinking, fanatical and deranged.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHERE IS THE FORDE REPORT

#USER# BLOCKNIG release of Forde report into Labour's anti-Semitic activities while demanding Boris have an inquiry into Tory Islamophobia base don the word of #USER# a proven liar sacked for misleading parliament.    #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Any idea how stupid a suggestion that is, a liars license. Putting so called journo's above the law. So you want journo's to be free to tell lies and conduct smear campaigns without being held accountable. CC was told to stop telling lies, she didn't so now she pays the price.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They only have to get half way already dim wits, Navy can block them, keep them at sea until they give up - no pick up, that's the point. Bloody hell, does anyone have  a brain cell at GBNEWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He had China spy money, his turn is coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bill that will be debated in Parliament thicko, no obligation tell devolved administrations ahead of it being put to parliament. It's a UK and thus a Westminster matter not a devolved matter. Devolved regions assemblies have no powers over these things. How ignorant you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate tweets of Labour Head of Standards Committee. 

'If you voted for Brexit. You can f*** off out of here' 'You thick t***s. You probably voted Conservative' 'Brexit caused this. All other COVID affected countries have plenty'

#HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# We both know that wasn't true Zara, we can see the Chinese Labour funding outlet to right of picture, were you really out to pick up some Chinese pocket money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# sick little loser lol, get used to Boris, the people certainly are on his side.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Welcome to him, another Labour liar, well done. I am sure his constituents will deal with him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labour SLEAZE kills children. CAKE means more to LABOUR than Children's lives. Labour Council lose control of Children's Services. 

#USER# #USER# what are your priorities?

CAKE OR CHILDRENS LIVES

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's because you are a delusional FBPE who cannot comprehend reality. So you think your opinion is proof. You are funny. Might be why you lot screwed up the remain debate. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More bed wetting, really jolted them lose today. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# MET SAY - It's still there. Hanging around on Downing Street like it owns the place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# More lies from FBPE lol You people really do inhabit a bizarre world, a theme park of the Brexit losers imaginations. Still pedaling the 'racist' Brexit agenda. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# English fisherman have greater catch, Millions invested and increasing volumes of exports as do Scots salmon producers so renders your assertions bollox. Care homes, still there, no problems reported in England. Farmers, getting subsidies and adapting. What's the problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Recall petition requires certain majority of votes in constituency to achieve a by election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all about Brexit isn't it, notice how lefties trending towards attacking Brexit now. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Labour supporters favorite author 'respecting' Jews. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# love you triggered remainers profile, lots of blubbing and bed wetting eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Did you criticize Starmer saying the same about his illegal party in a constituency office but in this case peopel sharing an office shared a cake, hardly a party. You just make your party look stupid Zara.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hysterically funny. This is what the extreme left do. They are in meltdown, not so confident about Boris leaving are they.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Democracy, something you have no concept off. Nasty little lefties have to behave now instead of smashing stuff up and blocking ambulances. Tough shit, time to grow up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well done, you go sell it to people when they don't have to buy it, try that you'll find it isn't worth 43p a day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truth about Independent Sage!

Another left wing Con shop. 

Nothing but anti Brexit campaigners and hard core Marxist agitators opposing democratic rights of the British People.  

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My old boss had a Bentley, that was daylight robbery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13 followers in 12 years, how's the weather n Wuhan lol Another repurposed fake to support Zara Sultana's lies. Another fake set up to promote Labour lies. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Keir Starmer achievements but lets add protecting child rapists to preserve Labour votes and soft plea bargains enabling a terrorist to be freed who immediately murdered two peoples. 

May, you pretty stupid not knowing difference between Keir Starmer and Gandi. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starmer near silent today. Working up next distraction no doubt and recovering from his car crash interviews yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tugenhaut is a Pound Shop Tobias Elwood (another quisling and traitor) offered up a sacrificial lamb to test the water.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 3 followers in over a year, grow up, get areal profile not yet another multi managed fake one lol. Reflect on why you are not taken seriously by majority of reasoned people. All you have is hate and fakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# They are distancing and where in work groups not always possible so no rules broken, burying yourself idiot, that what happens when you pedal someone cut paste stack without a clue. So you agree, you have no evidence yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During 2016-2019 I speculated that some remainers would adopt a bizarre group delusion and pretend Brexit hadn't happened. I suggested a post Brexit theme park, EULAND, where they could go, Be an MEP for a hour, experiences, rides, souvenirs. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Money on T&amp;T wasn't wasted. It saved many lives and provided important data. Even got Keir Starmer shut down 6 times because he never follows the rules. You are just a lost fanatic poncing money of your hard working members.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nationality &amp; Borders Bill in final round of the Lords, after it comes back Govt can get it done and ignore the upper house.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Irony is that Starmer is NOT  a lawyer, but he is a liar. The sycophants of the left really are so lost and so ignorant. Imagine wanting to be led by a anti-Semite, failed lawyer, who left the profession, who protected child rapists for votes. The sick peoples party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Femi baby hates Bowis, Bowis did Bwexit. 

What was it Femi once said 'why does Boris keep on winning' It's like shopping Femi, if you have to ask the price . . .you shouldn't be there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keir Starmer appoints new Labour Chief Whip

Labour MP's live in terror. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Starmer demolish Boris in open debate, jog on. lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Boris didn't kill them . .you are sick, shamelessly exploiting the grieving because you hate democracy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Rachel, he'd win it lol LOL That's exactly what the party might do to humiliate and expose your and Starmer's lies. By the time its done you will look like the liars and Starmer will be resigning long before Boris. Lets compare notes in next few days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Not much noise for anywhere that side today. Starmer imploded in two interviews yesterday. Real world ain't like Fabian sycophants and Momentum bar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK, let me get this straight, ditching a charity that funds learning, literacy, in Africa because it reinforces the 'white savoir' stereotype thereby not helping little African kids learn to read is to the benefit of little African kids. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at his shirt collar, he has quickly dressed or put a tie on. Not checked knot in mirror, boy is under STRESS. The bobbing head, bobs forward like tortoise. Then does a peacock puff of chest, bizarre body language. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Brexiteers

So much achieved in just ONE year. UK is now a globally respected, revered and feared nation across trade, security and Covid response and stand out European  economy investors world over flock to. 

Meanwhile what have yEu done #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at the arse licking thread of this potential Lab candidate. Look at the degenerate Lefty sorts he attracts. How anyone wanting public office would not block the vile followers I do not know. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, he got shot dead so it worked out OK, one less Islamic extremists to put others at risk. We need to be protected from terrorists. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Just spent £400bn on Covid dim wit. But hey, we have leading G7 economy, export growth, and the reason is, we left the EU. Se how you look profoundly stupid and ignorant all in one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can anyone account for obvious collapse of reason across the left, they are all turning on MET over a report not even released. 🤣😂🤣😂🤣😂🤣😂🤣]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does SNP keep pedaling the lies that Scotland can decide to walk into the EU, the EU wouldn't want them, why, Scotland has NOTHING to offer the EU, especially as a broken country with no currency, no central bank. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Just dived into Red again after reading ages ago. On cusp of 18 darting around in my (two piece) NBC suit and in Thetford . . . . oh joys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# C4 is funded in part by grants as well as advertising, you keep telling lies - see how your pathetic fanaticism and hatred just makes you look so, so stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is near silence form the press since MET went in. Why is that, it's like they fell of a cliff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# threads backed up by these fake followers, like this one 11 yr old profile, 49 followers and history redacted. Left wing liars and scribblers like Dan rely on these fakes. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep, that's why Catholic priests finally got nicked in droves for buggering choir boys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another remainer quisling taking his chances, another to go when all done. Sick, arrogant opportunism of an egotistical and small man. Backed by remainers because they think they can fudge that with some flag shagging. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 700 British soldiers murdered by the IRA but not one inquiry or any IRA man or woman facing justice. 

Burgon doesn't remember, Burgeon doesn't care. 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Imagine if we had a dress as a nun for a day and asked Muslim women to do . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yo lot really bed wetting over it, sadly for you guys the report will be fine for the PM and expose low life media types abusing their position. Enjoy, your little echo chamber will implode.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hate group, Black Lives Matter, with Labour MPs, breaching lockdown rules on the PMs birthday. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boris Brexit success causing French and EU tantrums continue. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Making yourself just look so very stupid Billy. Everyone knows the Jet isn't just for her, secure coms, sovereign territory, security detail, admin, junior minsters and aids. That you do this just shows you haven't any meaningful rebuttal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Relax, it's just like Brexit dear, you just don't like it. So you will scream, make wild unfounded accusations of conspiracy and fit up, and lose. You will refuse reality, the truth, you will forever sneer on Twitter while we laugh at your insanity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Boris didn't kill your sister and neither did he party party over Covid, neither is Boris controlling when Gray report is released. I suspect your focus on Boris is motivated by your preexisting political outlook. Clearly you are just a remainer who hates Boris anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Another of Starmer's Sleazy Labour party sacked for saying another deserved a life threatening illness bit not sacked by Labour oh no, hate is allowed in Labour. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 104 followers in 12 years, lots redacted history, another repurposed fake backing up discredited drunk Alistair Campbell, all these 'faces' have a host of these fakes circulating and supporting their nonsense content.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# so, they'll make it even worse than it is lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Red meat as opposed to Divine Brown (oral specialist hookers street name) and Hugh Grant, convicted of a sex crime. Having a blow job in public where kids and families were around. State of you Hugh, the state of yet another convicted sex criminal supporting Labour. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Independent Sage are a bunch left wing losers, academics and B list TV presenters who were not up to the grade to be hired. Just another platform for lefties to do whatever Govt decided not to. Self appointed egotistical left wing busy bodies and nobodies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sajid Javid exposed his credentials, Wragge, Ghani and others. The removal of whip and reshuffle in Feb/March will be a bonfire of remainers egos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COME ON DONALD! 

LETS HAVE A BIG UK CHEER FOR TRUMP

RIGHT ON NATO
RIGHT ON EU
RIGHT ON CHINA
RIGHT ON WUHAN

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Worse, the NHS leaders who think it's not their job to recover money from foreigners or even check to see if people are entitled to treatment, GP object to it, they want anyone to walk into their practices and sign up, no checks.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>