<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Definitely one of the most disturbing things I've seen today. And I can watch The Room on the regular.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Correct. I said Snyder did a dumb Batman. As in, he's written like a dummy who doesn't do logical things within his own world view.

Ben Affleck's portrayal of it beyond that is fine. He didn't write the material.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just saying.... Can we get a reboot? 

I can watch this dude sit and a chair and savage garbage all day long. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So much for "cancel culture", amiright?!

The future just won't stay dead!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I know! 
No Brown and Yellow. No Shirtless and pants-less! 

No variety.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Also, Pre-Time Skip and Post. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why do you assume I don't like "white spaces"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Thanks everyone! We know you've the real rock stars behind this series! And I'm excited for it's return.

(humming)
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# you're right.  Stupid people should die for their mistakes. Especially when dealing with cops. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Same! Not enough people know about Blood &amp; Bone... not even the Kimbo Slice fight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeff Bezos' Space Vacation Is Capitalism Gone WAY OFF THE RAILS #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah probably. You can tell the executes stop paying attention and the BSP notes get less crazy, so they can actually tell a functional adaptation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# more reasons for me to watch this show. I mean... they probably put her ON the moon, just so they could reference that song.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nothing but the true there.

A country by wealthy white male landowners, more than half of which were slavers too. Who lied, cheated and butchered the indigenous population, and at every state fight to maintain that power structure. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Which means Luffy will die when he's potentially anywhere from 70 to 80. He'll find One Piece before he's 20.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Especially for this series. I think the way DBZ got introduce to us in the states really ruined the concept of long serialized storytelling for most people. Since most folk never watched/read Dragonball, they assume you can always just skip to mid-series for the "good stuff".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# YES! It is!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# This is definitely the best video advocate for the Lincoln Project...
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# hooray shitty cops #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Very possible! Maybe to do with their big bodies or how they were apart of the Rocks crew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Dude is going to burn Jabba's Palace to the ground.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Making infants choose between they're foster dad and a weapon... perhaps it's time, for the Jedi to end. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The action man's princess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# this is what happens when your brain is rotten with macho-unchecked or challenged-male power fantasies mixed in with some good ole' fashion Amerikkkan-ism.  You go around thinking you can solve any problem with a  gun and that it's your "right" to do so..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maaaaaaybe.

But we need to prove that Mandalorian works on it's own. It's like tryin to get to Deep Space Nine after season One of Next Gen. 

Let's demonstrate one thesis works first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not waiting for the NRA to come jump on this, for OBVIOUS reasons.  But still no word on who their warrant was for or WHY they needed a no-knock in the first place.

Police Kill Black Gun Owner Within Seconds Of No-Knock Warrant Raid #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# My guess, it started from the "Ultra Instinct Shaggy" memes

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm fixin' to call somebody... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The fight against the capitalist and their goons continue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Religious people twisting their text to justify their shitty behavior?! Nooooooooo #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He's got the mental capacity of a deranged 8 year old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I miss "POS" Pudding. This was such an amazing turn, and I loved every minute of it. She should have stayed the secondary antagonist in the arc because Katakuri never did it for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# These movies are the best of the lot.

Movie 6 is just brilliant cinema. It's BEYOND Piece.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So literally, Corporations have SO MUCH POWER that they can be found guilty of poisoning whole communities of people, but the person who serves jail time is the person who defended the community? And that defender doesn't even get a jury trail. 

Does that seem right to you? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# explain...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# hetro-normality is such a cloak of bullshit. 

Literally, nearly EVERY hero in straight relationships on screen and some idiots get to have shit like that without a hint of irony or self-reflection.  You're right, they just want to be dumbass bigots. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# HAH!  "Fix" News.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.......... I was a college student working at Target when we made the boneheaded decision to invade Afghanistan.  We all said it was a bad idea then...

‘They Owe Us’ Rand Paul’s Total Lack Of Humanity For Starving Afghans On... #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah, that sounds like a sub, alright.  I hope you tortured them plenty in return.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This old white dude gets it... It isn't hard to understand! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Agreed. So much better. His performance was one of the highlights to the movie... and they basically gave him nothing to do for the sequels. 

With an Ex-stormtrooper finding his way with companionship is such an important theme.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I argue the BO did it better than KoS. Both have extra lore, but we know what the BO wanted and what they were actually capable of. They're threat/challenge was fulfilled narratively.

KoS stood around, it's what they jokingly were known for. And then they died.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hedging their bets is what they ALWAYS do. They buy both sides so that no matter who is in charge, they always win. 

Which is why we need to get money out of politics and get rid of Citizens United... like Obama promised to do... and we saw how that went.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dragonball is one of the best comic reads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Danny Phantom too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Thinking to myself)... I know Spider-man made a ton of money relatively... but I think The Suicide Squad is still my movie of the year.

I just think about that movie more. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It was the 80s. We all had short shorts.  Lion-O, He-Man, Rainbow Brite.

(Technically 1990, but the trend continued)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stop ruining my boy.... Grandpa Munster doesn't deserve this insult.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Law... maybe. But I doubt it.  

Robin isn't going to look. Luffy should destroy it and say "Get on my boat and see for yourself!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I can assure u, corporate entities like Disney, Turner, Google, Apple, Boeing, Northrop Grumman or Amazon will always give themselves positive talking lines to make themselves look like they're doing the right thing.

After Obama, THIS is the real story. 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# In story continuity. So I have to start with Snake Eater. I'll get to the original Metal Gears after I beat Phantom Pain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We still need to know how and when Roger meet Kureha. She knew his real name... And even before he meet Oden and got the One Piece, he was sailing with Raleigh for a while.

I'm sure Rocks/Shanks will be the one of final One Piece flashback before the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That doesn't make sense and that is not the topic of the scene itself. The implications of wealthy elites funding both sides of a galactic conflict for generations... joining the Resistance with that knowledge only continues the war cycle. He'd be a fool to join in to not stop it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's literally the only way I know how to communicate an idea most of the time. No biggie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whaaa? White folks (keep it real) want to ignore history that makes their heroes/ancestors look like monsters? Nooooooooo #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You're ignored.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hah, he's always comfortably Number 2. Sanji is the one who can't handle it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I felt that way about this one.... When you want to talk about pure hype, symbol, iconic, and minimal, it says it all. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah. It'll just be good old fashion lying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This show actually has continuity from episode to episode.

First Star Wars show ever... You can tell they didn't know how to reproduce the designs from the films in animation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am not surprised.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My honest reaction to the TITLE of this #HASHTAG# episode was... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# All brilliant! These are amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks is one of the largest companies on the planet. If they can do it, McDonalds can do it, Walmart can do it, Target can do it, Amazon can do it, and most importantly YOU can do it!

Starbucks Workers WIN Union Vote! #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Imagine if Tim Pool were black, or a woman, or apart of the LGBTQ+ community... whew boy, then he'd REALLY have something to rail about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Manga of the year? No doubt.

I mean, the thousand chapters alone, plus with all the craziness that followed it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I see you're a woman of culture of as well. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Quiet, son. Grown-ups are talking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be ruthless with institutions and kind to people." - #USER# 

I quote this a lot on the Fight Together Podcast for #USER# 
Today is the year since Michael's passing. I knew it was coming, but I still wasn't ready for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not even a contest... but respectable openings all. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cops planting drugs in Baltimore? Noooooooooo #HASHTAG# nnWhy don't people ever listen to us?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This scene was so good. 

"I don't know how to sword fight." 
"Neither do they... use the thrust" 

Addams Family level of dark humor, yet in keeping with Wondie teaching girls how to be strong and confident. 

An Epic moment for your kid!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Probably because of that shithole country he lives in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Welcome to the club. You made it thru the Birdcage. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Conservatives dont view non-whites or Christians as American? Nooooooooooo. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is like second christmas.

Also it does fan service smarter than S2 of Mando. There, I said it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the Right-wing swing is global, and this is how we push back against draconian rules that limit civil rights.  When you tell women they don't have control over their bodily autonomy, you're showing your hand of oppression. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# For the kids... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# hooray Florida cops.  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes. Yes it was. It also teased Cap being worthy... and fucking Thor's face was priceless. 

Also first mention of Wakanda. Also first appearance of the Hulkbuster. Also first tease of the eventual defeat of the Avengers. Also first, and so far permanent, major character death #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fuckers are already going to try and spin it away from his war crimes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching the making of the Star Tours ride and beyond.

I can not tell you how much I love that original ride with Pee-Wee.

"Brakes... Brakes?! WHERE ARE THE BRAKES?!!" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also I'm glad the siblings got to have this talk finally.  It's wild that Izo is now 20 some odd years older than her and he looks fantastic. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So thankfully, the Nazis were fought and taken down, and German was forced to stop it's genocidal behaviors and we all recognize they were doing a holocaust of Jewish people. What happened to the Natives, African Slaves, Chinese immigrants, and etc. here got no such relief.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# As opposed to another author.... who is really riding that line. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Shirtless men are for men too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Our oppression isn't up for your negotiations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you've read the "The Art of Star Wars: the Force Awakens" this is obvious.  Finn was the co-protagonist and the "Han Solo" and love interest of the series.

"The Last Jedi" fucked that up. Now, movie series often change directions, but this was a change for the worst. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hopefully not exclusive, but yeah. Good point!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If you don't understand what I'm referring too, that's fine. 

Here is a clip with a better breakdown of why Biden is totally in the wrong here...
#URL#

With quotes from people who do the work that Biden didn't. Biden is a conservative Dem punching Left again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Republicans use gay slurs in referring to gay Republicans? Nooooooooo #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh... that's old news. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Genius!  Was it Lancelot murdering a wedding or the rabbit beheading knights. 

Both are historically accurate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I've been voting since 2000. Prior to Obama (literally even in that election) the constant narritive was "Is America ready for a (insert minority) president?"

It was usually "black" but that often came up for gay or woman too. Obama broke the combo, but he dropped the ball.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes.
Yes.
Yes.
Yes.
YES!!!
YEEEEESSSS!!!
Yes.
Yes.
And.... Yeah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thank you. This is informative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had a brilliant time with the Big Brain Chungus Podcast! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Starship Troopers... the movie that just keeps on giving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And probably sacrifice his life to make someone immortal? Someone who needs to stay alive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It isn't a matter of training when we've seen police arrest and apprehend or show hesitation in murdering white people at disproportionate rates than POCs. 

That training, is something we all receive in our culture, called "anti-blackness" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I am a fan of Barret and this new figure. I hope they do a few more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nope. That was new to me!  Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This poll is incorrect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Ah. Another conservative.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# In reference to the United States and Putin. My comment was a contrast to him and U.S.A power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They wanted her from jump. She checks all the boxes and will protect the status quo and wealthy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Great choice! Pretty much the same Luffy energy. For sure!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Power to this GIF.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thank you! She's my precious wittle one. 

Now a full cyborg with her feeding tube.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because it's "Listen to Black Women but change nothing about the material conditions that have created the inequality where he ignored the plight of marginalized groups like Black Women."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My boy's got Berserk and Naruto tattoos. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nope. I have no idea. 

I wish it was "Housing for all, Medicare for all, Student Loan elimination, Labor Unions for everyone, And a basic income for all." I would LOVE that big event.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well that's good. I mean, they also got two more Mother games than we got too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He's the hero we deserve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Now if you just want to say "Well, you're not president so you can't complain"... demonstrates, you don't understand how a Democracy works. 

We voted for him. We are disappointed in his service... TO US. And we are dismayed, that the result was a Oligarch Fascist like Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It isn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Maybe "kitchen" has a different meaning across the pond, cause........ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That College life. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I mean seriously. Thriller Bark and Sabody had great animation sequences.... let alone... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Those wishes often backfired.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Partly, yeah you're right. What I love about Clayface in Batman TAS is that he's a victim of his own vanity. In this episode, he wasn't the victim as much as Tim's heart was, represented by Annie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The cost of "Profits over people" and when your Republican Conservative Governors lie to the people. 

Texas Gov BLAMES Green Energy For Texas Blackouts #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Read/Watch for a sense of the world - Mobile Suit Gundam: Origins (the definitive retelling of the original) and Mobile Suit Gundam: Thunderbolt (a great new story)

Both of these manga are great reads so you kind of know what to expect in the Universal Century series.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# this fucker is making black coats and katana's look embarrassing. I hate him more for it. 

I need a quick cleanse with Blade.  Okkay, I'm good now. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I don't think filming began on BP2. And there has been viturally no filming during the pandemic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is the second worst valentine day card I've seen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yup. Since Urouge showed up in Sabaody, the hints have been there... 

My top three Novas coming thru.  (Gang, Urouge, and Scratchman) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did they do this to my boy? 

Not sense Snyder's Batman being a murdering psycho have I been more disappointed by how he's portrayed in media. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hah! I knew this was in development for years, but I wasn't on the team. 

What If...? comics are as old as I am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thinking about an ABBA and Tron:Legacy Soundtrack combo? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The often overlooked and brutal history of colonialism. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And to reiterate my point, the solution to dealing with racial extremism isn't to slaughter in retaliation. It's just causing death, suffering and resentment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Same, it's not a series I have any nostalgia for beyond "it exist, I've seen it, and understood the references"... but Cobra Kai is an amazing show. I went back and rewatched part 2 and 3 a few years ago... still bad movies, but now I'm hyped for this season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are all the 2Amendment Andy's now?  Now firing a gun like that is terrifying and dumb as hell, no question.

But that cop fired blindly into a backyard with ZERO warning!!! Fuck that cop.

Man Gunned Down By Cops In Front Of Family #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He's a selfish, craven, right-wing political corporatist who is only serving himself and his wealthy friends to make sure that they're wealth and elite status is maintained. Doesn't matter what fascist or white supremacist he has to support to do so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The show was made for flash before the program existed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what you're telling me. If I want to be the Punisher, I can. Right?  

I can get a gun... go looking for trouble or "find myself" in a situation where I "need to use it" to "defend myself"... and that's okkay?

Sure. That sounds reasonable. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whaaaaaattt?  Conservatives and Right-wingers don't think things thru?  Noooooooooooo... #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# To me... THIS was an absolute disappointment at the top of Obama's Administration. This is when I felt "Something off" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Bill, Francis and Nick, Coach.

my buddy was ALWAYS Rochelle... and then we'd get a random fucking Ellis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 cops. All four with guns drawn... on a man with a cellphone and local changing equipment in a predominately white neighborhood.

This is how it starts... we've seen several incidents on how it can end. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Especially after Sonic Spinball, that is a major crime.

SEGA dropped that ball. (pun intended) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dude! The receiver of the first on panel Gum-Gum attack... the legendary Gum-Gum Pistol!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah, cause if you want to operate on who knew what and the chaos of the situation on the ground... Kyle was the one who just shot someone with a rifle... he was clearly a threat, more so than a dude with a plastic bag and his bare hands.... but you know... America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Can't wait to hear Biden's excuses on why people can't have healthcare during a pandemic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# They're cloning him in a lab as we speak!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I do find the fact that the Mt Rushmore statues singing as really ironic, I'm sure the people of the Black Hills Tribe might not be celebrating yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Who leaked, indeed.

If you have any objection to what's actually in the video, not the fact that the video was leaked and released... here is the full video, if you think that clip is unfair.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today in "Why Bryan prefers the Manga over the Anime", we'll do a quick lesson in best use of negative space and gesture. 
It's minor, but this drives me nuts

I know the anime production is strenuous, but this is why the hand of the artist matters in communicating an idea. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I wouldn't mind Devil being the "D".  Considering the main idea of the series being the "Devil Fruit" seems like it might be obvious at this point.  They might still relate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# At the same time, Marvel has some of the lamest and awesome villains. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rotten fruit doesn't fall far from the rotten tree.
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rent free in my head... 24/7 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Jet Twin Pistol! A Classic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This poll is correct.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my top lines in fiction.

"Ray, if someone ask 'are you a god' you say... YES!!"

Especially coming from a brother a few scenes earlier espousing how much he loves Jesus's style.

Fucking comedy. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# southern cops taking the freedoms of black people...... Nooooooooooooooo. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's your time now. Us old folks got our rodeo already. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'd settle for a good old fashion full double page spread.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Got a brother sweatin' like... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah...... fun with photoshop.

I got one going, but it's basically Luffy wearing articles of clothing, not mutating his features.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If he did, he'd ruin the ending of that arc.  

Hence, he better not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My hero!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Alan Moore gets to go out on top for writing one of the greatest superhero novels ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Both of these aren't right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There should be more toys from your work. Seriously... a crime has been committed against the community!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yup! You're correct. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Definitely don't think anyone should be thanking fascist for that. Our anything really...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The line "Not all skinfolk are kinfolk" was created specifically to be skeptical about people trying to represent us who aren't actually looking out for us. 

The woman at the end nails it perfectly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SSJ3 is still one of my favorite beyond Super-Saiyan transformations. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm definitely one of those "Low Boys"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Blackness, Anti-Browness, and Anti-Poor People is an old story in America but it's not ancient history, it's current and systemic.

"Takeover": Young Lords' Juan González on Hospital Protest Doc. Shortlis... #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Looks good! Appreciate the effort for Michael.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cops using similar tactics as white supremacist Terrorist who murder people? Noooooooooooo, really? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MSNBC Suddenly Shocked By Poverty After Ignoring It For Years #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's vapid. Empty.

Joe is responsible for oppression and sided with white supremacist and oligarchs for half his career.

Kamala is responsible for harming poor people and letting rich assholes skate free.  Further creating a class divide.

Am I in the ballpark?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah. Now that concept is introduced, you might be right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Biden and Corporate Dems like him are also responsible for this nonsense. Just as much as the entirety of the Republican party, they're bought by the insurance lobbyist.

Non-Americans Stunned By American Health Care Costs #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If I see your version of Goblin in "No Way Home"... I will lose my mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You're rambling. You said that already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Part 4 IS weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Whaaaa... Right-wingers in the US military willing to sacrifice the lives of our soldiers in order to prompt warfare... Nooooooooooooooo.n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Progress in #HASHTAG# executing an unarmed, fleeing man... Cops only mistake was moving his taser. Oops. #HASHTAG# n#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# At least Queen being a cyborg gives him SOME excuse. Like, if he's just "This is what Dinosaurs do!" justifying the weird things he's done to himself. But Sasaki's Triceratops fan... that's just biology.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# So........ where was his self defense? Kyle had an illegal loaded weapon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Comic... with the visual appeal of the psychodelic colors and designs. Same with the show and games. 

Not novel.  Shit's not Tolkien.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'll be there with you. Wait until you read some Berserk. That'll be over 35 plus years in the making. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Agreed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Luffy?!  All he wanted to do was become Pirate King! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Correct! I think that goes all the way back to Chinese mythology that carried over. Hence the Sulong transformations of the minks... As pictured here #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally got thru Squadrons on Veteran single-player. Ready to keep it up thru ACE all the way.

Gotta get my skills up.

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Man knows his craft. 
He did this on a whim too... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is literally a video about kidnappings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the record... it's been a real sore spot for me since '97 that people act like the Final Fantasy series started with the seventh game. And pretty much ignore any game that isn't just a copying FF7 in theme or aesthetic. 

I'm looking at you 8,10,13,15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope some one wrote out the entire "Rogers the Musical"... cause I'd be willing to sit thru it.
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah, you're right. Similar to Red state voters... it's just about being comfortable, and that's how some people vote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No. He wasn't. #URL#

Where does it say he was killed by "Antifa rioters". You're making shit up. 

You can say he was killed by looters. But what does Anti-facism or Black Lives Matter protest have to do with robbing a pawnshop?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's interesting that this new one doesn't have Shanks wearing it... probably because they're current versions of the crew and we only ever saw young Shanks in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# This is why officers of the law should attempt to preserve life, as best they can... to make sure that young girl could go to trail for whatever assault she was committing and save ALL of their lives. 

That's the most reasonable exception with their training and jobs.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>