<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You have to learn calculus. You have to do 30 pages of calculus problems every day. You have to practice calculus and apply it in your own engineering projects. ðŸ’ªðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's just weird that a billionaire would go for that when he could get a supermodel in her early 20s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Are you one of those "people" who thinks formal education imbues people with higher IQ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Cope. Lifting weights won't stop the collapse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, the US doesn't need to start mining. They will censor transactions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mossad agents work with British Royal family, no surprise there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "Better to give your undivided attention to whatever girls want"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Your life has to be perfect before women will even bother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Oh no, don't do that! It would be horrible if White people had their own country! We'd definitely die of starvation and poverty! ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why would people of color have worse labor laws than majority-White countries? That seems to run counter to the narrative that White supremacy harms the working class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is another way of saying "White men are a liability in America".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The money supply grew more than 18%. That's all that matters. The whiplash back up will be face melting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No, it means George Soros and Klaus Schwab led world empire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hitler tried to save Europe from this. He lost the war, remember?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Relatively homogenous European nations shows this isn't the case, their fertility is also below replacement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sounds like a smart strategy. You scared?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# All the White liberals would abandon the diverse areas ASAP. It would actually be hilarious to watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wish people would stop including the earliest price data in these "best fit" curves. It's stupid to include data from the early years because the growth from zero was rapid in order to catch up to the # of users.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You talk like literally every other race don't hate White people with a burning passion ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Then have kids. People will refer to you as a mom - much more dignified.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# These goobers wouldn't be anywhere near the halls of power if they were White men with the exact same qualifications.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Dude has more in common with a Reddit mod than your average White conservative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mass immigration causes far greater destruction to the planet, but I bet you support importing millions of "refugees" into Europe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Nah, they can make just as much money on the upside as the downside. Bitcoin is still "on schedule" as far as its growth rate. It'll be over $100k by the next halving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I wouldn't doubt it. They want to put more White men in jail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is why we always hear about "strong women" in news and entertainment media. It's a meme that makes women less agreeable to men, which reduces healthy relationships and fertility. Then they blame the decline in fertility on "beta men who eat soy and don't lift".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lmao women trying to save themselves from responsibility AGAIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# So you think ethnic cleansing has its upsides? Interesting. I guess if you prefer nonwhites to whites I could see how you'd arrive at that conclusion. Do you think that ethnonationalists believe in preventing all international travel and tourism?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "Minorities", bro they're 95% of humans on earth. Get with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just avoid the "diverse" parts of each country and you'll be safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Killing itself? Well no wonder he failed, he thought it was a suicide!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Explain how White people made South Africa into a developed and wealthy country? It was virtually empty before Whites showed up. Why couldn't the native blacks do that? Why couldn't the aboriginals make Australia wealthy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I would argue it's not so much cultural as it is policy - women entering the workforce and universities. Obviously divorce is another big one, but it's mainly women working that did this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# White women anytime they're responsible for destroying something: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# N's don't think Europeans look normal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Our youth culture is nigga rap and transsexuality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It's not my country. It's owned by Jews. Whites haven't had power in America in nearly a century.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# We need more mining to be done in non-US aligned nations. Otherwise we will eventually have a centralization problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's only going to get more dramatic as time goes on. Movies will be made about it. I think now that the Charlottesville trial is over we'll see a movie about that soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because it's a good proxy for dissent, and they want to punish dissent and separate libertarians and conservatives from their source of income.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ever heard the phrase "running on fumes"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's actually stunning how dumb the masses are, which makes it far more understandable how so many evil people are able to become super rich - they just take advantage of the situation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stoicism is basically just "stop whining and be a man", which is another way of saying "get back to work and stop complaining about the decline".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why can't women handle criticism? Maybe female sex workers deserve criticism for perpetrating the industry. "It's all men's fault!" is the rallying cry of two X chromosomes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol it's cute anyone thinks that's how it'll work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If anybody knows guys like this, let me know so I can follow them. ðŸ‘ŒðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Savage men = not the best men

But that's a conversation y'all aren't ready for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Politics is ultimately just a physics problem disguised as a persuasion problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You'll have to try harder than that. White men don't have a feminine hissy fit over words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Ehh, I don't think we should expect a bond trader to save Western civilization. At least he's got kids and grandkids. That's a great contribution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Isn't that the excuse people use to justify circumcision for boys? "It gets dirty in there"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Individual US states have higher GDP than many European nations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# LMAO @ black ppl thinking they invented spices. Y'all needed us for the WHEEL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# A male feminist is a man who thinks women have the right to define "masculinity" and shame men for being "beta".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is a sassy way of saying "how dare you!" Not very compelling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# He's got pronouns in his bio, not worth responding to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is an interesting theory. They might attack crypto in the hopes it pushes young people back into the labor force. But it'll make smart young people that much more resentful of the ruling class, which is dangerous for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Lol. We tried the whole equality thing. Didn't work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're right, there are tons of black athletes that have raped, beaten, and abused women. We need to confront this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# They've only ever cared about beating down whites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Doesn't matter. Governments don't need trust to survive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Defensive nukes are valid, lindy, and inclusive ðŸ™ŒðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The book was never banned. It was just removed from the curriculum. Why do Jews insist on lying about this? It only makes them look less trustworthy and reinforces antisemitic stereotypes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wouldn't call them weak. The Left are much stronger than the Right, politically speaking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# So if the average man can march several miles, barefoot, with 100 lbs of gear, women will be tradwives again? ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Jeff Bezos is an antiwhite leftist. The average Jew makes more than double what the average White does, and that's at the national level. In NYC it's probably triple or more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Humiliation ritual. Jews want to force their enemies to ingest bugs while they are sterilized and later killed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Look at fertility rates and marriage rates in Western nations. They have been plummeting since the 1970s. We are going to have a population collapse because young women are free to wh*re themselves out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Women wanted to work, that was part of the whole feminism deal. I support banning women from the workforce. You would scream and cry if such a policy were actually implemented.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wait, what? Tons of races have political autonomy. The Chinese Han are the most obvious example. Native Americans are another. Koreans. Indians. The Bantu in Africa.nnYou can't give me a quote? Just one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't mean to come across as rude, but the fact you think "freedom always wins" just shows how sheltered and heavily propagandized you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# is another example of this. He's on assignment from the Pentagon/CIA to endear himself with Bitcoin Twitter (and promote patriotism among libertarians who would otherwise hate the US FedGov).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Lol okay, I read it. Basically she's complaining about alphas refusing to commit. All women want to settle down with a guy who's in the top 5% in terms of attractiveness and money. But there's zero incentive for those guys to stop having hookups.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I remember when people thought Trump running for office was insane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# There are tons of nonwhite immigrants who vote Republican, too. Do their kids vote Republican? No. Does it even matter if Republican politicians win? No.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Actually when you take into account free time, family, stress, pollution, and a few other metrics, a compelling case can be made that the average person today has a significantly worse quality of life than a feudal peasant from the 1100s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No, voters don't set policy imo. I think it's due to the fact it puts women on the defensive - our society is gynocratic, so it's built around allowing women to have maximum freedom and minimum responsibility. Calling out women for not having enough children is forbidden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Your whole feed is just you seeking male attention online by bashing men in a cutesy way. I just get a kick out of women like you, and the simps that orbit you. Gay men can see what you're doing! ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I think that's the idea. The goal is to create polarization and possibly violence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Maybe libertarians and conservatives shouldn't have let antiwhite communists take over the media. Turns out culture matters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The Atlantic? Might as well reference Netflix. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Probably not, but I'm worth more than 10x you two combined.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I want to know what Nancy Pelosi's trades are before she makes them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I think it's mostly Twitter that has colored my thoughts on this, and also seeing the behavior of my own sister.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That would've been a great way for Trump to have won a second term. Sailor strategy. But instead he pardoned a bunch of Jews and Nogs. I'm not in a swing state, but I voted for Biden because of that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You're not going to make it out of this at all, the way you guys are trying to preserve feminism.

I used to care a lot about White survival, but I've learned to stop hinging my happiness on a group that's desperate to maintain delusions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Look at old rap music videos. The black women in them are all skinny as rails! This whole "thicc black woman" thing is a meme created fairly recently. Basically they are promoting unhealthy and lazy lifestyles and tricking men into thinking this is normal/attractive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nah, all corporations are woke now. Being anti-woke causes you to lose more business than being antiwhite does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Freedom of speech doesn't mean freedom from consequences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Electric cars are a wonderful way to convert transportation into CO2" ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maybe. A lot of it depends on if Russia, China, Iran, etc are able to prevent the Five Eyes countries from destroying BTC. Fingers crossed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Not possible anymore because we've lost freedom of association. Poor whites will be forced to live in the violent ghetto filled with antiwhite blacks seething with racial animus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because White men have been tricked into giving women legal equality, when they should be ranked just above children in hierarchy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Rich old Jews*, funded primarily by middle class White men.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Until WW start to lose job opportunities to nonwhites, they are safe. And they'll continue to be antiwhite. But it hasn't hit them in the pocketbook yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# They counted Jews as White in that survey. Jews aren't White, they are a Middle Eastern tribe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Libertarians be like

"Check out this hypocrisy, lol. Btw, I'm completely powerless to stop it and if you suggest I collectivize against it I'll call you a racist or evil."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Kids don't cost money to have. Poorest people have the highest fertility rates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Nah, it's what happens when you let women go to college and enter the workforce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# There is never assimilation, there is only hybridization. Blacks have been living among whites in the Southern US for centuries. They haven't assimilated at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I suspect it'll be shockingly boring, tbh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# She's also slept with dozens of guys, guaranteed. That's the main issue with these urbanite women.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Tbh I doubt it could. America is beyond unification now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What about "The White Nationalist Manifesto", by Dr. Greg Johnson? It advocates for the peaceful creation of a White ethnostate. It was banned from Amazon and it's in no libraries or mainstream bookstores.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Was that recent? Darrell Brooks was just the other day. Antiwhite black man murdered 6 whites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The Bible is the reason antiwhite leftism is spreading without any resistance. Christians are incapable of defending whites as a group.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That counts Jews as White. Jews aren't White, they are a Middle Eastern tribe. There's a reason they want war.nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I prefer the classic book "The Jewishness of Wealth", because Jews are on average more than 3x wealthier than whites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stacy reminds me of some girl who would sing in a 90's shoegaze band]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# So other races didn't consider White people inferior to themselves? They considered all races equal? ðŸ˜‚

And if IQ has no bearing on anything other than IQ tests, why does it perfectly correlate with success in life, earnings, health, scientific discoveries, academic achievement?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What were they brainwashed into believing? nnKeep in mind the German people are internationally despised. And Jewish Bolsheviks had launched a violent takeover of Berlin. And the communists in Russia had millions of Jewish sympathisers in Germany, and intended to invade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Until you support banning governments from owning guns, you're just a run of the mill authoritarian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Stop trying to make excuses for female immaturity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That actually originates with Abrahamic religions, so it's Jewish rather than European. Europeans were polytheistic and fairly tolerant of other religions prior to Christianity. Look at the biggest pushers of globalism today: Jewish elites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well even when your guy wins the election, they don't actually do anything significant for their voters. Trump never built the wall, never locked up Hillary, never pardoned Julian Assange, never deported the illegals, never passed a worker ID law, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And I say this as a wealthy man myself. I'm also gay, so I don't really have a dog in this fight. But I do care about the future of humanity and I care about men generally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's not a trap, it's the correct solution to modern day communism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I defy anyone to find me a woman under age 40 who agrees that women have duties and responsibilities in life. I have literally never seen this before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Why couldn't the women provide for the family and protect the men?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's complex. Lots of moving parts there! What makes you think that'll fix the fertility rate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If the elites were "trying to divide us", they would be supporting and helping secessionist and White nationalist movements. Instead those are the groups they most-harshly demonize. The elites aren't "trying to divide us", they're just antiwhite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Lmao. "I love our woke, trillion dollar, CO2 belching, invasion machine that can't even hold Afghanistan!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Telling young women to get over themselves", lol. You think that'll do it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm racist and I support gun rights for blacks (when they are in their own countries).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The UK is importing millions of Arabs, Africans, and Indians to compensate for the falling native population. But that's increasing the crime rate in cities, and reducing economic sustainability. And the immigrants don't have replacement rate fertility. Either way you are fucked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think there's a grain of truth to this but I also think it's a bit more subtle: by associating the online Right with cartoonish bodybuilding accounts, they can disarm real intellectual progress. Those BAP guys are mostly hardcore feminists who don't think deeply about issues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Twitter is borderline unusable these days. Sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You really think that'll matter when they import millions of Democrats every year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why do you assume it's not possible to be a normal, healthy person and also be a fascist? Why do you assume fascists are automatically terrorists?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# "They can't actually be decent people...That's impossible. The corporate media told me they're evil...this must be propaganda."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I think if I were a powerful psychopath trying to cause problems, I would do my best to convince the masses that the problems are self-inflicted, and "just part of human nature". Wouldn't you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Alts don't do as well as bitcoin over longer term. That's what all these ETH heads are about to learn the hard way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# America still has attractive, thin, blonde women? Huh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's the erasure of European culture and the silencing of White voices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Putin has made some dumb moves recently. He needs to make Russia more expat-friendly to pull skilled Whites away from Western Europe and America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The base layer of Western civilization was "White supremacy". Abandon that, and you'll see everything else fly out the window with it. Libertarians are about to learn a very hard lesson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Your classification of one as legitimate and the other as a cult is ultimately just an expression of your antiwhite hate. You're like most people - terrified to criticize Jews as a group. I bet you know nothing about what Orthodox Jews do with their children's penises.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is fantastic! Cheap homes! Less traffic! Less destruction of wildlife and land!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# So you would rather force blacks to be policed, governed, and judged by other races? That's weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They're at war with Russia and conservative White Americans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He used the term "judeo-christian" in his bio, that tells you he's a Zionist stooge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Feminists desperately trying to infiltrate the dissident right is my favorite Marvel crossover. "The reason fertility rates are so low is because most White men are gay now!!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hmm he sounds like a conspiracy theorist. Only a crazy antisemite would claim old Jewish men closely monitor women's menstrual cycles like they're property or human breeding cattle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Fun Fact: Jewish Bolsheviks killed tens of millions of White people before Hitler came to power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Do Haitians know how to build pleasant and dense towns?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's a nice sentiment, but there are tons of rights that governments take away from people. An example is the Civil Rights Act, which took away Americans right to freedom of association.

In order to have freedom, you must first have *power*. Libertarians don't get that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Humans have always been divided by race. It's why races evolved in the first place. Only White people are dumb enough to believe in the "anti-racism" ideal. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No, they're more like national socialists (Nazis). They call themselves communists, but the origin and practice of communism in the 19th and 20th centuries was internationalist and price controls were common. China has state capitalism, like the US. But they are not globalists!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You're assuming successful men agree to get married. More and more men aren't falling for the marriage scam.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democracy is just whatever Klaus Schwab and a few Jewish billionaires want. How is that different from dictatorship? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The Left have always been communists, but they became much more powerfully antiwhite and anti-male after WW2. Their goal is retaliatory genocide of the White race (as revenge for the holocaust and slavery).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Libertarians and conservatives often want to "go along to get along". But that's INCREDIBLY dangerous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Imagine having 12% of the total mining capacity and not paying for a satellite connection backup. Insane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Y'all allied with the communists and gave Poland to Stalin on a silver platter. Then you made up some BS propaganda about the Katyn Forest massacre being committed by Nazis (when it was actually done by the Soviets).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Funny how the "resource curse" only affects nonwhites. Then once White people show up, the resources are extracted and utilized effectively.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I'm not even a Christian myself. This isn't about religion, it's about race, and you know it. You despise the White race with the intensity of 1000 suns. Our success makes your tribe genocidal toward us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They should see if they can cram New Yorkers into an even smaller space. The less area they take up, the better!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Exactly. This is also why you see the drive to push White men out of universities and high-paying jobs - they are trying to reduce White male SMV to increase miscegenation by White women.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Electric cars are actually better than gas powered vehicles because you can make your own electricity at home. You can't make your own gasoline.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I guess they need to create a better balance between black crime and White crime stats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah I'm sure Intel has tons of top positions for White men. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes. Lmao. That's literally how civilizations (and all scientific progress) happened.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# "Massive altseason" ðŸ˜‚
Have you considered that alts are what killed the golden goose?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nope, there are plenty of cases where the poor were built up into a solid middle class. Good leaders cultivate greatness via good policy. The free market doesn't do that. Look at our current batch of billionaires - they are all rabid feminists, promote bug eating, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 1. This is complex, difficult to answer in a single tweet. But we can see which groups began promoting feminist ideas early and learn from that.nn2. Low fertility is great for certain populations with bad genes. But we need far more high IQ people in the world. Nature &gt; Nurture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hate to break it to you, but you're far more likely to freeze in the dark when you're competing with millions of other upright apes for electricity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's a good point. Arguing with the left is always a waste of time, whereas arguing with the right teaches conservatives and libertarians new concepts. That should really be our target.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Every major corporation supports all of your trendy political positions and fires any employee who comes out as remotely pro-White or nationalist. When's the last time Amazon fired someone for being a communist?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Have you seen what gay White men do to real estate values? Have you seen what nonwhites do to real estate values?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Libertarians need to stop fantasizing about anarcho-capitalism and start working with ethnonationalists to defend the White race from annihilation, because that's what's coming if we don't take our own side.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Well don't take my word for it. The UN and WEF have published papers on this very topic. They know educating young women and pushing them to enter the workforce causes fertility rates to fall drastically.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Literally the only reason NYC didn't go the way of Detroit is because of Wall Street. Without access to that Federal Reserve money, the city would have crumbled decades ago. Whole this is a leech on the rest of America via the Cantillon effect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Could you link me to a thread where White supremacists make fun of Jews or blacks for owning guns? I've never seen them do it.

You guys regularly bash White men for enjoying guns. It's almost like you hate my race more than Nazis hate blacks and Jews...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "I thought I'd be long dead by the time the place turned into hell! It wasn't supposed to happen like this!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# "The elites are trying to divide us! That's why they force us to live with people we don't like!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I don't hate anyone except the people forcing my race to give up our nations and territory. I've never had a beef with any individual nonwhite because of their race. You've got a Hollywood idea of what White nationalists are like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We don't know what percentage of those girls were selling sex for money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# China has a declining population, and they won't bring in foreigners. So their real estate prices will plummet, which will mean everyone living there will enjoy super low rent/mortgage payments and quality of life will increase.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It's democracy. They are outnumbered by the Han Chinese, so they will just have to learn to live with diversity, like the Tibetans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dan, I'd like to make a suggestion for better messaging on this:

Calculate the % of electricity generated globally that's suitable for bitcoin mining (in other words, show that the overwhelming majority of electricity is not profitable in mining). That would help assuage fears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The outcome of this poll so far is making me bullish ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is the biggest load of horsehockey I've seen in a while. Why the fuck would the Nazis tattoo a little kid? And why are the tattoos always on different parts of their arms? None of this shit adds up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yep. I love Orania! Every year it grows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You can't build a defense using "love".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Humanism is also a religion, despite being secular. Antiwhite, anti-male humanism is the religion of Western democracy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Not sure why you think I'm a Christian. It's a religion created by Jews to spread Jew-worship around the world.

And I'm not sure where you get "genocidal" from, considering I literally just said every race deserves their own homelands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I can't believe he's only 8 years old!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I call this clownish, kosher "masculinity" the Black Rifle Coffee Company theme.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Exactly. Libertarians are about to learn a very harsh lesson about how much the FedGov hates them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They're gonna say they are putting their plan "on hold, due to global uncertainty about Russia".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Imagine having real representation in government. Hard to fathom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I speculate this is sexism in disguise. Women see ornate homes like this and get angry because skilled men built it, rather than dumb laborers making a modern white box.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Neither. I hope he spends it on shit-tier propaganda that has zero effect on anyone except to increase the amount of anti-Soros/pro-White sentiments of the masses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yup. She made up some bogus accusations that he molested her when she was younger, but it's obviously BS because if it were true she would've reported it to police long before this incident.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# On rare occasion they make different decisions, but they are usually punished for it. A good example is the invasion of Europe by "refugees" - most people were against it in 2016, but they crack down on any political org that speaks out against the Great Replacement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The dude's answer to every problem is rules, which are only going to be followed by people who have a certain rare set of genes that care about civility and fairness.

It all comes back to genetics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is this meme a joke? Women openly demand traditionally masculine men. What they hate is for men to desire traditionally feminine women.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That's probably because you've only eaten grits prepared by yankees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Of course I know he was an ape-like Jew. He was one of the earliest communists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Is the FBI going to add me to a list because I like lifting weights and reading stuff by a Yoram Hazony stooge?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>