<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Best Redhead OnlyFans (Top Only Fans Red Heads)  – LA Weekly #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Standoff With Putin, Biden Makes Sure European Allies Are With Him #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Northwestern Medicine Launches Nation’s First Urology Clinic Targeted Toward Needs Of Gay And Bisexual Men #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Oakland County Priest Pleads Guilty In Sex Abuse Cases, Sentenced Up To 15 Years #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Lynch: Home secretary approves extradition of UK tech tycoon to US but his lawyers vow to fight order #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pittsburgh bridge collapses ahead of Biden’s visit to discuss infrastructure #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 40K Cera Applications Filed In Detroit, Landlords Left Waiting For Payment #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Housing Market Up $6.9T in 2021: Zillow #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘How do you know if your test is a false negative?’ Dr. Murphy answers COVID-19 questions 1/28 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auckland light rail project ‘extremely expensive’, won’t deliver – lobby group #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Race Thompson, Trayce Jackson-Davis lead Indiana over Maryland 68-55 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State failing to protect sex workers – Amnesty #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada defeats U.S. in Hamilton to remain unbeaten on impressive World Cup qualifying run | CBC Sports #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin’s options: Aside from full Ukraine invasion, Russia has other ways to lash out at US, NATO #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH | Gauteng hospital bids farewell to doctor who helped women with fibroids become moms | News24 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Downing Street parties: Boris Johnson awaits his fate as Sue Gray’s partygate report expected this week #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This family spent a lifetime perfecting self-isolation. They still caught COVID-19 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stanford Completes Season Sweep Of No. 15 USC, 64-61 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Presidential Center will dedicate public space to Hadiya Pendleton, teen slain days after performing at inauguration #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New legislation will widen economic sanctions against Russia, Liz Truss says #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NRA post video of elderly lady firing powerful rifle to the delight of gun enthusiasts on Twitter #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[31 Nordstrom Valentine’s Day gifts for every budget | CNN Underscored #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q&amp;A: What is the difference between cloth masks, surgical ones and FFPs? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pak Eyes $3 Billion Loan During Imran Khan’s Upcoming China Visit: Report #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bette Midler Attacks West Virginia Gov. Jim Justice: ‘His Dog’s Ass Would Make a Better Governor’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Activists, officials raise awareness of human trafficking before Super Bowl #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Revolutionary” Estate in Greenwich Sells for $11.77 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philadelphians Flock To Grocery Stores For Winter Storm Essentials #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alcohol ‘directly causes several types of cancer,’ doctors warn #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicolais: Stephen Breyer gets caught by the politics of Supreme Court appointments #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Several apartments damaged in blaze at Chesterfield complex #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utah rolls past CU Buffs women #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power Outage Hits Thousands of SDG&amp;E Customers in North County #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Mom’s Javi Marroquin praised as ‘the best dad’ after sharing video of son Lincoln, 8, crying over Christmas gift #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Window Washer Killed in West Village Was Months Away From Welcoming Baby #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whitecaps training camp: Brian White’s goal? Keep the goals, and team success, coming #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Diego Unified approves redistricting map meant to increase racial minorities’ representation #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scottsdale’s Big Flood Bet Could be Just a Wash for Homeowners #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adams to NYPD’s 35,000 Cops: ‘I’m Here for You … New Yorkers Are Here for You’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ocean City Police Officer Jacob Harris Arrested After Allegedly Using Tracking Device #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Illinois COVID Update: IL reports 15,453 new cases, 120 deaths #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Los Angeles and San Francisco football rivalry is super fun for fans #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rescue dogs from Afghanistan bring barks and love to B.C. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two-alarm Daly City fire claims woman’s life #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea Fires Unidentified Projectile Into East Sea: South’s Military #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Animal rights advocates raise bloody hell in Midtown over carriage horse collision #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honduras: Chaos in congress as politicians brawl over election of new president #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Island’s Faye Winter alarms fans as they spot big scar on her tummy in Ann Summers shoot #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aicha Coulibaly, Auburn women close strong to stun No. 4 Tennessee #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funeral for NYPD Officer Jason Rivera held at St. Patrick’s Cathedral #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Volunteers who supported Syrian refugees reconnecting to help Afghan newcomers to Canada #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Run-on Review of The Woman in the House Across the Street … #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boris Johnson talks tough on Russia – but does the UK have the military might? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hundreds of truckers pour into Ottawa in protest #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The $30M House That (Possibly) Built The Brooklyn Nets #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farm Laborers Wage Board Will Reduce Overtime Threshold Over the Decade #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cocaine worth €3.1m seized at Dublin Port #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taliban, Western officials hold landmark talks on food crisis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man got fired from Walmart — and blamed it on COVID to collect unemployment, feds say #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Local Community Helping Support School Leader Who Lost Everything In House Fire – WCCB Charlotte’s CW #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World remembers Holocaust amid rise in antisemitism during COVID-19 pandemic #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington state trooper dies after quitting job over vaccination requirement #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TV star Howard Hesseman of ‘WKRP in Cincinnati’ dies at age 81 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. researcher shows how Syrian refugees settling in Vancouver adapt #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[March for peace held in memory of Melissa Ortega #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Irish clowns defeated orange Toronto cops #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Illinois prisoners wrongly used to wash cars, shine shoes for IDOC employee fund, says government watchdog #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report says Tom Brady, who lost two Super Bowls to Giants but won six others, is retiring – but that’s disputed | amNewYork #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live updates: Trucker convoy protest in Ottawa #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MeToo protest in Amsterdam after sexual harassment allegations at TV show #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gardai investigate alleged sexual assaults on teenage girls in Sligo #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake Trump electors in 7 states subpoenaed by Jan. 6 committee #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ukraine crisis: Putin to review US response to Russia’s security demands amid fears over invasion #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late winner brings 10-man Celtic close to Premiership lead ahead of Rangers clash #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detroit Public Library Branches Distributing Free At-Home COVID-19 Tests #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New year means new rules for cannabis industry #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Founder of dating app for men with small penises launches site for bald singletons #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human Nurture review – urgent tale of race, identity and privilege #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘I love you’: Kyrgios and Kokkinakis show emotions after becoming champions #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regis Jesuit High School fires advisers, pulls student magazine over pro-choice column #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Harlem vigil for cops shot in ambush, Adams and other leaders pledge to shut down the ‘iron pipeline’ | amNewYork #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Latinx’ embraced by Latinos seeking gender-neutral identity #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harris aide meets Dem Hispanic caucus, expresses ‘deep regret’ over tweet on illegal immigrants #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghanistan’s Taliban have started their first talks in Europe since takeover #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Open men’s final live: Nadal devastated as final hits insane level #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Approaching Winter Storm Impacting Flights Nationwide #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gay’s 30-Yard FG Lifts Rams Over Brady, Buccaneers 30-27 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Identical twin released on bond 9 years after brother confessed to murder #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Asian grandmother sucker-punched while walking in Brooklyn #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Savannah mayor vows to stop drunkenness and include minorities in Saint Pats Parade #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six arrested after investigation into robberies targeting Asian women in San Jose #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Prioritizing Antiviral Pills for ‘Non-White’ People #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wounded Warrior Project 5K raises money to help injured veterans ‘Carry Forward’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lamar and Yuma schools cling to Savages and Tribe after being told to drop Native American mascots #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow quickly pilling up as nor’easter hits New Jersey #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barty outplays Collins to win maiden Australian Open title #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFL bettor turns $20 site credit into $579K on insane championship game parlay #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ukraine Releases Photos of President Zelensky After Controversial Biden Phone Call #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transfer Deadline Day 2022 live: Latest news and moves as January window closes #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Wall Motor ploughs $1.9bn into Brazil as global expansion picks up #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Port Houston sees record year for containers, tonnage fueled by imports in 2021 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facing complaint against mayor, Surrey may shutter ethics office until after election #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off-Duty Clearwater Police Officer Arrested #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future Of Parklets In Downtown Menlo Park Sparks Debate Among Neighboring Businesses #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perry Johnson Becomes 13th Republican To Join Race For Michigan Governor #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peyton Manning eschewed Tom Brady talk to gush over ‘Emily in Paris’ on SNL #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boston snow ties record as winter storm gives way to bitter cold #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK to offer major NATO deployment amid Ukraine crisis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GM CEO Tests an Autonomous Car Without Safety Driver: ‘It’s Surreal!’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harry and Meghan weigh in on Spotify row saying they expressed concerns about COVID misinformation last April #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hanya Yanagihara’s ‘To Paradise’ Is a 720 Page Exploration of Relationships #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phoenix officers save man from burning car #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloomington man faces attempted murder charge after shooting at apartments #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miscommunication Led To Handout At Denver Rec Centers Of Expired COVID Tests Without Instructions #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Community Mourns Faribault Woman Struck And Killed by Rice Co. Sheriff’s Sergeant #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lula leaves clues about plans for Brazil’s economy if re-elected #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While NFL plays title games, world waits on Tom Brady #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dori: Seattle K9 killed in line of duty mourned; loss triggers memories for dog owners #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State epidemiologist says omicron surge is beginning to peak in Texas but hospitals remain strained | Houston Public Media #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indigenous, Native American tribes are pushing for voting rights #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strange island on Google Maps sends Reddit users into frenzy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man found shot last weekend becomes Toronto’s 10th homicide of year #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cameroon blames stadium deaths on ‘massive’ influx of fans #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photos: Antifa supporters, Proud Boys clash in Portland | US &amp; Canada News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interstate 580 Reopens in Both Directions Following Police Activity #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are Asian women the target of xenophobia? – The San Francisco Examiner #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘I want Jesus Christ Superstar at my funeral – live!’: Mel Giedroyc’s honest playlist #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro-life advocates warn of ‘egregious’ Democratic bill that would guarantee abortion rights throughout US #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Washington to Trump to Biden, new presidents meet unwanted foreign crises #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Law enforcement officers leaving departments at staggering rates #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rafael Nadal needs one more win to break the record he shares with Djokovic #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Possible new victim identified in decades-old case of San Francisco ‘Doodler’ serial killer #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tribal eviction plan pits Native American authority vs. civil rights #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three dead in east Vancouver house fire #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dozens of new hotel projects are in the pipeline for Phoenix metro #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A third Covid-19 case reported in Taranaki on Sunday #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chan, Zuckerberg fighting Native American vaccine hesitancy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mega Millions $421million jackpot won by single ticket in California #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multicultural Health Foundation Spearheading Effort to Improve Vaccine Rates Among Minority Families #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotify to add advisories to podcasts talking about COVID-19, CEO says – National | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky told Biden to ‘tone down’ his messaging about invasion #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Couple Staying at a Sonoma Airbnb Allegedly Stole an Adopted Cat… and Took Her to SoCal #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protests flare across Poland after death of young mother denied an abortion #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Owner of wandering Lake County, Ill., bison just wants her back home #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Franklin County Sheriff’s Office to Establish Body-Worn Cameras Program – Columbus Underground #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GUIDE: Free Snow Removal Services Available For Seniors, People With Disabilities #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US to block millions for Egypt over human rights #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow kicksleds from Finland catching on in rural N.B. community | CBC News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Rep. Dan Crenshaw sends mail-in ballot applications to voters after Texas banned the practice for local election officials | Houston Public Media #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[France: Left-wing presidential candidates reject running together #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man Survives After Driving Car Into Icy Pond On Limerick Township Golf Course In Montgomery County #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kyrgios set to cash in like never before #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy Gives Winter Weather Briefing #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chicago Weather Alert: Dangerous Driving Conditions With Snow Causing Low Visibility For Friday Commute #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Diego bikers to collect blankets for homeless folks and veterans – #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Minneapolis, Historic Churches Find New Life As Neighborhood Centers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Simple Solution for Getting Cars Off the Road Right Now #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBA-Best Suns Roll To 9th Straight Win, Topping Timberwolves 134-124 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Storm Malik sweeps across northern Europe leaving four dead – after two people were killed by falling trees in UK #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[St. Brigid’s Day to be marked with new Irish bank holiday and lots of music #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Multiple Vehicles’ Stuck on Cape Cod Roads as Winter Storm Slams Massachusetts #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Romantically-involved Florida deputies dead after possible murder-suicide in St. Augustine #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 100 ex-Afghan forces and officials slain since August, UN says #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SD County Supervisors vote to micro-enterprise home kitchens – #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best stays for book lovers around the world #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men’s soccer: After Canada’s historic night in Honduras, now all eyes are on Hamilton #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Mom Chelsea Houska’s daughter Aubree dances with Cole DeBoer #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syrian refugees face yet another struggle as heavy rains flood displacement camp #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday Sport: Sides forced to share the spoils in Allianz National Football League | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4.0 magnitude earthquake strikes near Palomar Mountain in north San Diego County #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pittsburgh bridge collapse: Human chain formed to help people from dangling bus #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TMD resolving issues with Texas National Guardsmen deployed with Operation Lone Star #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martyn Ford vows to settle rivalry with “disgusting” and “useless” Iranian Hulk #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 priests, 2 lay people to be beatified in El Salvador #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AFL player Jordan De Goey pleads guilty to harassment #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US newsman explains Russia and Ireland situation as some ‘worry’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How a hyperactive cell in the brain might trigger Alzheimer’s disease #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family to Biden: Prioritize release of Lombard man held hostage in Afghanistan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amber Alert Issued For 1-Year-Old Philadelphia Boy After Car Theft In Strawberry Mansion #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-cop’s trial for Taylor raid offers new chance for justice #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bond denied for Oscar Rosales, shooting suspect in death of Pct. 5 Cpl. Galloway #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two African refugees set up a sports platform to prevent other refugees from being trapped in human trafficking #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel president on 1st visit to UAE amid regional tension #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says Biden can’t enter a sports stadium in the US ‘without being loudly mocked and ridiculed,’ but the former president was booed at a 2019 World Series game #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Child, man dead at idyllic Sydney bay #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lunar New Year 2022: What to know about Year of the Tiger #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FanDuel promo code heats up last January weekend | amNewYork #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motorcyclist Dead After Fatal Four-Vehicle Crash In Arlington #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judiciary – not just gardaí – face questions about past actions #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bay Area Projects to Benefit From U.S. Infrastructure Funding #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Convoy protesters call for end to COVID-19 health restrictions on Parliament Hill #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four men wounded in Oakland shootings #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Inappropriate’: Republicans Break From Trump’s Pledge To Pardon Jan. 6 Rioters #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can former Scientologists take the church to court? Or are religious tribunals the only recourse? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deb Cook appointed as new Brownsburg Town Manager #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dozens of children with spina bifida are still waiting years for surgery #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michigan High School Students Participating In Safe Driving Campaign #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump dangles prospect of pardons for Jan. 6 rioters as he teases presidential run | CBC News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ayoka Lee scores NCAA record 61 as K-State women rout No. 14 Oklahoma #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayer and Prostitutes: Redeeming Love Tackles Faith-Based Romance – LA Weekly #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>