<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Forgiving fans began to chant "It's OK" while the singer cried over the phone. #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox News host doubled down on the theory that Democrats are "intentionally accelerating demographic change" to replace voters #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrew Lloyd Webber Talks Transgender Performers, Theater Advocacy and ‘Starlight Express’ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JoJo Fletcher Shares Amazon Winter Fashions &amp; Beauty Must-Haves #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Reviews Are In! Our Editors' Picks From the Sundance Film Festival #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘The Gilded Age’ Review: Carrie Coon and Christine Baranski Add Pizzazz to HBO’s Blissful Period Drama #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Mom OG's Cheyenne Floyd and Cory Wharton Had a 'Rough Time' When He Left for 'The Challenge': 'I Did Not Want Him to Leave' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Teen Mom's Maci Bookout and Son Bentley Are Normalizing Therapy for All Ages #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Outstanding Carrie Bradshaw Hair Moments In ‘And Just Like That’ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adriana Lima looks glamorous in slate grey iridescent metallic dress #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Stamos Goofs Around With Son Billy, 3, In Adorable Video After Bob Saget’s Death #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Megan Thee Stallion grinds on singer Shenseea in raunchy music video #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Mom's Briana Dejesus Responds to Kailyn Lowry's "Meritless" Defamation Lawsuit #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carole Baskin responds to the first trailer for Joe vs. Carole #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paris Hilton says she wants 'probably two or three' kids #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rachel Brosnahan Wears Open, Midriff Top With Nothing Underneath In Stunning Look—Photo #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prince Andrew's 41 denials ahead of civil trial - and 8 things he admits #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 18th birthday Princess Ingrid Alexandra #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Time to Admit Kim Kardashian's Romance With Pete Davidson Just Might Have Staying Power #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kacey Musgraves Delivers an Impromptu Performance of Fleetwood Mac's "Dreams" #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan Gosling Takes Daughters Esmeralda, 7, &amp; Amada, 5, For Ice Cream In LA — Photo #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Noodle the pug to star in his own picture book #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘The Princess’ Director on Crafting a Diana Documentary Using Only Archives #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goldie Hawn talks staying out of politics in new interview #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Megan Thee Stallion Dances In Tiny Gold Bikini In Sexy Mirror Video: Watch #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bawk! Bawk! Chicken Hands: The Internet Cares Naught As Khloe Kardashian Cryptically Cries Out Amid Tristan Thompson’s Latest Trollopy Tryst #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rachel Lindsay Reveals Where She &amp; Hannah Brown Stand After ‘N-Word’ Controversy #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Afterparty Cast Went Full Method for the Unique Murder Mystery #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sundance 2022: "I really wanted to make a film where my daughter could see herself on screen," James Ponsoldt says #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foy Vance Reveals The Moment He First Met Anderson East That Led To Their Duet ‘Sapling’ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Henrik Lundqvist Reflects — and Looks to Future — as Jersey Retired by Rangers: 'Extremely Grateful' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Brady’s NFL Future: How Wife Gisele Bundchen Factors Into His Decision To Keep Playing #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jogger Discovers a Decomposing Body Inside a Tent in Central Park Behind The Met: Police #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anna Kendrick and Bill Hader have been quietly dating for a year: report #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blac Chyna flaunts peachy derriere in black thong and sheer catsuit #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gun control advocates express disappointment with Biden #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rescuers save dog by attaching sausage to drone: 'Millie was hungry' #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mahershala Ali and Bradley Cooper on ‘Swan Song,’ ‘Nightmare Alley’ and Not Quitting Acting #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gun control advocates nervous as Supreme Court takes up first 2nd Amendment case in a decade #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Madonna takes daughter Mercy James to Tupac Shakur interactive exhibit #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Mom's Maci Bookout Has "No Interest" in Communicating With Ryan Edwards' Family #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 great moments from the 2016 Tony Awards — in GIFs: Neil Patrick Harris is actually bald, folks #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How do you keep growing the legacy brand? You just keep going back to what it's all about," company president Halle Stanford says #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Hiddleston Supports Fellow Marvel Star Benedict Cumberbatch at 'Power of the Dog' Screening #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shudder Acquires Sundance Psychological Horror Film ‘Speak No Evil’ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Are the Sundance 2022 Films You’re Going to Want to See #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Josh Duhamel Joins 'Mighty Ducks: Game Changers' Season 2 | Entertainment Tonight #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Real's Jeannie Mai Jenkins reveals first child Monaco is a GIRL #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Padma Lakshmi Bonds With Daughter, 11, While Sitting Courtside At Knicks Game — Photos #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Casey Affleck, 46, and girlfriend Caylee Cowan, 23, share open-mouthed kiss #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From returning favorites, such as “Atlanta” and “This Is Us,” to new series like “Abbott Elementary” and “Partner Track,” here are 24 shows to keep an eye on in the new year. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Am I OK?’ Filmmakers Tig Notaro &amp; Stephanie Allynne Set ‘Time And Space’ As Next Feature; Judd Apatow Producing #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doja Cat, Ed Sheeran and Liam Gallagher to perform at The BRIT Awards #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The non-alcohol drinks and spirits that pass for the real deal (and the one's that really, really don't) #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Babysitter’ Review: A Hilarious Psychosexual Horror-Comedy with Technicolor Pop #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black Women's Stories Are Center Stage At Sundance 2022 #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Household Cleaning Products, According to Editors Who Swear by Them #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Mom's Amber Portwood Sends Tearful Apology to Daughter Leah Amid Strained Relationship #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chrissy Teigen &amp; John Legend Step Out on Lunch Date After Adopting New Puppy! #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the Kim Kardashian and Ye divorce drama is so uncomfortable to watch #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laura Marano Debuts New Song 'Worst Kind of Hurt' From 'The Royal Treatment' - Listen Now! #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erika Jayne’s Estranged Husband Tom Giardi Denied Discharge In Bankruptcy Court Allowing Creditors To Go After Former Famed Attorney #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Teen Mom"'s Cheyenne Floyd's Fiancé Zach Davis Gets a Tattoo of Her Daughter ...#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the Bombshells From Kanye "Ye" West's Latest Interview: Kim Kardashian, Pete Davidson and More #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "Late Show" host tears into the Senate minority leader over voting rights. #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amy Schneider wrote a long list of thanks after her historic “Jeopardy!” streak came to a close, including a heartfelt message to her girlfriend, Genevieve Davis. #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TheWrap Screening Series: “Inside every beast lives a victim,” says Hugo Covarrubias of “Bestia,” about the mental state of a secret police agent in Chile #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TLC Star Shauna Rae Reveals She Visited an OB-GYN to See If She 'Can Carry a Baby' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Krispy Kreme is offering a dozen free doughnuts to blood donors #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cardi B Awarded $1.25 Million in Lawsuit Against Tasha K, Whose Allegations Made Her "Suicidal" #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billions: Peloton Says It 'Did Not Agree' to Appearance in Season 6 Premiere #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The Mighty Ducks: Game Changers' Casts Josh Duhamel In Season 2 After Emilio Estevez's Exit #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dionne Warwick Recalls How She First Met Sidney Poitier: 'Actually, I Stalked Him' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Batgirl Casts Ivory Aquino as First Trans Character in a DC Comics Film #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Mom's Tyler Baltierra weeps as he reunites with daughter Carly #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Naomi Campbell Pens Emotional Tribute to André Leon Talley: 'Rest Easy King' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RHOBH’s Erika Jayne and Tom Girardi’s Divorce and Legal Woes: Everything We Know So Far #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New couple alert? Brad, 58, is linked to Swedish singer Lykke, 35 #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sundance 2022: Film follows three college students of color struggling to figure out what to do when they find a white girl passed out in their apartment #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Mom's Leah Messer Introduces New Boyfriend to Her Kids Amid "Surprise" Romance #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Resurrection’ Review: Rebecca Hall and Tim Roth Face Off in Impressively Deranged Psychological Thriller #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TheWrap magazine: "The higher we go, the less dialogue we have," says director Patrick Imbert of his mountaineering tale #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biracial American opera singer Maria Ewing dies aged 71  #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian Remembers Thierry Mugler After His Death: ‘There’s No One Like You’ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Mom's Catelynn Lowell and Tyler Baltierra Reveal Their Baby Girl's Unique Name #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heavenly Bites | Official Trailer | Netflix #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's “no defending a system that endlessly inflates the wealth of the world’s richest while condemning billions to easily preventable poverty,” said the Patriotic Millionaires chair after the group's letter asked for higher taxes for the wealthy. #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 best albums of 2021, including Ed Sheeran, Lil Nas X and St. Vincent #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the Secrets on How Penn Badgley, Ed Westwick and Jessica Szohr Were Cast in Gossip Girl #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Holland, Andrew Garfield &amp; Tobey Maguire Reveal Whose Idea It Was To Recreate Spider-Man Meme In First Group Interview #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freshman golfer J.R. Smith is seeking an NIL deal #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene used an offensive term for Asian people while arguing that the Republican Party has supporters from diverse backgrounds. #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tuesday Ten: Tips for New Dog Owners #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Addison Rae Recalls Watching Grandfather Survive Kidney Cancer: ‘He’s Very Inspiring’ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elle Fanning delved beyond the headlines to play Michelle Carter, a Massachusetts woman who was convicted of involuntary manslaughter after her boyfriend died by suicide in 2014. #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox News' Ingraham reacted to being parodied on "Saturday Night Live" #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kanye West Goes Off On Kim Kardashian For Letting North, 8, Wear Lipstick On TikTok Without His Permission #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alicia Keys parties with her pals in a 'bubble room' in London #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fans have been chronicling the style evolution of "Succession" characters — from the inner circle to the hangers-on — over the past three seasons. #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Juan Williams: It's Trump vs. McConnell for the GOP's future #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['We're family': How the I-Collective is bringing Indigenous people and food together #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wake held for NYPD officer Jason Rivera #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ian Alexander: 5 Things About Regina King’s Son Dead By Suicide At Just 26 #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Travis Barker’s Daughter Alabama, 16, ‘Can’t Wait’ For Him To Marry Kourtney Kardashian #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perrie Edwards Enjoys Beach Day with 5-Month-Old Baby Boy Axel: 'You Are My Sunshine' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a roll, Amy Schneider now holds the second-longest 'Jeopardy!' streak of all time #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jensen Ackles Explains His Reasoning For Not Telling Jared Padalecki About 'Supernatural' Prequel Series #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Madsen's son Hudson dies at 26: 'We are heartbroken and overwhelmed' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sofia Vergara Transforms Into Griselda Blanco For Upcoming Netflix Series #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Legend Is Launching an 'Affordable and Accessible' Skincare Line Which Celebrates Diversity #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hailey Baldwin Rocks Nude Bra &amp; Underwear In Sexy Photos As She Teases New Skincare Line #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Horrific": Six found dead in Milwaukee home and police suspect all were homicides #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TheWrap magazine: "Most of the time, indigenous folks on television or in film are relegated to what we call ‘feathers and leather,’" says the Native writer and actress #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘The View’ Debates Shailene Woodley’s Engagement To Anti-Vaxxer Aaron Rodgers: "Marriage Is Difficult Enough" #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Not all menstruators are women': Why nonbinary folks want to talk about their periods #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kanye West shocks fans by posting Jordan brand logo to his Instagram #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Mom’s Briana DeJesus Confirms She’s Single 3 Months After Javi Gonzalez Engagement #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tiffany Haddish addresses DUI arrest: 'We're going to work it out' #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arnold Schwarzenegger involved in LA car crash #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kourtney Kardashian shows off her curves in bottom-flashing dress #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Mom OG’s Tyler Baltierra and Catelynn Lowell's 4th Daughter Leaves Hospital; Parents Share First Look #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Aftershock’ Review: A Vital Look at the Maternal Mortality Crisis for Black Women in America #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kourtney Kardashian turns up the heat in red leather 'fit in new pics #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aaron Rodgers’ Feelings On His Future In The NFL After Green Bay’s Playoffs Loss #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peacemaker Blasts Onto List of Most In-Demand New Shows #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black Lawmakers Walk Out in Protest as Mississippi Senate Votes on Critical Race Theory Bill #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sam Raimi Explains His ‘Spider-Man: No Way Home’ Feelings, Reveals Whether ‘Doctor Strange 2’ Is Finished Filming #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reports: Sean Payton to step away as the head coach of the New Orleans Saints #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rachel Zegler on ‘West Side Story’ Oscar Buzz, ‘Shazam 2’ and White Latina Privilege #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See how Olympic athlete's phone call to mom ended in happy tears #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Mom's Chelsea Houska Shares the Comment About Daughter Aubree That "Makes Me Sick" #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan Reynolds &amp; Blake Lively Link Arms &amp; Twin In Matching Navy Coats While Out In NYC #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 5 Home Trends Millennials and Baby Boomers Just Can’t Agree On #URL# via #USER# /]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Stamos shares photo of Bob Saget getting in one last dirty joke 'even in death' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daisy Edgar-Jones Takes a Feminist Horror-Comedy Bite Out of Modern Dating with ‘Fresh’ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Secret Invasion' Set Photos Feature Samuel L. Jackson, Cobie Smulders &amp; Kingsley Ben-Adir! #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the "Sex and the City" &amp; "And Just Like That..." Hot Spots Where You Can Dine in New York City #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Priyanka Chopra and Nick Jonas Welcome Their First Child Via Surrogacy #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Girl Picture’ Review: Finnish Teens Look for Love and Orgasms in an Honest and Affecting Coming-of-Age Story #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rihanna Snuggles Up To BF A$AP Rocky For Saturday Night Dinner Date In NYC — Photos #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Hatching’ Review: Girlhood Gets the Horrifying, Hilarious Creature Feature It Deserves #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahsoka Tano Disney Plus Series Adds Mary Elizabeth Winstead #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[R&amp;B/Hip-Hop Fresh Picks of the Week: Babyface Ray, Denzel Curry, Beam &amp; More #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taylor Lautner Says Fiancée Struggled to Accept His Proposal Because She Was 'Weeping So Hard' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pinocchio first official teaser: Ewan McGregor voices Jiminy Cricket #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lykke Li: 5 Things To Know About The Singer Reportedly Dating Brad Pitt #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebs Wearing Slip Dresses #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queen Latifah Breaks Silence On Co-Star Chris Noth’s Firing From ‘The Equalizer’ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dwayne 'The Rock' Johnson upsets animal rights advocates with pictures from aquarium visit #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peacock Releases First Look Trailer For Upcoming Comedy Series ‘Bust Down’ Starring Sam Jay, Chris Redd, Langston Kerman &amp; Jak Knight #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The supernatural drama has a straight-to-series order #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ciara opens up about her trip to the White House #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disney Assures Peter Dinklage on ‘Snow White’ Reboot: ‘We Are Taking a Different Approach’ on Dwarf Characters #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Descendant’ Review: Africatown Documentary Rectifies Black Erasure by Filling Historical Gaps #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Secrets of Playboy’ recalls the ugly side of Hefner’s empire of beauty #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Black Panther: Wakanda Forever" to resume filming as Letitia Wright returns from injury #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sundance 2022 Winners: From ‘Nanny’ and ‘Navalny’ to Crowd-Pleaser ‘Cha Cha Real Smooth,’ Indie Fest Spreads the Wealth #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oscars Predictions: Best Original Song – Kid Cudi Could Make History As the First Black Person Nominated for Two Separate Movie Songs #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Julia Fox denies romance with Ye is motivated by money and attention #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicole Kidman Bought 10-Year-Old Kristen Stewart Walkie Talkies for Christmas After ‘Panic Room’ Rehearsals #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Mom OG’s Catelynn Lowell and Tyler Baltierra Reveal Their 4th Daughter’s Name #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regina King spent New Year's Eve smiling and toasting with her son Ian #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Mom's Amber Portwood Comes Out as Bisexual #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chrishell Stause Calls Out Exes Justin Hartley and Keo Motsepe for Being Love Bombers: 'I Let Things Slide' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Betty White’s Final Video Released #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mace Neufeld, Producer of ‘Patriot Games,’ ‘Beverly Hills Cop III,’ Dies at 93 #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missouri's Second Amendment Preservation Act frustrates law enforcement and gun enthusiasts #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sundance 2022: As women's liberty to choose faces demise, Phyllis Nagy's drama looks at the secret group that provided abortions before they were legalized #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barbara Walters’ Spouses: Everything To Know About Her 3 Marriages &amp; The One Man She Married Twice #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[W. Kamau Bell told HuffPost about his docuseries and coming to terms with his own complicated feelings about the disgraced entertainer. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Emergency' cast discusses comedy, racism at Sundance #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad Bunny Announces Ambitious 29-Date Stadium Tour #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sam Waterston Returns to "Law &amp; Order" as Jack McCoy in First Teaser for Upcoming NBC Revival #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only Southerners Know the Right Way to Make This Sandwich #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the man who started a movement offering stand-in 'families' at LGBTQ weddings #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ian Alexander Jr., son of Regina King, dies at age 26  #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Javier Bardem dressed up as a Bond girl for Daniel Craig: 'Oh, my God' #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Mom's Amber Portwood Walks Off Reunion After Learning Secret About Daughter Leah #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Wahlberg congratulates his daughter Ella on one-year anniversary #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jessica Szohr Opens Up About Getting Backlash For Vanessa Abrams on 'Gossip Girl' #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kanye West Wears Bright White Contact Lenses With Red Leather Clad Julia Fox At PFW — Photos #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jan. 6 committee member reacts to Newt Gingrich jail comment: 'Really unconscionable' #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pregnant teen's baby cut from womb after she was strangled to death #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Jennifer Hudson and ‘Respect’ Could Set a Record for Black Women at the Oscars #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thomas Doherty Sports a Different Look at Dior Homme Fashion Show #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devon Windsor shows off her incredible model physique in a red bikini #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sundance 2022: "Someone would tell me a story about a sister, a friend, a cousin who had died from complications of childbirth," Tonya Lewis Lee tells TheWrap #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teri Hatcher Reveals She Had a Miscarriage in Her 40s While Trying for Second Baby via Sperm Donor #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the Editing of ‘The Lost Daughter’ Captures the Way We Think #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT THE?? Interracial Couple’s Racist Engagement Photos Go Viral On Social Media #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Streaming service is making $10 per paid sub, including advertising #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Fugees Cancel Their 25th Anniversary Reunion Tour #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Eurovision to "SNL", Måneskin Suits Up for Their Saturday Night Live Debut #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everybody Loves Raymond star Brad Garrett, 61, secretly wed #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Idina Menzel's 'Not My Name' Challenge Pokes Fun at John Travolta's Infamous 'Ade...#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iHeartCountry Festival to feature Thomas Rhett, Carrie Underwood, Maren Morris #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Celebrity Big Brother" season 3 cast revealed #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['RHOSLC' recap: Jennie Nguyen says she 'broke' husband's ribs in angry fight #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mom and Baby Who Died in Petco Park Fall Ruled Murder-Suicide #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catelynn Lowell and Tyler Baltierra Cry After Reunion With Daughter Carly: 'Doesn't Get Easier' #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>