<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Sure but what are the current hospitalisation and fatality rates? What is the government's forecast case load and how are they gearing up hospitals?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow!!! The Age and Herald Sun must be feeling shameful for having promoted those anti vax riots. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Worst case scenario he uses "Australia's national interest " and an army of flag waving RWNJs to successfully win the election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We know Scott's sound bites are aimed at people who MIGHT vote Labor. Malcolm is the perfect counterpoint to people who MIGHT vote Libs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You must be racked with guilt having completely abrogated your responsibilities in quarantine, aged care, vaccine roll out.  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tell me again how I should listen to advice from business leaders. Great community minded leadership.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Only one thing left to do. Set up a union led popular media platform to counter the overwhelming   far right MSM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm not sure we want such a softy leading us into war with China #USER# . Any chance you can do a puff piece for Dutton headlined with "The man who can save Australia "]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Emergency call out to #USER# for another uplifting article for the NSW Premier... we're getting desperate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# To be fair Dan had forced him to stay home for the longest lockdown ever where he couldn't figure out what Dan Murphy's opening hours were.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm not sure facts are relevant any more in an election campaign.   #HASHTAG# need to win at managing the news cycle and hijacking the headlines. We need stunts to undermine the Murdoch/Stokes/Costello LNP gaslit recovery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Not sure I could cope after revelations star #HASHTAG# Premier found to have ignored health advice purely to differentiate from Dan Andrews. Just sickening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's like the Dr in Wuhan who alerted the world about Covid on SM but was shut down by the government. I hate it when to government tells people what to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think may people I Geelong will remember they used to have jobs at Ford until Joe Hockey and his LNP friends shut down Australia's automotive industry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If anyone can improve Duttons popularity it would be Speers. Hopefully will get to hear Phil Coorey's opinion on how popular Dutton could be too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Any news on how 7 profits from fuelling racism?  Any news on which companies advertise and therefore fund these divisive programing decisions? Any interviews with seven execs on the cards? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yes that's true. So why did the current government get elected and why, even in my wildest dreams,  will #HASHTAG# approval rating not drop below 40%? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yellow peril paranoia at its finest. Thank you Stan Grant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We need another inspiring piece from super Phil Coorey to save the country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Scotty told me he didn't want government telling people what to do.  Is he lying again? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Think here we're confusing contempt with the intentional baiting of reasonable, considered views, designed to destabilise society for political gain. The stoking of hate with outrageous pub comment is contemptible. The contempt is justified. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How many fatalities can be linked to half arsed public health response from #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I don't think it's fair that #USER# gets to use his platform to highlight a minority grievance during a public health emergency.  Follow the public health guidelines and ignore the disinformation. We desperately needs media diversity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# In terms of fairness and sensible policy development we need to rid Australia of our obscene media players pushing public debate further right. Media diversity and policing of community standards. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# will be more reliant on #HASHTAG# church group voting blocks to stay in power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I would say regulation and preparation of the aged care sector is a bigger failure at 600+ fatalities.  But it's early days. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Drum, 730Report, QandA, Insiders. When can we just bite the bullet and have a subscription based community news service?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "We" voted by a slim majority for one of the most corrupt and inept governments in living memory. If the media didn't actively promote #HASHTAG# disinformation we might have a chance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But let's give a brain dead footballer a platform to undermine public health directives for balance. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Same here.  Funny how it was no surprise. Like watch a train wreck. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "Destroy jobs and divide Australia's " neatly sums up the last 12 years of government policy development.  Keep it up guys. We'll be a third world, low wage, rust belt before anyone realises. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I would say Joe Hockey destroyed Australia's manufacturing sector.  Ask anyone who's worked in manufacturing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Let's be clear. Corporate media fully backs the LNPs corporate welfare agenda. Ambitious "journalists " get promoted and good researchers don't. There needs to be a community subscription based media model sponsored by government grants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just sickening. Corrupt and negligent but happy to use mental health as a false flag to undermine public health. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If Premiers don't lockdown with unvaccinated population of children what's your alternative? 
Die/live with the virus?
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm busy today but I'm hoping my Twitter friends will report the details of the French ambassadors speech at today's national press club.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Please ask him to tickle you tummy David #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What would you do if Scott wins another miracle election?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Let's face it. The "controversial" discrimination bill is intended to divert media and public attention away  from Colbecks catastrophic aged care disaster, Frydenburgs pathetic debt and deficit, Duttons embarrassing plague ship and Scotty's integrity. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right on. Forget noname celebrity.  Where are the journalists asking about Stokes community responsibilities and Hawker immigration systems.  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just stunned Vic Libs can persist with this anti lockdown garbage given the situation in NSW. If you wanted to make a contribution Lobby your NSW and Fed colleagues to lockdown harder. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Media will choose the winner. Large cohort of disengaged voters will be voting based on their favourite influencers. Kyle, Jackie, Huesy,  Hadley, Mitchell.  How will #USER# beat Scott at gaming the media cycle?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If the Federal government lied about ADF support at the start of the pandemic how can journalists take subsequent claims at face value? Vaccine announcements,  free trade announcements,  superannuation announcements,  Medicare announcements.... #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Wow! So this issue isn't that the information is objectively true and correct? Tells you everything you need to know about #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And apparently you don't need a science degree to be an epidemiologist or public health professional. Go Tim.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Does anyone have the ratings for last night tv? I was watching muster dogs for the record.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They've had two years and they just don't care. Corporations pursue a corporate agenda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm sure it was Dan's security guards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I guess the issue is how he actually supports public health directives rather than what he says.  If he's voting with Pauline undermining vaccine mandates he is working against his publicly state position. Consistent with #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow. Progressive leadership. That's what we needed 8 years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Cohort of goldfish in the electorate and captured media a bit concerning though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I briefly caught some of the Drum "I don't like Twitter " episode yesterday.  Is it just me or is the ABC running a campaign to delegitimise Twitter? Asking for some friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wow. Who could have thought LNP could be so disconnected from reality? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The reality is that MSM pushes a distorted world view where sensible progressive policies are framed as extreme LW. Australia's current #HASHTAG# has more to do with the media than any politician.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Harden up buddy. It's a public health emergency.  Think of you fellow free citizens you can help save and keep free. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Surprisingly little engagement with #USER# pathetic little tweets.  Not sure why #USER# bothers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do we know the Challenger disaster was caused by Imperial/Metric o ring mix up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Looks like Costello management all sizzle no sausage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If only Scott implemented timely quarantine and vaccination programs this economic catastrophe could have been averted. Josh should have gone into bat for Victorians but was more concerned with the media bargaining code for Rupert. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Seems like lying has been normalised in the elitist corporate welfare lobby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No federal quarantine, federal aged care unprepared, media and federal government undermining public health directives. Vic learnt the hard way so why should NSW repeat the same mistakes? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Labor has sensibly targeted a a figure it thinks it can sell to the uninformed electorate. If you're wondering why the electorate is being fed garbage from a captive media rather than credible scientists tell me how Greens will regulate media diversity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Joe Hildebrand and Ben Fordham would be proud ... boys. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Busy drafting sky news talking points]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow! Letting it ripped living with the virus might have huge implications for the economy. Not even an economic with kid like #USER# could have seen that coming. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Surely skynews should be compensating the nation for its long anti lockdown activism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Let's cross to Stan Grant to hear his analysis...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is the best looking scam since Angus's "strategic fuel reserve " located in the US. #HASHTAG# has got Australia covered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Agreed.  Federal gov bungled quarantine.  Federal gov failed its duty of care through poor regulation of aged care facilities,  Federal gov failed procuring vaccines. State government pub health made plenty of mistakes responding to a one in a century pandemic. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'd also be advising parents to vote #HASHTAG# because the #HASHTAG# won't end well for anyone #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Remember Hokey telling the auto manufacturers to leave Australia. Remember all those news stories about white hot anger of all the manufacturing jobs lost and the damage to the economy? Neither do I. #USER# really doesn't have any credibility left. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ludicrous! Why does #USER# let Fraudenburg comment outside of his portfolio? Not relevant and not credible  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "We have allowed our campaign finance laws to become a strategic threat to our country." #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is the inherent conflict between "entertainment " and public interest journalism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That's more employment than the coal industry.  I wonder if they have similar subsidies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I'm fairly confident media can dictate policy agenda and bring down any government so I would say Murdoch shelters LNP rather than the other way round.  I'm not conf LAB could or would want to regulate and would be left exposed to another franking cred/mining tax campaign.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Look over there!!! It's an African Gang/Death Tax/Yellow Peril.  Seriously Matt.  Drop the cos play and come up with something credible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So. Is Dr Nick still getting paid? Richard Colbeck still getting paid? Why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 1029 cases, hospital code yellow and the media is talking about outdoor recreation. Where is the public interest best served?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Harvey Norman needs the Corporate Welfare apparently #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Unlike parliament house where bullies and abuse are dealt with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Therein lies the value of all this constant outrageous RWNJ media circus. Sensible progressive policies look extreme against the likes of Coorey, Creighton and Credlin. Morrison looks like a moderate. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Your the reporter. Do some research and give us the context. What are the revised odds and how does that compare to the Tasmanian road toll? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Seriously #USER# What is it with you and the cafe owners? Leigh Sales and the anti lockdown activism now this #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# In the name of balance Speersy and Sales should be relegated to "ABC After Dark " 11pm time slot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Any comments from the responsible minister. Richard Colbeck,  Greg Hunt,  Scott Morrison? Easily preventable catastrophe but Scotty was "going to the footy " instead of leading a national pandemic response.  No consequences for failed ministers or failed gov policies. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Fascinating must read article but Geezuz! For example, in 2001, when Bob Carr, a Labor Premier, was about to appoint Michael Costa police minister, he sent Costa to Jones’s home to discuss law-and-order policy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh Jeff. True to LNP form. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Where is the political leadership nationally and in NSW? What is wrong with these people? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think Louise Stanley has got some questions to answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm certainly sick of media personalities with platforms engaging in divisive politics. Media should be working in the public interest. If a manufacturer caused a public health emergency they would be shut down. Time to shut down #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We could ask Angus to sign up for some offshore strategic nuclear fission reserves. Go team Tim!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow. 43.5% are seeing something I'm not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# All that time studies bible, going to church,  praying and talking in tongues and he still doesn't know right from wrong.  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Even better.  Come home and call an election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm surprised you're not suggesting kids need more strong coal in their lives. You're starting to let the side down Matt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My thoughts exactly.  The issue has never been their nationality but how do we justify exceptions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I forgot Hunts vaccine and RAT supply failure. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Vic outbreak triggered by failed NSW containment weeks after start of NSW outbreak.  That would be why the Vic curve is after the NSW curve. I'm not even an epidemiologist,  or a journalist. Just common sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Poor Tom. Only a 3AW shock jock. Must be humbling to have a dad like John]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I thought Tudgy Wudgy was one of the Hillsong faithful? What will happen to all the car parks promised for Knox?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Agreed.  Equally let's condem media orgs undermining public health directives and providing cover for political negligence.  How about each working journalist donate 30% of the wage to essential workers? What do you think #USER# ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not recycled? Just the standard issue LNP brown paper bag. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How are we going with our record debt and deficit Mr Tresurer. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# New generation mask and PPE required.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Headline - "In hindsight, LNP foresight not so good. Thank God for our franking credits "]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Another forgettable contribution from Murdoch's minions. I can't believe Murdoch can get away with not paying tax.  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Surely you can't be suggesting nines chairman Peter Costello isn't prioritising public interest journalism?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sounds like a great idea to extend the life of coal extraction. #HASHTAG# at his best]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But will the government do anything about online disinformation from known sources like Craig Kelly? How did we get to the position where anonymity is the cause of Australia's problems? Thanks for the quality journalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hey! Love your work.  I take back all those bad things I said about MSM but we still need a #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I can't tell if this is the Age parody account or not. Comments attributed to Downer are comical because he is irrelevant. KR and MT clearly have something to offer in terms of public interest commentary. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Also keeps the swing voters disinterested in "politics".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So how will #USER# counter media bias to win the election? Labor ads so far are pretty ordinary. And when in gov what will Labor do to improve media regulation and diversity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# So how does #USER# stand platforming a "corruption apologist" and how is the normalisation of corruption in the public interest? I'd like #USER# to take this question on notice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But it's OK to politicise the armed forces if you don't have proactive policies and have gutted the public service...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# shame. I'm embarrassed. What happened to our ABC?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# On the plus side. The media management strategy seems to be working.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wow! Foresight! Even more impressive in hindsight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I get a bit defensive when people criticise Twitter as though MSM is all squeaky clean.  I would have thought journalists and "personalities " providing platforms for misinformation and hate speech were the bigger problem and worth a regulatory response.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'd always understood that's what it meant and LNP apologists were OK with that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The problem is not the minority of dissenters. The problem is the media amplifying a minority view  into a sustained campaign to undermine public health directives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm expecting a pilots cosplay outfit for this tweet.  Do better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Agreed.  How do we explain all journalists reporting that schools are safe and no one asking the obvious questions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Think of the money they'll save on ... public health services]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How does Costello's #USER# provide a conflict of interest disclaimer on this headline? Surely someone found guilty of falsifying an election by branch stacking is not a credible news source. Oh. Wait a minute #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It beggars belief that #USER# can still draw a wage given his lack of credibility after his "Gladys saves Australia" puff piece. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wel it's an improvement from his last trip to Engadine Macas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I would have thought, in this case, governments were OBLIGED to get involved in people's lives to protect public safety. If we compare Victoria's governance of the pandemic vs Federal governance of climate change which approach protects public safety?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just beggers belief that a government with such a strong background of law and order and a supportive police chief can't police basic public health directives. We can arrest youtubers but not people putting lives a risk. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Beggars belief #USER# "journalist" can run aa story about Gladys and not mention the overwhelming evidence of corruption. WTF is wrong with the #USER# and what happened to the public interest here?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Any of the diggers ask about Federal aged care services? Anyone remember the fallen from 2020 aged care catastrophe? #USER# seemingly working as a paid propagandist. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lots of people opposed seat belts when they were introduced. Mandates required some political risk for public safety. In hindsight reduced fatality rate AND the fact that people are not rational proves why mandates are necessary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thank you NSW LNP. Thank you VIC LNP. Thank you MSM. Thank you Corporate Welfare Lobby. But most of all. Thank you to Morrison and Fraudenburg for you ruthless media management strategy.  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good news story at last. #USER# finally supporting Melbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is how LNP can win the next election.  They have the infrastructure in place to manipulate media narrative and therefore public discourse.  Only way LNP will be beaten is with new media and concerted attacks on usual MSM suspects]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sadly I share your fears. The Corporate Welfare Lobby have got an army of propagandists posing as ministers,  every media outlet eating out of their hands and the IPA. What do the Public Interest Lobby have? Albo and Twitter... #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Looking forward to the national broadcaster running commentary supporting public health directives and not highlighting the the contrarians]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The regulator and the government needs to be held to account. Media diversity and journalism standards are life and death issues. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Factual informative info required to counter the BS alarmists from Murdoch. Great to see infrastructure projects being delivered rather than just promised and taxpayer money syphoned off for marginal seats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think most Australians can relate to Macron's frustration and the offence caused by the #HASHTAG# All Australians know how Macron feels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The reality is that most Australians understand the value of vaccines and are waiting patiently for their turn.   Why the constant BS about hesitancy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Breaking - NSW hoteliers and clubs have the new premier over a barrel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Should media personalities with platforms forment conflict?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hard to avoid the accusation the point of this article from the Costello daily was to hijack the headlines.  Embarrassing how many ABC journalists fell for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I can't believe Murdoch pays #USER# to quite this garbage.   #USER# should hire some journalists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Gold Standard.  Can't wait  to see the Sky News headlines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So will the swing voting margins turn on the nightly news tonight and see "heroic struggles of the working man fighting against tyranny of government" or will they see Victorian democratic processes under attack by a violent mob? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm certainly against media personalities fabricating dissent to undermine a popularly elected government doing a great job managing a public health emergency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ABC working in the public interest again.  I'm so relieved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Credit where Credit is due. Good one Speersy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I think many people are ashamed #USER# and other media personalities with large platforms legitimise ignoring mainstream science. We desperately need media diversity. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Liberal Party have a clear cut "open the economy " corporate welfare platform.  But what do the National Party stand for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I would suggest #HASHTAG# and his brand of media management are more a threat to ordinary Australians through his attacks on social services, Medicare, universities, free press, wage stagnation, export markets, housing affordability....rather than national security.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Masterful framing of election narrative. Freedom vs dictatorship. If there is one thing the #HASHTAG# is good at its winning elections. We need #HASHTAG# to start highlighting opportunities and victories of good governance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He's waiting for #USER# to come back and ask him about how tough his favourite cafe owner has been doing it over the pandemic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I believe all the hivis costumes were bought out for the CFMEU cosplay parade a couple of weeks ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is Macron safe from prosecution with his recent truth bomb? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Looks like he's done it tough over lockdown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hey but let's deny, deflect and delay. Isn't Twitter a real problem...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# For all the stupidity in this tweet I'm glad people haven't forgotten the 800 deaths in aged care. Federal minister responsible for quarantine and aged care still have their jobs despite gross negligence.     #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# FFS. It's a science and technology org you moron. It's supposed to be researching new tech. No one argued it shouldn't develop WiFi because it would put print media out of business.  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# One Victorian has described Libs adoption #HASHTAG# disinformation tactics as "insane" and suggests they stop sponging off taxpayer incomes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Remember that time when Jesus covered up a rape to win an election...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Think of all the non belivers he infected. Maybe Creighton was right and we should sacrifice some people for the greater good. For good measure they should be quarantined in their churches to avoid burdening hospitals and the economy. Win win. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What was their response when they were told their taxes would be used to prop up failing businesses who donate to #HASHTAG# like  coal, gas, oh and Murdoch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I would like a constructive way to challenge the dominant outragy media cycle.  What are your suggestions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Can we relocate all the PMO staff, Qantas staff and St Joseph boys to Western Sydney and essential workers to Eastern Sydney till the vaccines arrive? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How are you gwith your gas lead recovery? Maybe time to sell your fossil fuel shares]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We're talking about the federal government right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# JFC give it a rest. No one cares what #USER# says. Not  worth the tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And when will #USER# and #USER# issue an apology for undermining public health directives?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# On the plus side Vic tracing has always been very proactive and the test numbers are still high. Let's hope people adhere to lockdown guidelines till we get 95% of the total population vaccinated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not really news worthy is it. Maybe stop and think if it's relevant to the public interest before posting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Quality writing, especially the bit about a government full of Ayn Rand fetishists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I thought Scott had already destabilised our economy and healthcare after not implementing quarantine,  not preparing aged care and not ordering vaccines. Not sure how anyone could do worse. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I believe Big Wino has got a lot to answer for. Making money off poor students with the cask conspiracy is unconscionable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Imagine a state premier announcing that we should all learn to live with the fires and keep everything open because fire restrictions, back burning, fire resistant building standards aren't good for the economy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The problem is when a vanishingly small proportion gets overrepresented in the media. That's not democracy.  That's the majority being exploited for clicks and ratings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# What!!! Why does "ALP need to commit"!!!  Morrison gov is corrupt.  They need to be held to account by the law, by the media and by the voters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Can't even build a chook shed properly let alone manage record debt and deficit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well worth reading.  Thanks for posting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The whole country is waiting and seeing.  The whole country is relying on NSW success.  The whole country has heard about NSW gold standards and green shoots.  But go ahead and experiment with a soft lockdown after Victorias solid successful go hard go early approach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Geezuz.  I'm surprised he could show his face in public given his record debt and deficit. Must be the worst treasurer in Australian history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Makes you realise how well #USER# did to pull a critical mass of Victorians into action with a unified purpose.  Not a simple task. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# important question. Has Fraudenburg used public funds? Did China owe Spud a favour in return for the Port of Darwin deal? Is #HASHTAG# making a killing from his DC pizza shop front? The public deserves to know public officials are working in the public interest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As opposed to Scott who responded to a once in a century pandemic with ... "I'm going to the footy "]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I want the government in my life...a good one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We mandate seat belts, speed limits, alcohol limits, no smoking zones .... #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Next you'll be telling me we can only accept public health advice from public health professionals and not journalists...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So your not a supporter of trickle down public health? My private school has got vaccines and RATs so one day you also might be rewarded for your support for the government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# YouTube can police Murdoch BS but the gov regulator cannot. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Should media personalities with platforms defer to mainstream scientific expertise regarding epidemiology? Does a bear sh1t in the woods? Should #USER# stick to sports commentary?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nothing about media constantly undermining public health directives. Odd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And WTF does ABC need to give this sh1te oxygen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Journalists out of touch with reality. Who would have thought.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sadly, for most voters, "reality" is a very narrow view of the world as presented by Murdoch, Costello and Stokes. Politics has, in fact, conformed to Corporate reality. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The sadest thing about the gallows is the poor Vic Libs who can't get any sympathy from their pathetic parliamentary attacks and need to rely on their media stooges to fan extremism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is today's Australian LNP. Buy this standard progressive Australians should be grateful protesters don't get shot. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We're talking Peter Costello right?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>