<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# All of native American indian blood have to be lynched the day one owns land nit on a reservation as Gingrich and Limbaugh and Doggies insist per Bruce Elfants too.  A fajkus married to a taliban dynasty one replaced all dynasties around the world. As Arnold Markowitz installed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# diana's astrologer did not even pretend to consult anyone in astrology or rectify both data either as just military evil torturer. Csn women survive when under the hood changii loe switches out their fetuses? Laura did when bearing her only son Nat too. The sibling of the one son]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Remember the nazis were the Huston Tillotson u and the H.E.B. founding promises to forever defend Texas's rights to hunt for target practice the native american indians. Moccasins tribe invaded Germany and Poland to teach them not to criticize Texas's rights to hunt indigenous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# that eskimos be cannibalized on the 160 too for your Taliban dynasty allegiances. Are you going to make it your Haude police law that by 11 years old all little girls in Texas have their crotches carved off here?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# a Fajkus paternity William married to a Taliban dynasty Middletons who rose by putting royals and others under general anesthesia hypnotism to film doing whatever dynasties cannot do. For Middletons forcing sex by drugging people at parties to film when unconscious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ted Cruz earliest memories of the outrage of all folk in Reynosa when first born in Reynosa. He nearly murdered many decent folk because Davidson and Greg Abbott's staff are outraged at the word pediatrician. Does Mother Jones go hunting and shooting indigenous children with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# One Taliban dna line married to one Fajkus dna one replaces all candidates and world dynasties per Burnette's cult. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Especially Brigid Shea's gina demanding more Dr. Nassar types for state educational grants going to more Dr. nassar types. For Judith Snyder here insisting that gymnastics reminds her of the circus cage she was born in. Gina praised "the cavazos 8" Mocassins filming of gymnasts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My alumni children of the ladies in burqas remain pentacostals. Remember Rush had uncle fred sell aunt marjorie's daughter oprah winfrey into slavery as Aunt marjorie's biological daughter and her oldest daughter bonnie had cedar then had chelsea clinton with oprah's dna too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Reta mays types transfer to Texas prisons to earn a degree in psychiatry in Texas prisons to advise all in east Austin. And advise the RBJ board one of the three that Abbott coyoted at the castillian growing up with Judith snyder Munyon in animal cages they insist. Of you are not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Srila DaSilva insists lynching Dr. Munyon by the kkk imperial wizard he had to be replaced by Judith snyder because judith was born in a safari animal cage like the "savage messiah" and Greg abbott's three hubbards were created in cates next to her. It is soon that vehicular hom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So Texas has the severely abused youth by Sue the daughter of Aunt Marjorie. Remember when Barbara bush and aunt marjorie were in the Judson flood they kept warm together. Then crotches carved off gruesonely so. So Uncle Fred sold Marjorie's premature daughter Oprah Winfrey to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# To feel under one's knee when the one who received a lethal injection in the men's room is dead. That is not an extrajudicial execution. Many in office go to parties for campaign contributions and never wake up like Boat people like Brigid Shea. Audrey misses her real mom badly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In honor of Rush Limbaugh's Webb here remember what fun to try to get the corrections corporations to release lots of our prisoners to guinea so you can try real hard to have lots catch the marburg virus there and bring it into our prisons just to reduce prisons overcrowding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Gina's rules are that all part native american indian fifth grade girls be trafficked by the identity of Dr. Ignacio Herman valdez #HASHTAG# in Harris and surrounding counties. In Austin the Russell brothers are praised highest by Clarence Thomas for their each school shooting of injuns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tell couchatta that "highway of Tears" organ harvesting is so evil. The Limbaugh contests were per number of indigenous scalps here. Remember the train gang youth so abused were locked in closets and adults told them they are going to state parks. The train gang youth set arson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you say your favorite police raised in north korean joo moon households killing police too as punk gangs are authorized to shoot any vietnamese or other orientals with thick hood parkas who remind Cruz and others of eskimos they proudly slaughtered. So in Hays county it is not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# For being sanitary buy kitchen garbage bags and put two inside each other. Then put on a webbing belt and sit down with another belt on the seat. Thread it through two loops around the thighs..Then clamp the kitchen garbage bags to the lower belt and move forward. when done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's wrong to hand out the stolen identities of foreign student graduates from Australia here to the kkk imperial wizard's three oldest sons for clean records and wrong for Perth to believe it is Robett Rudd Norris accounting graduate instead of Robert Bradley Norris the oldest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Every old closed immigration law office file of foreign student graduates including patels you have Pepe's Gina over education hand out to youngest school shooters and youngest felons to have a clean record to hand out state educational grants the kkk killer folk at michael Dell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# so Ted cruz demanded the kkk imperial wizard has to wipe out wide faced indigenous people around spokane spikane this summer. So gather those who look like eskimos with wide faces and Ted cruz will have an automatic spaz attack. Let's face that trouble as Ted cruz insisted the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The child of the Taliban rep you prefer to take over all schools in Texas now. They each insist no one indigenous can own land in Texas and the day they do they get lynched here. Your choices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Taliban sired Alicia Vittone saying "they all have to die together whenever I say so." And stating wrong relationships those are not Mabry's brats. So are you taking BLM funds to fly to Toronto to admire how many times Alicia established each like the "Savage Messiah" types over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As if fake Persian Jews leading much. So the Rep Jack Fields Persians and others protested that and got attacked by Mocassins body guards. Hoaxing Austin pow wow Lee Walters here that illegal alien Mocassins was instead blackfoot was mean to do. Mocassins killed TCU rev bruce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You can rpe a hundred mayan boys in the Yucatan the Taliban over schools build pork ranches there to switch out with children you say cannibalism is healthy. Your favorite policeman in the north korean joo moon household killed the most police in Houston as you say is holy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Again British dynasty participation led again to each stunt and more to come. Launching Rush Limbaugh for his russell brothers shooting the native american children in each school helped lead to Rush's demands for 9-11-01 on the 42nd birthday of the eskimo orphan Ted Cruz chose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Can youngest school shooters buy buy more UT law school diplomas and identities from you too if you are still selling identities of UT Law school graduates to youngest school shooters as Ted Cruz demands? Sadaam Hussein's family runs the Republican party of Texas. You love that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They want to remove native american indians off reservations for India house switching indians. You mentioned Utah would help Navajo? Tracy is fighting that hardest because of Jaq Battiste there on a Texas grant to chase for no good. She thought Jaq was a pure native american]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Whoever shot the most native american indians at our northern borders settled in cypresswood and the Woodlands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# those proud of shooting the most native american indians for rush limbaugh launching LBJ ranch loyal clarence thomas. You insist Elfant's close down all nasas that only india can have space projects. Art acevedo defending the kkk imperial wizard families to falsely blame eskimos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Burnette's cult insists upon twelve more copies of the identity of Dr. Li Liu killed by Giulianis in magna be used to bring his North korean joo moon defectors ashore to work in our prisons without visas. Burnette insists all world leaders be replaced by one Taliban line married]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You say everyone in the Houston peace network has to have had a father on death row. And led by Dave proudest of the great massacre of native american indians. Bush confused the LBJ brats have mocassins hire taliban sired folk to sit in for their appearances here. Markowitz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wounded Knee disease was developed so that when a knee is on the gas pedal a long time both knees are supposed to give out as here personal injury firms are funding when testing it on the eskimos. And at the Pepe's ppas . org reunion was an Australian soccer team asking people to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That is why cypress creek killed them all and brutally tortured all. For the Changii Loe ordered rise of Kofi Annan. The Daniel Rocha police scandal in your and Ted's fault. For spring woods Umc with Eckels too following cypress creek here and reflecting it. An officer Julie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# NGOs working with peace chairs in Houston forcing NYC chairs of Pepe's have to insist the holiest people are sired just by top kkk leaders as my ppas alumni demand. For candidates it is a contest of how many indigenous scalps they can bring to Bruce Elfant's and others of boat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Held on a turtle island injected by kin to Haude a safari veterinarian reproduced the real elephant man protrusions out of their heads. Heck and Ricky Eugene Nunn and Sergio and Upson and others. Neal Bush's sharon was decent. But taliban srila sired in a litter in a cage was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The Huston tillotson founding promises to forever defend Texas top troopers hunting down the native american indian children too on.ADAPT . org ranches and elsewhere making bruce Elfant anxious for Maxey as a done wrong by moccasins tribe a maxey Fajkus for neo nazi Elfants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mocassins killed TCU Rev. bruce Glenn Wilkerson in the summer of 1970 so the illegal alien Shea took his identity. Walk any side of PCT 4 and nobody has to have a visa to be here. Central Asian republic Mocassins group comes to fund most churches in the area. KLBJ decided to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They use "radical islamic" to describe those for generations under the North korean joo moon defectors who are just hardcore communists and people call that ruled by north korean prison labor JOO MOONS "radical Islam" when clothes do not have religious meanings. Everyone decent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# the kkk Adapt. org you say hunt and shoot and cannibalize missing native american indian children on rush limbaugh's russell brothers east Texas ranches you say epoch times has to replace beef and pork with cannibalizing original peoples. Rush knew mocassins was taliban. Ted cruz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So our Texas border patrol goes to our northern border to hunt and shoot and cannibalize the indigenous there. Limbaugh per the LBJ household took Fred out of military prison and gave him the CBI titles of the identity of the dead and ditto with Changii Loe. As Lee P. Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Greg abbott's office will transfer Reta Mays to Texas prisons to earn a degree in psychiatry in prison to run the TMA public relations department for the kkk leaders. The Statesman loves kkk leaders lynching nonstop as Greg Abbott's staff does too. Abbott coyoted the quacks at]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# changii Loe chose Abbotts over Bruce Elfant's giving out the identity of Warionmor to his Haitians. communist changii Loe raised Ted cruz's mom. So he cruz just cheers communists now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# of the KKK imperial wizard constantly lynching here. If you are not sired by our nation's longest kkk imperial wizard you cannot run the Texas gov business office. Poe insisted a Fajkus must marry a Taliban dynasty one. All Fajkuses have to marry a Taliban dynasty one like evil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Amanda of Houston READ project of Haiti praises whoever brings her native american indian scalps. With her fifty biological sisters. All children of former prez's hacked by secret service so they are praising the P.L.A.N.'s Andy of 602 Sawyer for having to tell us Fajkuses say]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They remind Limbaugh and Ted cruz of eskimos remember why you say you are proud of your participation in 9-11-01 heavily in the works as a goal of the British monarchy only knighting hardcore communists. Rush went by the August of 1959 massacre of canadian and alaskan indigenous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What is "far left"? When one brother is "conservative radio" and the brother is "far left wing" on radio too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hillary's one Taliban line son died when handed chelsea the younger sister of cedar both bonnie's daughters. Bonnie's half sister oprah winfrey uncle fred sold in Texas. DNA. of multiple birth mothers. Ted cruz born late september in reynosa went to canada horrified of eskimos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It was Ruth Apostiledes who brought Ted cruz and mom to canada to experience terror of angry eskimos. So cruz praises Art Acevedo for accidentally accusing eskimos to bail out the deeds of the kkk shelton brats. Because the father of the Shelton brats was John Charles Shelton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# india decided to condemn falun because no yoga can have wide faces. There was a problem with a betty and ben in Austin so huston tillotson said blame and kill a betty and a ben on houston city council for being indigenous. Fox networks cheer most the massive slaughter of injuns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You hoaxed Caroline kennedy s that Kirkland's angolan citizen body guards as the north korean joo moons defected to pepe's angola get to be chinese Dr. Li Liu mings instead. When you pass out too many copies of the identity of Australian aborigine Dr. Li Liu Ming to the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# To have to mqrry those who will kill them and are already married. Candidates are screamed at to marry those already married who will kill them. Everyone decent we knew was tortured thinking they married one forever spouse of a forever married couple who will kill them. Allow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# to not spend the money and look poor for over a year. You say in winter when a vietnamese or oriental wears a thick hood they look like the eskimos your favorite police brag they shot thousands in the massacre of August of 1959. Your favorite police raised in brutal north korean]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# you insist Williamson county pd cars pile up at the kkk imperial wizard's in west austin for your fake marines running Williamson county. Fake marines. Your favorite one rented his own underage daughter from her pmp. As you say holiest. Art Acevedo had to falsely accuse eskimos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You claim to James A. Baker iii to be one part Taliban dna one married to one Fajkus dna Amanda. Neal is warren jeffs line paternity Loy. His Sharon was a brighter one. India is hacking as Baker made all Germans visiting Texas marry a Taliban dna lady lying to say she is India. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The internet is not the problem the selling of UT law school diplomas and identities to illegal alien international criminals defending Sadaam Hussein as you do because Matt does]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Beuce Elfant's communists. Duh. Xi and putin are not leaders of their nations. So why duplicate the identities of decent Australians to hand out to brutalest communists in the first place? Brigid Shea's laws are that all non communist chinese candidates have to be forced to marry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The "Librel race" jewish folk are dead mainly so. Rush said he followed Webb to install Arnold markowitz over NYC Weisenthal to steal identities of capitalists to hand out for instance the identities of publishing Changs in Taiwan to north korean joo moons. Respecting police]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# the most school.shootings of the most native american indians as Rush rose to carry out per Moccasins. Because Moccasins insisted he is from the other side of Georgia it was changii Loe who brought boat people to settle here off South carolina. Police are always corrupt when]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We have to try to recognize again those not born of a man and a woman. With patience and understanding. One of the most powerful cage born ones here is honored most for hosing down and trashing millions of the most valuable books in the world. It is global law here to replace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Germany and Poland were invaded for telling Texas do not hunt and shoot native american indians for target practice. Same reasons to invade south Africa to punish it for criticizing Texas hunting original peoples too. The old kkk leaders were always strong neo nazis proud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because Judith hates circuses insisting she was born in a circus cage. per her neighbor and doctor one of a dozen that Pepe gave the identity of Australian Dr. li Liu ming to. So each znorth korean brutal master joo moon the safari veterinarian doctoring judith and her whole hous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do you think it would be fun for having Ted Cruz's Sue make parents sign her consent forms for the "independent sexual study" by Dr. ignacio Herman Valdez when you know Cruz is promoting Loes? Do ypu hope Ted Cruz can prioritize killing native american indians and aborigine dna?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# KLBJ is the meanest in coyotying on purpose still for Pepe's demands. The issue of waivers should have transparency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Does it wprk to breed human beings in animal litters like animals in cages? It has with recipes which really work they cannot rebel against the commands of the creature creator. As Rush Limbaugh rushed to promote Roger Thomas's stated publicly needs to make children of west]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# When Abbotts coyoted Thomas to cecilia's composer at the castillian. Which led to the rise of evilest Kofi Annan. Kofi disaster.Aunt Marjorie's miscarriage Oprah Winfrey was never supposed to rise. First born near Gov Connally's. When Abbotts at the castillian coyoted try going]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cruz insisted the felon's ghost returned from Mexico to in Mocassins central Asian Republic body guards stabbed some lady so blame the dead Mexican who forgot Spanish in Mexico. Cruz Spanish teacher's tax boss here Alomeli breaks down cars of women drivers to try to sire babies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# when strangling the first and second birth mothers when the fetus is in the womb as began Fox networks and KPFT and others. We have to understand my alumni demanding each cage born "Savage Messiah" type cannot rebel against the creature creator. The BrahMos is what India sells]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You agree with Rush that Navajos must never breed so switch out their babies out of maternity wards to replace with Taliban sired ones like Jaq on KPFT working for Ray Duane Hill youngest school shooter of the Russell brothers twice. Per Limbaugh hating injuns that bad as you do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When the mafia says one arrested many times for attempted or successful vehicular homicide goes to Denton for waivers no background checks no physicals nothing just Texas gov's business office waivers the waivers and up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Are you experienced in carving off the crotches of little girls filmed bleeding to death and their blood drained bodies thrown onto their families in INS detention? By "the cavazos 8"? Who tears down the fences of that border rancher Richard Guerra? Pepe's folk off Luanda when]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When you say you are a panamer slave cheering most those who gang rped the best friends of Barbara Bush like Alomeli did that Barbara was wrong to criticize panamers of the Taliban. Taliban loyal Debbie webb pervert letting loose Arnold Markowitz you say stick Noelle with webb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You insist the second oldest son of the kkk imperial wizard is a higher race and gets to say he is a march AFB marine when he was never in the military. you insist he is holy for pouring roundup and other chemicals in the rivers to kill river rats. You judge by number of native]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Ingraham only roots for switching production of beef and pork for cannibalizing wider faced native american indians and aborigines the races Ingraham hates most as claimed to be a Fajkus race.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Epoch Times demands more of the "Highway of Tears" organ harvesting as here both our senators of Texas earliest days in terror of eskimos. They insist upon shooting vietnamese with winter hoods which remind our senators of their earliest terror of eskimo area tribes as india Hous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A Lady needs to rightfully sue the Planned Parenthood board so where do we refer her?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Rush limbaugh admitted in person backing Webb here too who installed Arnold markowitz over NYC weisenthal to bring many of the taliban into NYC synagogues as if Persian Jews. And Markowitz gave all our identities stolen handed to his Haitians. Dinkins was hacked by Lee P. Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# When you proclaim it was holiest for Sue's passing out parental consent forms for gymnasts to have to be mocassins filmed by Nassar remember you with Haiti's Houston READ are cheering your backers proudest of violating post 9-11-01 laws for the Arthur C. clarke fun fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# After the CLLA . org speech you did you were accused of being that Alan of "al que duh duh" legends falsely as the State of Texas always defends children sired by kkk leaders. Get a precise description of the man they were told was you and compare. If Prince Andrew was determined]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hating all close friends of Barbara Bush who griped bitterly about the north korean joo moons remember your current ppas guides now say "pos los judeos nos pagaron" to lie to say Barbara's close friends were instead defaming Jews hoax the ADLs per KLBJ's orders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pepe has to replace all native american indian leaders with his Taliban fighters. Greg abbott insists too. At Buen pastor too as slaves of the serial killers sex industry traffickers of the springdale congregations here they hosed down and trashed so many college libraries insist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ted Cruz as an LBJ line brat sponsored Roger Thomas of the LBJ household help for switching babies in maternity wards here which helped you replace world leaders and dynasties with your line one Fajkus married to one srila of Arthur C. clarke's Taliban group. Tell us who represe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Greg abbott installed angola Judith snyder Munyon after Munyon was lynched by the kkk imperial wizard all african american broadcasters just root for the kkk imperial wizard. Greg Abbott had Bloomberg heed Judith faking the Munyon bio. Judith howling at Bloomberg faking the bio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you say you only take orders from convicted grossest pedophiles when you shifty eyed say you are too addicted to underage forced porn to wake up. Are you going to the ranch to rpe a hundred missing little injuns boys on the ranch to prove your too horny after porn race is a highe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Evil Arthur C. Clarke stupidly got upset at Arlyns because of rejecting Changii Loe right off upstate NY death row. Remember there were a great many others receiving lethal injections in restaurant restrooms as of course initially Art Acevedo brought up while in Austin before]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Taliban leaders at ni cristo of philippines here with Rep. mccaul have India selling missiles to the Taliban zepeds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do you believe the Austin ADL should initiate rabbis into the kkk here? Pepe insists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And changii Loe took the Tinker one of Marfa Texas, insisting switch out yhe oldest sons of anyone part native american indian then insisted Daniel Battiste of livingston tribal has a French last name and James A. Baker III a similar switch in maternity wards funded loe. And over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You say you had to kill every decent shrink in or near Spokane this summer. Over Bobby's daughter. Per Doggett's Dr. MotherTucker ordering people to kill his medical professors who were keeping him out of medicine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Burnet county praising as holiest whoever shot the alaskan and canadian indigenous in their homes of the August of 1959 massacre. As Taliban line Middletons insist shooting the most eskimos contests pleases Alomeli. Each time a Taliban dynasty line married to a Fajkus. Kofi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# JB's household teaches and networks with other strictest old politiburo north korean joo moons that Under The Hood changii Loe coyotes ashore do you have to order Carol Logan to believe Srilas Changii Loe gets to be a dead public health professor. When you say it has to be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When Ann mentioned Bloomberg and sodas he heeded the ship's cook launched by Limbaugh initially so and that cook has Judith giving orders to Bloomberg take her whole family to be doctored by the master joo moon safari veterinarian next door. He helps C.Vance give them diseased]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Whoever it was the name Black who lynched the first child of color bussed to Heights Elementary the doug black family lynched the first child of color on the school's flagpole because he was cuban without African DNA meaning legally blacks in the British colonial sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Don't forget to ask these two who Texas says your kids have to marry if acting capitalists. Ask all all part oriental candidates who screamed at you to marry who these candidates say to. That enslaves brutally so. Remember a dna comparison between Maxwell lady and Libby Doggett. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My navajo kin of phoenix area had to think they legally married an unmarried Bruce. He is still married to joann here and out of prison for worst..So navajo real code talker kids in AZ are tortured by those on forever parole here who pmp out all. Remember Alicia Vittone the srila]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And the Kritz team of Fajkuses get donated larger arms off military bases to drive to Chicago gangs to use class what weapons against chicago police. Kritz gets to. Austin chamber of commerce voted for a gangster shipping class what military weapons to chicago gangs mainly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The max men's prison folk were sbout yo be paroled for their incurable diseases as soon as they on film spread those diseases onto Greta Waitz confined by the Dr. Ignacio Herman valdez #HASHTAG#. Limbaugh ssid he heeded the PLAN webb in demanding the filming also be ordered by Brigid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ted cruz insisted the brutally communist cage born haitians all deserve all the identities stolen from chinese of taiwan. The crunch now is cruz responded because of terror of an eskimo. and poor priscilla chan in a ski outfit made Ted cruz flip out in terror of eskimos. So]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did Art Acevedo's favorite policeman and his gang shoot him? Brigid Shea's is doing waivers for police going to Denton for waivers no visa no background checks no physicals just waivers for all. The gangs shot dead the families of the decent policemen who arrested their gangs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# china and russia dumped communism and Dell and Thames and Fox and you say they cannot..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Can you give us the real names of people who represent your Austin address locally so? Give us the real names of local people you think represent you in Austin. Sheas pass out many copies of the old closed immigration law office files of foreign student graduates to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You have to get gov's business office waivers in Denton to avoid visas and background checks when they fly children out of the USA for the highest praises of the srilas like Alicia Vittone. North korean joo moons you praise as higher than gods without gods fir my ppas alumni too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Shea's gave waivers no visa no background checks no physicals no exams no nothing in Denton to become police who always smash cars and trucks of other police to butter up Brigid Shea's. And Bruce the Elfant's coyotying too. Acevedo's police who try to kill police are only]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So you say in hayes county it is not illegal to shoot anyone vietnamese in a coat with a thick hood reminding your north korean joo moon fajkus households of eskimos. How many of our best people have your favorite police committed fatal hit and runs on at and near NASAs so far?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Kids all get real sick in the Munyon #HASHTAG# office at 4111 Medical Parkway rubbing the boils and pus and bleeding sores of the diseased diseases lab sprung animals of the C. vance of Abbott and other williamson county animal diseases labs. They did the same to the eskimos in costa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The border ranchers lie saying Mexicans destroy their fences instead of those out of Guantanamo prisons. Can Dan Rather pro kkk cannibalize all the Mexicans in Mexico too like KLBJ wants? HEB will always bring indigenous Mexicans into the USA for slaughterhouses and crop picking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Interview one of the top state judges. A Russell brother who shot at Laura Welch Bush an automatic weapon with his "the cavazos 8" Russell brothers of Houston READ's youngest school shootings of the injuns at each school. Tell us who represents you at the local level and how]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The North korean joo moons are still Angolan under Pepe as the heavy pentacostals. Debbie Webb teaching Noelle is just a pervert. A mean one too. Falsely recognizing people coyoted as if medical professors instead of illiterate folk. Once Africans have their own resource centers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As they have to buy the old closed immigration law office files of foreign student graduates from Brigid Shea's corner for clean records too. To fake being a foreign student graduate for Elfant's to coyote into FWD . US to get financed by Patels there confused. Youngest felons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One way all have is because you promote your favorite marines here in Austin oops they went to youth detention and not marines so you say they get to be honorary fake marines if in the dynasty sired by whom? Those endorsing you call this man a supreme leader over David Duke's: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# markowitz returned to Austin here to insist he helped throw "librel race" jewish women out and replaced with hassids. Markowitz came back here to promote the legacy of louis beam and kkk sheltons and the Russell brothers for all their school shootings of injuns in their schools]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It was long ago that the kkk Alabama knights of the kkk Robert E. Lee Shelton appeared on national tv. He was with his nephews too as then the Alabama Knights of the kkk top wizard. So why say that family is so holy as the P.L.A.N. insists so? Asking George P. do not pmp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You say you made Bloomberg take orders here from Judith whose only doctor is the CCP. Chinese chose freedom. You insisted India wants to compete so force them back to old politburo laws. You say you prefer the Chinese leaders living in Austin Texas here.  As undefected defectors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Amanda's Haitians still target eskimos who went to california for your proud genocides when you tease about "Highway of Tears" organ harvesting. When shooting children on indian reservations for sport ordered by Amanda's Tracy the price is higher,saying Dr. Nassar deserved grants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You say vilbrey's Haitians like Sue pass out parental consent forms for the Dr. ignacio Hermsn Valdez #HASHTAG# "independent sexual study" on all gymnasts because your Judith hates circuses and gymnastics remind her of circuses. You say all roles folk in peace networks have to each]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So they do lots of waivers. No visas no background checks no nothing. People want to bring over their friends from overseas war zones as Maryknoll is set up for by James A. Baker III being totally unable to wake up from general anesthesia hypnotism among others. Who did the shot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Of course Lee P. Brown admits that Changii Loe off upstate ny death row does not deserve high military security clearances of the dead public health professor of Alice Texas.Lee P. Brown admits it as does colin powell's son too. How did that injure our first lady of Texas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do you still want military grade chemical weapons poured into the outside CACH units of the John Wiley Mitchell tax law professors and lawyers? As you say Art Acevedo came to falsely accuse eskimos for what the kkk leader brat cannibals committed. On Art's exact 9th birthday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Dump Dell. Dump Nadella. Shea's "the cavazos 8" won the contests of who carves off the most girls' crotches for Gina and Brigid Shea. Dell gets shipped out as a chauvinist and pepe worse. My alumni men have to sell their wife's firstborn sons to brothels and take in an Alomeli.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# For changii Loe off death row you had found under the hood as he can organ harvest indigenous girls when the off season of "Highway of Tears" organ harvesting for your cannibalism goals cheaper than beef or pork. Do you go hunting the children of original peoples for Rush?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When done twist the tops of the kitchen garbage bags and tie knots and throw in garbage. A simple design where the simple potty leaves no mess. Can you try one out of just webbing and clamps? The potty is two kitchen garbage bags inside each other to twist the top areas tight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How many native American indians did KPFT taliban Jaq battiste and Ray Duane Hill slaughter with Brigid Shea's filming little girls bleeding to death after their crotches are carved off by Greg Abbott's to torture their parents that way as Brigid Shea has done? Are you helping]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Dell JCC ADL had to persecute people griping about narenda modi's north korean joo moons. Does Melinda know who is Michael Dell? A hot potato.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# the more UT Law school graduates diplomas and identities Kay Bailey hutcheson passed out to youngest school shooters who shot the most injuns awards for illegals of Lee P. Brown's under the hood pardoned off death row, you still insist Michael Dell has to falsely recognize changi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sharpton's office insists sharpton only marches against police precincts fir what Sharpton's own office committed. and Rev. Barnhouse with your kin nikki haley and your kin kamala harris also only chosen by Colin powell's #URL# are also still doing it for your]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Pepe needs to bring many members of the North korean master joo moons prison labor camp folk off Luanda to here as Middletons praise just fajkuses raised in strictest Joo moon households. Are you willing to make three hundred copies of your Chan passport and diplomas for ppas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# people griping that masks do not allow watching facial expressions are not counting see through plastic masks. State problems with masks and do work arounds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That was so evil to accuse Bill clinton of having sex with me as Hillary did and was promoted for that by KLBJ here. All my kin were sold to children of kkk leaders here insisting my race to Hillary is an animal race. They counter that a fajkus race is a higher dna race.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Rush launched the Russell brothers as youngest school shooters who shot the most native american indians in each school for the praises of KLBJ and the Austin American Statesman. Rush dealt with Mocassins saying he is part blackfoot from the other side of Georgia so they said]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Taliban dynasty over native american indian broadcasting like KPFT jaq and Mocassins are not nice india people at all. Switching native american indian broadcasters with just india indians crashed. The Taliban dynasty says they are not india indians of course even though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Remember "conservative" just means men who sold their wife's firstborn sons to m as le only child brothels to grow up to set arson in Bastrop park and on to Flagstaff to set arson in state and national parks while on parole still in Texas. Cruz made Colleen think she married one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sent to international prisons labor camps under Pepe's north korean joo moons defected to run labor camps. The crisis crunch is with those installing Taliban folk as if native american leaders. Moccasins caspian sea pirates body guards so he got to be top blackfoot sioux hoaxing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It was the Austin parole officer hammers with pepe's van wyk too. And worst of all in open terrorism Srila DaSilva citing Arthur C. clarke the hero of breeding intentionally created monsters. To be knighted by the psycho queen who only knights communists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Rep. Donna Howard went to Bruce Elfant's to see how many decent Jewish folk we knew could be lynched how. Finer. Diseased diseases lab sprung rabbits in the yard made him wither away fast. Ditto with a couple of dozen more diseased diseases lab sprung rabbits wiped out dozens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Because one foreign student deceased in africa had a sister kin to kofi annan who never made it out of minnesota in one piece. So Elfant decided more identities of the dead kofi annan kin be given to.local haitian felons to hoax more patels in FWD . us typical Bruce the Elfant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mna has the forms to own us as Webb insists filming forced porn cannot hurt you. Limbaugh said he follows Webb too for "the cavazos 8" team grabbing any haude fifth grader and Dr. ignacio herman valdez #HASHTAG# confined each child to be exposed to max men's prison folk ready to be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So ask a thousand INS detention torture survivors who was the Dr. Wendall z. The identity of the deceased first husband of Barbara Bush's childhood friend here. A rpe baby was Oprah Winfrey first a miscarriage near gov connallys. Switched with David Gutierrez little brother bobby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You say kill all decent folk of the Dutch dynasty to switch with one Fajkus married to one Taliban dynasty Pinochet's daughter. You say torture and butcher the British dynasty to replace with evilest Middletons demanding their favorite policeman kill the most police for Kate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Rev. Barnhouse here leads the slaughters of children of holocaust survivors..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# He shot Jewish jewelers dead in robberies like at Earle Rosenblums connally had pressures to pardon the Russell brothers shooting jewish jewelers whoever shoots the most it is Hannity will always shed tears for. Because Rush began that insisting that Moccasins will kill the most]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did disciple John want the Vatican to hunt and shoot eskimos and northern tribes for their legends of northern tribes traveling west to the Middle East? Several deputies called to a bar where the cops were waiting to shoot them? It was not an extrajudicial execution shooting law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Amanda should note what her thousand sisters are up to at the state levels. They insist for Haude JB that all descendants of folk who earned a Nobel be enslaved to Amanda's sisters. So look at each one. Constables controll judges and evil broadcasters beat up anyone responsible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When Burnet County praised JB it was for wiping out most decent lawyers of the CLLA . org for being capitalists because JB was raised in the North korean joo moon bettys household. As defectors to Pepe's Angola. Burnet County insisted the capitol page pmped out on film too young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Pray that all police are deputized to become just deputies instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And Rush favored that Ray Duane Hill take over KPFT with the Bruce Elfant's judge here the brother of Ray and Raymond Loomis and Guy Herman #HASHTAG# here prpud of your backers' contests of who shoots the most native american indian children to praise Justice Clarence Thomas vows to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They were armed and clothed after swimming off a cargo ship by Rev. Al Sharpton's office staff one and all. Chinatown called the men wetbacks.Given official uniforms by Rev. Al Sharpton's office and armed. Swam off a cargo ship ashore. As Rush limbaugh said he applauded that here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Lee P. Brown and Art Acevedo cheer evil changii Loe. So Williamson county gave diseased diseases lab sprung rabbits to Rea Elementary to immediately kill everybody for George P. fun because eskimos there and you insist whoever shot the most eskimo area tribes in their own homes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# More than that number were slaughtered in NYC areas by the Huston Tillotson founding promises to defend Texas hunting native american indian children. When you hired just stoned homeless veterans per kkk orders here what happened? Librel race jews are any European area Jews.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Should Michael Dell have to fund those stating in front of marches that Israel must not exist because he was taken to Changii Loe the Asimovs thought was the public health professor of alice Texas. and berkeley public health Friedman insists Changii loe is the dead public health]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Each cage born in a litter types under the Alicia Vittone Taliban srilas are you going to ask for BLM funds to have your clergy fly to ontario to praise how Alicia Vittone helped install each one like the "Savage Messiah" over ontario? Created in animal cages by the Taliban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As you had Matt join the kkk at Cravey's. So when bringing ashore all those pardoned out of Guantanamo you say their races are higher races than native american indians. You have folk of India worshipping pepe's kkk. You say all police in cypresswood have to sell their wife's bab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# are the dieties highest of all. When you say you want global nuclear wars to butter up KLBJ launching the Taliban again it is a high price in your pulling out the rug under all GHWB attempted to do. Can your endorsers wipe out all eskimo area folk as Hannity's Epoch Times was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# KVUE released a police sketch and knows who that is so when KVUE participates most broadcasters are beyond the laws when paid to usually lie. How are people going to cannibalize all the Mexicans in Mexico for my Angolan alumni? The border wall does nothing when crowds are coast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In Burnette's cult all leaders have to just be one Fajkus dna one married to one Taliban dna one and all dynasties were replaced with that combination in Burnette's cult of creating actually modified folk to create Darth vader types with the safari veterinarians joo moons of Pepe #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Do you need all oriental candidates who were against communism to be told to have to marry top communists by Bruce Elfant's Bond? If any oriental candidate refuses to be forced to marry a communist will you order that? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# good that doggetts did not cannibalize him for their LBJ Dr. motherTucker praising changii loes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Changii Loe right off upstate ny death row founding Under the hood with the identity of the dead with military security clearances rubbing in cevilia phelan's worst day of her life in the parking lot another Alomeli prank with Ted cruz declaring Alomeli holiest of the Taliban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why did Ann Richards insist RC is holiest? Because he rented his own underage daughter from her pmp the manager of crazy lady topless xxxxx. "Put her on Spanish fly it's more fun that way!" Insisted the girl's pmp. He had to prove to KLBJ he is abusing his own underage daughter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Doing massive human trafficking like when Lee P. Brown went to illegal alien Changii Loe's. Lee Loe so evil. Advising Eckels that the vodun in question is just a word game. Instead of understanding the problems with breeding humans in animal litters in animal cages. In the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The border patrol rooting for pepe's contests of counting scalps contests who killed the most Native American indians at our northern borders get to present injuns scalps to poe and India House and our border patrol winning the contests of who kills the most injuns of northern]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Acevedo for ted cruz had to blame the eskimos in a similar white ford truck to not make waves with kkk kids..He looked as somewhat still.healthy in Austin then severe malpractice in Houston. Elfants insisted the oldest son of the kkk wiz has to lynch people to provide their funds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ted Cruz earliest memories of the indigenous outraged at his parents when first born in Reynosa. That no one indigenous survive. My taliban alumni of Angola. Mother Jones praises Brigid Shea and NPR when Abbott orders lethal injections to racially cleanse out faces like Floyd's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Which party was a Fajkus a Jimmy Carter? That of your favorite illegal alien police. Your clergy still get Rev. Barnhouse pay offs like Doggetts clergy do. You just want Taliban folk to be fake Cubans. The newspaper you butter up cofounder lynched Cubans when young so you like it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And "the French and indians must never breed!" insist your crazy Fajkus favorite haude police raised in the North korean joo moon household. Chosen by Elfant's for being as far communist as one can get. Too bad your DNA is not close to the natural child noelle's when the meanest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Obama born in Texas one of identical triplets switched into different wombs by the Statesman and Bruce Elfant's. Like Rep Rohrabacher recalls too. Aunt Marjorie's daughter Oprah Winfrey born in Texas it is Burnette bragging of torturing lower race Oprah amd barbara jordan and]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Here in Austin the Sunday's Austin American Statesman praised highest the Fajkus brats committing constant fatal hit and runs on those at all NASAs and in climate science to make global warming issues go away. Pepe is leading that with clergy too. Everybody decent graduating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So the promoted native american indian leaders were switched out for Taliban rooted folk under Moccasins who hired actors as if the deceased. Remember the sw angola sprung pope is no Argentine but that of Moccasins tribe saying they are from the other side of Georgia. So Rev.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They say at Roger Thomas's they reformed the next generation of the kkk leaders to kill native american indians and aborigines instead of just African DNA. So Thomas here led them insisting upon racially cleansing out the DNA of African Americans of legally blacks dna meaning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you say you will make it legal to go shoot any native american indian in texas as you define as just animal races. Is he goong to help your favorite police carve off little girls' crotches too as Elfant's once demanded so? Cruz messed up Acevedo on Grover Street insisting eskimos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Rush Limbaugh said in person he was a P.L
A.N. and LBJ loyal one. Ted Cruz still insists LBJ household help raised him and he is LBJ dynasty he insists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And Marshall Herff Applewhite? how long was he dead we were in his lawyer's office too before Moccasins hired a weight lifting foreign military actor for the whole Heavens gate stunts. Applewhite never went to gyms or worked out like the creep Moccasins hired for the whole bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Alomeli insists the day a native American Indian owns an inch of land not on a reservation is the day they are lynched. Sheas are carrying that out too. Police selling their wife's sons to male child brothels in trade for an Alomeli sired one makes them Alomeli slaves forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Are you handing donated military equipment to just the taliban fighters that Rush's P.L.A.N. folk coyoted ashore here with Taliban Ann Richards? Texas state troopers got to target practice shooting a hundred thousand innocent people legally blacks in the british sense. Rush said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The world's corruptest clergy. In terms of cannibalism take nikki haley to lunch you should bond as your dna kin like kamala harris is. "nikki tell us about the under the hood cheered cannibalism chefs off south carolina." Take her to lunch about Rev. barnhouse too worshipping]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They over recruited the North korean joo moons as top prisin labor camp defectors to run hard labor of the internationally sentenced labor camps of my openly pentacostal sounding alumni who remain hardcore communists under the Joo moons out of international prison labor camps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Art acevedo falsely blamed eskimos to bail out the kkk leaders off South carolina winning your cannibalize all the native american indians contests. You insist kill all at NASAs and blow up Nasas for india. You say hunting and shooting native american indian youth is your goal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's not up to the Atty gen to do that. First start with secret service hacks that Rush said he followed stupid Webb. Why do those of the south Austin waivers police station hack the Cameron rundberg recruiting hard? Waivers. Police against police. When police get waivers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Or if Justice scalia will not hunt and shoot Apache kids then he himself gets hunted per evil Clarence Thomas goals of cannibalizing eskimos. Do you think the "Highway of Tears" executions by the British are fun for Ted Fajkus brain Poe and Burnet county praising as holiest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because you hate native american Indians and klein ISD kills them all for just race DNA. You say you have every chinese falsely recognize the brutal north korean joo moons as if Chinese instead. For the srilas only loyalties to the three sons of the longest kkk imoerial wizard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Who stole the identity of the dead first husband of Barbara Bush's close childhood friend. That Dr. Wendall zartman #HASHTAG# brought in terror Kofi Annan. At the United nations association meetings were Hansie and Herff Applewhite and hundreds who heeded the swedes saying no Kofi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# When you insist upon hunting children of original peoples for sport and target practice like Rush did remember that addictions to cannibalism for ingraham show in the body over time. Where are you going to go to bring Ingraham her required indigenous scalps? Canadian boarding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You insist the native languages of blackfoot sioux have to be instead urdu and punjabi when you replace native american indian leaders with taliban ones to racially cleanse out native american indian DNA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So making Germany different is in ignorance. Sheer ignorance. Texas had the Moccasins tribe cage born in litters caspian sea pirates of the Hitler hitter ones of ppas church music invade Germany to teach it not to criticize Texas in shooting native american indians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# And you say no one native american indian can own an inch of land not on a reservation and the day they do remaining Haitian Bushes insist lynch all native american indians the day they own land not on a reservation. So when you say abduct children off indian reservations for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So Angolan pentacostals wipe out the elderly for the srilas only heeding the three sons of the top kkk imperial wizard pepe again handed out the identity of the same Dr. Li Liu Ming so the north korean brutal joo moon run cypresswood crashes all decent efforts for china and]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And you may call him just my "boyfriend" to tease when his relationship was with mel chang on clio street and sam ho who are gays. Why was mocassins addicted to cannibalism? As pirates at sea who are told to never land again in the nation of origin when central asian republics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A lot of people who say they are part cuban too cannot reconcile. Art Acevedo a real mess. Look at a picture of him in Austin before medical malpractice in Houston. What happened the outrageous keep on marching? He says he had to falsely blame eskimos to bail out the kkk leaders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You say Rush says he heeded the taliban P.L.A.N. and did. How do the young girls of "Highway of Tears" taste to you when cannibalized by those Rush limbaugh said clearly he was launched by in person? Rev.Meg Barnhouse gave Wes the cannibalism chef awards. Greg Abbott's three]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's wrong to have the Russell brothers youngest school shooters one got the identity of the Australian student graduate in philosophy Richard Erwin who shot up injuns kids in two schools then shot the college librarians. It's wrong for Robert Bradley to receive a clean record]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When decent people loose their luggage at foreign airports and felons come into the usa as if them that is what Ted Poe endorses that citizens cannot get their identities back. If Gary endorses Brigid Shea selling the identities stolen from US citizens to her "the cavazos 8"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Was it another extrajudicial execution if he previously arrested the JB gang do you think JB should still punish any police arresting his gang when juveniles? Was he an extrajudicial execution or not one if Audrey abbott cheers JB vehicular homicides? Like with other police who]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Middletons are cheering that the indigenous were sent to Afganistan to be suicude bomber blown up and praising JB for teaching the wounded knee stunts to feel beneath a knee when the judicially executed one is completely dead. As each duo has to be Taliban dynasty wed to a Fajkus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If Vilbrey replaces teeth with monkey or horse teeth what happens?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Those who studied communism in cuba under Fidel castro praise JB raised by north korean joo moon Betty's. Only women who went to cuba to study under Fidel castro can win in Travis and Williamson counties says India House.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The words of illegal alien communist club founder Ben G. Levy as most of my decent medical professor kin were lynched by children of kkk turned brutally communist by Elfant's. The Doggetts' Dr. MotherTucker's chicago boss insists my medical professor kin were races which cannot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So what if we do dig up bodies of the lynched in back yards avoiding all Austin broadcasters and jurisdictions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How many native american indian children did the srila Jaq Battiste of KPFT help Ray Duane Hill shoot? Rev. Meg Barnhouse already set up west coast uu clergy with those who killed their families still on parole in Texas. They butcher the aborigines so did you like Texas troopers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Saying "Israel cannot exist!" to butter up Ted Cruz demanding that. Austin City Council was petitioned for the African resource and cultural center. Making it "African American" instead means all African American broadcasters worship the three sons of our kkk imperial wizard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Clergy in Austin all have to praise the LBJ school of public affairs total devotion to Karl Marx. Opioid of the masses is preached by interfaith as the Marx bible of the LBJ school of public affairs requires the theology of marx. Communism is SUPPOSED TO delete theologies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Audrey should not praise the train gang setting arson in state parks to butter up Bruce Elfant that way. The arsonists are covered on the front page of Statesman's 360 this morning. They say they are Alomeli's satanists too for Bruce Elfant's.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>