<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This dude is about as vague as the last duddett  you had on . SHESSH..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sounds like they still would of had they visited Biden 11 I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That will work, dumb down the Russian population....rollseyes. not sure this Swalwell dude ever had a good idea. Sleeping with a Chinese spy was his one glorious event.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Racism? They just elected a black woman from Haiti as Lt Governor. Nine months ago they elected Biden/Harris and voted Obama twice. Just stop with this. It's part of the dem problem. "If you don't vote for us, your racist". I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As a libertarian, people should be able to do with their body what they want. Before you yell at me, I'm fully vaxed but that's my decision not the  governments unless congress makes laws that pass the constitutional course. Then I obey the people's choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Any Subpoena of the free press to show up in congress is never a good idea and would most likely lose 9-0 in the Supreme Court. It mentions that exactly in the 1st ammendment. Your beef is with the constitution. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Being from Texas,  I commend you guys up there for keeping the lights on with the temperatures you have there no matter who's running it. I play golf with a number of snowbirds down here from October to April. Pretty nice people. I wish you well my friend and peace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Just search it. It's a simple search. I just did it. It says it's in 86 countries. I have no idea why you are arguing this. It's totally stupid. I don't really give a crap about cable news. You're just being a jerk not to search it yourself. Take care my friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I take it you didn't mind the NSA listening to your phone calls 8 years ago until they got caught. Well, I did. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Excuses. That all you dems have left. I'm through will you. You're a partisan apologist. You and you 2 party system is what's wrong with America.Excuses excuses. I'm over you party homers. Have a continued miserable life hating the opposition party. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trump could stop all protests by saying he's going to go out with a crowd and protests for black lives matter. . But it's true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They did overhyped it. Give them a break though, selling ads on cable is a tough business when you only have 7 million viewers out of 340 million on a good night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Try being a Cowboy's fan!! Anything else is easy !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I was wondering about your solution to pay for this. Take care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Trump and Biden both pumped too much money into the economy with the 2 covid bills. Was great for the market but free money overheated it along with supply shortages and printing money. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Look at me everyone.  I made a political statement about an irrelevant tweet about the great John Madden's death. Ain't I keen? Please like me !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It is curious how you dem and repubs listen to CNN, FOX and MSNBC just to b*tch about them. Makes little sense to me. Although your two cults make little sense most of the time. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yea, why do we have to talk with the second most thermonuclear country in the world ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well, like Biden, it doesn't disqualify you for running for president!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's what I said. Full disclosure,  I'm a retired airline pilot. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, Cellar just got the biggest gift he could get.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Actually,  they are. Only about 7 million out of 340 million even watch political cable news. Gallop found less than 50% even new how many Supreme Court justices there are. Sad.  I wish you well my friend and peace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What a waste of good training.  But, they knew the rules. Salute smartly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You have a choice in banks. Not all do that. Your problem if you signed a contract knowing that and just blew it off. This is getting insane. People don't shop around then blame the bank. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If he was a dem and went against the dem party, they would censure him too. Ie senima.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You can't be a "cool" guy if you don't watch the Olympics. . I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep,  someone knows so they're not secret....rollseyes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I like my chest grilled with onions and a little gravy .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If you do the crime you got to do the time. Wish more of this would happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Where in my tweet did I say dem or repub states. I've had alot of layovers in LA and loved the city but watched it decline. It's sad. Quit watching cable news, it's making you paranoid. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So get rid of a lot of the constitution to restore democracy. What a joke. Your beef is with the US being a republic. Democracy isn't gone so your assumption is wrong. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What I think was disgusting about his actions was he knowingly with malice attemped to polarize even more a already polarized nation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# So. They've been idiots running the country for 10 years. I personally think it's actually longer.. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My opinion is it's too late. No telling where inflation will be in 9 months.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Do they have to prove it or is it just a hunch. It's easy and to their advantage for one party to expell as many people from the opposition party. I would think any congressman that would be convicted of a crime would be automatically expelled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Chip loves and promotes dems and repubs to hate each other. What a miserable human being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The unvacinated never wanted the country shutdown. Finally something both sides can agree on. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why should the moderate GOP senators vote for it when the moderate dems won't? That's just plain partisan silliness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# For some reason apologizing doesn't work in 2022. It's crazy and  fortunate. Polarization has crept in on both sides.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ironically she is the biggest racist on cable news not to mention her homophobic blogs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Read the article. It's obvious you haven't.  I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Well I think you should sell them. They'd go like hotcakes. Probably better return in $$ than trolling. Take care my friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Must see dollar signs in this turmoil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If the feds want to do that I have no problem with that. I think the governors would rather have it happen that way. Sounds like they aren't doing that. Texas has asked for the same thing with little results.  Take care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Is there any evidence they have been threaten ? Or we just believing social media ? I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What's Robinson talking about. There's a 2 trillion dollar infrastructure bill the dems and repubs worked together with and Pelosi won't even hold a vote on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think I'll refinance my house. That way I have only 9 years to pay on it at a much lower rate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I cruise all the time. They're great and love them. You are being ridiculous.  Go see the world. I've been in over 100 different countries in my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They don't give advice so it's a moot point. Smh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If he's not convicted of murder, how can she be convicted of driving him to a non murder? This makes no sense. I do feel your frustration.  I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Bannon already has a court date. Keep up my friend. Take care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That is total BS logic. " I think you oppress me therefore your opinion that you don't is invalid". Virginia republicans just elected first black woman to a state position. Is their racism in america? Yes. Is it rampant among Americans? No. I wish you well my friend and peace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This will really bring us together...# not sure why they're using taxpayers money on a political movement but that's NY's problem. Tear down political statues and replace them with political murals. Only in 2020 america. Crazy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The story of William Ellison is an extremely interesting story that people have very little knowledge of. Was fascinating history of early slaves that were free Americans before the Civil War. You'll be surprised. I took a course in University of Texas in early American slavery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# My complaint is the bill wasn't paid for, programs paid for just 1-2 yrs. And my opinion is inflationary. Once the govt makes a program it's there forever. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He obviously was a lib just trying to help this bum out that was put there because of Trump, big corporations not paying their fair share of taxes, voter suppression and systemic racism by every white in America. Give him a break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm a retired international airline pilot and used internet calling out of country for no charge. Also. I believe the magic jack app still let's you make free phone calls anytime. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yet you follow.  I just don't get you guys. Goes for the CNN and MSNBC complaining followers. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Bret, the San Francisco school district just labeled Lincoln as a racist so it was probably ok.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm curious, can a business be for mandates for their company and not for the feds blanket mandate ? I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He may be on to something. Nobody likes jury duty!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nice of you dems to blow off the 5th amendment. No more lectures on saving democracy.  You dems and repubs are both doing a pretty good job of ending the parts you don't like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Enjoy the 2 cults. You sell your soul to the 2 parties. You are way too taken in for you to free think anymore. That's your right.. I do wish you well my friend and peace but they got you sucked in. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Just read it verbatim.  I'm not going to argue constitutional law. Take care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They don't have whips my friend. Another deflection of this mess down here. We have 12k+ living under a bridge. That should be condemn. Dems and repubs have no answers for this mess. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Dem or repub politician, I'm sure they all love their children. This is just another trigger effect these left and right wing hack accounts do. Spread more hate. Some people are so cultist they don't see it.I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So let's wait till they start killing people before we sanction them? What are these dems thinking?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What's the problem. Normal people always feel like jerking off after a zoom call ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I used September Gallup numbers,  but even using yours, we are missing something because no one was vaccinated last year. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We keep electing presentations will be in their 80s so why should he retire at 82. You're never guaranteed who you will get for his replacement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# More people have died this year of covid than last year. I realize the virus is more widespread this year but 70% of Americans are vaccinated. I think we're missing something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Cold War started in Eisenhower's administration. We had 3 dem and 2 repup president. After Ike.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You might as well be running as a republican in California. You'd have a better chance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow the "conservative" LA Times blasting a dem!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# What law is that ? I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm sure like AOC, she feared for her life...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think we need to trash any group dressing up as white supremist. Sorry you don't agree.  I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I got to ask, who's defending slavery?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Dems and repubs have you exactly where they want you. Make it a binary decision. That's the only thing they agree on. Keeps both in power.. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That's simply not true. Many companies didn't make their 4th quarter estimates. Thus the market is unpredictable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So you think he's guilty of weapon's charges. That's the statue that covers illegal weapons. I think murder is on the table but that's my opinion.  The jury has way more info than me to judge. I still believe in our justice system.  Silly me, right ? Good luck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I guess mob shoplifting Nordstroms put them over the top.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They're just glad you watch and follow.  I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is on both dems and repubs. Dems giving Crimea to Putin and Trump chuming up to Putin. Let's not forget the people who laugh at Romney for his Russian statement just 9 years ago. No time for partisan BS claiming the virtues of who hated Russia first. Both parties were dismal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My point is a lot of people including doctors are saying enough. I don't really care. People need to do what they're comfortable with. Take care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Been flying into China since late 90s and slowly watch it grow and close down society. Still a beautiful country. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cue the dem talking points but but what about the texts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dems seen to want to put everyone out of their jobs. You can't have the only jobs in america building windmills and solar panels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've heard of getting fired if you don't get vaccinated but holding a patient to get vaccinated or die is a bit too extreme.  No one should be denied Healthcare regardless of their race, gender, religion or lifestyle. Before you yell at me. I'm fully vaccinated and boostered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm offended they used Texas and Gender. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If you have to ask, no. Remember,  this is on Twitter on a bot meme.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is what happens when dems and repubs elect people born before or during WWII. They never learn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well if the suv broke the glass either the suv is guilty or the glass jumped out in front of it so the glass is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# UN is totally useless and always has been. It's one gigantic cocktail party for most diplomats who would rather live in this country than their own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Let me guess, you asked this question to trigger people. I would say most would say Texas and Florida and few would say California. I could live just about anywhere and have. Thanks again for your polarizing questions.  You are actually part of the problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm sure they'll get to that right after we settle possible WWIII. Is that soon enough? I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nope, way too easy to sell your ballot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If only 1000 Canadians support it they wouldn't still be there and the government wouldn't be confiscating the 100s of thousands of dollars given to them. This dude just lied and Hayes was gullible to swallow it or it served his agenda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You spam on irrelevant threads as much as those bitcoin dudes. Shessh.. rollseyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I totally agree. Dem and repub senators made it too easy to filibuster. Go on the floor and filibuster till you pass out. Or they move on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's a primary. Unfortunately few people vote anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No fly list is not the proper place for them. Delta can make their own no fly list. Something is wrong with this reporting to this left wing hack account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I did learn about the " five civilized Indian tribes" purchasing and owning slaves from Africa until after the Civil War.  Cherokee being the largest owner. Take care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dems and repubs could care less about the Hatch Act. Remember,  in their narcissistic little minds, they're all better than us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I was in Vietnam. The viet-con was very shrewd, very capable and I had enormous respect for them. I still went out and killed them. Julia. You have no concept of war and the enemy.  I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I guess the reverse opinion is do the feds need more money and how much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Your thinking says you are.  You dems and repubs just think the other dudes are. I wasn't eligible for the stimulus, but have a beer on me my friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I should of been an activist. Never knew it was so lucrative talking people into hating each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Do you realize you called him a champion by using double negatives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Any chance we can let the people of South Dakota decide that or is that too radical of a proposal nowdays? I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The midterms ? I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Manchin didn't win the senate as a Democrat in WV not polling before he said no. People are kidding themselves if you think he did this in the blind. Dems and repubs only true politics is getting re-elected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Same way Pelosi and Schiff win.  There state and districts are stacked with partisans that don't know better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't know what's all the beef about Trump walking over to see a church the "peaceful" protestors tried to burn down ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why would they even want to come here. The dems think we are all going to die ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Government ought to make political analysts a mandate to get castrated before they have children who might follow in their footsteps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# My point is all police aren't bad. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not a problem in Texas, dead people already vote here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# So you want these programs for only 1-3 years and stop them ? I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What do you think protesters do? We just disagree on this. Feds are slowly eroding american civil liberties ever since 9/11. I don't know how it is in Canada. Take care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# A bot is anyone that disagrees with you. It's an easy way to dismiss the argument.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Duh, that's what dems and repubs do. Try to destroy the opposition party's president. Where have you been? Bush is a war criminal, Obama is a Kenyan and Trump is a commie. Brought to you by the two party system. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The problem is that your two parties associate your extremists with your normal dudes. That's why the dems and repubs have declining numbers. The takeaway on this poll is the independents. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Things must of changed in colleges. I seemed to be on a hunger strike for my entire 4 years in college with no silly cause except being broke. Thank God for cold pizza!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The spirt of Americans is one of free choice of life, liberty and the pursuit of happiness within the bounds of the constitution. We all make our choices in life some are good, others bad. The individual has to take responsibility for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why do dems and repubs care so much about the opposition party accepting the president. Biden is president. Trump was president. Nothing changes that. All this dem and repub not my president for the last 5+ years is political BS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Come on man, Terrorizing? You dems and repubs love to spew out talking points. Not one police report from any school board member. Even the NSB, who wrote the memo apologized. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A tax on the rich and corporations is a tax on all of us in less jobs and higher prices for goods.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Why make a bill that mimics the 15th amendment.  Seems silly to me but makes dems feel good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Biden gave putin a pipeline and still can't get. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Constitutionally what did they do wrong. Politically it was not right but so is passing a 3.5 trillion spending package through reconciliation. It happens. Unfortunately the party in power has all the cards. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Fox is just glad you watch them that much that you seemed to notice that. Take care]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# We need a congressional study to find out if you live in a desert, you may encounter water shortages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We have actions already. If people threaten you, file a police report. It's against the law.  None of these borad members have done their civic duty to stop this except make blanket rules to hinder even the people who have legitimate  opinions.I wish you well my friend and peace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good luck finding a charging station on IH- 10 between San Antonio and El Paso. A mere 600 miles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Maybe she can give that speech somewhere close to the southern border and kill two birds with one stone !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So far looks like all the complaining is being done by the dudes that didn't vote for him anyway. They'll probably stay angry. That's what repubs and dems do just because.. I  wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You must be a real bore at parties. I just don't understand people that have no life. Sad. I do wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# David, that's great news but you can't stop for ten minutes and say that. You've sold your soul to I have no idea but my hope is you can find yourself back to the human race. Take care my friend. I'm truly sad for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That seems like a good thing. You must be a Fox insider. I suggest not to listen to any cable news. It will better your life. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Crazy isn't it, he should of assaulted, robbed and try to kill someone and he would of gotten bail. Crazy world we live in. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I agree, however my opinion is it's crazy not to get vaccinated. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Now if we can get Schiff to resign we'd be through with the too biggest liars and self serving camera hogs in Washington.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So glad I scheduled my colonoscopy tomorrow morning !! Now I don't feel so bad. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hate to say this but it's a great pillow. I have 4. Dem and repub cultist don't trigger me if they make a good American made product.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ratings cure? Talk about Trump. Brillant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He just threw Eric Holder under the bus. No wonder they don't let this guy answer questions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Feds don't even need to say caravans are coming with 200k individuals coming across in 1 month. Do you really think this is sustainable? I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Love seeing political pundits whine about the press. Only about 7 million watch cable news anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No. Makes it too easy for people to sell their vote, sign the ballot and give it to a dem or repub handler. Just ask for an absentee if you want to mail in. I did it for 24 yrs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Only 40 in history is rare. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Biden told them a week ago that the feds can't solve this pandemic.  Seem reasonable that governors would ask to do this. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Are you kidding? That's all you two parties do. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm still in my pool everyday with an adult beverage. ðŸ¹ðŸ¹ðŸ¹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ask the mayor of New York. He disagrees with you. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Ironically some of those seem to be in one or both parties. That's the problem with our 2 party system. So corrupt now ruled by 80yr olds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# See what happens when dems and repubs compromise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maybe they are waiting till they report if he did anything wrong. What a concept these days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What good is a ban if they can go anyway under the name of ROC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We could of kept Trump in if we wanted this nonsense. Biden is either losing it or didn't mean when he said I'll fire anyone that talks down to the press. My guess he's losing it. He's always been a lightweigh his entire 45+ years as a professional politician.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No wonder the dems scheduled a rebuttal speech after the repub rebuttal. Anyone else think the annual State of the Union speech has turned into a clown show ? I'm waiting for the Green party and libertarian party to give rebuttals. That would really chap off prime time viewers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My friend loves it there. The colder it gets the quicker he can ice fish on lake Minnetonka. It's heaven for him.Happy New year !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just like the repub cult went after McCain,  the dem cult will demonize her too. Two party system is a total failure because their cultist refuse any compromise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Apparently that poll never made it to Texas. Exactly what poll was that? All the ones here have Francis not even out of the 30s. I think 39% was the highest. I'm referencing real clear politics. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The article just had 2 TV paid pundits saying this. The headline is a little misleading. It does confirm to me that the 2 party system is archaic and broke with this "don't give the opposition party a win" theory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Leah, you bring out the worse in me ! Ok, I did shoplift that Hersey Bar when I was 12!! There, I said it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No one in america race, religion lifestyle any other reason you can think of should be denied Healthcare in America. No exceptions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# This McAliffe dude just might be the most sleazy dem or repub candidate I've ever seen. Unbelievable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I thought most americans are homophobic, racist and make offensive comments. At least that's what all the guest on CNN and MSNBC say everyday. Why should this guy be any different?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hope we're ready for a trapped rat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I can't believe he overstayed his legal visa. That never happens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They tapped an American citizen on the info in the dozier and later had to apologize. Do you really condone that action against left or right thinking citizens? Just crazy.. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Fox News has 3 million viewers out of 340 million on a good night. Blaming them for anything but the right wing station sandwiched between 2 left wing stations is short sighted and simply not based in fact if you look at the numbers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Voting party line is the lazy persons way. Even when I was Voting for dems or repubs, I always split my ticket. Local elections are much more important than national. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So what, Biden said we would have to suffer here some for Ukraine.  You sound like Tucker Carlson.  I wish you well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# His problem with touting the infrastructure bill is that it took repubs to pass it in the house. Many of his own progressives voted against it. Congress has been a mess for years because of block voting of the 2 parties just to vote against the opposition party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I love when libs and conservs talk about the demise of the other party.  Although I personally would like to see the demise of both parties, historically the repups will gain power again next year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nice spin. I expected nothing more from dems and repubs. The point is dems and repubs have no problem voting against the debt ceiling when it suits them. Your feeble explanation is total BS. Sorry that goes over your 2 party cult head. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You're wrong but we just disagree. A lot of people choose lifestyles that are dangerous to other people. I never give up on hope they will change their ways. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Since there's no fraud, dems won't change the outcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That pesky 10th amendment always gets in the way of these dudes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I thought the CDC said you can spread covid even being vaccinated. Take care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stocks go up and down. Spotify is a social media stock. People are addicted to it. It will do fine. I'm a hold on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One of the problems I have with you dems and repubs is that when your dude slips up, it's a Freudian slip and when the other party does it, it's what they really believe. These opinions keep you dems and repubs hating each other and aids in both party's erosion to independents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You do know this is a democratic hack account.  I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Of course I have a problem with that. I'm thinking that's an opinion. Are you saying that is happening? I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yea, because San Francisco is such a hotbed of white supremist!........rollseyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ironically,  30 minutes later, dems did the same thing. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This actually isn't true. A simple Google search of the IRS numbers will tell you this. I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good luck. Tesla sold 1 million last year. Musk, not a people's person is brilliant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Does the CDC have any plan on how many people that have to be vaccinated, herd immunity,  before we lift mask mandates or is this here forever. Just a thought.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh boy. Where do I begin. The irony of this is incredible. If you can't see it, you are part of the problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We all will eventually get our turn. It's a virus here to stay. Thank you China.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Everyone tells me they're safe already! Guess you don't think so. . I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe and wear a mask.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oooo. The boogeyman,  1 millionaire. All jump on my bandwagon.  A millionaire gave. Lets trash him because he doesn't think like us......rollseyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The south use to do that for voters. It was a bad idea and racist then and still a bad idea and racist now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Who's my treasonous president? I haven't voted dem or repub for over 20 years. This mess is on your two parties not me. So far looks like Crimea and Ukraine are going to be handed over by dems. This isn't a partisan problem but dems and repubs will make it one. You can't help it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Then enjoy the corrupt 2 party system my friend.  Take care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Lorna, get real. You really believe this nut job has cable TV ? I wish you well my friend and peace. Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# John Nance Garner, FDR's vice president, nailed it when he said being vice president is no better than a warm bucket of spit.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>