<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, US forced China to start the arms race. China arming up is imho very wise in order to deter war from an imperialistic &amp; fanatical regime with a sustained history of war makings. The ball is in US's court to abandon Coldwar which it started. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You like projecting your thought don't u? Yes, journalists are like many career climbers do frequently do fake news in general to advance their careers. Yes, China is a frequent victim of MSM owned by government and press barons with ulterior motive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Something really turned in ODell. We followed each other after I retweeted  her excellent (in fact, pro China) article of her Covid experience during the beginning of the Covid crisis when we were both in China. Her tweets been mostly very positive on China but I think she 1/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# People are not calling it Chinese variant 2 because unlike you, most people aren't ignorant, shameless hate mongering racist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It was an educated guess by experts.  No one really know if 12 weeks period was ideal, fair or too long.  It is of course  very good that the experts made the right call.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I got it for Android phone... but I think it should work for IPhone too.  But you better check from reviews.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# very impressively healthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ain't cheap. £299 it is OCculus Rift2. I want it for both games and occasional watching content as well as research &amp; communication with friends. 
I shall sort it out this month.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad news on environment.  China has destroyed a desert. 
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Thank you Prof for highlighting the relative risk of AstraZeneca vaccine. I think the government has put prestige of 'our' vaccine before UK public health. This is not a dilemma that ordinary public should be subjected to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Indeed. Chinese first to report, identified and provide the world the genome sequence of the virus on 10th Jan which allowed researchers across the world to immediately start rrseaeching for vaccines and test kits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Conflict escalation could lead Russia to nuke us or lopped a few missiles in Britain if West keep up its greed for expansion into Russia sphere of influence. Russia (and China for that matter) are not defenceless states like those in M.E. which UK help destroyed in recent time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sorry. What about 'Freedom of Speech' and 'Freedom of expression'. nnMy #HASHTAG# to some liberals who defend Islamist preachings and practice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frankly, most Americans wouldn't know "What is Ukraine?" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ungrateful racist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello friends, 
As promised, here is my little gift to you for this festive holiday. Between 25th to 29th December my book "Blood, Dragons and Lions" is free to download in your local Amazon store. Some excellent reviews in UK Amazon. 
Search under 'kin f. kam to locate it quick. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9/ On the origin of Covid.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is US foreign policy too hostile to China?

Ans: Obviously. US regime not merely acted hostile to China in geopolitical sense, it and its so-called free MSM shamelessly &amp; liberally lied and promoted some of the worst racist propaganda campaign against another nation in history. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The minimal that the public can expect right now is for Arcuri and Johnson to return the cash they deceptively stolen from tax payers. 
Then prosecute them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust of China govmt is one main reason China beat back Covid so easily back in Jan/Feb. I was there. Chinese just haulkered down without stupid defiance to govmt advice &amp; #HASHTAG# was starved into submission within a month. China then kept Covid down by increasing vigilence. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I take a Lordship anytime.  It sounds cool and I get to visit London for free; just pop into the House of Lord for an hour or two to earn about £400.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sure, I was really attacking those war mongers who ARE really using the 'civilization difference' narrative to justify attack China ie they often say things like "they've different value or not same value etc".  I wasn't attacking Christianity or Judaism specially in the tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Sinopharm/Sinovac are traditional inactivated virus vaccine while AZ is novel adenovirus vector based vaccine. Anecdotally, I would think follow up with AZ or mRNA would bring greater efficacy. But IMHO, the biggest advantage of Chinese vaccines is its relative safety profile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course,  I don't support or believe in journalists exploiting athletes and sports in order to shill for their governments' or media bosses' political agenda. My tweet below simply demonstrates the hypocrisy,  racist and agenda driven motives of western journalists. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What is the Wuhan study?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know it is not 'nice' to say this, people like this Norwegian deceased guy are better off dead, since him died of Covid would prevent many more others dying with it. Similarly, it was a big shame Donald Trump survived or not suffered terribly for longer when he had Covid. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A white man is not qualified to tell an ethnic Chinese person who lived in West since 10 years old what is or is not racism. Your white privilege obviously made you blind to Trump's and Pompeo's deliberate use of 'Chinese virus, Kung Flu etc.' Much more of these shits in MSM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the wisdom of the Chinese.  Make peace, less spending needed on weapons.

US still not learned this lesson as it tries to encircle China with military build up. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yep..a mixture of insect chemicals and bacteria  I guess 🤮. Fortunately it looks like my immune system has conquered it. However, I hope there ain't some nasty virus it transferred to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reporting to you on 13th April 2024. The West &amp; western value have prevailed. The People's Republic of China has just submitted a surrender request to UN after US &amp; her allies nuked 30 Chinese cities which instantaneously pulverized at least 200 million Chinese civilians 1/ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They are heavyweight warmongers and propagandists though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[rights of Taiwanese people while totally blind siding/ignoring the wishes of 1.4 billion Chinese in the mainland. This is classic white supremacist logic/attitude to dismiss China's history, narrative and actions to deter separatism in Taiwan. They exploit their selective 4/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing in common here; all these countries elected popularist 'leaders' for their countries. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have been suffering from tireness and  inertia in recent years.  I am RT the tweet below to motivate myself to get one of my inventions on China's shelves in 2021. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the main reasons that the Wuhan variant of Covid has disappeared is because China &amp; Chinese people took drastic and the only correct way to controlling a pandemic potential virus with a sharp proper lockdown with responsible control of border travels. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Without Chinese successful oppression of Wahhabism, Uighur women would have been making TikTok videos of them secretly dancing in their burkhas or defiantly showing their face. nn#HASHTAG# innit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This reminds of a famous picture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There ARE really still many people who believe this.  If you are one of them, you have been brainwashed. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, highly trained scientists are really dumb like Sinophobes and racists who rather trust Murdoch, Daily Mail, BBC, Sky News and other MSM written by uneducated journalists following their press baron and/or politicians directivrs. n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South *African]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Never said or implied they are same, except they share same condition of being top tier powers (Russia in military, diplomatic, resource and geopolitical influence despite a weakling economy) under US meddling intentions and actions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# thanx Laura.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So it was widespread in the West, yet no western authorities knew better until China first reported and identified the virus. Looks like #HASHTAG# and it is brilliant solution to scapegoat China because Yellow Peril racism is so rife &amp; average citizens so gullible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# because they are vicious and moronic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*inactivated virus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you believe western MSM lies and narrative about how China government tried to delay giving out information about SarsCov2 genetic sequence, here is something for you to digest;
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frank and controversial broadcast by CGTN. 
Imho, US unconditional support of Israel is actually a poison chalice to the ultimate survival of Israel and Jews living there. US support made Israel arrogant, uncompromising and ruthless, thus making peaceful solution forever pending. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To watch. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If u were paying attention at all, I am a defender of truth &amp; critic of ignorant &amp; malicious bullshitters. Tbf, I wouldn't bother defending China if it weren't for the industrial amount of racist crap/propaganda/lies produced by the genocidal US regime &amp; ur so-called free MSM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, you right not Blinken directly. It is Murdoch and David Asher (former lead 'investigator' on Covid of State Department under Mike "lie, cheat  steal" Pompeo). Asher is now under Hudson Institute. It is so obvious both SkyNews and Asher are 'in it' together to smear China.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a typical route for tourists on the Great Wall! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I reckon this reporter is either high on drugs or he was paid by pharma. 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# In many ways, Chinese like this Yu guy are the worst kind of catalyst for fanatical sinophobia.  They helped justify the innate Yellow Peril fearmongering of white supremacist racists like Pompeo because he could point to Yu and says look Yu is my advisor and a Chinese.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You are projecting the awful conditions of Native Americans to Tibetans.  
Most Tibetan lifes have improved massively since CCP destroyed serfdom. Sadly there were also some oppression too as China fought US funded separatists, but fortunately stable Tibet continues to improve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You forget democracy is worth it. Better dead and homeless than without freedom. #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh shock. First, China forbids Islam, and now China pays Muslims to pray.n#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I suppose you also support jihadists who blew themselves up too. AFAIK, everyone of those poor burnt Tibetans were radicalised by senior political monks (mostly funded by CIA). Do you know any senior monks who immolated themselves? You are a CIA tool. 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Western media impartial reporting. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11/ Some other incriminating tweets on Covid in this thread of tweets here
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia inspired by its fellow Five Eyes leaders in Covid assimilation; Great USA and Great Britain, #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me at Culham laboratory, UKAEA almost 30 years ago! 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Covid was already hugely widespread in US by mid December. Funny how people like you dont blame US for covering up first?  
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It is Biden's choice actually. If US regime could find the wisdom to work with China instead of making wars everywhere, then US will come out winning, along with rest of the world. If not, we all lose, but China will loses least compared with the warmongers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Xinjiang already had a series of ambassors and diplomats made visit there.  
By the way, I want to have unfettered access to your house, bank accounts and social media activities because I am accusing you of...... 
Glasnost killed Soviet Union.  No thax.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simple equation to remember.  
UG=WMD, 
where U=Uighur, G=genocide. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, but not in HK until NSL was imposed last year. The prolonged violent events and direction of HK youths unjustly turning into rabid China haters were as a result of China's extreme tolerance of allowing HK its freedom. Unfortunately, some people &amp; countries exploited  this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Who is she? Feeling confused momentarily. 
Lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia will not attack Estonia, but any envoy of weapons by road or air through to Ukraine would  be attacked by Russia.  Accidental escalation is possible too. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Everybody is talking about who would be funding the wall. But has anyone asked who will be building it? With low US unemployment, I reckon US will need to employ Mexican immigrants to build it. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, talk about character when you have clearly shown yourself to be an ultra racist opportunist making &amp; having made hundreds of videos that you gleefully &amp; deliberately infused with demeaning, condescending and dehumanizing broad sweep insults of China and Chinese people. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Ukraine upped the stake by increasing bombardment of Russian separatist regions. No doubt this is at US order as the West has predicted Russian invasion &amp; is trying to double bluff Russia. This is a v dangerous game where West is doubling down in making Ukraine a NATO member.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Covid origin.  Interesting. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I fear a military solution may be the only option left to China unless 
1) CN accepts Tw Independence, which is virtually impossible unless CN government collapses. If some fancy Gorbechev figure leads CN &amp; liberally let Taiwan separately, then China will surely collapse as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top tip for assimilation. 
Note bananas have unhealthy amount of sugar.  
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not all mangoes are same though.  Here in UK, most mangoes in supermarkets  are from the Caribbean and they taste awful. In summer in Asian areas, one could get Pakistani mangoes and they taste great.. but the best are from HK which I think are imported from Thailand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Surprise,  surprise... another Indian racist.  Here's a video of your country men enjoying a bat dish. 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Overall,over 90% of Chinese support their government. Fact is Western political motivated lies &amp; frequently racist slanders against China are rarely challenged by most ordinary people (liberals included) because they think they know better or don't really care about Chinese ppl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I am looking forward to read part 2 by this George Calhourn guy. Typical;so much projection. I wonder how many cents he received to make up his pathetic disinformation article, with inconsistent/dodgy logic and numbers, in order to fit his master's narrative to demonise China.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have a problem, Major Tom. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Classic lies and slanders from shameless West MSM and politicians which are then believed by 100s millions worldwide as fact.  
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Rubbish. See my thread on my pinned tweet for numerous refurtation of Western (mostly US) political motivated lies.  
WHO was in Wuhan in Feb.  Both WHO and Chinese authorities agree stopping spread priority then, and origin research to be done later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Prof Villani is a brilliant and ultra creative mathematician, obviously. But creativity alone is useless if his imagination is exercised on false information or influenced by prejudice. 
On CN,it is fact that many westerners are similarly brainwashed by their misguided certainty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No.  Crazy is just an adjective.  That's all.  You can't just make any allegations like you did with those people you mentioned without evidence that support your all too frequent accusations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ditto, then there would be one less world flash point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True. NATO gave false and unrealistic promise to Ukraine. Russophobic Ukrainian politicians lapped it up and even use it to poke the Russian bear harder. Yup, everyone are at fault here. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah right. US and EU have  never subsidized their industries #HASHTAG#.nnMore to the point, isnt US/Eu research grants to their Universities State aid also. Oh, how about Boeing &amp; Airbus receiving 100s  billions through State (military) R&amp;D grants and orders?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As for 'established' speculation and rumour that SARScov2 escaped from  Wuhan lab, one should be aware the rumour was promoted by US State Department right from the start and repeated frequently. Funny despite massive resources, no evidence ever presented
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The danger of Shamima Begum returning back to Britain is she could be reradicalised again. I heard her father is in Pakistan, so I think the humane thing to do is to try to negotiate with Pakistan to allow her to join him. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# LoL. You guys are so brainwashed and ignorant. Indians have Covid deaths in the millions... Your country has more people in malnutrition than entire African continent. Communal violence, caste apatheid thuggery and rapes are regular parts of your country.  Grow up and learn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3/ E European States would've failed miserably too had they not got the massive economic assistance that Western Europe provided. If China had a similar 'revolution' (say 6/4 led to fall of CPC) in '89/90, there is no doubt in my mind China would be in pieces &amp; millions starved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# not sure about less ill....Recent UK news I read suggest otherwise especially among younger infected people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way US could stop China as the number 1 economy (which is just inevitable rather than any world domination design by China) is to create major military conflicts, so that Nato and US lapdog allies are coerced to sanction or perhaps even join in a war with China. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump virus could have got Biden. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# why not?🤗]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US is so insecure because it has to defund its Military Industrial Complex in order to be able to invests in its people. This is nigh on impossible. Furthermore, years of easy print money and attraction of global talents are coming to an end too. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# lol, nowhere near China! Please spare me your logic of Europeans/Americans/Australians lecturing China when they are thousands of miles from their ancestral Europe in the first place. You guys are just totally hypocritical. Just get out of SCS &amp; ECS to ease tension.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I call this aggressive provocation for civil war within China.  And if US/EU intervene militarily,  then WW3 is possible.  Don't western politicians never learn from all the calamities (eg Iraq, Syria, Libya etc.) they caused or proposed around the world in this century alone? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Also check
#URL#
Note my point isn't about the origin of the virus being from China or not. SarsCov2 is a naturally occurring virus, so politcising &amp; blaming a country are pure evil racist hate mongering by politicians &amp; MSM with anti China agenda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep... the same bloody scumbag wrote it. 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# China should absolutely punish the fascist  Bolsonaro moron, but I don't think China would do so by withholding vaccine ingredients, unless the limited supply meant China might as well gave priority to other equally needed countries instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3/ and society. I was in China right from the start of the crisis. So even by end of Feb, I felt impatient &amp; wonder to myself how come restaurants aren't opening yet? How come there are more hassles with track &amp; trace apps, how come more road barriers when no cases for weeks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No surprise... 
#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# yup...  a puppet indeed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just discovered another self hate Chinese-American  idiot promoting anti Asian hate in America.  Look at that profile and her promoting c*nt Bill Maher latest's racist yellow peril sketch. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There is a big difference calling it the Indian variant against a backdrop of many other variants also labelled with country origin (or where first noticed) versus naming a virus with the name of a  country attached to it. I am ok with Wuhan variant.. but Wuhan virus not. Get it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[However, it should not be particularly surprising or shameful either if Covid's origin is found to originate in China. Afterall, China has both large population and probably the largest range of biodiversity life on Earth.  Pandemic is inevitable on Earth periodically.  2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# So here's my writing advice to YangYang; be as critical or disparaging as you like about China, but you should apply similar level of criticism to US, ur adopted country. If you won't do same because you desperate for US nationality, then u should tone down your prejudice against]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He sweats like a pig? #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Go and check YouTube videos from many non Chinese vloggers. I know too from personal experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fact is paramount. If majority of Europeans judge China from half truths or extremely biased narratives born of Western elites' prejudice and their MSM propaganda, then it is not unreasonable to expect Europeans to better themselves with better education, starting from schools.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The ignorance and obvious BS are in you and others bombarded by decades of Murdoch media and narrow minded Eurocentric education. Hilarious to say Australia bans were never designed to influence others...Australian leaders went of of its way to lobby UK &amp; others to ban Huawei.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shamima Begum is sounding more &amp;more convincing by the day! But seriously, what she said is obvious. She was gloomed online and within British society. UK government needs to address radicalising problems in Britain. Simply excluding 1 British citizen will not solve the problem. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Excluding children that is 120m doses. I meant twice not 4x.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# China was the first country to experience a major outbreak and first to identify the virus. But it doesn't mean it is the origin (like AIDS first exploded out of US cities in early 80s,  but origin was eventually  traced to central Africa of made decades past). 2/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. This is the best article I read to refute the constant blame China social media posts because of the constant stream of damn lies that came out of Trump's regime (thankfully gone) and rehash of old news in new msm 'documentaries'. 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My error. The above figures not global...probably just Philippines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dream on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Call yourself an author when you put politics and hateful nationalism above saving lives? 
Would you say no to Chinese imports of PPE and oxygen generators too just to satisfy ur petty nationalism?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little known fact about US-China-Global history. #HASHTAG# money didn't just fueled the British empire, it did it for US also. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is #USER# 's Australia not pushing US to open itself to WHO's investigation on the origin of Covid? ScottMo was so aggressive pushing for investigating China early on, but now total silence about US refusal to cooperate.  Why? 
Ans: Australia is US's lapdog. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On US police violence. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most important graph showing UK's devastating number of Covid cases compared to European countries in the continent. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must get this book. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I suppose it's a start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Chinese vaccine's safety and efficacy in immunocompromised patients. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extraordinary drones display. 
Amazing historical connection of China's brilliance in firework display has passed onward to drones now. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How about India pay for Delta variant then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You misunderstood my point. My point was since American soldiers are normally as fit as others,there was no reason why they would have performed especially worse than almost all the other teams; unless they were already sick or they've especially weak immune system to catch Covid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What's so nationalistic about a song mocking America's response to Covid which led to over 700K dead Americans? Chinese reactions and propaganda contents are a drop in the ocean compared with the amount of mis/disinformation &amp; racist slurs by West on China in the past 22 months.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China builds,  US bombs. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A friend who caught COVID 7 months ago recently caught second strain.  Both time he suffered a lot... so it must be true. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I recall one of the biggest disinformation agent in the Covid saga is Niall Ferguson who claimed China deliberately let international flights out of Wuhan after lockdown was also a Harvard professor or fellow. Why all these dishonorable people have Harvard connection?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My remark that US would rather 'Chinese live in poverty if necessary ' is not really an exergeration or extreme given how US politicians currently enforce such situations with sanctions on various countries while never learned from previous war failures eg Iraq, Libya, Syria etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wish too, but we must respect their human rights to shoot arrows and petrol bombs to policemen. nn#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Shameful.  US puppet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More evidence are building up that are revealing Covid19 was already widespread in US, before Wuhan, China. The chronology is increasingly pointing to the country where the outbreaks and tolls gone nuclear the quickest, where now 600k of its citizens died. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Sure,  that's a good personal decision too.   All I was saying is if I had two Sinopharm shots with no worrying side effects, then I (personally) would not bother (risk) taking a novel tech vaccine simply because it has better efficay against mild infections.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread: on Uighur related smear campaigns. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Classic Western arrogance, ignorance and racism. China and Chinese shouldn't be allowed to teach the world about their cultures and values. Is this why Confucius Institutes being smeared and shut down all over the Anglo world? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Therefore,  India's true GDP is really about twice as large as China.  😭

Please don't tell this formula to all the Indian trolls out there.  They will be boasting this fact to humiliate China and Chinese.  🤫]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Not now... not with 21 days quarantine 😅.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Rubbish. Ukraine's war started in 2014 when West instigated bloody coup there. This war is so preventable if only West respected Russia's red line (see my pinned tweet). West used Ukraine in its geopolitical game..the best West can do now is deescalate &amp; give humanitarian help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Childish Slovenia politicians will regret its grandstanding BS. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4/ BBC never bother to clarify that Chinese authority was facing a novel virus, one with long incubation period, produce mostly mild flu like symptoms only with nearly half cases asymptomatic. So certainly there were definitely at least 100s or even &gt; a 1000 cases in Dec.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jah bless Bob's wisdom;
#HASHTAG# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# apparently not!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important reminder that many western 'socialist' liberal politicians are in fact quite evil too. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to hear some positive good news. This is a start. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These two HK Chinese lads are really simply great.  Fully recommend their videos for fact, logic and explanations of various nuance issues. 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I made a truly child friendly Nunchuka. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is an important clarification from Dr Daszak about having raw data on animal testing in WIV lab, because it is only via animal testing/experiments could a new virus like SarCov2 possibly emerged from a lab. 
W.H.O scientists concluded that did not happen. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Blah blah blah... the most you can blame China is Wuhan authority prevaricated/procrastinated over human to human transmission by a period of 6 days (according to critical Washington Post after Trump ordered MSM to get China). It makes no difference to outcome in West 1/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Indeed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Everything I wrote in defence of China is based on FACT and reasonable stance of human decency, rather than ideology (thus, I don't really make distinction about China and CCP when discussing current China issues involving governance). I am motivated by educating people  4/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Thanks.  Just read it. The whole thesis behind this article is the fake assumption that Chinese vaccines are useless compared to western vaccines apparently able to resist infection much better (really?). 
This article is funded by people/orgs with interests of Western vaccines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is happening again and some people are complaining about delay full opening up on 21 June.  Do people ever learn? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note I dont speak much politics at home,except on Twitter! I've no desire to talk politics with a young kid or influence him with my bias. My question was raised in a neutral tone as I was really interested in his assessment from such a young innocent mind. He answered "bad." 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I agree. It is ridiculous to rule out leaks from Fort Detrick. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how fucking idiotic and low level western education is still at about China and Chinese people. Makes me wonder why I ever bothered engaging/educating with some people in social media who really have been so educated. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep. China tries to prevent terrorism with re-education camps temporarily locking up some innocent people regrettably, while the West sent missiles and bombs onto Muslim lands killing thousands of innocent people regrettably. nnWestern values win. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India has issues with China, but I don't think even India is as dumb as BoJo's apparent new direction of kissing US's ass over new Cold War against China. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Good article highlighting the different approach between the civilised West and barbaric China. The west prefers to bomb Muslims and invade their lands, while the Chinese try to re educate their own Muslims away from jihadist and backward Salafi ideology. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So, basically within a matter of 3 weeks there were hardly any more new cases in my city and across China. But what happened next is the biggest difference between China and West; 1) instead of relaxing restrictions I experienced further prevention measures like more checks 2/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# nah...I seen your ripped muscle in one of your tweets. I reckon you will survive to 3rd round, or maybe 4th if lucky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Setting the narrative. Yes, it is racist and your tweet is racist for implying Covid and the suffering it caused is all China's fault. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I doubt it. If AZ vaccine was Chinese or Russian then your suggestion was very likely to be accurate.  
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Here's the extract from the review; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Jerry. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like Trump's America will need to subsidise their farmers ad infinitum. nnGreat socialist policy! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When will it ends?  #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# haha... classic fake headlines trick for general public.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ignoramus &amp; racists are blaming China when China had the virus under controlled by late February while western countries messed around with herd immunity which spreads the virus widely across their countries. Genome studies confirm this pandemic is basically all European strain. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# RIP.
Wish more people neuter their pets to minimise unnecessary sufferings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But the Chinese data must be fake right?
And you are a shill for CCP too, right?
#HASHTAG#. 
Seriously,  thank you #USER# for just doing your job and dare to be honest despite much pressure on you to say otherwise. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[at all costs. They'll persist whipping up the worst kind propaganda to promote hatred against China &amp; Chinese (note they would claim they're against 'CCP' only while fully aware their lies create animosity &amp; hate against its people) ie. this is manufacturing consent for war 2/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is AstraZeneca/Oxford vaccine just too big and prestigious to fail? 
Sadly I think there has been at least some covering ups or sweep under the carpet attitude. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So UK and much of west are starting its disgusting yellow peril, sinophbic Cold War against a country whose workers &amp; savers benefited West hugely with sustained high living standard due to low inflation &amp; cheap loan that sustain west's sovereign debts. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Even Obama admitted it in his recent autobiography. Also take a look at the numbers
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Including Chinese Taipei Island, China probably has the most advanced combination of theoretical and practical studies of material science and electronics right now.  
Ironically, US/West will mostly fall behind further unless their universities recruit more Chinese talents. 😜 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The people in the vid were pathetic , I agree. But racists generalise too readily. As for your racist tweet, show some self reflection instead. Americans shoot millions of animals for sports every year. About 30k Americans shoot each other dead every year. Talk of compassion lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah, how could China and Wuhan allowed those missteps and coverups to happen, especially weeks AFTER Covids killed so many across cities Italy, France, Spain, UK and US. Lombardy region even locked down on 23Rd Jan &amp; those Chinese repeated all the missteps of Western countries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think it depends on the subject discipline.
Interestingly, the most famous alchemist and scientist who dabbled in the 'occult' was Isaac Newton. According to scholar of Newton, he spent more time on alchemy and theology than on real science!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fort Detrick next. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I learned 2 days ago a family friend in York, his wife, son, bro, mother &amp; father have all caught #HASHTAG#. Both he &amp; wife are struggling a bit, his son, brother and father not too bad. But his mum is in hospital needing ventilator. 
Meanwhile morons like #HASHTAG# roam large.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hopefully, the tragedy will be far far less this time round due to vaccines and Omnicron being less aggressive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He is a racist just like Nigel Farage.  I hope he is kicked out of China.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The diaspora are still as vulnerable.  The hate and lies deliberately invented or tolerated by MsM and politicians, especially since Covid are very effective in creating greatest animosity towards Chinese.  Afterall, there is now a huge blood &amp; economic libel according to them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm afraid the beautiful flower in my old tweet below only lasted 3 days. Then it sank into the water. I tried to rescue it by lifting it out of the water. Well, that was foolish of me.. the flower has died.  Shame it didnt live one more day as a new flower bloomed as u can see. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tracking Covid pandemic;
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# trending.  No it should be Jimmy SaVILE. Just remember VILE goes with the name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Disappeared? They were prosecuted and jailed under the law of the land.  HK had over 6 months of extreme violence... with at least 2 innocent people killed, many seriously injured by those so called 'freedom's protesters, yet zero killed by police.  Look at US, 4killed in 4hours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Oh yeah.. sure. #HASHTAG# police pulled out a gun, you run away, not keep going forward which leaves the police no other choice but to shoot the assailant. Had he shoot in the air, the terrorist could have time to grab the gun and put the policeman's life in mortal danger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Covid origin. Interesting. I missed this tweet and its study from last year. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Funny I've done business with US companies and got ripped off twice. China is the most competitive place with  huge entreprenerial population popping up all the time. Inevitably, some are shitheads. The #USER# is a an example with many unpaid creditors in his past biz dealings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I feel there is more optimism now that there is an official inquiry. But I also share your pessimism that the outcome may not warrant the optimism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He isn't sick. This Matt Tye guy is being who he is, a rather stupid asshole racist with little integrity and ethic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please spare me your Christian heart. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Here is the direct answer which Director Li  should have said; NO students were killed.   You politicians are truly ignorant or just yellow peril sinophobes. 
Here's details.. can be cross checked if you like, but I guess you guys arent interested in truth
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such generosity, after I invaded your home and robbed billions in oil revenues. #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>