<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Wha? good luck checking the plates underwater RT #USER#: ADVISORY: Number coding is implemented today August 20,2013 #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTF!!! No signal!!! How idiotic is this?? What if there’s an emergency???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banning cars for one day a week didn't work at all, did it? So what makes you think banning it for 2 days will? #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Besides, pork barrel reduces an already limited resource. Instead of spending big money on big projects, it gets divided up into small…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes because priests are EXPERTS in law and everyone must listen #HASHTAG#  RT #USER#... (cont) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They should just stick to the keyboards and bots. Forget about showing up as real people because they will only be embarrassed. Parang yung Duterte “Youth” group.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good Job to the Mayor of Makati. That's how you show them who's boss! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They should be encouraging ridesharing, and working with them, instead of making things difficult.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Meralco price increase is due to the downtime of the Malampaya plant, does this mean this increase is just temporary?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# obviously, they are not REAL Christians. Diba, #USER# ?#USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t these religious conservatives EVER get tired of being on the wrong side of history? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# LOL. Let the guards watch TV or play games instead? That could relieve their boredom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yes, Napoles getting VIP treatment is wrong. Does that mean other prisoners should get VIP treatment as well?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# somebody tell them that god said go forth and multiply…. Wait scratch that. Better that they don’t multiply.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dengvaxia was a risk vs reward decision. From a purely medical standpoint, the rewards are much greater than the risks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# well, Trump would take those same millions AND proudly treat women as possessions at the same time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# in that case, the placement would look like an org chart #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah... I can believe people preferred the Wild Wild West...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# these guys are trying to one up each other in the hypocrisy game, no? #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Tama. Stop giving a voice to those who do not know what they're talking about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Heh. Even hardcore Catholics pick and choose. They ALL do. #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolute horseshit! “#USER#: UNA exec: #USER# an able lawmaker despite missing House sessions #URL#”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who think Du30 will be their “savior” will probably be the same ones who will call for his head when he doesn’t solve crime in 6 mos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ahh. That I did not know. Still, they had balls of titanium. #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, why not? UFO = Unidentified Flying Object. So I guess it makes sense to spend a few bucks trying to identify them :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# oh sure, we lack class because we support equality for all. Those who support rapist priests, now THAT'S classy. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A/C for his personal washroom eh? #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was 1 of those comedy bar jokes right? Coz that was OFFENSIVE RT #USER#: Estrada says no Ejercito has ever stolen money frm public]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#%}^@#!!!! Times like this I wish there was a god I could pray to. Beat the Heat!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact: some doctors don't pay proper taxes. Fact: some of them DO pay proper taxes. Fact: the BIR campaign is full of shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Totally agree!!! Because all this hyper-complicated conspiracy was made in order to fool us into thinking that the earth is an oblate spheroid, with the final objective being... uhh... umm... err... I don’t get it. Who profits from a round earth conspiracy again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# is he still the only atheist kid there? :) glad to hear he’s popular with the girls :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was a great joy to drive in Canada and the US. Even in LA, where most Americans think has the worst drivers, it was driving bliss for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We expect statesman-like behavior at all times. RT #USER#: #URL# uLOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# more kids begging along Gilmore st corner 3rd at new Manila]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You are mistaken. That pool is where we kung fu guys relieve ourselves. I hope you have not been drinking from there. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Haaayz o sige na you can join us... #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I agree! Too bad I despise CebPac hahaha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# how’s the fact checking working out for you Christians? #HASHTAG#  #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# By Odin's Beard! That sucks!  But hey, as long as the priest's word... I mean god's word is followed, it's all ok! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hmm… Not as bright and airy as I hoped it would be…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# they’ve stooped to quoting some random person spouting random stuff that praises Duterte?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But hey, at least he wore a suit! Maybe it’s a start…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# that's what the CDC says. Read the whole thing. It advocates proper and consistent use of condoms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have to learn to always keep our options open and not be blindly locked into one candidate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can they just shutdown communications on a whim?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy crap really? He’s willing to sever ties with other countries over this? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Chairman Tolentino had any balls, he'd tell all the other agencies that he can't fix our traffic problems if they do not cooperate. #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# is he serious with that question?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yeah they have the onsen here, but I don't really care for being in my birthday suit with a bunch of other guys... lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because without a hammer, obviously the Martilyo Gang can't do anything, right? Right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now they’re spinning it to say that Duterte was cursing the reporter, not Obama. You know, he could have avoided all this by NOT cussing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[W…T…F!!! As if government  services aren’t shitty enough already #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# it seems you choose to ignore the entire message of the CDC article LOL typical of a religious nut.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus: they’re using us for their own purposes again #HASHTAG#

Mary: I know, right? #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Jordan didn’t need two other established superstars to do it though. Please don’t compare the two. #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I totally agree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# fat chance. 3rd party maybe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, I’ve never been a fan of Leni. I just don’t understand what the fuss is all about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Duterte keeps this up, he better be quick in finding jobs for the millions of OFWs who will be returning home soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# well, now that makes it all ok! The poor catholic priests are being set up by the kids! Jail the homos!!! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# hmmm that’s something I could also use :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# why aren't you bitching about Kim Jong Un? He's probably worse than PNoy! #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# really? Magnolia also?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# apparently, Binay is Makati personified eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like Crapper? :) #USER#: Shrapnel was invented by an Englishman of the same name. Don't u wish u could have something named after u?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# happy new year! Get well soon :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# did you know that making false claims linked to looking like an idiot? #USER#  #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# at least they were informed :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Never mind that said potential risks come with potential benefits. EJKs on the other hand...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# LOL they must have seen the long lines of TNT wannabes forming outside their gates ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# it seems that Floyd isn’t the only one who should have “Money” as his nickname]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# honestly, we all know what the problem is. It’s just that no one has the balls to fix it. #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Make proper bus stops every few blocks. Minibuses for smaller roads and regular buses for bigger ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# so true. It’s sad that #USER# #USER# gives him a platform to spread his BS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Make sidewalks available to pedestrians. Make buses run on a schedule. Phase out jeepneys. Discipline the drivers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As if traffic isn’t bad already. Don’t they have that billion peso mega church? Or is that a different religion? #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hammers won't be sold inside malls anymore. Ahahahahahahaha! LOL! One of the stupidest solutions I've ever heard! Hahahaha!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# this is why I dislike religion. It gives people with not so good intentions a way to “look nice”.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial analysts pissed at #USER# but there’s truth to what he says. Foreign funds have been selling for the past couple of weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yeah because militant atheists write books instead of just peacefully bombing &amp; killing. #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# let’s prioritize rebuilding roads and bridges. Let the church take care of its own. It’s not like they have no money #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“#USER#: You can see it in their eyes #URL# #URL#” LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# easy answer: they were all in on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I walked into Mercury Drug and found that the queueing system is gone. I asked what happened and they said PEOPLE DIDN’T LIKE IT!!! WTF?!?!? WHAT IS WRONG WITH US????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# oh that’s where he practices his aim. He’s a terrible shot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philippines one of the safest countries in the world.

??????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My question was directed at those who thought the VP of the Philippines was being disrespectful when she posed for photos with a smile at a Holocaust memorial in Germany.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Watch Hamilton in Chicago. A lot cheaper than New York. But honestly, it’s not as good as the hype makes it out to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I can see where you're coming from #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# WTF... releasing a list is already NOT due process...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But anyway, wrong or right, she did the right thing and took full responsibility. Unlike some other leaders out there...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why is acupuncture in the list?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People seem to forget that the root of all this is his penchant for hurling expletives on live TV.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m sorry #USER# but your toilets at the 3rd floor of your BGC outlet are an absolute mess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But then again, there are those who really don’t care if they look like ignorant jackasses as long as they get to push their agenda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop politicizing Dengvaxia. Stop twisting the facts to suit your needs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# should mocking a man for his size or weight also count as violence? #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Chief Justice flying business class isn’t really something to raise eyebrows about. I think that’s one of the perks of such a high position.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# exactly. The way I see it, it's mostly driven by Aquino's haters...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s on Mars that cosmic rays would specifically come from there???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# they should be branded as heroes and given free houses and shit by grandstanding politicians #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it just me or does it look creepy? RT #USER#: Hello.
It’s your 
Mother. 
#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# sometimes I wish there was a “punch” button in Twitter… #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ian Vega is your teacher?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes you’re not beholden to Obama. Yes the Filipino People is your master. Then please stop embarrassing the Filipino People.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you should have called off the bet when thy lost game 6 :) #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lacson wants “a free hand on the job” LOL! Interesting choice of words :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sigh… out of school and out on the streets… #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# sadly, that seems to be the case #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# are vehicles equipped with PNP commemorative plates exempted from coding?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# there’s a crucial difference here. Obama never endorsed or encouraged the killings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# not with the perennial flooding in Metro Manila #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I fully agree with that. #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# well if they continue to be blind to the real cause of traffic, wala talaga mangyayari.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I’m sure they are. A lot of the govt bureaus are sick at its roots… :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# thanks! But the link you gave doesn't have London in it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Four Seasons Total Landscaping debacle reminds of how things are run in the Philippines. When those in power fuck up so badly yet INSIST that they are right...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I went meditating on top a mountain as what kung fu guys are wont to do… ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All you are doing is giving money to criminal syndicates, and worse, perpetuating the cycle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys guys… let’s not resort to insulting the Binays for their dark skin. It detracts from the real issue, and makes us look superficial.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# LOL yeah because there’s a law that states that atheists can’t worship just like minors can’t vote. #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And forgo the money-making opportunity? Wish wish...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# are you turning Muslim? ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you know, I keep asking my anti gay marriage friend that question, and he could never give me a straight answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# are they your kids?:)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# does it even matter who wrote it? He was the one who approved it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pull my trigger… #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I believe the world's oldest Chinatown is in China ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# wish wish… #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When you have evidence, you don't need faith. But I'm guessing that's not something you're familiar with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# sickening no?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy holidays to everyone :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# can we please stop being pro-poor and start being anti-poverty???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Oh I see... so how exactly do they profit from this ball earth conspiracy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As far as we are concerned, these Angkas riders giving free rides are private citizens giving free rides. Free. No payments. So why the heck would they need permits?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHO THE FUCK ARE YOU KIDDING??? RT #USER#: #USER# Catholic church has zero tolerance for paedophile priests]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If you’re going to watch Hamilton, I highly recommend that you watch Spamilton after :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I’m sorry what price is she willing to pay under those circumstances? What is her sacrifice when an innocent man loses his job?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I’m sorry but putting together “SMDC” and “5-star condo” already makes it an obvious scam LOL #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh please do #HASHTAG# because I’d really love to get front seats at a reasonable price!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now the shameless politicizing of the issue makes me wanna puke. It’s not genocide you fuckers. It’s a calculated risk that turned out to be a bad bet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serious question: Photo taken at funeral of Former First Lady Barbara Bush. Are they being disrespectful by smiling? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She has repeatedly disappointed me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People taking photos and making V signs at a bus hostage scene where somebody actually died = offensive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# lol I hope that burka helps :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# wish u guys can clear E Rodriguez Sr of all obstruction at the side like mga parked cars sa tapat ng De Los Santos Medical Ctr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Starscream’s facial expression is priceless :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# oo nga e. Pero we will be branded as the bad guy or "too sensitive" if we did that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn look at the SMOG! RT #USER#: Traffic View of Katipunan-Berkeley as of 7:18 AM, #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you’ve got good looking kids :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# or “kids” for that matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I’m sure you’re full of shame, right? I would be if I was Muslim. #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can keep accusing the media of trying to make DU30 look bad, but it seems to me that he’s doing an excellent job of that himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what will you do when the 2 day ban fails? Make it 3 days naman? #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# maybe we should start reporting religious posts  en masse too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I agree. God is unprovable, just like Superman, Santa Claus, and the Tooth Fairy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# well, as they say, hindsight is always 20/20 :) #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All this blind support and worship is getting to Duterte’s head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# as far as we can tell, deities exist only in the mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fix the corruption problem first. THEN the people will be more willing to pay proper taxes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NO. We need more DISCIPLINED DRIVERS DAMNIT!!! “#USER#: ‘Skyway needs taller, stronger barriers’ #URL#”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Sunday, Jesus will come out of the cave shouting “April Fool’s guys! I’m still alive!”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# should every prisoner be afforded the same, in case the same thing happens to them? #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“#USER#: “#USER#: Atheists must have the most boring sex lives!” yeah because guilt must be SOOOO exciting #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# of there's someone in my timeline who praised that shit I'm unfollowing him/her right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# well it's what was implied by "so much for love of country." Maybe I misunderstood what you meant...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# so… I guess this absolves SM of everything, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# what the heck??? Please fix your system!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone attending Cafe Scientfique?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have enough trouble connecting to the WiFi in the other room...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# GMOs are not bad for us. Just because companies like Monsanto act badly doesn't mean GMO is also bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah. I wish it was the other way around...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# exactly. It’s like altruism is lost on them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the 2 day coding pushes through, those who can will just buy new cars. Guess where they will park those extra cars? #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh, you mean the FAITH-BASED association of physicians? Yeah I'm sure they are unbiased in their views #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Loa loa? Guinea worms? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Vanilla ice cream goes really well with it ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# …they are the ones who make it harder for those of us who want to do it the right way. #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# how is that a bad thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The solution to our traffic problems is easy. We know how to solve them. There's just no will to implement them. #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Deepak loves his money! RT #USER#: “#USER#: Always choose love over logic” #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# apparently this deity has an unhealthy tendency to meddle in the bedroom antics of people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the original number coding did was increase d potential number of vehicles on the road. This second round promises to do even more #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# that is EEEVIL!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victory or the graveyard daw according to #USER# . I vote the graveyard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Store display at Watson's SM Aura. Says everything you need to know about SM lol #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# we. He came home, trapos showered him with gifts, sya ba yun? #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# besides, if they even glance at their monitors, they’ll see who really causes traffic along EDSA #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# then why didn’t DU30 staff clarify this when Obama asked his staff to check if the meeting will still be productive?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# that's good to hear...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# damn right!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I do all my bookings and reservations by myself too. Cheaper that way lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope the rallyists pick up after themselves and not leave tons of trash like certain religious groups do when they use Quirino Grandstand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# that's a different issue #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Daaamn!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# because any form of criticism is disrespectful… unlike grabbing pussies, which is totally respectful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# then I guess the panel of judges were all rabidly intolerant anti-religion Nazis then #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# what? I thought it was more and smaller???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And why the fuck is a lawyer heading the MMDA and not an engineer???]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>