<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[How do we hurt Putin without hurting the Russian people?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Charisma is like pornography (as defined by Repubs in the 1980s)--you can't describe it but you know it when you see it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chef Andres to the rescue, as usual. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 100% Brett. And you're bucking that mythical truth with bits of facts and TRUTH about Native stories and histories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't know if entire galaxies are made of antimatter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will never get used to hairless cats. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes I find that shocking. A real escalation in what EU is willing to provide to Ukraine. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Local coffee place closed due to staffing shortage. I’m assuming it’s covid related.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The term "nursing home industry" is nauseating. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In that case I’d recommend Space 550 on Friday the 11th.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Done!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For how many years have they been saying we'll lower prescription drug prices? Never happens. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lady at the table next to me has a stroller next to her, which I assumed contained a small human. Nope! She brought her dog to dinner in a stroller.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It feels like Putin WANTS to resurrect the Cold War. Feels like he misses it.  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Birds of a feather. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sending you faith that somehow, somehow, everything will be ok.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems like a viral way to spread the virus (so sorry). #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Allegedly said by Ukrainian women to Russian invaders. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe those countries need reassurance. Might be nervous about Russia. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, I'm sure the National Guard is overrun with antifa supporters. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ordered an emergency box of dates and feeling better. I hope that paying for grocery delivery is a habit I let go of as the pandemic eases, along with subscribing to too many streaming services.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly. I think I remarked on this earlier today. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't seen anyone in Oakland without a mask since CA ended its mask mandate. It's like a collective decision has been made that it's too soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love it! I can add to my collection of t-shirts I found over twitter (such as Bodega Cats and #USER#). #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hahahaha yeah I feel like this has happened to me once or twice. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hahahaha. Sylvester makes a little chirp when I do it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the Taliban always keeps their word. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spend a lot of time here hoping that the experts are wrong. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The ways that Western countries would support a Ukrainian resistance are beginning to take shape." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ouch. And given all that people of color have suffered lately, to say something like this. It’s just beyond. This is 19th century thinking. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup. Not to mention the painful legacy of what actual Nazis did to Ukrainian Jews not that long ago. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's trust? Not occupation? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got outside today, away from my self-imposed omicron isolation. Humans need attunement with other humans and with nature. That was today's lesson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Agreed. Can't dance in N95, can barely dance w fabric mask.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No Country For Old Men" is really something. The dialogue, the foreboding sense of doom, the acute sense of place and time...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m sitting across from a baby who is in the “I stare at everyone for uncomfortably long periods of time” phase of development.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could say that about the US too. I heard Denmark has separate lanes and traffic lights for cyclists. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia House, Hunt for Red October, Spy Who Came in from the Cold #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will be crushed if Zelensky dies. I think most people will be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the gloves this year, Olympic figure skaters? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever evangelicals say, they often mean the opposite. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard to see him as anything else. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel considers Palestinians a "demographic threat." Didn't Nazis consider Jews the same under Third Reich? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It buys peace of mind, which is everything #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe that's why it took big media awhile to pick up the story. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it me or are Twitter spaces not accessible via laptop?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard to fall asleep w a peaceful heart tonight. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, Aetna, I would not like to look at my most recent claim.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This sounds like fun. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# wait but she's saving brown women! Don't hate. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UN estimating 5 million Ukrainian refugees, per NPR just now. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I miss the Olympics. Streaming online not as fun as watching on TV w family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew a border collie who used to “herd” humans into the kitchen. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These look decent? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DANCING tonight. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s Friday night and I feel free as a bird. Dancing of course (how could you even ask), and ski trip starts Sunday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A witchhunt against one of our most vulnerable populations. GOP policy veers into sheer cruelty. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because Jews have never been victims of alleged racial/cultural superiority. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So did Native Americans. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminds me of those pics of cats on glass tables taken from underneath the table. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This feels like the beginning of the end. Masks have been the most visible part of the pandemic. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Belarusians not falling in line with what their dictator wants. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's their fault for not being Jewish. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would that it was this easy for Afghan and Syrian and African refugees. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# oh I thought "the gays" did that. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the point people are making is that’s it too risky to try finding out the hard way. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoa. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that the guy who tried to assassinated Hitler with a bomb under a table? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This thread makes the most sense of any assessment I’ve seen. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh gosh, sorry to hear that. Yeah, baffling to think about now but I guess the US did side with Saddam, from what little I know about it. And the war was shortly after the upheaval of the revolution, I believe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to my first event that required proof of vax and a negative test. People went without masks and it felt pretty ok.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That should be the default going forward. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students have no way of pushing back because they have no voice in Washington. Another example of the cruel unfairness of the student loan system. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# they're a different species, tbh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love these “like wordle,” but not, memes. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There’s no limit to how much worse things could get. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best part of the #HASHTAG# is watching it unfold over Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is the destination, not the journey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Heresy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we declare a moratorium on comparing just about anything to Nazis? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Heya Sarafina! If we cannot see the entire universe (or the edges if it has edges), how do we know there is no center?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. Contracting is the new normal. I wonder how much of this is employers not wanting to pay for health insurance. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooooooh! More attention on the gig [graft] economy. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sylvester has been a relentless lovebug all week. Relentless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will never not find it jarring to see slot machines in an airport.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cat update #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of the special people in my life happen to be Jewish and it's infuriating to think about their having to be afraid in ways I don't. Grossly unfair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will I even like any of my regular clothes once I start wearing them again, whenever that happens to be? It'd been so long.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sad and lonely. Also still wearing her braids?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cute emu video to brighten your day. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again I ask, how does Twitter know which toothpaste I use?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[War seems like a series of impossible decisions. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh my god I'm so sorry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not uncommon, Dr. Hellyer, as I'm sure you know. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe it’s not dead after all. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second dance event of the evening (stay tuned for tomorrow’s complaints about being up this late).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Which film was that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Some of the actors are from Baltimore. The writer said he referenced some Shakespeare even.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s about owning the language of the crisis. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think Putin needs to [further] invade Ukraine to get what he wants from the west. I think he knows we'll do almost anything to avoid war.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would have to happen for you to let go of your judgments?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's important for Zelensky to remain visible so he can control the narrative. Also has the effect of boosting Ukrainian morale. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This could get much worse very quickly. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrifying and worthy of mad respect. Like the captain going down with his ship. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It took a long time for me to give up arguing on Twitter, but I’m glad I did. It’s kind of like cutting off someone in traffic and then getting angry that they honked at you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmmmmm. In politically fraught situations it is hard to know who to believe. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is Cory's take on Manchin. I can see how he arrived at that conclusion but I'm not sure I agree completely. I think that Manchin's own political fortunes matter more to him than anything else. I can't imagine where else his intransigence is coming from. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hm Thursdays aren't a great night in SF. If your Friday frees up space 550 is great for salsa/bachata. they reopen on march 11, don't forget sf requires proof of vax for everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We should divide illegals into two lines: one for murderers, one for rapists." #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being out of shape is no fun but what is fun is getting back into shape! Get to watch my body change and evolve and get stronger each week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not sure Putin would abide by any boundary set by the west, and might deliberately test it. Not sure it's worth the risk of finding out the hard way. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn’t Olympic walking the funniest sport? It looks like wiggling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah this is my concern. A NFZ sounds good until you realize what it really means. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have CNN on in the background (not voluntarily) and what a contrast between it and Twitter for info on Ukraine. Can't believe we were once limited to television for info on critical situations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Her smile breaks my heart bc we know she was so unhappy. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm never going to get the difference between "who" and "whom." Resigning myself to my fate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I heard that the cost of her defense is $10 million?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Most of Jerusalem's Jews lived off donations collected overseas..." (1895) #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don’t know much about Russia or European politics or nuclear policy I just use my intuition and analytical thinking skills to try to figure out what sounds reasonable and what doesn’t.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. Fargo, 2. No Country, 3. O Brother. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There’s one girl who becomes prominent in later seasons who grew up in Baltimore and even did time in prison before joining the show. I love how real the dialect feels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia likely has a "kill list," per US intelligence. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never know how seriously to take the UN though. They're decent with humanitarian relief but horrible at preventing atrocities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They both were, in my book. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“#USER#: #HASHTAG# in a statement condemn killing of #HASHTAG# by #HASHTAG# border forces. #HASHTAG#” #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Who could have ever imagined we would be reading these words." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m full of anecdotes about life at Lake Tahoe, most of which are sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Livestream of UNSC emergency meeting on Ukraine. It's nauseating to see Russia officiate. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m flying tomorrow for the first time in two years. Wondering what kind of crazy anti-masking behavior to expect. Have to wake up at 4am and should probably not be out dancing tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad had a terrific Swedish Chef imitation. He could be very silly. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was so nice to be ANYWHERE ELSE for a view days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brain drain. Russia is losing the war in more ways than one. Or I should say that the Russian people are losing. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# also because our pres is secret Muslim from Kenya #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I highly recommend this Twitter space. It focuses on Ukrainian experts and is moderated by #USER#. 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is it not even 12pm already, can someone explain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really tired of not dancing. It’s a whole world. Wherever you have people dancing there is joy and exuberance and connection and celebration of life. It’s free and for everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Masao my dad was in leadership at Lockheed during the 60s and 70s working on guided missile systems. Any idea where I could learn more about his work? I know he worked on the Polaris project but did more beyond that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s also hard to know which predictions to believe. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin looks like one of the unhappiest people I've ever seen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I tweeted yesterday... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ll be curious what, if anything, would persuade Sinema to change her policies—collapse of institutional support? Decrease in donor money? Grassroots pressure from the left? It would show us who her actual constituents are. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to start pre-emptively listing them on my resume. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean Nazis are probably the purest example of evil we can easily think of, and are convenient for drawing analogies, but it probably dishonors their victims to do so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huh. NPR reporting that the second biggest risk factor for dying from covid (after age) is schizophrenia. Studies from multiple countries are showing these results. Some think there's an immune deficiency in people with schizophrenia!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Jim Cramer just doesn’t like poor people. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course Amazon raised the cost of Prime. Of course it did. We got Bezos'd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fond memories of dancing in the airport w dance friends while we waited for our flight to the Reno dance festival. Joy follows us everywhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gas almost $6/gallon in Palo Alto #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a dark and conflicted guy. Fascinating case study in psychopathology. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha! Here's the other side of the student loan debate (granted I haven't done any of my own research on this end). #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm putting as many dance festivals on my calendar as possible. Need the joy boost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agreed. His decades of experience are serving him well. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I swear half of "innovations" today come from engineers who just wanted a promotion. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrific interview regardless of how you feel about Anne's politics. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How does Twitter know which toothpaste I use? I don’t even buy it online]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now China is speaking. Opens with a fairly predictable "all parties concerned should exercise restraint." China will promote peace talks "in its own way." #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ha! It’s that “well, it already happened, so people should get over it” narrative. Nevermind the fact that the violence is ongoing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cis woman has hurt feelings #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There's no way he'd mention the biggest failure of his admin so far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He’s watching history come full circle. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brazil up. They affirm commitment to "territorial integrity of all member states" but don't mention Russia or Ukraine by name. Interesting. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks as if he's had bad plastic surgery. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California is envious. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[None of our invasions give Russia the right to do what it's doing. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# on1! only on2 i know of is Wednesday nights in SF.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cops w "anti-terrorism" written on body armor patrolling at Rhode Island ave metro stop. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think this is his way of saying he doesn't like homeless people. SF quite safe. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really enjoying this peculiar shoulder pain, which is getting worse, not better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I gave up on having just almonds for dinner and made my favorite lentils.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m not sure how helpful predictions are when we can hardly figure out what’s happening in the present.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting to hear Germany say that to someone ELSE. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn’t it just easier to pay people a living wage to start with rather than dealing w the “headache” of union organizing? I do not understand corporations’ calculus on this one. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is it not wine o'clock yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There will be cat tweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To say that Ukrainians ferociously insist that they will win would be an understatement. I think we all may have underestimated them. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder what Sylvester would think about a cat stroller. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking my life into my hands (literally?) and going to an outdoor dance event w two masks. Dancing in an N95 not feasible bc it's not breathable enough. I've had it with my self-imposed dance embargo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# especially if your president is a black Muslim from Kenya. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's bartending Twitter? I'll have a martini please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yes. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mom and I. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it shocking or not shocking that decades after MLK’s civil rights movement we still don’t have equal access to voting? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# forgot if i mentioned space 550--they reopen march 11 for salsa/bachata and usually have great turnout.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He has to maintain the facade of believing it will happen. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small scale is the only sustainable option. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Russia-Ukraine thing seems to be a bit of a Rorschach test, with everyone seeing exactly what they want to see (and on one agreeing on what is happening or is about to happen).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter narrative is "Russians really messed up, war going awfully for them," CNN narrative is "Ukrainians are outgunned and outmatched."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s nice to have a real orator in the senate. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Funny how the Islamic line "from God we came and to him we return" reminds me of the bible's line "ashes to ashes, dust to dust." They kind of mean the same thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UAE has a different representative speaking tonight. Other countries had mostly the same people speaking as last night. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wouldn't it be great if one of the unforeseen results of Russia's invasion would be greater dissent and activism inside Russia? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the new question is how far progressives can get nudging the party left, if at all. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are the odds they didn't test this technology on Palestinians before selling it to the world? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Number of people of color at Thanksgiving: one. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did he assume it would be different? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survived my first zouk class!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When will Russians ever get the benevolent, kind leader they deserve?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ghana unreservedly stands by the territorial integrity of Ukraine." #HASHTAG# Also underline concern for civilian well-being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP essentially opting out of participating in our political process. This isn't new, but it's becoming more obvious. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad used to quote someone about how "some people create history, others have it thrust upon them." #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>