<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He's already mentioned Mathis' crew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# All he speech writer needs to know is how to write laugh tracks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBC producer?  

But didn't #USER# try to tell us it was a freelancer?   

I'm sure Brian Williams will tell usnthe truth. 

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No words can make things better. 

Hang in there and remember the good times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Big Least?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And he's well on his way to doing it.  

He showed his lack of leadership when he allowed a false political issue to steal the All Star game from Atlanta. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Penn State is playing Villanova in football? 

Why? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A.  Men.  

And A.  Women.  

The ACLU is underestimating the resolve of Tennessee  Daddies and Grandfathers.  

We're ready for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Translation:  

"Because it's none of the American public's business what we are doing in the White House, now.  But it was when Donald Trump was the President because orange man bad." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chill time .......

#HASHTAG# @ Hilton Head Island Beach &amp; Tennis Resort, Inc. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Absolutely. And one of those young guys whom getting away from home isn't necessarily a bad thing. Just hate that UT slow played him like they did and really never showed him fair priority.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, #HASHTAG#- if Vogt is out for a while, don't play the Contreras game again. Bring Shea Langeliers up. He's ready and a better option both offensively and defensively.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best thing i have seen in this game so far?  

The  video from Keeneland being used in the outros.  

April can't get here soon enough. 

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just proof that star ratings and high school stats can be deceiving. We've all seen it many times over.  

And there is definitely such a thing as a "fit" for a specific offensive system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Madam Speaker is spending the House of Representatives time and taxpayer monies wisely.  #HASHTAG#  It's time for the games to end the House actually do business that matters to the American citizens and not the democrats agenda?  Pardon my language, but this shit has gotten old. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Harris is going to become a reality soon.  

The set up is just about completed. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They might start with actually learning how to count, just like the Big 10 needs to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 

Last night wasn't Soler's first time hitting leadoff.  He did so down the stretch in the regular season and in the NLDS, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents potentially sending their young folks to #USER#  is this who you want teaching them?  

Higher education is a complete cesspool these days.  Everywhere. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The GOP leadership needs to stand firm and show some backbone for a change.  Don't fold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's always sweet beating the Tarholes, especially beating them like a drum. The only downside is that Roy Williams is not still on the bench. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty much sums it up, except for the part about the local TV sports talking head blaming the fans again. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Jeez. I was feeling good until you reminded me that Will Smith would be closing. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That guy needs his ass kicked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back when SNL was actually a comedy show and not a politically leftist activism show. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But ...................

Orange man still bad. 

And no mean tweets. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# RIP Lance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get the damned deal done. Don't be greedy, #USER# , and don't be stupid #USER# and owners. Baseball doesn't need your infighting right now.  

And give Atlanta back the all star game you stole for purely partisan political reasons. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the Paul Harvey on the DC police officer leftist blue check marks are claiming was "murdered" on January 6.  

Just more lies from the left.  

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shocked that we haven't seen this reported in the MSM yet. #HASHTAG#  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You are completely clueless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not surprised that #USER# #USER# and #USER# showed up to do a live show today when others in that building didn't.  They are pros.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I've worked in the same press boxes with some great PA guys over the years. There are none better than is Robbie Howard.  The definition of class and professionalism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He's trying to figure out how to get part the future increase in revenues to UT in to his bank account as we post.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great example of his leadership ability ....... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduating a year early and starting college is one thing.  Quitting on your high school team in the middle of your senior season is quite another.  

Don't do that.  It says a lot about you, and what it says is not good. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You are a lifer, my friend. That's where you belong.  

I would love to be back in a booth on Friday nights again if my glaucoma weren't preventing me from doing it. You don't realize how much you miss it until it's gone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Don never disappoints.  

Recent photo of Don. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I'm sure somehow someway the #USER# Administration, congressional democrats, and their willing media allies will blame this on Donald Trump.  

But .......................

No more mean tweets. 

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My man Luke Jackson strikes out the side in the bottom of the 8th. 

Here's to you, Luke!  

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a good afternoon to watch some college baseball on TV with my youngest Grandbuddy,  Abel. 

#HASHTAG# @ Powell, Tennessee #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perzactly. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No.  There's no chance of voter fraud by Democrats in this cycle.  nnNone.  nn#HASHTAG# nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And yet another example of that civility the democrats are waring the GOP that we need.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# For me it's the Ric Flair theory - to be the best you have to beat the best.  Throwing in the towel isn't going to help the program get better.  

And the extra money will go a long way in helping to pay for the "non-revenue" sports that are still going to be there. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# May have been. Thought it was the side judge,  but I'm not positive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's happen to our mid range shooting game?  We've been so good at that under Barnes up until now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solid advice. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So did you follow the trial at all?  

Apparently not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# So official names trumps what you actually know as reality?   

Young lady, you need to grow some backbone. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Lots of local area representation, especially regions 2 and 3 5A.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# A Knox County coach pointing fingers at others about transfers?  

No offense intended, but really?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And Oak Ridge's Tee Higgins has had a monster game, too, and especially on this potential game winning drive.  

The Knoxville/Chattanooga region of the country showing out right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ha!  Saw it with my 7 year old grandson's team last Saturday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, I'm just asking:

Is it really a news story when a TV talking head picks a team that is all of a half point underdog (Fanduel right now) to win?  It's virtually a pickem game. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfortunately #USER# your short sighted corporate actions are hurting some good folks who own franchises. Your decisions are killing those who make it possible for you corporate types to flourish financially. 

That's just stupid woke business. 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yep.  May as well just let everybody in the playoffs so they can hang a playoff banner.  

Everybody gets a trophy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Great message to send young people about fulfilling commitments ...............

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Amazing how Donald Trump provoked the Iranians to start committing terrorist acts against America 37 years before he became the President. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Locking down government?  

Good for the truckers, and I think that's the idea, bu apparently the Premier Whateverheis isn't smart enough to figure that out. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those whining about others of us posting about Meat Loaf and seeing him during our lifetimes, instead of being a know it all asshole go to YouTube and watch some of his work.  He was one of the real talents of our generation.  

Don't like it, we don't really care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I don't want to be behind whoever it takes 19 minutes to get from Powell High School to Neyland Stadium. That's about a 9 mile drive - 11 minutes tops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I understand.  

But General Neyland's name hasn't been on it for 100 years, so as Neyland Stadium it's not 100 years old.  

Like I said, agree to disagree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nope, we don't, but some on both sides of the aisle won't accept that. 

And yesterday #USER# mentioned that RVZ &amp; Young "made up" before Ronnie died, and that's true.  But what Young said about Southerners still offended us. Ronnie may have forgiven, but Southerners haven't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You don't really understand much about sports judging by your work.  

PEDs aid in training, especially recovery time between workouts.  Figure skaters spend an incredible amount of time training.  PEDs can help speed that process up and allow more on ice time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What in the hell is wrong with people these days?  

Youth sports would be so much better if parents would just let their kids play and shut up and watch.  

Don't be a helicopter parent.  You aren't doing your kids any favors.  

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Somebody better conduct a welfare check on Jackson Mahomes ............]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the democrats want to shut the media out of covering the discussions?  I'm sure we'll hear this from tne main stream media. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They spearheaded the effort to raise the money to keep him and do tje facility improvements.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The Democrats using a crisis to play partisan politics?  No way. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thick cut pork chops on the grill now, Mahi Mahi and scallops will go on in a few minutes. 

#HASHTAG#

#HASHTAG#

#HASHTAG# @ Powell, Tennessee #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welltheydid ...............

But as #USER# told us, this isn't about who gets to vote, it's about who gets to COUNT the vote. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My "box" would include, in no particular order, Travis Tritt, Keith Whitley, George Strait, Lonestar, and Dwight Yoakum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, it's not, Dr Fauci. In fact not testing illegals is much more harmful. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# At this point, all that matters is surviving and getting 1 game closer to a world series title. Doesn't make a rats ass how you do it. 

Everything else is secondary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah.  Just like her husband playing hide the salami with Monica Lewinsky was nothing but a right wing conspiracy, according to her.  

Seems to be her "go to" excuse. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope the concessions stands stock plenty of these in the south end zone. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, yeah.  It's a "comfort" playlist Thursday morning for me, which only means one thing:

Cross Canadian Ragweed.  

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Don't think we are a high school team, but we are a long way from being a top 25 caliber team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there is one Justice on the SCOTUS who probably should avoid pointing the "partisanship" finger, it's Sotomayor.  She sat on the bench and flat out lied to back the Covid agenda of the left not two weeks ago. 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But the science ........... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And all with 2 out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And on left leaning Meet The Depressed, no less. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are a lot of people trending in this direction right now. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's not a Knoxville newspaper. It's just Useless A Today's Regional Edition. 6 pages of local, the rest regurgitated "politically progressive" propaganda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So #USER# and Rob Manfred - Give Atlanta back the all star game you stole from the people of the city with no legitimate reason. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second pick of the game for Murfreesboro alum Woodi Washington. He's  having a hell of a game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Madeline Rogereo (sp?) Should explain it all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No fake burger for me. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Maybe to some, but mostly he is making himself and his administration look stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# just done got pawnt by the intern. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Matt Jones isn't smart enough to understand that his is downgrading his own program a lot worse than he is putting down Tennessee.  But of course he'll never be accused of being very bright in the first place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's really serious, too. 

And I am sure she still insists that the "Nazis" at the Youngkin rally weren't actually democrat plants. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep. How many BLTs for the needy could 4 1/2 gallons of mayo dressed?  

Just wasteful. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Did somebody pick and eat a booger?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Hate to say it, but I find myself pretty much turning and going the other way from those who make it a point to point out their alleged Chrisianity these days.  

Call me cynical,  but that's where I am.  Been burned way too many times  by people flouting their Christian virtue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What about Muslim women's right not to be beaten and killed?  You are "negotiating" with the very group that does that.  

You are a hypocrite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If she means by having the military take out its top two leaders he has aligned himself, then yeah, she's correct. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Their funding isn't being stripped. More and more money has gone in to public education for decades now, and look where we are.  It's not a money problem.  It's an accountability problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's quite a reach right there. 

You really took the time to go 5 years back on my timeline to somehow find something you thought would "get" me?

Compete apples and oranges comparison, by the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been asking this for a while, now.  

Pretty much the only answer I get is ...........

But Trump! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Kiss our baby boomer asses.  We really don't care what those still living in their baby boomer parent's basements think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shocking. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So has the 3 second rule been taken out of college basketball?   

Must have been, because that Auburn post player just spent 7 seconds in the paint.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simple answer. Making sure the transfers make it to Hunter's off shore account, including the "Big Guy" cut. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will make the democrats and leftist media happy. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Building back better, you know ............ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just anotjer rules for thee but not for me Democrat politician. 

Move along. Nothing unusual to see here. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And it's a long way back to Vicksburg
Mississippi River is muddy and wide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Translation:  

Our lawyers told us we would lose our asses when he sued us, so we had no other choice but to throw somebody under the bus. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Zgree to disagree. What LSU did pr didn't do is irrelevant to what happened here. Pearl fired himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I want to believe that, but I don't trust any democrat right now.  

Not one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 states last 2 weeks, people were awesome to help with customer service everywhere we went. Been home less than 24 hours, go in to a #USER# and ask for something simple and am met with a "I can't" right of the bat. And that's happening way too often at that store.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maryville started 0-4 that year with some real adversity early on.  

The next week they beat Powell in OT at home, which started an 11 game win streak resulting in #USER# 1st state championship as a head coach at Maryville.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting take from Clay. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh my.  

Really bad visual. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good stuff there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No worries. The #USER# Administration sent a letter to the Taliban asking them nicely to help Americans get safely out of Afghanistan. nnI'm sure they will comply. nn#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is me. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You are all that's wrong with media these days.  Take your partisan hat off and put on an objective journalist hat for a minute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How utterly virtuous of you.  

Looking at your profile, I'm guessing he's also conservative.  

Pathetic look for you, by the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# At 63 I'm not sure what normal feels like. These days normal is waking up and breathing in the morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decided to get out and run some errands and grab some dinner.  With so many local eateries now closed on Monday we ended up at Chili's for the first time in about 5 years.  I think we now remember why it's been 5 years. 

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big.  Series.  Starts.  Tonight.  

Wheeler vs. Morton.  

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So much for it being the "People's House ...........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate the way flopping has become so prevalent in college basketball.  That's one of the issues that has made today's NBA game unwatchable. Here to see it filter down to college basketball.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough news.  Hurt was one of the best of his era. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fitting way for the Tennessee/Memphis series to end permanently, and then Knoxville TV sports talking heads blaming the fans.  

Arrogance and leftist media spew.  I know I am not the only one completely over it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I prefer my Gerd sautéed with garlic, peppers, and onions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, they do. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Be driving by there in October.  She'll get our business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And it's interesting that it happens when Covid numbers are dropping in a big way.   

Makes one go ............... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my!  Gnashing of teeth!  He's on their list!  

#HASHTAG# 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He showed his chicken shit self after our conversation last night and his trying to justify his mocking dead American Military.  

Badge of honor for me.  I did my job. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miller and Veera start school Monday, so we are getting as much of their pre school starting weelend bucket list accomplished  as possible. 

Scratch another item off.  

#HASHTAG# 

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another hypocrite democrat elected official?  

Shocking.  Just shocking. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lunch. @ Gus's World Famous Fried Chicken Knoxville TN #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Have a feeling that a lot of rot gut whiskey was consumed by UK fans late Saturday night.  They weren't happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that a ....................

White power hand signal?  

ALERT THE MEDIA IMMEDIATELY! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this group of Texas elected democrats are smiling about turning tail and running away from their duties?  

Yeah, says a lot about democrats these days. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a better block than any Longhorn lineman made on the football field all year.  

How do you not call that a foul? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a reminder:

A democrat President is bowing to the demands of terrorists, and a democrat congress is now putting not just our grandchildren in debt they can never recover from, but now our great grandchildren.  

But ...............

No mean tweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have to admit that the fact that they aren't playing on the actual field from the movie takes most of the luster off of this thing for me.  

Just saying. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep.  Great dogs and burgers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The targeting rule interpretation is completely out of control.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was entertaining as he always is. ZR never disappoints. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Slow down.  4 QBs played at Appy State this fall, and he wasn't one of them.  And he is a walk on at UT.  

Temper expectations.  He's not his father.  Let him enjoy college.  Very low likelihood that he'll ever play a meaningful down of football at UT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right.  Basing a platform on men using the women's bathroom and giving illegal immigrants more rights than legal citizens is perfectly sane.  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A blue state overinflating those numbers?   

Shocking. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting.  And true. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those of you who voted for this guy, you are stupid.  

But ....................

No more mean tweets.  

Hope it was worth it to you. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Shocking. 

No, not really. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Looks vaguely familiar ...............]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# - This is one of my happy places. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Looked it up - 2006 and 2007 seasons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hauls has it!  

And a double dose of a strong antibiotic normally gets rid of it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Debate?  I've proved that you don't know what you are talking about on several occasions in this "debate".  But by all means, continue to pat yourself on the back.  You really got one over on me.  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And we haven't seen any "British Open weather", either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The home plate umpire was absolutely brutal last night.  No consistency, no clue.  

It's time for #USER# to scrap the "good ole boy" system of assigning post season umpires and start assigning the better umpires. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, yeah. Austin Riley is a legit NL MVP candidate. 

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I like Republicans who actually help Republican Presidents win re-election, not those like you who work against their re-election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fully functional brain. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this really surprises anybody with a functioning brain? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# We hit the one in Fort Valley, GA on our way to Orlando a couple of weeks back &amp; the one in Daytona on our way from Orlando to Hilton Head the next week. 

Brisket tacos, Kolaches. Takes me back to Texas when I stop at one.  

Love me some Buc-ee's. 

My coffee vessel as I post. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looked like General Norman Schwarzkopf's troops running through Saddam Hussein's (alleged) Elite Guard. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saturday morning breakfast at our house with Verra and Lochlin. 

#HASHTAG# @ The Mynatt Abode Kitchen #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Awesome guy. Happy birthday Coach!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Says the guy who mocked dead soldiers on his Twitter feed. Stop being a hypocrite, Jimmy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Soto takes Will Smith deep in the T9 to tie it up i am burning every bit of #HASHTAG# gear i own and canceling my #USER# subscription.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great question. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Probably need to ask #USER# that question. She obviously is the authority on all things native American.  #HASHTAG# Still waiting for her to take the DNA test, by the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep.  

They apparently spend more time practicing bat flips and celebrations than on baseball fundamentals these days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She's busy drinking Vodka Martinis and eating $14 per pint ice cream at fundraisers, Congressman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Big fan of the 3 "major" service academies, plus the United States Coast Guard Academy,  too.  Support them 24/7/365, but want to win on the football field againt 2 of them 1 day per year.  

It takes a special young person answer that call.  Proud that my son was one of those.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Actually it does.  

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# RIP Danny Joe.  One of the great voices of Southern Rock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But that was a world premier video, you know ....... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just Penny's guys being Penny's guys, you know. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, yeah.  That's pretty much how it works, #USER# . You are accountable for your own words. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can't laugh at this you have absolutely zero sense of humor. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rules for thee but not for me on display again. 

Hypocrites.  All of them. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cher is the definition of a nut bag.  

No wonder Sonny sent her packing, may his soul rest in peace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anybody else find it interesting that the democrats supposedly don't trust "old white guys", yet the 2 odds on favorites to win their nomination next year are ..... drum roll please ...... 2 old white guys in Joe Biden and Bernie Sanders. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My much better half is having dinner with her cousin tonight,  so for me it's grilled chicken thighs tossed in Buffalo sauce. 

That's  ......

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Off the top rope for the pin right there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody saw this coming, did they?  #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah.  Absolutely pathetic on the part of school boards who are doing everything they can to deter the educational process right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shocking.  nn#HASHTAG# nnStill 10 short of the number of GOP senators they will need, assuming no democrats defect.  nnComplete waste of taxpayer money and time.  nnMove on and get to real legislative business, #USER# . #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, yeah. Some leftist idiot actually posted this on Facebook. And with a straight face. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Actually, he's been an Aggie heavy lean since he got to Powell back in the summer.  No surprise at all. 

And Walter and his brother both stand for the national anthem, by the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geez. Both Aaron Rogers and Russell Wilson are just awfuul today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two SEC teams playing for a Natty in Indianapolis. 

Just not natural.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Steven Ray Tickle.  

And I would support his nomination. He's much more qualified than Sotomayor, Kagen, Roberts, Breyer, and Kavanaugh, for sure. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new year brought in by some Waylon on Texas Red Dirt Radio is the way to go. 

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And getting a healthy Mike Soroka and RAjr back will certainly help the cause.  
Big question:  Assuming Freddie is re-signed, which I believe will get done in a fairly short time, which of the late acquisition outfielders do you try to keep?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Go ahead and run against either of them.  I'm sure your 23 followers will push you over the top.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ha!  My only play yesterday.  Went to bed down 6-0 and woke up seeing that it was a winner.  

Love those nice surprises.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And he also needs to be prosecuted for sending elderly with Covid back in to nursing homes.  That was not only irresponsible, but criminal, as well. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm expecting to be on his block list soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Crushed.  Just crushed.  

Virtue signaling is alive and well.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>