<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# WB women voted bit early for TMC and forfeited their right to earn free Rs.5000.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So what? The christianity that was in kerala was non-aggressive but new christianity post protugese/british arrival is invasive and harmful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Same people beg Modi to save them in Pakistan and Afghanistan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how Woke Western media in love with Islamists should have report terror attack on Jews in Texas. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think all this BulliBai and SulliDeal are done by Congressis and proxies so that muslim women who came in support of Modi after anti-Triple Talaq legislation move away from BJP and vote for Congress and proxies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just waiting for the day when Tikait brothers will join Azam Khan in jail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I agree but why did govt. give him Padam Bhushan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What do you expect from a man who was named Tunku by his parents? Even they did not want to waste time on him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good that you chose to quote Netaji. He was also against Islamic communalism that triggered Hindu communalism. Islamists always have first right to communalism. Others just react.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Besides this SP has given ticket to Taukeer Raza (rioter) who threatened Hindus with genocide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Gandhi can only be saved by bans and violence against truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Vinod Dua is part of my early political awakening when he and Pranoy Roy covered Indian elections in 1984. Later I realized that he had Bhakti towards Nehru-Gandhis but that doesn't mean that I have to hate him. I simply stopped watching him. RIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ola and Uber getting bad name for nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# UPA days were most dreadful.. Inflation was sky high..add to that scams..and on top of that weekly bombing of Indian cities. It was most horrible time for India.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The way it is going, radical Islam won't survive in next 25 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Basically calling their own Nabi violent. This Maulana should be punished for Blasphemy as per Islam.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And sticking to 6th century text literally is very progressive indeed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# China has enough money to buy morality of west and the east.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# first arrest all these people and send them to jails in UP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Goa is still free of Bangladeshis so you have no chance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Modi has class and Pidi journos &amp; their masters are crass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There is no hope for justice in Congress ruled states because Paltoo media keeps giving Congress ruled state govt. covering fire. The paltoo media's outrage is always selective.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# At the earliest she needs to be in Tihar for supporting extremist Islamists in their call for violence against Hindus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Mast joke maara. Pretty sure he will come back in BJP post 2022 election. Bina Malai ke roti nahi digest hoti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ukraine has never been pro-India. Just look at its record.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Actually for FB and Twitter, Hindus don't matter as India is the lone country that will raise issues of Hindus whereas issues of muslims are raised by 56 Islamic nations + wokes in all other nation backed by Islamists in those countries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lynching is bad but some religions actually support it save honor of religion and its prophet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Russia is now basically a junior ally of China and is tying down US and its allies in Ukraine so that China can have window to invade Taiwan and capture it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Didn't ur ancestors comes from Afghanistan, home of Taliban? Ab apne karma bhogo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# What if China gobbled up Pakistan like Tibet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I was banned again and again for 2 years in 1 month interval on FB. Someone in FB definitely had strong love for Islam and China.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No one should forget that approx. 95% of muslims living in current Indian borders voted for Muslim league and demand of Pakistan in 1946. BTW majority stayed back in India post partition. 100% unadulterated truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I always wonder why Nehru let go Kartarpur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# nnIslamists have made hindus refugees within India. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Muslims exploit caste divisions in Hinduism whereas muslims following same caste order remain united.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That terrorist who hoisted a flag on Lal Qila]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# IAMC spreads hatred against India and Hindus in US. It openly works with Pakistani associations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In few days NDTV will call it anti-muslim step and you will be doing a show to further that propaganda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Political question being asked to kids just to push same old anti-Modi agenda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Commies supported Islamists during Moplah riots. Then they supported partition. However Pakistan banned communism. These commies still have same old agenda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think we should not mimic Islamists. We are better off without so much of religion in our daily lives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# KSA moves away from Radical Islam and Indian Radical Islamists move away from KSA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Indian missionaries are hell bent on declaring Jesus a Hindu and Christianity a sect of Hinduism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Rare step by Congress govt. I hope Islamists will not destroy this memorial as they did in Mumbai.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Modi kept mum in WB. Now same script is being followed in Punjab.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Rajasthan and congress-opposition ruled states top the charts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peaceful Indian muslims declaring Jihad #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tikait has taken money from opposition to divide Hindus in western UP. He has been able to fool many Jats. Now it is up to common sense of Hindus to understand Puppet Tikait's game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indian journo taking words of NYT as word of God. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Audrey Truschke seems to be a Tucchi troll rather than a Professor. What a low life!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I understand their ideology in an out. For them we are worse Kafirs than Shia and Ahmediyyas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Get your facts right and not get fooled by Islamists embedded in media.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Odisha: MissionariesnDelhi: KhalistanisnPunjab: KhalistanisnJ&amp;K: IslamistsnnAll backed by Congress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So pakistan wants terrorist friendly govt. in India?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pakistanis are feared in Norway. Perfect place to talk about human rights of Islamists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Paltoo media ignores crimes of Congress all the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Islamists with the help of leftists control narrative all over the world US included.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sikh in 1947 knew exactly how to deal with Islamists in Punjab. Ye joota khaa kar hee sidhe hote hein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Big talk...nothing happens to Islamists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# These so called modern muslims have been highly radicalized due to Zahil Naik's venomous videos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# His two sentences are beyond me-
Jab Allah se deedar hoga - According to Islam Allah as no form
Allah se poochna - Aren't you suppose to talk to Allah thru Mohammad?

Yeh chal kya raha hai..Everyone has their own interpretation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mamta Bannerjee and Opposition ka khelo hobe in 2024.. Mamta can win election in WB thru imported voters but not across India

'Khela Hobe' in 2024; BJP will be defeated across India: Mamata Banerjee #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Modi think that if he plays by rules, he will be able to win support of leftists and Islamists. Not going to happen but in this attempt to woo opposite side, Modi will lose support of his core vote bank.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Music is haram in Islam. They are just following fundamentals of Islam.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How dare they? These people deserve death for murdering a person who stated truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extremist Maulana openly threatening TV anchor with violence. Western media will never notice this. #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Islamists have learnt the art of throwing terrorism allegation on everyone who points out blatant support for Islamic terrorism in their community. It is like a thief when caught starts calling others thieves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A country with 200 million muslims and close to 500,000 mosque is unsafe for muslims? There is something seriously wrong with people compiling this list.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well said. Both are client states of China]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 70 years of patronage deserves dog like loyalty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is the difference between Congress and BJP. 

Congress is always worried about its Pidis whereas BJP only cares about winning elections.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why no action against habitual fake news peddler like Zubair? Why is MHA sleeping?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Feel sad for Dimple that she is married to an absolute nut.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# BJP found another partner TMC for its project Congress Mukt Bharat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bal Thackrey must have kicked Raut ass really hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sonia and liberal? It's like saying Rahul Gandhi and Truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No one has yet claimed that it is Kaaba on moon. 😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Saba Naqvi is hardly a journalist but a full time propagandist. Ab to iski bakwaas stale ho gayi hai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This coming from a party who has destroyed India in its 60 years of rule.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wokes calling it an achievement

Michigan City Is First in the Nation to Be Led by All-Muslim Government: 'Historic Achievement' #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A huge insult to real doctors. Can not pardon Anand Rangnathan for this 😉😉😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gems from peace loving Islamist politicians #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The whole purpose behind forming MVA was to loot Maharashtra totally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This was just a dry run by extremists backed by Punjab Congress govt. #USER#  needs to take notice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Peshwas provided protection to Mughals and saved them from outsiders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Imperialists have their own laws and give shit to International laws. Shamelessness at its extreme #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is so strange that foreign corporates are worshipped in India but Indian corporates get only abuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, it was a successful dry run. Don't gloat. They succeeded. Modi-Shah need to act swiftly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Arfa Khanum is a propagandist fit to be ignored.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I always wonder why Buddhists did not react when Bamiyan Buddhas were destroyed and hail by most peacefuls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Also the one who puts his tail between the legs in pakistan-afghanistan and keeps mum on the plight of sikhs in these countries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terror has no religion but its face always looks like this #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Check how Islamists treat dalits in Pakistan and BD. They did not allow dalits to migrate to India because they didn't know who will clean their toilets. BTW read about Jogendranath Mandal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# For Rana Ayyub, lives of Indians never mattered. She is hardcore radical Islamists who has started hating Saudi Arabia because its ruler has decided to de-radicalize his country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Only muslims in Indian sub-continent follow strict casteism. You said you are going to free people from caste but promise made by Islamists was never kept.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Pure BS. It has been established that it came from China. Now the only question is whether it was intentional or not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Gandhi is a stone that has been tied to neck of every Indian by West. Get rid of Gandhi and you get rid of western imperialism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Islamists ne already "Islamophobia Islamophobia" rona shuru kar diya hai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Twitter has been shamelessly pro-violence by supporting communists and islamists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nehru sold Aksai-Chin to China shamelessly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This happens when laws is applied selectively. Aur Vishwas Jeeto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's a good thought but Dalai Lama himself has diluted his stand on Tibetan Independence. He will be happy to join Communist China as long as it allows Tibetans religious freedom. BTW then he will support Chinese stand on Aksai Chin and Arunachal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Now he can join Congress, local shop of Communist China]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Govt. office ki timepass bakchodi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Propagandist like Arfa, Ravish, Barkha etc. are as important as Yes-Man like Chaudhary, Devgan etc. in a messy democracy like India where people still suffer from acute inferiority complex.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# My Childhood playground had a ditch where water used to fill up in rainy season. Now on google, it shows some sadakchaap Dargah. Har jagah dargah kahan se aa jaati hein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# All three jokers surrounding Mamta are Islamic supremacists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In WB, intellectual bengali babus put files on the ground and sleep on the table.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why is this pig standing on his legs? Shame on Gujarat Police]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Let us know when you encounter an alien]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Western journalists suffer from visceral hatred for Indians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Churchill is guilty for causing Bengal famine which was basically a genocide. But these racist colonial superracists just gloss over this fact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I am asking how Jinnah was able to annex some princely states for Pakistan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is Pakistan calling BJP govt. anti-terrorists?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But when referring to Mao or Xi, it prefixes them with Chairman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# During Anti-CAA riots, most rioters were brought from Kerala into Delhi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Shiv Sena's reactions are usually petty. They deserve Congress-TMC-NCP as their partners.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This narrative is pushed very subtly thru bollywoodiya dialogues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is true face of Congress. All those who vote for this party are either naive or criminal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Add to that Corruption, Criminality, Communalism and Casteism. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I like few aspects of Gandhi but don't support his lot of irrational thoughts and behavior. As religion can not be imposed on anyone, please don't impose Gandhi on people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Manmohan was the most honest PM that we ever had except that under his watch India had biggest scam.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Sorry to say but Bengalis hide lot of things behind fake secularism and intellectualism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am secular when it comes to food. Sarvbhojan nirpeksha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why is Union govt. so soft on FB and Twitter that support violence in India?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We have seen Rahul Gandhi lying repeatedly. Now Congressis are following his footsteps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You are very desperate. It is clear from your tweet that as an IAS officer you worked more like political worker. Anyway keep your hate on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There was a video of some dumbos marching towards Israel on horseback in some Pakistani cities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You can't do anything to Arfa, Rana Ayyub etc. who spew fake news and hatred day in day out. You arrested Wasim Rizvi but did not touch douchebag Tauqir Raza.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Actually all self-respecting Shiv Sena workers should leave Shiv Sena that is dancing to the tunes of Pawar and Sonia. They should not commit the sin of betraying Bal Thackrey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Islam is religion of peace
Missionaries serve people
Nehru liked Children
Gandhi was apostle of peace
Rajiv Gandhi was Bharat Ratna
Sonia Gandhi served India
Rahul Gandhi is fit to be leader of Congress
Pappi can make a difference in UP
Owaisi is dignified]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maximum violence is committed by two abahamic religion followers on Jews and people from Dharmic faiths i.e. Hindus, Buddhists, Sikhs and eastern religions. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Raghuram Rajan has acted more like a Paltoo than professional.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Let us get away from British imperialism. Plain and simple]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And Kerala continues to contribute 50% of these cases daily...This is the Kerala Model that commie journos like Ravish were promoting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such lies. Facebook is being misused by Islamists who are dehumanizing non-muslims daily and getting them banned by biased FB.nnFacebook stalling report on human rights impact in India, allege whistleblowers #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Brahmins are not so innocent. There are many instances where they did not let even Kings do their duty. The son of Peshwa Baji Rao and Mastani was not accepted as Hindu and was raised as muslim. The Nawab of Banda Khandaan comes from same son Bahadur Shah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greatest day in the history of Indian Aviation. Finally Air India is in the hands of original owner. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Please raise the issue of 1971 Hindu genocide and why it continues in free Bangladesh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Congress is an expert in making chootiya of everyone. Two prime examples are Khalistanis and Islamists. Now they are trying to fool girls in UP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Urdu actually represents Indian muslims. Urdu has no grammar of its own so it uses Hindi grammar. Urdu borrowed words from Turkish, Persian, arabic to look foreign language.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I have many statements of Nehru praising China when it occupied Aksai Chin in 1959. Modi has not spoken but on LAC forces have been given full powers to respond.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No hate but disgust. Almost everyone who is corrupt and hypocrite. I hope Modi remains out of this list forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Surprised to see negative article on China in western media.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Since when NYT has become epitome of truth. It once praised Hitler and Nazis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Birthday wishes mein bhi politics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Islamist from Hyderabad India threatening Hindus with genocide. BTW this happened before so called bigot Hindus talked of reactionary violence.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When will Tibetan genocide be recognized? Do rights of Buddhists matter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This Salman Nizami was found to be supporting terrorism against India. Ye kab se fauji ke liye roney laga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Some people get sympathies for their parent and imposed as PM on country. This is nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# There is no doubt we lost to refugees who betrayed us. And then they converted locals and we have people like you now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yogi has task cut out for him post 2022 win. Take care of Tikaits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Owaisi's father was chamcha of Kasim Rizvi. When Kasim Rizvi was packed off to Pakistan, he handed over MIM to Owaisi's father. Why did Congress govts. allow parties like MIM and Muslim league exist after partition?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But who will block biggest pro-pakistani pro-chinese outlet Congress?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That is really one very big drawback of  atheism 😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This guy needs do do community service for 90 hours in Army Cantt sweeping roads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I hate taliban for what they did to minorities but wish them luck against Pakistan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One sadakchaap converted mullah was recently accusing Prince Salman of not being good muslim.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irrational views are Gandhis that are forced on Hindus by West and Islamists #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Then stop lecturing hindus if you have rejected hinduism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100% Truth. Muslim commies who supported Pakistan movement. Those who stayed back in India remained commies and those who migrated to Pakistan became ardent Islamists. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I see same from the sides of muslims. In fact their holy book asks them to hate non-believers. Go and look at videos of your hero Zakir Naik. These Hindus are just aping Islamists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hindus should learn from Islamists how to remain committed to ideology.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dozens of article on Haridwar Dharma Sansad but not one on Owaisi and Tauqir Raza.

Hindu extremists in India escalate rhetoric with calls to kill Muslims #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This Maulana should be shown that video non-stop 24/7 for at least 15 days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# For the first time, Mamta spoke truth and she is being called mad by Adhir Ranjan (Darbari).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# West has been denying genocide of Tibetan Buddhists for decades. Now they are not able to deny genocide of Muslims because life of buddhists is cheap as compared to muslims.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# UK is a third rate power and should just keep shut.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Priyanka Vadra feels emboldened because she knows that Modi will never send her husband to jail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Those from UP know that SP govt. is basically govt. of Goondas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Bal Thackrey created Shiv Sena. Uddhav turned that to Sonia Sena and inducted biggest chamchi of Sonia as VP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What about those who died because of blockade by so-called farmers? What about the Mazhabi Sikh guy who was tortured to death by Nihangs? This selective outrage is the reason that no one gets justice these days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In Islaaam, breaking idols and religious places of others is Sunnat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# US needs to take care of its own human rights first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Britain is anyway third rate power emasculated by Islamists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# China knows that Commies-Congress-Islamists are with it. They will amplify chinese propaganda in India.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't know why Modi is so desperate to get validation from left and Islamists. Bhaiyya ye kaunsa master stroke hai. When did left-congis-islamists ever honor RSS people?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pretty sure Arfa got job in Rajya Sabha TV because of Hamid Ansari.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I really feel bad for Amitabh Bachchan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But Sri Lankan Rajpaksha dynasty will only play in the lap of Xi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Manmohan destroyed dignity of Prime Minister's office so this should be expected from Congress Chief Minister.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Modi govt. expected its supporters to take care of road blockade during Shaheen Bagh and then farmer protest. Supporters have voted Modi for taking care of such issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I initially thought you were Twinkle Khanna. Couldn't believe my eyes. Then reality dawned on me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nehru called himself last British PM of India. Basically a lifelong loyal servant of Mountbatten.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Extreme appeasement of muslims and christians during UPA rule which resulted in large scale VISIBLE conversion to Christianity in Andhra Pradesh and many other states. Now Hindus are fed up and speaking up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did you report Owaisi, Taukeer and thousands of Islamists who threaten genocide of hindus on daily basis?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In last 1000 years, Hindus has perfected the art of appeasing violent invaders just to survive. They forget that we are no more under rule of invaders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# With this Bill, Kafirophobia has become approved behavior.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have to agree with this. Zakir Naik is also doing same but why is he getting massive support from Congress-Commies-Islamists?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I will say vote any party other than Congress. It is criminal to vote for Congress party that has become a tool in the hand of Pakistan and China.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A big slap on the face of commies-islamists. This is real hindutva.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Germany jails Islamic State member for life over role in Yazidi genocide #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Does this so-called BJP IT cell really exist? If it was then you will se consolidated narrative from them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sikhs during 1947 were not fools and chose India wisely. A Pakistani friend of mine told me that Pakistanis hate Sikhs more than Hindus because Sikhs killed lot of muslims during partition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Arfa means that Muslims are making India unsafe for Muslims by their acts. Read between the lines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Elon Musk seems to have all the qualities of a politician just like Mark Jokerberg and Jack Dorsey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There is an army of peaceful journalists backed by fiberal leftists woke journalists in media who prop each other up and live in an echo chamber.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Islamists in London have carved out Sharia zones. Have seen videos of them beating british girls wearing western dresses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# With the repeal of farm laws, SKM activists have ensure 50 more years of poverty for Indian farmers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congress provided full Security to Pakistan and its non-state players post 26/11 attack #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>