<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I can see how access to a free ID card if people wanted it to open up access to services etc would be a positive thing but everyone having it worries me how it can be abused by the state in the future. Particularly as our constitutional rights are even being tested by this lot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Or better yet give up trolling and find a better hobby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hi Tim Best practice is not to single out gender neutral or trans specific toilets as it were but to look at toilets to become "just toilets" with a sink a toilet walls and a door. These toilets then don't need any gendered signage and can be described as a toilet. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wear a mask yes and for you Matt stop wearing #USER# until you actually support all LGBT people and go on some actual training. Your continued rainbow washing shouldnt be ignored. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# thank you for the fantastic work you are doing too!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This &gt;&gt; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This government makes up the law as they go along.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the world getting scarier every hour that passes at the moment, #USER# and I have decided to have a break from the media and watch the wonderful #USER# on #USER#. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our NHS providers are calling No deal #HASHTAG# a crisis. Ironically a crisis being created and led by our Prime Minister Boris who is trying to force through a no deal Brexit putting all our futures at risk... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You are such a talented and experienced leader on inclusion we need to amplify each others voices more glad it went well :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have such top inclusive services at #USER# we like any NHS org have alot to do on inclusion but we have leaders like Richard at #USER# committed to making change happen now not on 5 or 10 years. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Love it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please share #HASHTAG# &gt;&gt;&gt; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Haha true :) but wish someone was advocating for it in mainstream politics. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Thanks Sabrina :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The impact of hate crimes on the mental health and wellbeing of the trans community is massive. Please consider donating to #USER# who are a trans and trans ally led health service who to many are a life saver. They do such great work #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...you have transformed my world into a sparkle filled ball pool full of love and positivity... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so day one man wearing the archbishop of canterbury's "dress" comes out to attack Gay people and oppose #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what you call a CASTLE.... #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are had a #HASHTAG# where one party's candidates are currently producing videos asking for forced Labour Camps making those deemed undesirable live in tents and work in fields. This is 2019 and the conservatives are bringing back scary politics in a big way :( &gt;&gt; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad to see the Islamophobia in response to Naz Shah's tweet. Reflective of the scale of Islamophobia across the UK. A massive issue that needs owned and tackled. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need some positive news in 2020 where are we with this research? #HASHTAG# &gt;&gt; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep that's the 1970s esk data they decided to include as advice on the LGB population in the UK. I've produced public sector Equality reports for countless organisations over last decade the conservative figure used is 5-7% reccomended by stonewall and everyone else. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You clearly havent looked at the contact form that goes with this advert. Take care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Adult slush yummy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When ever you see "clarifying statements" from well intentioned labour people on trans issues please tweet below back at them. We desperately need to get rid of conservatives &amp; vote for who ever will do that but there is no mistake Labour are playing politics with trans rights &gt;&gt; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yey friendly peeps :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Christmas and to celebrate her engagement to be married, The 7th Doctor #USER# had a special message for #USER#  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER# (Thank you so much Sylvester for helping make our Christmas special) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Watson mess..... thanks for nothing labour #HASHTAG# &gt;&gt; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi #USER# can you help us out here.... I mean the UK Government seemed pretty convinced this was a big issue or was it one of those memos you got from Boris on the culture war election strategy? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sod off. Your not facing daily abuse &amp; rising reactionary media attention to trans people with spike in hate crimes matching that attention on GRA reform. Your headline is definition of privilege &amp; trans people like me &amp; many worse off than me are suffering this is cruel. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see #USER# and his cabinet has released their own brand of sweets as part of their no deal brexit preparations to fund the billions they are wasting. Now on sale in Dover..... spotted by #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out our fantastic first Courageous Conversation on Trans Healthcare a partnership between #USER# &amp; #USER# hear what our medical schools can do to support trans &amp; non binary medical students &amp; teach more inclusive education #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hagrid is such a beautiful boy #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Carl you have my full respect and support for I know the tireless hours you put in for us all across the region. From outside institutions and from within we will continue to work together smashing the glass ceilings and barriers that hold our communities back. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic to have Josh Rivers leading powerful interview with Remi Arnold on intersections of race &amp; queer identity &amp; barriers across healthcare. Room silent with people focused on hearing authentic voices on reality of services #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like the #USER# may cause people to need to carry their birth certificate to use a bathroom or changing room in Britain. This country is becoming a dangerous place. Trans people's ID is not based on GRCs they simply give you new birth certificates #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mess of the #USER# approach to trans people in the UK. We need to stop the pathologising of our identities &amp; idea of specialist clinics and have GPs prescribe medication and make referrals to other interventions based on INFORMED CONSENT. The status quo harms trans people. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously doctors do you care about trans peoples dignity? ðŸ‘‡ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Nexstar 8se and zwo asi462mc camera :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please donate to #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# who support many trans &amp; non binary people do the same. Anti trans campaigners want trans people to have no lives please support your trans &amp; non binary friends to have the best lives they can #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politicians from all parties showing they are completely out of touch with people trying to live their lives and survive the pandemic. This will do nothing to stop rising cases and is simply adding misery onto peoples lives. It will harm peoples mental health truly awful #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now the talented Fiina Lord #USER# LGBTQ+ lead addressing us all about the support for LGBT equality across the organisation #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# has made clear the issues in the party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Thanks it's a world I'd like to live in. Lots more love reflection on the impact we have on others and where doors are not bolted closed for soo many. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# My first and biggest NHS role model Christine you continue to inspire me thank you the system misses you. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me think of Microagressions that may harm LGBT people.... maybe #USER# suggesting that transphobic website mumsnet should partner with #USER#? #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nazis weren't our UK government we are screwed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad that #HASHTAG# campaign is rainbow washing their awful calls to out every trans person at their GP &amp; when accessing healthcare. If this happens me &amp; many trans people will systematically avoid engaging in health system and will rapidly increase health inequalities #USER# &gt;&gt;&gt; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Congratulations and great tweet to see! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out in the glorious #HASHTAG# again with #USER# hike from Edale to Hope via Mam Tor and Castleton... fresh fab day for hiking #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yrs of gender theory &amp; turmoil for trans people sorted in 1 tweet surgery that gives you gender Winston Genius #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking cute #USER#... :) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Me too makes me so sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# We got a good challenge from one of advocates already that some staff cant wear lanyards or pins so we are looking at stickers small enough to go on name badges that are allowed :) vital thou there is something more than a lanyard a badge or simply signing up to something. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right here right now let's do it like the discovery channel....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Find our support networks, invest in safeguarding ourselves as best we can. Empower our allies with facts &amp; experiences to act. This transphobic govt will only be stopped by cis allies stepping up to them as there isnt enough trans people to do it &amp; not safe for us to do it too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# one min u claim its DC doing it to win votes then u bring how many LGBT people would vote for us into it #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The problem in prisons isnt the law it's the reality of how prisons are run, culture, resources and how polices are written in the centre to look nice and not on the ground considering needs of actual prisons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get tweeting peeps &gt;&gt; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It's free while its also launching mentoring pathways for all organisations in Greater Manchester the day will revolve around leadership development workshops that would usually cost Â£1000+ to arrange. Please encourage colleagues &amp; leaders across NHS third &amp; public sector to book]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I agree they offer a great service that seems much more holistic than the private care I was able to access when I came out compared to the gate keeping and yrs of wait the nhs has continued to offer the trans community.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The Electoral Reform Society seem to have a different view. But hey we dont listen to experts any more so what do they know ay. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Oh and apparently we are only allowed to leave for limited purposes... well except when we all want a nice waterside backdrop on your video. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#ãƒ¼19 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another first attempt last night here is the Cats Eye Nebula very small object but such a vivid green which is an amazing colour to see in the sky. Its 3200+ light years away. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# ðŸŒŒðŸªâ­ #HASHTAG# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry #USER# when your getting people to write on UK trans equality law please can you get people who have credibility in this area. This piece frames concept frames principles within a USA model &amp; concept of protected free speech which UK does not have #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# This is a good 7 years before #USER# became trans &amp; non binary inclusive and was giving any advice on trans issues, 11 years before quoted nhs guidance in article and over a decade before #USER# facts matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thank you. Yes and shared later :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America in 2019 black men being led in chains by a rope by white men on a horse.....#USER#'s Racist America. This isn't different political views and tame debate that's needed its fighting back against the tide of white supremacy &amp; fascism now at the heart of government #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've spent Samhain with my magical miracle the Goddess I share my light with and my protector from the Dark #USER#. We have spent today in wonder of the Warhammer fantasy universe playing disk wars &amp; watching #USER# lore on YouTube while snuggling on sofa #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eric Cartman "Respect My Authority" tweet from Boris.... sadly this guy isn't some random dude in crude animated tv show but the man in charge of nuclear weapons, our future economy and our rights. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# A good integrated Equality impact assessment process asks authors and planners to use the marginalised communities and risks to them as the starting point for decision. Log risks log potential benefits structure foundation around that. Why we need good EQIAs #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thank you for your tireless work and for speaking out so clearly and loudly in a see of toxicity. Only together will society be free from the hate that we have were through daily. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely Samina. There is nothing more unfair than treating equally those who are do not experience society equally or have access to the same oppourtunities and resources equally. #HASHTAG# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Sadly when we talk about the NHS too often what we mean is England when other parts of the UK have made often better progress than our London centric systems. We need to learn from great work other parts of country have led while recognising entire NHS still has further to go. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Hi Dan absolutely we have still much to fight for &amp; we are always stronger when we uplift each other &amp; do it together. Look forward to linking up on #HASHTAG# collaborative &amp; helping to grow the positive work &amp; energy that's already there across #USER# #HASHTAG# :) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's a breach of section 22 of gender recognition act and shouldn't be there as standard. If individual people want to consent then it's ok but it's actually more complex as any disclosure legally needs to potentially be informed consent if person has GRC which they cant know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sending hugs you always brighten up my Twitter feed x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After night of doing planetary #HASHTAG# with telescope looking at Neptune, Jupiter &amp; Saturn we decided to do visual astronomy with eye pieces sky was soo still. Silky smooth surface of moon &amp; detail seen visually on Jupiter. These pics through eye piece dont do justice #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking of sending pro #HASHTAG# military intervention article to loads of Russian media outlets im sure they will be so positive #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is our reality being Trans at the end of 2019. You are right Annie &gt;&gt; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing Cedric Diggory's memory justice by having my Helga #HASHTAG# cup broach and #HASHTAG# colours on while winning at the #USER# maze today with Ravenclaw ally #USER#. We conquered the Dark Lord, he who shall not be named who hid in the Maze Grotto! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Sam mentioned she was. Sad I wasnt able to join such a wonderful event. I'm sure much positive energy to recharge &amp; lift each other up (Ive needed it recently). But had prior #USER# request in Oldham with awesome leaders sharing sparkles. I'm backing #HASHTAG# thou! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thanks just random picture had to share giggle :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love #USER# so much. We survived being stranded on the other side of a river, a winter Gill scramble, 30km+ walking in a day, being soaking wet and a night hike. But as adventures go as long as we are together we can achieve anything #USER# you are BADASS! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another sparkly #HASHTAG# pic my talented #USER# took telescope out this week one night after id collapsed in bed after work. Dumbbell Nebula a planetary nebula  over 1300 light yrs away from earth. Taken with a #USER# sct 8" 2 min exposures x20 stacked #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have 75 new followers from USA ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸, and more last week. See #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One rule for them......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ‘‹ #USER# great joining you on air today you were super awesome and thank you for having my back over being misgendered before we went into the studio was appreciated! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Would be nice if people hired people who knew what they were doing for a change that sounds awful :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have a fab boss #USER# who nags me when she sees me working silly hours at night and when I'm on leave picking up emails etc. I repay the favour by doing exactly the same back pmsl!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How will they cope.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please dont assume everyone u are planning to sleep with is cisgender particularly if u dont want to sleep with a trans person &amp; are likely to be violent to us if ur sexual appetite gets carried away because your attracted too us. Me not wearing a badge is not a defence to murder #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have 58 new followers from UK., USA, Australia, and more last week. See #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That doesnt impact on objective reality around what bodies people may or may not have but accepts that the parameters to use whole classifications to describe multiple elements is rarely completely accurate or always helpful :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When will Greater Manchester #USER# be appointing a dedicated equality &amp; Inclusion SRO &amp; a well respurced dedicated equality, diversity &amp; Inclusion team? The NHS is resourcing inclusion expertise across the UK but local authorities still failing to invest in resource needed. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More of a mess from #USER# we need to "Reclaim" our pride we need a "Greater Manchester Pride" celebrating great work our regional prides &amp; #USER# do &amp; bringing communities together to co-create. How about it #USER# #USER# support? #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Exactly!!!! Being an equality professional is also tough explaining to people that just doing something can be worse than doing nothing. Research shows organisations that Equality initiatives arent linked to actual change perform worse than those that have no initiatives at all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to watch #HASHTAG# #USER# parade (refuse to pay to go into pride as pride is a protest and pride should be free) with my beautiful Goddess #USER# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And toasts to todays fox... #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Unfortunately we are scared about our future to the point its affecting our mental health its like the awful action of slowly boiling a frog in a pan of water. There comes a point where you need to stop your self being boiled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The ECHR judgement meant the UK had to introduce the GRA a case the Labour government fought against something often forgotten. Trans rights have always been delivered by our community and allies never by political parties.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Aww me too thanks for being as sparkly as ever :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bumped into the sparkly #USER# arriving. Look forward to making some sparkles again together very soon..... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Aww thank you and you too xx ðŸŽ„ðŸŽ…ðŸŽâ˜ƒï¸â›„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can correct your tweet for you. "Prime Minister Boris Johnson has told Sophy Ridge on Sunday that he lied but he is not sorry and will continue to push fake fakes as the media are happy to report it" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now estates check list includes inclusive toilets checking can they make the toilets in new builds inclusive for all rather than simply gender segregated. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Our little window display :) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Our identities are made up of multiple aspects that biology is neither binary nor responsible for the labels of sex. Humans defined sex as a classification &amp; has changed through history. Ultimately what matters is language any of us feels comfortable with &amp; labels that feel right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be clear as an ex student union vice president one of the early trans reps on #USER# LGBT Committee &amp; now a Head of Equality in public sector having had a career focused on wellbeing &amp; supporting people. I cant think of a uni that has let trans students down as much as Sussex #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.#USER# you criticise all church of england people so that makes your generic attack at catholics ok to? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Its complex multiple angles need looked at. Theres opportunities with new leaders &amp; cultures on an STP level to look at new local services if STPs can be convinced of how harmful current services are then leadership are able to negotiate ability to commission specialist service]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your definition of "respect" I suggest needs some research. When it comes to oppression minorities themselves define what is racist, what is homophobic &amp; what is transphobic. Suggest you ditch your privilege &amp; listen to trans people if you actually care. I doubt however you do. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Already connected they have done some fantastic work I agree and should be rightly amplified and shared. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi one big element your excluding is that due to 4-6+ yr waiting lists for NHS care for trans people &amp; many not being able to fund private care that many Trans people self medicate our health system is meant to have a harm reduction aim not punish people GP blood tests are vital #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ready for day 2 of Greater Manchester Race Equality Change Agents Programme. Today we are looking at recent history of focus on Race Equality in NHS &amp; growth of #USER# how WRES experts inspired the programme &amp; asking groups to present on social inequalities in our communities #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[apparently #USER# has blocked me... thats very engaging as she talks about feminists not engaging with #HASHTAG# people #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's not a local issue but a systemic organisation wide one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Launch event eventbrite is live. We would love to see leaders from tameside there #URL# Also for copies of application form to join RECAP FREE (targeted at managers &amp; staff not in EDI roles)  click on PAT link please share with your staff #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patriotic breakfast.... Britain has become a self parody. Are those of us eating pain au chocolat for breakfast letting the country down? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We have two different neuro diverse super powers and get to benefit from each others! We need to celebrate the super powers of neurodiverse people more! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 2019 our society is stuck in privilege those in power offer scraps to those who are different. We need to stop nicely nice slow progression &amp; demand change. This isnt just wrong its systematic abuse of citizen rights. If you're a public sector leader reading this WE MUST ACT #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this and with respect of what happened at #USER# today and #USER# allowing the trans community to feel attacked at pride it's time more people heeded these words #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# &gt;&gt;&gt; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone please support Home bargains #USER# and I will be doing more of our shopping from here. Great message to their staff and customers. Well done!! &gt;&gt; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NHS institutional Transphobia we need to tackle the dreadful access to trans specific care. No more words only actions &gt;&gt;&gt; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discussing Whiteness with our 1st #HASHTAG# cohort &amp; how important we have these conversations and the impact whiteness often has on experiences of spaces both learning and decision making. #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Police are stopping people in some areas tesco and waitrose have mandated it. Shows again in emergencies leaders act based on instinct and their privilege blinds them to impact and magnifies the inequalities of lack of representation across leadership roles. Awful to see]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a message for Jess you are not my ally as a trans person I dont bow down to spin and this is an example of a non apology political interview and finally I support sex workers and your continued support for policies that they stand against and will harm them is clear. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# In some regards the content of tweets are not focus of hearing it was judicial review of the actions of an individual police officer and of national guidance. Police never said behaviour was criminal or unlawful. However repulsive or regardless of judges views on trans as a topic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I agree 100% about your view on this Michael. We need to ignore these hate focused attention seekers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# and you claim its conservatives who stereotype! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Locking LGBT people up as criminals &amp; treating as mentally ill is something we can really be proud of in 20th century British history #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Looks very yummy!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to running a session for #USER# &amp; #USER# with Trans &amp; Non Binary people on #USER# Trans Residential this weekend on understanding Equality law &amp; Human Rights. It's so vital we educate &amp; empower our communities. Thanks #USER# for invite. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Still silence still no statement as usual trans inclusion is seen to some as just PR alot of nice words from Orgs but actions usually show the reality trans people left feeling excluded. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# "Nuanced policies" wasnt the tone of Emily's questioning or tweet. In fact its flatly hostile and factually incorrect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Having a strategy to identify existing self contained toilets that may have been gendered described as just toilets, convert existing shared communal toilet spaces into multiple self contained units which are better for everyone or identify space for new ones to be installed :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Thank you for helping make our first Christmas Engaged together extra special ðŸ’– #USER# was over the moon with such a special message from #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police are being a joke #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are at home trying to cope in a pandemic crisis...  they havent been given a funded career break to self develop. Getting through the next few months with wellbeing intact is number one priority not judging how best people cope. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We have just ordered more everyone coming to events in october will get one :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today we reflect on the 100s of trans people around world murdered for being themselves &amp; those who took their own life because they couldn't continue to face hate. All at a time in the UK when transphobic hate crimes are rising at an alarming rate. #URL# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recent right wing media stories attacking trans people accessing or working in health services just give me more evidence when visiting NHS trusts to deliver training in the uk of the hate &amp; discrimination trans staff &amp; patients experience adds to my training resources. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've heard this as excuse or as a why to not be too worried about whiteness of spaces we are in. While no space can ever be as fully diverse as society so we need to collect views outside room...equally no room should be so undiverse as to be obviously unbalanced #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why ever single development and learning space ive created around trans inclusively ensures gender is framed as something everyone should explore and understand not something only for trans peoole to think about. Powerful foundation to ensure allies can Centre their support. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is why we need the NHS to recruit trans people into decision making roles. So many of the rooms making decisions about things like this include no trans voices from a position of positional power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# This country is full of so many people who dont care about anyone else but their privilege selves. Message to minorities is fend for yourself we dont care. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Deeply depressing the only support we have access to is on the terms of those that don't want to centre trans people in the work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your girlfriend (#USER#) who lives over 200 miles away is nearly here and your getting to spend over a week together.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Your premise is wrong as you claimed approaches of those trying to reduce trans peoples access to sport is fair because they are not attempting to marginalise trans people as they aren't always being directly abusive. Ignoring reality their positions are based on marginalisation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Congratulations good luck for the future the civil service needs a lot of fab people right now to deal with the mess of this government :) (I know you couldn't possibly comment) best wishes tara :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sadly many want to use their powers to enforce the former and make up the later.....that's a very dangerous slope and exposes a culture in our police forces that's quite scary and needs to be tackled after covid19 circumstances are over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# We are everywhere giggle :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes when you realise your becoming a shield to hide their inequalities or that the organisation is fundamentally harming your wellbeing it's time to leave. I have done this earlier in my career not all NHS Trusts are created equally and not all that shines is good... #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disgusted to see mr gove appointed chief whip obviously positive discrimination to support older white men #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Night time approaches..... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ive continued to voice my fears that #USER# have real issues with minorities. Incidents like this visualise how nice words &amp; press releases are not changing decades of institutional racism &amp; discrimination. Utterly vile I urge #USER# to look at this as matter of urgency #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We both went on the wild mouse type minion esk theme looking Marble Madness coaster ride at #USER# always scary that your going to fly off the edges going round corners on these types of rides :) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for my queen....... #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Its time #USER# took the concerns seriously no other trust is allowed to throw their patients under a bus as directly in the media as they do. Hope #USER# takes the concerns raised by the trans community and allies seriously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope #USER# as Chair of the Commission you will listen to the concerns of the Trans &amp; Non Binary community in Greater Manchester. Im deeply disappointed to see this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic article from #USER# spot on in every way really resonated with how many trans people I talk to are feeling following #USER# &amp; defacto #USER# making clear her transphobic agenda. This article sums up reality of being trans in the UK #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The light has spoken #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yey thanks Kate we are excited to have a new colleague joining us. I'm lucky to lead a talented growing operational team in a wider awesome Inclusion function. :) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More examples of the police damaging any Trust the public have in policing right now. Going way beyond the law and making up powers while intimidating the public. Awful to hear this persons experience &gt;&gt; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bigots and privilege yes #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23 #USER# association chairman elected by a few people at a coffee morning talking about a mandate to the PM #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We get called an angry mob so some trans people decide to act like an angry mob.... #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So at weekend we had a newspaper threaten to out a celebrity for having HIV and now we have a BBC journalist trolling a father of a child in hospital because he also happens to support labour. The state of UK media in 2019 is disgusting. &gt;&gt; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My comments weren't statement on your meeting. Im glad you have a trans person involved in a LGBT group. My tweet was response to your implication that its ok to run LGBT groups without trans people as theyre hard to reach. Put simply we are not, but we are regularly not included]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi #USER# #USER#  way #USER# is being allowed to let this pan out &amp; #USER# &amp; #USER# responses are allowing gas lighting of trans peoples experiences &amp; reality by media. Services are TOO conservative yet we allowing transphobes to dictate agenda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Anyone that wants to can back our #USER# #HASHTAG# campaign asking to see more trans people promoted and supported into senior roles. We are doing work with senior leaders to advance work on this area :) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Loving the attention to detail! Its another wonderful creation thank you for brightening up our home with your talent and work looking forward to having some more bots on our walls :) I see many more Tarabot and Hattiebot adventures ahead too.... :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to London joining other NHS LGBTQ+ senior leaders part of #USER# #USER# networking dinner series. Looking fwd to interesting intro &amp; discussion led by #USER# #USER# hoping to hear Trans Day of remembrance mentioned which is tomorrow too #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had a Â£billion I wouldnt be spending hrs of my time on Twitter &amp; I wouldnt be creepily focussed on targeting a marginalised community to tell them they're wrong &amp; deserve less rights. People who spread #HASHTAG# just seem to be genuinely nasty they must just enjoy it #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Explained in a situation that could happen to a cisgender person what trans people experience from anti trans campaigners &gt;&gt;&gt; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It has]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I hear gay men telling trans people things are getting better and ignoring us when we say it's actually getting worse this tweet sums up the reality for queer/gnc people in uk right now. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who dislike the #HASHTAG# church who then decide to find a trans catholic and tweet them telling them church is transphobic #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for such positive feedback. We are one community &amp; we need to work together to deliver and measure change. Good intentions and delivering transactional projects however nice they look is not enough. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Racism in the police... we need to dismantle the structual racism and inequalities our major institutions still prop up. Stop the flashy statements and actually act to solve the problems that have been known about and shared for decades.  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to ensure country shutting down doesnt cement or make even worse inequalities #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stop trolling random trans women top tip #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we just agree #USER# in 2020 we shouldnt be having communal spaces for strangers changing/showering &amp; respect that giving everyone more privacy &amp; dignity is better for everyone. The focus on genitals seems a British parody. Plus Equality Act debated all this a decade ago #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My week on Twitter ðŸŽ‰: 488 Mentions, 69.2K Mention Reach, 2.06K Likes, 504 Retweets, 99 New Followers. See yours with #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We are launching our new LGBT Advocate Programme involving half day induction, annual attendance at any one of our LGBT topic seminars,  PDP goal shared with EDI team &amp; measured, volunteered for an Equality voluntary role. Dates last week in December &amp; across Jan at each Care org]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it me or do the Pro Trump Pro Brexit Pro being a bigot Transphobic trolls on here get weirder and weirder? #USER#? &gt;&gt; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Or some of these amazing people #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# all worth a follow all inspiring in their own right :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Well Charizard and Aerodactyl wanted to say hi too. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Im more &amp; more coming to belief one of the pillars of institutional discrimination is hiding of accountability for prejudice behind Rose tinted views that behaviours are just ignorance or misunderstanding. Historically we only tackle most extreme behaviour we need a lot lower bar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I do think allies have a responsibility to consider why people might be upset around something they are associated with. I also think we should explain that if we can rather than people just seeing upset. Which was what I was attempting to do. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And it's not new money so it's not 10% as its money NHS Trusts have saved themselves not money from mythical brexit money tree.... all lies from Boris but spun to rely on peoples ignorance of issues to make him look good. Worst kind of politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #HASHTAG# season has begun here in our house.... #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of public sector organisations and police forces are doing fantastic work at reaching out identifying the challenges they still have &amp; working with trans communities to make things better see #USER# work of #USER# inclusion of trans leaders like #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Attaching either a dslr camera or an astro camera like one made by zwo to telescope is first step... then if a dslr taking lots of still frames repeatedly you then use programme to stack best %. Or astro camera record short film programme turns that into frames &amp; stacks image.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've owned lots of mistakes I've made. I hope I've learned from them &amp; continue to do so. However those I claim to have learnt from i didnt wait until I was running to be a major leader to declare. Top tip if you want to be believed own your mistakes in real life not for a camera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love of my life my beautiful #USER# xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It's been great to share an hour with so many inspirational women and allies. We have so many wonderful role models to celebrate lets keep working to rise together and transform our NHS. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Stronger when we work together :)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>