<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[He's an All-American: #USER#'s Hebbeker earns 2nd team honors from #USER# #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A great book fir so many reasons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh, come on! We really, really love to dump on teams when they're down!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Callens drills a shot to the upper part of the net and NYCFC wins the MLS Cup! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EARLY ROAD WARRIORS: Red Bulls II open with 2 away matches for the 1st time #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations! Well deserved. It was an excellent story #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AND THE WINNERS ARE: United Soccer Coaches announce media contest awards #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you were wondering why Collin did not start, it's because #HASHTAG# rules state opposing teams can't have bald center backs #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two for the pros: #USER# products Johnson, Ritaccio selected in #HASHTAG# #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THEY’LL BE BACK: NYCFC signs Heber, Acevedo, Zelalem for 2022 and beyond #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PULISIC UPDATE: USMNT standout won’t start vs. Mexico, but he will play #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I heard rumors they are bringing in FIFA officials to help rig today's #HASHTAG# draw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Northern exposure: #HASHTAG# to host next 2 #HASHTAG# in Columbus, Minnesota #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#2022]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW ENDOWMENT: United Coaches unveil Dan Woog Staples High School/LGBTQ Fund #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five minutes of stoppage time in extratime #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STILL DEALING WITH COVID: USMNT is taking precautions, but Berhalter has a Plan B (alternates), just in case it spreads #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I was thinking the same thing. Since both teams are entering in the second round, a meeting would be likely later on, assuming they both won.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New addition: #USER# acquires Kristie Mewis from #USER# #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THEY’RE THE REAL THING: Wood’s late goal lifts RSL to another playoff upset, downing KC #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2' -- Excellent cross by Castellanos, which sails out of bounds on the left side #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# ##HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still dealing with #HASHTAG#: #HASHTAG# is taking precautions, but Berhalter has a Plan B (alternates), just in case it spreads  #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[REMEMBERING LUIS: Former Lancers players Sarachan, Cupello reminisce about late assistant coach Dabo #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# National story No. 9: #USER# is born, will compete as a D3 Pro League in 2022 #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah, I notice another filled stadium for a pro soccer game at RBA #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THE DOOR IS CLOSING: 6 teams reach Open Cup, 10 sides will try to qualify in December #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting some experience: 5 uncapped players on #HASHTAG# for Australia trip #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KEEPING A COMMITMENT: Clary, Yawn are ready for MLS Cup No. 26 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Updated story with more details: Eight is more than enough: #USER# romps to 8-2 win over Penn State in #USER# 2nd round #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FOCUSED ON ONLY ONE THING: Deila plans to use starters vs. Santos, worry about Sunday later #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Offside Remarks: A special #HASHTAG# to the most beautiful game  #URL# #HASHTAG#sDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OFFSIDE REMARKS: 20 local personalities to watch in 2022 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are all the fans at Red Bull Arena? Oh, sorry, old habits die hard #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# (Day 26): Years later, #USER# counts his blessings, recounts how he survived WTC bombing (2014)  #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Please do! (I didn't want to dump on you because your heart was in the right place)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IN TWO MONTHS: Concacaf Nations League draw set for April 4 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning to #HASHTAG# fans: Watch #USER#'s game-winning goal at your own discretion #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HIS FIRST TEST: ManU interim coach Rangnick makes debut vs. Norwich City on NBC Saturday #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Pulisic kid looks pretty good. Where has the US been hiding him? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NO TOUGH SANCTIONS: FIFA: Russia can’t play at home and will be known as Football Union of Russia #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone loves Raymon: #USER# to honor ex-#HASHTAG# Gaddis with Yeagley Award #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# take 1-0 lead in first inning over #HASHTAG#. Hmm. That should be enough today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BOXING DAY MATINEE IDOL: NBC will show Pulisic, Chelsea vs. Aston Villa match Sunday #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PLENTY OF SOCCER TO WATCH: MLS on ABC, ESPN, ESPN+ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1989 GAME STORY: Caligiuri hits shot that sends America through #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Updated story with #HASHTAG# statement about #USER# advisory about travel to Canada with #HASHTAG# game between #HASHTAG# and #HASHTAG# on Jan. 30 #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FAME FOR FOUR: Monmouth Ocean Soccer to hold Hall inductions #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been at Estadio Nacional in Costa Rica and it can be an intimidating place for American teams. Without anyone there tonight, it might give the visitors an advantage #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYCFC leads off first round: Castellanos fires it into lower left corner 1-0 #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interim no longer: #USER# names #USER#  GM, Lee assistant GM   #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This just in: FIFA lookiing into all the goals the #HASHTAG# has scored since1985, making sure none are offside. They might have to give back winners medals #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STILL KICKING AROUND (2020 repost): Ortiz to be inducted into Lancers Wall of Fame #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THE ART OF PICKING A GOALKEEPER: Berhalter explains why he selected Steffen to backstop USMNT in WCQ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The graduate (student): Former #USER#'s  Couzis to play for #USER# this fall   #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#WSoccer #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weah to go Tim!!! (sorry about that folks!) #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS LOSS HAD A SILVER LINING: USWNT loses an extratime thriller to Norway in 2000 Olympic final #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# legend #USER# starts a #USER# page for her horse rescue and outreach #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8' -- Glad to see #HASHTAG# hasn't missed a beat from the KC loss ( ) #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COAST-TO-COAST: Red Bulls to train in Florida, California #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man, Osorio is strict. Chicharito misses a shot and he is pulled #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HONORING THE BEST: Here are the USL League One all-star teams #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# signs Venezuelan teen; eligible to play on March 22 #URL# #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Offside Remarks: A writer remembers his first ‘cap’ so many years ago and why he savors every #HASHTAG# game he covers #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And a pretty damn good player in his prime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book review: Be All In, by Christie Pearce Rampone and Dr. Kristine Keane   #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BETTER LATE THAN NEVER: 2015, 2019 USWNT teams to receive world championship rings #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BEGINNERS SKILL: Rodman named NWSL rookie of the year #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I heard they are having a contest that if you guess all of the starting times exactly for one weekend, you win a $1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's good to see a packed Red Bull Arena again #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It has been an entertaining affair. Here's hoping it continues in the 2nd half #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am heart-broken for the 5 #HASHTAG# players that were not selected to the #HASHTAG# Fan XI for the all-star game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHY THEY’RE NOT THERE: Berhalter explains absence of Brooks, Reyna, Busio, Ream from USMNT for WCQ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heard a rumor that the assistant ref who called offside four times on the USA in the 1st half pulled a muscle in her arm she raised it so much #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abramovich selling #HASHTAG#; reportedly values #HASHTAG# club at $4B #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're no angels: #USER# fines #USER# $40K for tampering with #USER#'s #USER# #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6' 0-0 Red Bulls are pretty selfish, I think, not allowing United get the ball at all #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THEY WANT HIM: Red Bulls exercised option to purchase Coronel’s contract #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you were wondering, #HASHTAG# is on the bench for today's #HASHTAG# match    #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fame for four: Monmouth Ocean Soccer to hold Hall inductions Thursday #URL# #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TRAINING, BUT NO GAME: 25 players called into USWNT camp #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attention all #HASHTAG# fans who think World Cup qualifying in #HASHTAG# should be a breeze. Watch this video from former #USER# international Julian de Guzman, who puts it into proper perspective #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CATCHING THE WAVE: San Diego names its NWSL expansion team #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT’S OFFICIAL: Gonzalez named USMNT assistant coach #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Truly outstanding bids:' #USER# completes inspections of  #HASHTAG# venue candidates in USA, Mexico, Canada #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's that? Gregg Berhalter has been named #HASHTAG# coach? Wow! Did not see that coming!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DOUBLE HONORS: Espinoza, LaBonta named United Coaches Honorary All-Americans #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# down 0-3 but teams can come back. Didn't another NY team get four big ones at once Saturday night (Didi's grand slam)? Oh, never mind, that was another sport. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MEET THE PREZ: Knauf elected CDYSL president #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Herdman has done a great job with the best generation of players Canada has had since the mid-1980's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a great defensive performance by DCU. They have actually kept a team from scoring in the opening 8' #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet 17: #USER# selects #USER# F Oluwaseyi in 1st round of #HASHTAG# #URL#  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[City Hall celebration: #USER# players to be honored, get keys to the city on Tuesday #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Playoffs #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Hall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent TV transmission on ESPN tonight. .... Seriously, just wondering if we lose the feed at some time #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An interesting sight in the 58th minute: Jamaica's Damion Lowe came to sideline to have his left knee taped up and USA head coach Gregg Berhalter came up to him and apparently gave the Reggae Boyz a fist bump and encouragement #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Canada: #HASHTAG# can’t play in #HASHTAG# due to vaccination issue   #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11' -- Wow! This is rare! Felipe getting talked to by the ref #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# names Rambal its boys competitive coach of the year #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At another #HASHTAG#. I feel privileged to cover a championship game, whether it is youth, high school, college, pro or international. I remember my father saying to find something that I enjoyed. Glad I listened to him. Still enjoy writing after all these years #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah, while they run the world's best players into the ground]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facts and figures about #HASHTAG# call-ups for its January camp #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MORE ACCOLADES: U.S. Soccer honors disability, beach and futsal players of the year #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess it was a good World Cup if you liked goals, entertaining soccer, dramatic moments, twists and turns, controversy and some VAR moments thrown in. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buchanan puts it away at the back post for knot things up almost at the death. Wow! What a game! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GETTING THE RIGHT PITCH: When Plan A didn’t work out, RNYFC had a back-up one #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guest column from #USER# director of coaching #USER#: Breaking a myth and growing the game #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A NEW HOME FOR THE ‘MAYOR:’ LAFC names USMNT, Hannover great Cherundolo as its new coach #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# suffers possible hamstring strain in #HASHTAG# loss to #HASHTAG# #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MUTED RECEPTION: When the USWNT returned home as world champions #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THEY’RE HOT TICKETS: FIFA says 17 million requests received for World Cup #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OH, BROTHER: As the baby of the family, Dylan Nealis soaked up so much battling his older siblings in the backyard #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OFFSIDE REMARKS: Four WCQ scenarios for the USMNT in the winter window #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spurring interest: Reports: #HASHTAG# places offer for #USER#, #HASHTAG# like Sands  #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# hits the road, #USER# hosts in 1st round of #USER# #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From interim to permanent: #USER# name Ward head coach #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[INTO THE DEEP END: Andonovski: ‘Very, very quick into the game, we’ll find out who’s cut out for this and who’s not’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYCFC STADIUM UPDATE:  Garber: ‘I’m convinced that NYCFC would have sold out Yankee Stadium’ for MLS Cup but no news #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One last thing, Ream has scored 4 goals for his club teams during his long career. He has one for the #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's staying, who's leaving: #USER# makes roster decisions #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In triplicate: #USER# rolls to 3-0 win in #USER# D1 tournament #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BACK HOME: Former Lancer Ortiz to coach Philadelphia in MASL 3rd division #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scoring drought has now reach six minutes. What is wrong with Abby?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very, very, very unofficial ruling pending from MLS: League considering giving Ben Sweat an assist on Rodriguez' 2nd goal because his errant backpass was so spot on #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've heard rumors that FIFA is checking on Hurst's goal that might not have gone over the line in the 1966 World Cup. Heard they will bring the players back to Wembley to finish the game from that time on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BETTER LATE THAN NEVER: USMNT players welcome VAR in WCQ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BLACK HISTORY MONTH (DAY 4): Ex-Cosmos player, Trinidad national coach Everald Cummings experienced racism first-hand with Chiefs in 1968 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're welcome. Fans might not always get the answer they are seeking, but it must be asked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USWNT NOTEBOOK: USA’s concern: Trying to stop the unpredictable Kerr #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[28' 2-0 -- I'm a little new at this. Has France qualified for the knockout round yet? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yikes! It's a good thing I married a book lover. We have more books than you can shake a stick at.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ENGLAND BOUND: Armas reportedly will join Man United as an assistant coach #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asking for a friend: Was there a lot of cheering going on New Jersey when Mora scored the equalizer? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NATIONAL STORY NO. 4: USMNT pulls off a rare hat-trick win vs. Mexico #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hey, I understand where you are coming from. Fans should be given an opportunity to root on their team as close to home as possible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SHOWCASING THEIR TALENTS: #HASHTAG# event will take place at #USER# Men’s #HASHTAG# #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[INTO THE FINAL: Vowinkel’s brace paces Hofstra in CAA semis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scholars and athletes:  #USER#'s Littleboy, Suttner named to Scholar All-America third team  #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hmmm. Is that his bonus when #HASHTAG# gets a clean sheet? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOME INTERESTING INFO: About the USMNT for its game vs. Bosnia #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's why I wrote the headline as I did, as a big warning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# meet No. 10 Saint Louis in #USER# 2nd round Sunday #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YOU CAN GO HOME AGAIN (2004): Arena revisits the past, has USMNT team train at his youth soccer field #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone please wake me up for the 2nd half. I don't want to miss the scintillating action. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW ADDITION: NJ Youth Soccer adds United Nations Soccer School as a member #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holden just said he hadn't seen much from Altidore and Wood. That's funny because I didn't think they were on the field #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I heard the headline writer got a promotion. Wow! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SHARKS VS. TERAPINS: LIU to meet Maryland in NCAA D-1 first round #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell me if I am off base, but I don't recall a #HASHTAG# player who could make something out of nothing like Macario did tonight on her 2nd goal. It was magic. How many players would have attempted such a shot and have the ability to finish it so adroitly. Wow! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And you can quote them: Listen to what Berhalter and Weah said after #HASHTAG#'s draw at Jamaica #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope no one in the 2nd tier got hurt to Mitrita's wayward free kick #HASHTAG#  #HASHTAG#  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#isBack  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No. 8 local story of the year: #USER# reach 2nd round of the #USER# D-1 tournament #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations #USER# for pulling Bill's Books right in the middle of the segment for commercials. Neither announcer said what happened or made an apology. Wow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# player status report for their season opener Saturday: OUT: Andrés Reyes - Foot OUT: Wiki Carmona - Foot OUT: Luquinhas - Visa OUT: Tom Edwards - Visa #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a Red Bulls takeaway at midfielder, Lewis Morgan strikes for his 1st goal with his new team from atop the box #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#vTOR #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I call him K-Rod because he has struck out so much, especially in these playoffs #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# From the camera angles they have shown, it seems to be less than 1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this Starting XI. Let's see how they finish tonight #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's happened before: When a future soccer standout and his family left #HASHTAG# many years ago #URL# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#RussianWar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# take #USER#'s Lucy Shepherd as the 24th overall pick in #USER# draft #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THREE BIG HONORS: CAA fetes Hofstra’s O’Malley (defensive), Tatafu (rookie) and Nuttall (coach) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End of the line: #USER# eliminated from #USER# D-I tournament #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walker Zimmerman in the box gives the hosts some breathing room off another Acosta free kick #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Offside Remarks: It was one crazy night in Marseille for #USER#'s Esse Baharmast and an American journalist at France ’98 #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Sargent's 1st two #HASHTAG# goals for #USER# #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not trying to put any extra pressure on him, but Alexandru Mitrita's scoreless streak has reached three minutes #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#isBack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice goal by #HASHTAG#'s and #HASHTAG#'s No. 10. Pulisic's 3rd of the season for his club #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP, Pino: Former #USER#, #HASHTAG# defender Wilson dies #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH JORDAN SCORE: 3 out of 4 Pefok’s goals #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long Island Soccer Player Hall of Fame ceremonies set for Feb. 26 #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Soccer #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT IT MEANS: NYCFC players, Deila savor their accomplishment #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOOKING BACK: At the four Red Bulls draft picks #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FOR MERITORIOUS SERVICE: United Coaches foundation honors ex-William and Mary coach Albert #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SO MANY TO PICK FROM: ABC, ESPN2, ESPN+ to show 49 WCQ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Author website unveiling for #USER# book, Alive and Kicking #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're scholars, too: Record 3 #USER# named Academic All-Americans #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HONORING ENRICO: Romano elected to ENY Soccer Hall of Fame #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK, its time to whine as we Americans can do so well. So why hasn't Pulisic scored yet? He's been in the game for several minutes. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GUEST COLUMN: United Coaches CEO says convention will be held with attendees’ health, safety in mind #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# teammates will clash: #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# to meet in #USER#'s Round of 16 next year #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all you old-time #USER# and #USER# fans out there, I I took one look at the BMO Field and I had flashbacks to the condition of Holleder Stadium in Rochester for so many years. Franz Beckenbauer called Holleder "a nice place to grow potatoes." #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#vTOR #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# 3 pm kickoff seemed like a good idea to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Video of #USER#'s City Hall celebration #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Cup #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# (Day 21):  Ready to cast this own shadow: #HASHTAG# embraces being the son of a former soccer great, which inspires him (2018) #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are possible 2nd-round #USER# match-ups for NY/NJ area teams #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adding on: #USER# sign forward Mullings to #USER# contract #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THE GRAND SLAM: Pefok tallies 4 goals in Young Boys win #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grand slam: Pefok scores four for #HASHTAG# #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My take on the #HASHTAG#'s win over Bosnia: This group of players need to go to finishing school #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Focused on only one thing: Deila plans to start regulars vs. Santos, worry about Sunday's #HASHTAG# opener later #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent defense by Nashville to deny Red Bulls from scoring 35 seconds into the 2nd half #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking to the new year: Berhalter: "It's clearly unfinished business" #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THE STOPPER: Seattle’s Frei wins MLS save of the year #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘TRULY OUTSTANDING BIDS:’ FIFA concludes venue inspection for 2026 World Cup #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ANOTHER SIGNING: Red Bulls II add GK Chan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THE FINAL TWO: U.S. Soccer confirms 2 potential candidates for president #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rather disappointing showing by the USA in the 1st half. Give El Salvador credit. Playing as though the cold isn't affecting them. Bottling up McKennie and Musah in the midfield #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A HELPING HAND: Fundraiser page started for long-time youth coach Doug Lyn #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They game for the Gamecocks: #USER# to meet South Carolina in #USER# D-I 2nd round #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dates are set: 2023 #HASHTAG# will be played July 20-Aug. 20 #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NOTHING DOING: USWNT play Czechs to scoreless draw #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully, they're not going to use the same company as the Silverdome #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This border clash could heat up: #HASHTAG# aims to give #USER# the cold shoulder and grab #HASHTAG# lead #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>