<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Well you need to flip the asset &amp; add the Guerilla logo....now it's critic-proof! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sony improved nothing, they simply inherited it.
Had they not come along their big name games would have been made anyway under a different banner.
They should never have entered the market as a SNES addon! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They have to face facts, the "Dorian Grey" scenario where both the console and Gran Turismo's fortunes were linked and having the biggest car roster maintained that beauty...wore off when Forza Motorsport smashed that portrait!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Mental gymnastics are a lot easier with a disposable account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They showed us what the Saints look like now.
I gasped, they were so bad! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# DDS files I work with can be added to BA2 archives so just like zip archives you save a little more, but to be honest it's minimal when using already tight files. If they are BC7...sure...crunches down hard and you save so much space...but they occupy so much VRAM when used. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the oldest CD I own.
#USER# "New Adventures In Hi-Fi" 1996, bought it the day in was released.
Used it as a master to create MP3s, then WMAs, then AACs on my phone as I commuted.
It's condition is perfect to this day, and has survived three new "CD killer" formats. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It got so stupid, discs were being sold with a little "Playstation 2 compatible" patches on the back of the cover. PR masturbation for sure...but having "compatible" discs implied there were discs that werent...so store staff got so over dumb customers askingðŸ¤£ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I should have contested it, didn't know you could.
First offence-warning
Second-12 hours
Third-24 hours
Fourth-7 days
Fifth-Permanent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well...think like a developer....what would YOU make it be and do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...when the town drunk stops giving any &amp; all f**ks #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# I've never played #HASHTAG# or a souls-like title.
I can't give bad design will dull style &amp; horrible gameplay a free pass because it's more difficult than it deserves to be.
That little trick is for male minds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes they truly are the stern parent or cool substitute teacher we needed. No?....demanding gym coach? Brutal dominatrix? Seriously how far can one hurt something because they love something before it becomes plain old ass whuppin?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# There is a bunch of 8 or 9 playstation trolls and their various sock puppets going round trying to pretend Andrea is someone else because they convinced themselves it's her weak point for massive damage. Honestly it's like watching pigeons play chess. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Many places on earth toyed with the idea of not having a police force &amp; relying on peoples good nature, South Australia being one of them.
It always ends with them creating a police force.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Grew up in a small town, moved to a satellite town of Sydney &amp; moved in circles dominated by mostly men. Wasn't easy to find my voice, but Janeway showed me you don't have to belittle others or throw your weight around, you can meet them on their terms &amp; trust their strengths.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Human nature, it's easy to abuse minorities then claim you aren't when challenged.
...or pretend it's an invasion or takeover when they threaten ones total majority even a hint. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well #USER# is the only one with a successful economy out of all the wreckage, based on fair trade between content creators &amp; consumers. Somehow I don't think all the newcomers have the patience for that amount of non-exploitative revenue. They want trillions...right now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not having witnessed hot, red, smoking incoming live fire before...it's nothing short of nightmarish.....but seeing a loved one hit by it is worse.
Russia never recovers from this!ðŸ¤¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pfff...yeah like Forza has been doing for like two games nowðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah cause scoring points is the most important thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Now they're going to popping up out of nowhere screaming you called them ducksðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...they said gameplay...and the footage wasn't first or third person. Shall it be the firing squad or hanging?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Crazy doesn't begin to describe sony's goon squad round here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They can't really enforce martial law, all capable soldiers are filing into the Ukrainder! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that has to be terrifying.
Not for the crowd....but for the russian troops.
They'd have no idea if there was a "wolf among the sheep". #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's Fallout 4!
Some people go into it for the story or gameplay....I need to establish Sisterhood Island, Boston first.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep!
Same old joke too.
"Where is the dishwasher?"
"....your father"ðŸ˜‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER#TheSeries #USER# M-hm...I don't think they're blind or deaf....just taking that very dangerous "poetic license"ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# - Never give up...no...really...you're sure to beat it any day now! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hahah...sony f**k off with these obvious bots!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# One of my first introductions to him.....then he joined them on stageðŸ˜²
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's not his job to check the weapon, he's not trained and doesn't know what to look for. That's the job of a supposedly trained armorer...and she f**ked it up. Blame Hannah Gutierrez Reed for failing in her duty &amp; handing a live weapon to Baldwin on the assurance it was safe. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's not as catchy as "stop over-funding police departments at the expense of other public needs" but...people understand nuance and don't need that spelled out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah I wouldn't be going anywhere near such a vehicle unless I changed the markings.
Drone strikes come out of nowhere. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# One more bit of geeking out...promise!ðŸ˜„
Every video is comprised of frames.
I=like a jpeg
P=records only the changes since the last I
B=Bi-directional...caries details of past &amp; future frames
If there's an error...it's never in one specific tiny spot!
...and it leaves a trail! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Now there's a name I've not heard in a long time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been using "teh internetz" since may 1999....nothing has changed!
Except some of the worst perpetrators have jobs in our press now. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Shareholders!
You see the same from elon musk fans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh is Guapzilla screenshotting this?
I see they enjoy doing that &amp; then thinking up some way to make it look bad to their fellow vermin.
Mental gym trainingðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How many miles does 2.5 hours charge get you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜±Wrangling 1015HP from a little 4 cylinder Toyota Corolla engine in #HASHTAG# has to be the worst idea.
It's only practical use is drifting, but you'll turn the tires to smoke long before you reach a drift zone!
It goes from 100HP to 1015HP in the last 25% of the revs! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I know insecure people need external validation they "backed the right horse"...but it's really off-putting!
Attacking me never nor will ever give them what they're looking for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Understandable!
It LOOKS like the bigger userbase, till you realize they don't buy games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ....like it matters anymore!
Every interaction you have here is potentially tomorrows headline.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After more than a decade of media manipulators, fake accounts, #USER# and others all screaming "America is evil and murders innocents" after one friendly fire incident on a journalist...Russia ends up doing far worse.
...you lost your screaming rights today, fellas! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The industry tried really hard to move away from physical media &amp; ownership to rental &amp; infinitely reproducible copies for maximum profit.
I always warn industry types against such a house of cards because once the veil is lifted.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What on earth???ðŸ˜®
I go to browse the latest styles and get blasted by a Miss Rodeo pageant. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She lost all credibility the day she started supporting bernie sanders.
If she's that duped by "what's on the label" while ignoring the contents...America's highways are littered with free bottles of Coca-Cola!ðŸ‘ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well it's the default brand, right? Xbox is only for weird people, afraid of success or enjoy being denied exclusives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's like....are you s**tting me?
I get where you're coming from, trying to police the armchair experts but COME ON!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure their instructors told them "if they have you besieged in your home, they are likely to throw flash/stun/gas grenades through your windows then come in shooting up everyone they see". #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Powerade &amp; dump a teaspoon of matcha powder in before you shake it.
Most headaches are a combination of dehydration &amp; blood pollution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Like we'll stop being human wherever we goðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bears repeating, comparing #HASHTAG# safety measures to ANYTHING #HASHTAG#-like in any way voids all credibility. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well teh psferve has six of themðŸ¤ª Makes up for every other design flaw!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine this in VRðŸ˜‘
You would have to ruin everything!
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As my own personal form of timeline cleanser....I really need to try this...it seems so relaxing! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Also the possibility, they excluded platforms to avoid backlash.
And because they never fear Xbox backlash.........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right, right....respect!
Because it would indeed be childish to make fun of any brand for your own benefit, then claim it was only joking or all in good fun when you get caught.
Maybe blame everyone else for "taking it too seriously"? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah...dude made a chart...A MOTHERF**KING CHART!!!! I guess it's game over for Series X.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It's really just #USER#! He got so mad someone attacked his beloved brand so he thought "I'LL SHOW THEM". .....then he watched the "very different to 2013" media landscape side with Jay! Hope he learnt his lesson, stop beating on Xbox for clicks! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think they believe "opposite" is beneficial for them.
They don't understand anything so they take the simplest route.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You know it's every "edgelord" who spelled Microsoft with a $]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ....can everyone stop speaking for me!
This is fringe stuff by about 4 guys blown up into "an entire fanbase".
Stop it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Never noticed him.....but....now that you mention him!ðŸ¤”
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# M-hm......people routinely move expensive companies because of lockdown protest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[....that was literally the point of Russia shoe-horning him into the role. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes I meant the cars only.
Ponies are going really hard on the fact that an incredibly detailed model in one game isn't an incredibly detailed model plus cheese &amp; chalk....maybe a beard...in the next game. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep...cause that's like 5.5GB of detail per second flashing by! However will a 2something gig a second SSD cope???? And with only 16GB of total system RAM that's like....OMG....over 60 seconds you've seen over 300GB of pure graphical awesomeness! ....need I go on? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pro gaming-in-general post
PSðŸ¤¡:You're blocked!
Xbox Fans:....ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I care more about the people pretending I care so they can make fun of me for caring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The sock puppets are desperate to keep this garbage going.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# From Neogaf. Call me paranoid but why is every hollow account I see so keen on pushing a 10/10 narrative on such universal perfection? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #USER# &amp; #USER#Support, your automatic content filter needs some tweaking.
I saw an automated warning the video I was looking at contained NUDITY, turns out it was just a ramen NOODLE review.
Gives whole new meaning to the term "send noods" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Isn't it like 2.2 million nowðŸ˜„
Tells you all you need to know about the mentality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He performed a greater service, letting more people know musk is a sociopath!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Mainly to see if twitter actually DOES anything when it's this obvious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No no, you saw the argument he put forward...Sony is teh winnar...go buy a PS4 PRO right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Any residents watch Sky news?
Might explain the hesitance to get vaccinated!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Can we see some actual consequences for #HASHTAG# this time?
Rich, white man has been breaking the law for years in a way none of us would survive because the media keeps doing puff pieces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Not sure the hardware could take much more. The manufacturing hardware is already ruining half their yield because the equipment wasn't prepared for the sheer brilliance of Cerny's genius. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The stupid persons idea of a smaht guy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Civilians found spent Smersh casings on the ground there.
What more evidence do you need?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The biggest threat to life in the US measures only 5.56mm across!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# is competing with #HASHTAG#!
Forza Motorsport is in a different league so above everyone's heads, they still can't tell it apart from Forza Horizon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# We're done tolerating idiots, who call everyone else nazis not knowing what that means.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Standard worthless troll parting missive, the formula is "have fun in/with your [bad thing] you [bad name]". They miss the tags but everyone in the room knows they don't actually wish for you to "have fun".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The "buy an item and carry it through many games" line really hit their "buy the same ultimate team players every year" business model.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Open world third person survival crafting adventures?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# So attuned to thinking "everyone's an xbox out to get us" that fellow PS users get trampled.
Such a sad existence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sooner or later the "dads" of the industry will stop idolizing this f**king company!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As I was going to St Ives, 2.5 hours....how many times?" Porsche engaged in verbal trickery here. They give you the total journey mileage and an amount of time...but don't tell you how many miles you get for that. Considering max range on full is 227miles and 4 hour minimum. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Could never really get into it due to the near instantaneous cleared area respawn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[....feel this in my bones!
I said to a friend last night "imagine if you travelled back in time one week, what could you do?" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#Hype #USER#rati M-hm...starts out as an eco-warrior...then pivots to being a cheapass when the facts don't line up.
I know it's hard to admit you made a very expensive mistake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Noooooooooooo...it promised something everyone asked for...over technology that was normalised across the entire planet with no areas of limited connectivity &amp; full relinquishment of ownership rights for an eternal rental model. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah can they delete their review bombs once they go through?
Or are they there forever?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But #USER# said they have more reviews in a day than the first game had in 7 years. Surely he wasn't trolling?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So tiring in this day &amp; age people still ask for "an example" in an argument when it's so easy to Google one.
Really it's a test/bulls**t tactic.
"SHOW ME TEN EXAMPLES RIGHT NOW OR I'LL ACT LIKE YOU HAVE NO EXAMPLES".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When idiots bring their A-Game arguments to something that isn't a discussion! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not the brightest bunch, considering how tangled his belt is.
I can't speak fluent dumbf**k so I choose to believe he's saying "gun did a jam...why it not work now?".
"Oh grand meatsack...you have to pay it"
"F**k this...I punch tank"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# They are incentivized to carry a particular narrative for their benefactors. They don't care who lives or dies, Australian lives are disposable as long as they can politically pin their deaths on someone else or offer themselves as the solution. Remember, motive!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As literally EVERYONE who isn't a clueless mainstream media hack job told y'all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not paying dividends, the whole of tesla stock ownership is those looking to cash out once it's higher than they bought in.
Nobody is in for the long term because they "believe in the product"ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well you know...when one is in their 20s they know everything! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Can we just transfer via ethernet cable or stick in a f**king flash drive???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ugh....makes me sick listening to him!
F**king idiot console warrior thinks Xbox is competing with Playstation.
...those days are gone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's the kind of thing PS fans expect from us.
They never notice I call sony exclusives dogs**t today, I still call them dogs**t when they become available to me.
I'm something called "consistent".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Journalists &amp; reviewers don't care......they saw how easy we all swallowed Cyberpunk!
It's a job/scam for clicks/views.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think he'll take some, but others will be too difficult &amp; costly.
Endgame?
Putin is either removed, or the borders get redrawn yet again &amp; everyone goes back to stalemate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Playstation got by on having token competition at best. They strong-armed their way in, sending Sega to an early grave &amp; relegating Nintendo to a niche it remained in ever since. Xbox may have been the outsider but they fought, they suffered...now they lead a changed industry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You're not big on freedom of speech"
I don't have to be!
It's not mine to grant anymore than it's mine to take away.
It both starts and ends with the government.
You can't credit me for something I didn't give, to give me the blame I don't deserve!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mneagh....not quite.
I think they just added microphones, not much else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think we got "Rosie The Riveter" beat!ðŸ˜„ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Riiiight....and the speeding ticket was the police's fault for chasing themðŸ™„
Teach your son "you can't shift blame"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Their contempt is measurable against their panic when the acquisition was announced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Waiting on the "hospitalized" and "sadly passed" stories in about 3 months.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One of musk's many burner accounts!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh grow up....there's a war on!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Unpopular Opinion" - Where you go against the grain....then deal with hordes of internet creatures. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Very strange that he ordinarily doesn't give a s**t any of us exist.
But when there's a PS flaw to defend....he's there for days!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Biden doesn't want to waste time with a scam company anymore than the CDC wanted to consult with Theranos! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Unless you're a sony studio, you're gonna get dragged for doing so!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The difference between science &amp; politics. Politically you say one thing...now that's your thing forever...you can't change your thing as new information comes out or people freak out "FIRST YOU SAID THIS, NOW YOU SAY THIS AAAAGH" Science is all about finding out new things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The real dangers to life are rarely something you can shoot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, #USER# is just a genius who spotted a massive government plot when nobody...not even trained intelligence officers could pick it up. They should totally recruit him to some kind of secret spy organisation with a gym &amp; Q branch like in 007! ...do I need tags?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'd have to press X to doubt on that.
This is only possible by leveraging the CUDA cores on my card that aren't present on AMD GPUs.
Series X GPU can't both run a game at 4K 60fps AND record it live at the same.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#C #USER# ...speaking of things that don't work! Honestly...get rid of putin....he will destroy russia! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If reheating leftovers &amp; adding butter is "eating good"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm less scared about nuclear conflict than a totally preventable disease killing millions because people like doing the opposite of everything you tell them.
Maybe I should demand nuclear powers use their weapons?
Then will they all decline out of oppositional defiance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Always said nobody really wanted ANY playstation....it's just.....what were your alternatives?
Xbox 360 was the only time sony ever had a rival they couldn't destroy or send into a niche.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#GamePass #USER#GamePassPC #USER#P3 #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Out of all the rendering technologies I've witnessed in my time, ray tracing is the only one I can recall in the last 10 years that leaves non-gaming folks in awe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think they're past caring, but the day is young.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Oh and don't forget the vanity fair cover!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hey....they wouldn't be pissing &amp; moaning if they weren't biting!
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Until it does.....then it doesn't again.....then it does again!
Just so tired of PS fans flip flopping on it wether they like the score or not.
....then accusing you of doing the same thing without even checking to see if you have, like that makes it okay!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Twitter is full of "genuine as apple pie people of colour who support trump" Basically any fight someone has a dog in, there will always be fake accounts out to try &amp; affect public opinion to suit their needs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I take it smuggling through the stone mines underneath isn't an option?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Always genuine questions from someone with an assange profile photo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talk about a weird way to discover disinformation.
Someone posted a pic of a 90s band saying they too withdrew their music from #HASHTAG#.
My cynical sense of humor thought they looked like actors so I made up some garbage and posted it.
...yeah it was a film I never knew existed! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# trump doesn't give a f**k about America. He declared bankruptcy too many times for any local bank to lend him money so he turned to Russia. And we all know their loans have no stings attached.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She's here to troll on behalf of sony &amp; act like the victim when she gets it back even half as bad, not make sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# M-hmðŸ˜„
Along with...
-Tess Virginia
-Colorado Rita
-Sandy FranFisto
-I Da Ho
-The Dakota Twins
...and Kimsass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# was essentially misguided middle class Europeans blaming the nation's condition on minorities.
The state allowed and even encouraged crazy fringe beliefs into national policy.
Enforcing vaccine &amp; mask mandates is the OPPOSITE of that! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sure....blame them instead of Fromsoftware.....idiot!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Not quite sure yet.
Only photos I can find of her seem really "stalker scrapbook" in nature.
Means the industry has a very strange perception and attitude towards her.
We'll see if the project bears fruit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Loading all the themes....still no ray tracing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's odd, on youtube the phenomenon doesn't happen. So it was either corrected on a second attempt or faked in on this first. We're thinking it's to make the "experts" cry wolf so many times, nobody listens when the really heavy fakes appear on actual serious topics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Mneagh.....okay.....missile produces an extraordinary amount of flame, plume as big as the aircraftðŸ¤”
Most Stingers don't need to.
The whole spectacle looks like "exactly what we expected".
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wait...so that framerate chug before each glowy purple portal was a loading transition? Money well spent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nooooooo...I was so looking forward to my hard disk being paralysed for random 30min intervals when I'm in the middle of something crucial! What am I going to do now? Finish them without frustration?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Legend has it, Randy "F**king' Pitchford robbed Sega &amp; their budget for this game to pay for Borderlands 2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bears repeating, we aren't texting each other on 90s brick phones with buttons &amp; limited characters.
"Laughing my ass off" isn't an argument, it just means you forgot to make one. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got a horrible message from a Twitter user tonight saying I was a "Cartoon Avatar" and "Nothing I said had any meaning &amp; nobody cared". I did a quick google search and he was right...not one image of me beyond the first 4 pages. My Flickr stats too, only 7.3millionðŸ˜¥ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The #USER# always pretends someone is out to scrap the #HASHTAG#...yeah because one person can do that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My first car!ðŸ¥°
But Australia does draw from the Asian market.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If anyone is going to complain about Halo, can we mention we can only have one kind of bleached, harmless-looking villain these days apparently!
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See...same colour...it's like an icky 1950s industrial greenish aqua.
I'd expect to see it on a non-dyson handheld vacuum! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's a......erm.........odd....thing!
Front end looks strange like it's from something else entirely....and the loading area looks sunken!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...and aren't they always the most inspiring types. Like you just know they have a firm grasp of politicsðŸ™„ #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It was a terrible joke on a topic that routinely gets attacked by trolls in exactly the same way! A lesson to everyone use tags!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You don't have Spotify?, you buy CDs?...how backward are youðŸ˜„" Backward enough to pick the tunes I want, rip, resample, expand and play over bluetooth sound systems that make people weep with joy. But please, continue telling me how much of a luddite I am for not renting music. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# *sigh*
Covid19 is a self-assembled nano particle...but antennae with decent range weren't high on the to-do list.
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Transparent, blue, maybe some animated matrix code]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ooooh I dunno....just 2 hours of her would have done! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# *sigh*
Another person not understanding the problem.
In real life, people aren't being listened to by millions...that carries a responsibility few are prepared for.
And in real life...you make a mistake...nobody notices.
On his show...half a continent gets disinformed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Just like last time really.
Only I hope they get more resources this time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Virtua Fighter 2....even got the outfit! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's been tried, several times through history.
Always ends badly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They just have to remind people sony don't know what they're doing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That demonic nun from August better be the prayin' type!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# To do all the things the Series X (and even XB1 did) while turned off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Play with fire, eventually get burnt after more than a decade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I've taken to adding tags as it doesn't come across and everyone takes it as something it's not! Imagine someone quote tweeting or screenshotting it to throw at you weeks from now. ...any attempt at explaining taken as fumbling/making excuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# God...damn...clear the deck &amp; close the hatch!ðŸ˜±]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, I began with a Sega Mega Drive, then a Saturn when they came out...but due to living in regional Australia and having no distribution, the more popular playstation was all that remained in the market...so I abandoned consoles for PC.
Then Xbox, 360, One and Series X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The f**k are you even saying with this huh?
Really?
What do we do with it?
Tell the rest of the world f**k off?
Sort your own s**t out?
Did you think it was clever?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure that sounded like a gotcha &amp; really clever in your head, but like all straw man arguments you do it wrong on purpose so you can moan about "how wrong it is".
Pineapple is used only sparingly on pizzas that call for it, and even then there is only 2 varieties I know. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Also any ear, eye and respiratory protection you can manage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the wake of #HASHTAG# telling people to "engage" with the idiots in life who will...never...listen...I'd remind you it's not your job, you're under no obligation to "hear them out"...and they'll just blame you for being the way they are no matter what you do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# May want to show them some casualty vids first. Men missing jaws, eyes still open, dogs eating the soft tissues above the uniform collar, limbs laying in the street with no apparent owner. War isn't call of duty, and humans are very fragile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Imagine if another comes along later, with an actually important topic...and people tune out "yeah we did this dance before". I mean I've warned Schindler before, this was right up my alley. To debunk something on my special topicðŸ˜‘ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh her....yeah she blocked me for association.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ......kremlin says a lot of thingsðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good....means you're still alive &amp; paying attention.
I worry about the people who AREN'T!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Most of the famous ones actually, but anything GTA feels like it was made for someone else.....and that someone else is a total a**hole!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Implying the new Indiana Jones game will both...
-Not meet expectations
-Arrive in 2026
....got a friggin GENIUS on our hands!
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Took the jibe tonight "Hey you should send them some of your surplus gas masks". While I do have a few, I threw away the cans. They have dates printed, some date back to 1991...all would have expired, none would meet any security standard and russians aren't using gas in Ukraine #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They really enjoy having a role given to them rather than making one. Guide their famous game's famous character through environments for drama &amp; storytelling. They really want to make films, but they'd be laughed out of every theater if they did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well you know how there was always that one child in 3rd grade who said their favorite food was meat &amp; 3 veg so the teacher would give them praise for being "mature"...when you KNEW they enjoyed 3 square raw cookie doughs a day? People pretend to "love a challenge".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Do they know there is no viable alternative to youtube?
Owning discs was always a viable alternative to spotify.
Or did we get so caught up in the onward march we forgot?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh christ....don't kill him....he has to be handed over to authorities!
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah we got blamed for their own deathnote parties too!
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Plenty of footage, but haven't seen anything official.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If "belief" matters more than "provable fact" to #HASHTAG#...I was The Wasp!
Yes that's me in there starring alongside Paul Rudd...marvel now owes me millions of dollars. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As good a time as any to say out loud I HATE the stitching detail on these pockets.
It's rough as anything and rubs against the polyurethane coating inside each pocket &amp; makes holes as the material de-laminates. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# A former ABC/4corners/award collector now investigative journalist throws a casual sting in the tail about plunder by overseas corporations? ...this can only be dynamite supported by loads of facts &amp; evidence!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah I forgot selling the hardware was where the big money is!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Noticed it in the global politics space too.
It's like, reich-wing crazies lost all russia's funding so they gave up on running bot farms.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>