<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Orban's sinister anti-Muslim hatemongering now threatens lives in Bosnia: Hungary's Orban refuses to accept Muslims can be Europeans. His bigotry, and his collusion with Serbian nationalists, are provoking another war, while the backlash from… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black criminality must be recognized and dealt with #URL# ArutzShevaOpinion #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel loggs more than 83,000 daily COVID cases for second straight day: Health Ministry says 845 people hospitalized in serious condition with virus complications, 117 on ventilators; After 14 die on Monday death toll stands on 8,487 #URL# Ynet-Culture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor Lebanese, Syrians struggle to survive unforgiving winter: Hundreds of thousands of Syrian refugees in Lebanon and Jordan are sheltering in poorly heated tents relying mostly on layers of blankets to keep warm #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Mizrahi feminist who stopped asking for permission from Ashkenazi Jews: Loolwa Khazzoom has devoted her life to telling the story of Jews with roots in the wider Middle East and Africa. The seminal 2003 anthology of essays she edited, ‘The… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel holds bodies of 80% of terrorists: Defense Ministry responds to criticism after bodies of 3 terrorists returned in recent months. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hostage Texas Rabbi and wife said to be allies of the entire Muslim community: I predict the Rabbi will become an even stronger advocate of kindness to Islamists who might be embedded in the “entire community.”.Op-ed. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Iran’s threat to attack Israel’s Dimona matters - analysis: The decision to unveil a new multiple-drone launcher while splicing that with a digital mock-up of Dimona is a new level of Iranian aggressive threats.  #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abbas asks Gantz to release 25 veteran terrorists: PA chairman wants Israeli Defense Minister to release 25 Fatah terrorists who were arrested before the Oslo Accords. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US to citizens: Do not travel to Russia: State Department updates travel warning to Russia to Russia to Level 4: Do Not Travel amid tensions with Ukraine. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy with plea deal in corruption case, Netanyahu is absent from the Knesset: Opposition leader Benjamin Netanyahu tells attorneys to push on in negotiations with Israel's attorney general. Sources close to the former PM claim he missed Knesset… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadian Jewish group urges more security following Texas incident: Centre for Israel and Jewish Affairs calls for more security for Jewish institutions following hostage incident in Texas. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[80-year-old detained by Israeli soldiers dies of heart attack, Palestinian Health Ministry says: Omar Abd al-Majid As'ad, who is a dual U.S. citizen, was handcuffed and beaten by Israeli soldiers who stopped him on his way home in the West Bank,… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says he would pardon Jan. 6 rioters if he runs and wins: Trump stated that Jan. 6 rioters were being treated "so unfairly." #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel scraps all curbs on blood donations from gay men: Ministry's chief says the move will go into effect from October 1 and was made due to drop in HIV rates and preventative treatments undertaken by homosexual men, who until now were… #URL# Ynet-Culture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID-19: New variant, B.1.640.2, detected in France - study: The variant, tentatively identified B.1.640.2, is believed to be Cameroonian in origin and have so far spread to 12 patients in southern France. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID experts recommend reopening Israel’s skies within 2 weeks: “The continued existence of aviation restrictions is only relevant as long as there is no widespread infection from Omicron in the community," said the experts. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli and U.S. officials say visa waiver deal still far from happening: Despite optimistic headlines in Israel in recent months, the two sides are now cooling expectations amid technical difficulties. Meanwhile, Biden could face criticism over… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JCC Manhattan’s new director wants to help people ‘reclaim pre-COVID life’: The Marlene Meyerson JCC Manhattan joined JCCs nationwide in cutting staff when in-person programming abruptly shut down that spring and summer. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jewish Temple University student targeted by roommate: Jewish student at Temple University shocked to receive antisemitic text from new roommate. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expert prediction for Israel 2050: it’s going to be a living hell: Meteorological service forecasts include seven heat waves of over 48 degrees Celsius at Lake Kinneret a year, double the days above 34 in Jerusalem and much more extreme heat on… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alan Dershowitz's article in the 'Post' was misleading - opinion: Alan Dershowitz’s assertion that Giuffre not testifying is the most important takeaway from the trial is not exact. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Israel tried to dump African refugees in blood-drenched dictatorships: An Israeli Defense Ministry man paid bribes across Africa, with a nod from his director general • Former ministers and businessmen negotiated with failed states • Some… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID-19 in Israel: R rate drops below one for first time since November: Serious cases continue to rise as number of new daily infections drops, future of Green Pass restrictions uncertain #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harry Potter star Emma Watson takes pro-Palestinian stance on Instagram: Actress posts image of Palestinian flags, with 'solidarity is a verb' written across it; many social media commenters praise the Beauty and the Beast star, while others… #URL# Ynet-Culture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is the best way to pick a stock?: Understand the difference between growth and value investing. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prof. Mevorach warns: 'We don't know post-corona effects of Omicron': 'Children are a vulnerable population, we don't know post-corona effects of Omicron,' head of Hadassah Medical Center's COVID-19 ward warns. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reservists train for war with Hezbollah despite IDF's high COVID-19 numbers: Just days before the military canceled all reserve training, the 66th Brigade of the 55th Paratroopers brigade had a surprise drill in the Jordan Valley. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli study finds fourth COVID-19 vaccine dose boosts antibodies five-fold, PM says: Bennett says preliminary data from Sheba Medical Center's survey shows second booster is safe and will likely mean significant protection against… #URL# Ynet-Culture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Houthis second missile attack on the UAE: The new normal?  - analysis: The second attack appears smaller but nevertheless now indicates the Houthis believe they have a right to expand the war to the UAE.  #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID-19 in Israel: IDF returning to capsule systems: IDF units will return to the configuration of company capsules, with an emphasis on capsules in vital units. The new regulations do not affect the military’s operational effectiveness. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The slum in the heart of Tel Aviv is about to vanish: In the world's most expensive city, refugees, asylum seekers and migrant workers are living in abysmal poverty and overcrowding. The surge in housing prices in Neve Sha'anan and nearby… #URL# Haaretz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Betty White, working actress into her 90s, dies just shy of her 100th birthday: Her agent and close friend Jeff Witjas told People magazine: "Even though Betty was about to be 100, I thought she would live forever." #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barkat: Likud MKs cooperated with party's enemies: Ministers to vote on bills that would require all Israeli kids to study Arabic, create Unity Day #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HR survey confirms Covid-caused ‘Great Resignation’: 54% of hiring managers and HR leaders say many employees leaving their companies are choosing to work for themselves. 

The post HR survey confirms Covid-caused ‘Great Resignation’… #URL# ISRAELITY #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RFK Jr. apologizes for Holocaust - vaccine mandate comparison following wife's criticism: RFK Jr. curbs his enthusiasm for COVID Holocaust analogies following prompt from wife Cheryl Hines. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KKL-JNF tree planting in Negev resumes under heavy security: Ra'am has threatened the coalition over the issue. *Ze'ev Elkin called Mansour Abbas's use of political pressure as "legitimate," but said they don't need Ra'am's permission. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the Electricity Law, Israel recognizes Bedouin conquests #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EEOC Commissioner says Stanford antisemitism “deeply troubling”: Stanford’s Diversity, Equity and Inclusion program has advanced antisemitic tropes concerning Jewish power, conspiracy, and control. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran nuclear agreement unlikely without release of US prisoners - Malley: US Special Envoy for Iran Robert Malley said it is "hard for us to imagine" a return to the nuclear deal without the release of prisoners. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inoculated women pass higher coronavirus antibody levels on to newborns, study finds: Research findings show 100% of newborns had antibodies to protect them against COVID and that their antibody levels were 2.6 times higher than their mothers' #URL# Ynet-Culture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli minister warns of more crises with Diaspora Jews over COVID entry rules: Countries including Canada and France are being removed from the high-risk list, but aliyah official decries a pattern of opening and closing that has proved ‘taxing… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our mission to remember the Holocaust - opinion: Anti-lockdown protesters proudly wearing swastikas along with those who are wearing a yellow star on their chest showing they refuse to get vaccinated display the persistence of antisemitism. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bob Saget, Jewish-American comedian and TV actor, dies at 65: The actor and comedian, best known for his role on the TV sitcom 'Full House,' was found dead in a hotel room in Orlando, Florida, on Sunday. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sudanese security forces kill three demonstrators as anti-coup protests resurge: A week after Sudan's prime minister resigned from office, thousands took to the streets in the capital of Khartoum and other cities to protest the October military… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli killed in accident in Samaria: Israeli killed, two Palestinian Arabs lightly injured in accident near Barkan industrial zone. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netanyahu employed threats to get better news coverage, former aide tells court: In his testimony, Nir Hefetz, who served as the former PM's family spokesman, said Yedioth Ahronoth's publisher was warned that a competitor would destroy the paper… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Iraqi cleric's gamble to sideline in Iran-backed factions in new government: The movement led by Shi'ite cleric Moqtada al-Sadr already re-elected a parliamentary speaker opposed by the Iran-aligned camp, and could leave them in Iraq's… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The steep price of Europe’s surrender to Islam #URL# ArutzShevaOpinion #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mexico issues arrest warrants in 'Fast and Furious' gun trafficking case: The once-secret 'Fast and Furious' scheme set out to stop US-Mexico gun smuggling by allowing people to illegally buy arms in the United States and take them to Mexico. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel still not sure omicron causes milder illness, despite research: Which variant do seriously ill COVID patients have, and how many have underlying conditions? Lack of clear information is making it difficult for doctors to precisely assess… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One woman killed, two others injured in car explosion in central Israel: Israel Police suspect the explosion in the mixed-city of Ramle was an assassination #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Palestinian shot dead after attempted stabbing attack in West Bank #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teams search through night for 39 missing from capsized boat off Florida: Incidents of overturned or interdicted vessels crowded with people, many of them Haitians or Cubans seeking to reach the United States, are not uncommon in Florida's waters. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rabbi Rafi Feurstein: How can Smotrich attack Miriam Naor before her body is cold?: Tzohar leader criticizes MK Smotrich for attacking late Justice Miriam Naor within hours of her passing. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Historic visit: President Herzog and First Lady take off for presidential visit to UAE: President Herzog before take-off: I am bringing with me a blessing of peace and a message of peace to the entire region. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia offered Iran interim nuclear deal with US' knowledge - report: Iran reportedly rejected Russia's proposal and the US distanced itself from Russia's attempts at an interim agreement, according to the report. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bipartisan bicameral Abraham Accords Caucus established: Abraham Accords Peace Institute: "Israeli and American caucuses will help establish a foundation for peace in the Middle East". #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel starts clinical trials for second COVID booster shots: The Sheba Medical Center administers the fourth coronavirus vaccine doses to 150 subjects – all medical staff – after an expert panel recommended that Israel become the first country… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sexual abuse won't end if we don't stand with victims - editorial: How can we expect women to come forward and file police complaints when people in power like Chief Rabbi David Lau refuse to automatically stand with them? #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall of al-Bashir brings no change for Israel’s Sudanese refugees: Waiting, hoping and guessing remains the norm. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli TV star and Eurovision co-host Assi Azar accused of sexual assault: The accuser, the film actor Yehuda Nahari, told the Walla news site that he recently passed a polygraph test to discuss the meeting a decade ago with Azar, who denies the… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five arrested after police uncover hydroponic cannabis lab: Police discover explosives, hydroponic cannabis plants, in search operation in northern Israel. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yiddish copies of Christian Bible distributed in Rockland County, NY: Rockland County has a very dense ultra-Orthodox Jewish population, especially in places like Monsey and Spring Valley. The Yiddish copies of the New Testament are linked to… #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The president’s “not my problem” approach to leadership #URL# ArutzShevaOpinion #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Breyer Patch: Podcast: Stephen Breyer's retirement. View Post #URL# Commentary #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Ministry mulls fourth COVID jab for over 60s and medical teams: Hospital chiefs call on ministry to okay second booster for medical teams, at-risk age groups amid growing concern of Omicron overwhelming healthcare system; Health… #URL# Ynet-Culture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Likud MK David Bitan tests positive for COVID-19 a second time: In December of 2020, Bitan was hospitalized in serious condition after contracting COVID-19. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hamas commander accused of spying for Israel escapes from Gaza prison: Abed al-Karim Abu Odeh, 35, was arrested by Hamas in 2019 on suspicion of mapping underground tunnels for Israel. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli schools put on a brave face amid COVID surge: Principals have been left trying to cope with Israel's demand that schools stay open despite some 40,000 students and teachers had tested positive for COVID and 78,000 were in quarantine #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bennett responds to Netanyahu: He's back to sowing chaos, as usual: Bennett responds to Netanyahu's criticism of pandemic response: We’ll continue to run the country calmly and responsibly. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli high-school students’ satellites launch into space: Students from eight Jewish and Arab schools spent three years building satellites and watched a live NASA feed as they took off for outer space. nnThe post Israeli high-school… #URL# ISRAELITY #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[University of Toronto has a Jewish Problem: Social justice warriors blatantly seek to blacklist and purge pro-Israel Jews from campus. Op-ed. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID-19 booster reduces myocarditis cases among Israeli children: The Health Ministry announced only two cases of myocarditis were reported in Israel among 44,000 youngsters aged 12 to 15. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Turkey reconciliation gaining support in Israel? - analysis: If Turkey really is a potential partner with Israel against Iran, how come Turkey adores Iran’s leadership and never opposes Iran? #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omicron wave begins receding in Israel, but Bennett says hospitals still overloaded: Serious COVID cases in Israel rise to 1,069, the highest number in almost a year, but signs that the fifth wave is tapering off continue #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch: Biden booed, jeered during Minnesota event: The Hill posted footage of a Biden rally in Minnesota during which hecklers interrupted his speech. Biden called them 'ugly folks.' #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Israeli Supreme Court President Miriam Naor dies at 74: Naor has been part of several landmark rulings, including overruling a law to keep asylum seekers in detention, and authored the ruling abolishing the draft exemption for yeshiva… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pfizer CEO sees annual COVID vaccine rather than frequent boosters: Pfizer could be ready to file for approval for a redesigned vaccine to fight Omicron, and mass produce it, as soon as March. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 10% of Israel's population caught COVID in January, Health Ministry says: Scientist believes over 3 million Israelis came down with the pathogen since the beginning of the country's Omicron-induced fifth wave, ranking Israel first in… #URL# Ynet-Culture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli extremists threaten Christian presence in Jerusalem, church leader says: The Greek Orthodox Patriarch of Jerusalem says he believes radical Israeli groups aim to drive the Christian community from the old city, which has sites sacred to… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For first time in months, Israel sees nearly 4,000 new COVID cases: Health Ministry says infection rate continues to climb, standing at nearly 3%; hospitalizations rise slightly, but still remain relatively low; 94 patients in serious… #URL# Ynet-Culture #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Majority of Israelis learned very little on Mizrahi Jewish culture - poll: 75% of respondents said they could not recall any program or lesson in school that reinforced a positive perception of Mizrahi Jewry. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mansour Abbas: We will vote against Shaked's Citizenship Law: Ra'am chairman: We formed the government and brought Ayelet Shaked and others to be ministers. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jews in New York on edge for Election Day: Violent extremists exist on both ends of the political spectrum, with white supremacists and neo-Nazis on the far-right clashing with Antifa supporters, many of whom consider President Trump a facist #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch: Thief makes off with wigs worth half a million shekels: Wild police chase leads to capture of thief who robbed wig store. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saudi coalition shows footage of alleged Hezbollah involvement in Yemen war: The Saudi-led coalition called Hezbollah a "cancer" which is part of Iran's attempts to bring "destruction and devastation" to the world. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Palestinian-American gets two life sentences for murder of Israeli in West Bank: Military court hands down two life sentences and $820,000 in fines to Muntas Shalabi over shooting attack that killed Yehuda Guetta and wounded two others last year #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Mars our good name': JNF board members say they weren't told about controversial tree-planting in Israel's Negev: After days of violent clashes over forestation work on land used by local Bedouin farmers, six board members of the Jewish National… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US wants to achieve a measure of justice for Holocaust survivors: US special envoy for Holocaust issues speaks with the ‘Post’ about the spread of misinformation and the need for education. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japanese museum tells story of diplomat who saved Jews during the Holocaust: Museum's new exhibit showcases the stories of Jews rescued by Chiune Sugihara during the Holocaust who landed in Japanese port city. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch: A presidential snow fight: President Isaac Herzog and First Lady Michal Herzog play in the snow at the President's Residence in Jerusalem. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zuk Farm: Ranch-to-table steak heaven - food review: Zuk Farm (Havat Tzuk in Hebrew) is situated in the unlikely setting of an alley around the corner from the deli, which itself is in a sidewalk mini-mall in an upscale residential neighborhood. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knesset Speaker to address Bundestag on Holocaust Memorial Day: Mickey Levy will make a point of speaking in Hebrew #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Esther Pollard, wife of Israeli spy, hospitalized due to COVID: Jonathan Pollard's wife, who has been battling cancer for several years, contracted the coronavirus two weeks ago and is now suffering from a case of sepsis brought on by her… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gynescope remote systems deployed to save African women: Distribution deal will send 20,000 of Illumigyn’s devices across Africa to help detect cervical cancer before it’s too late. #URL# ISRAELITY #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 18 years, Ann Arbor condemns weekly synagogue protesters as antisemitic: 'Jewish power corrupts' protests outside Michigan synagogue led by self-declared ex-Jew are finally condemned by city council. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outrage after Iranian soccer plays in match with Israeli coach: Iranian media criticizes soccer player who played in showcase match with Israeli coach Avram Grant. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sydney festival apologizes to artists over Israeli funding boycott debacle: While the Sydney Festival has rebuffed BDS' demands to refuse Israeli funding, its board will consider whether the festival should accept government funding of festival… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How has the Chaim Walder scandal affected the haredi world?: All agree on one critical point: in the haredi public, no one knows how to talk about sexuality – and certainly not to young children. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coalition, Likud rivals gang up on Barkat: A biill that is set to pass would limit billionaire MK Nir Barkat and his family to annual donations of 100,000 #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli-American businessman helps evacuate Afghan, Syrian refugees: Moti Kahana explains how he got involved in rescuing refugees, and his latest efforts. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former US Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid has died: As Senate Democratic leader for more than a decade, he played a significant role in passing the Affordable Care Act and guiding through Congress pivotal economic recovery legislation. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberman: The economy is developing excellently: Finance Minister makes clear he will not agree to the extension of the green pass. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['JewFace' faces backlash: 'What's offensive is the idea that there's such thing as Jewish character traits': Acclaimed Israeli filmmakers Joseph Cedar and Hagai Levi respond to the uproar over 'JewFace,' the term coined by comedian Sarah… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Importance of Jewish activism against antisemitism in diaspora - opinion: Now more than ever, it is crucial that Jews in the diaspora stand up and support Israel, because supporting it is supporting our own Jewish communities. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UN refugee evoy in Israel: Canceled deal on asylum seekers still on the table: UNHCR rep says Israel must find a viable and humane solution to protect the nearly 30,000 Eritrean and Sudanese refugees, which some Israeli authorities have described… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice Minister to receive final 3 candidates for next A-G this week: Nomination committee to make final decision on candidates to succeed Avichai Mandelblit as attorney general. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea fires suspected ballistic missile: For the fourth time in recent weeks, North Korea fires at least one suspected ballistic missile into the sea. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['We're seeing a ray of light, we may be nearing the end': World Health Organization regional emergency director Dorit Nitzan optimistic Omicron could mark beginning of the end of pandemic. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This day in Jewish history: The man whom America never repaid for its independence: Haym Salomon funded not only the Revolutionary War but several leading politicians. He died on January 6, 1785 - bankrupt #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lapid slams Netanyahu for critical videos in English: 'Campaign against Israel': Opposition leader Netanyahu, who made a habit of bashing opponents for any political activity in English, released a series of videos calling the current government… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel’s leaders split three ways on Iran. Tehran promises “fresh ideas” for Vienna talks #URL# DEBKA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian Demands, American Plans: commentary podcast: Russian Demands, American PlansView Post #URL# Commentary #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China plants dozens of shell firms in Israel to prize out military industrial hi-tech #URL# DEBKA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rabbi behind weekly 'Dvar Malchus' booklets passes away: Rabbi Tuvia Peles, senior Chabad-Lubavitch hasid and the man behind the 'Dvar Malchus' booklets, dead at 73. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minister Kahana enlists aid of 3 experts for conversion bill: Dr. Shuki Friedman: "The trend towards private religious services raises the question- do we need a chief rabbinate?" #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lack of plan underpins Israel COVID strategy - analysis: The lack of a comprehensive pandemic strategy by the government grows in relevance every day. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How a jammed gun led to the discovery of a Hamas terror cell: Terrorist planned to carry out shooting attack on Israelis - but a gun malfunction foiled his attack - and led to arrest of terror cell. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US reduces Iran sanctions threat from any violation to 90% enrichment: There is a sense in Jerusalem that if Russia invades Ukraine, it could sharply change how the US deals with Iran. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When and how to test yourself: Israel fine-tunes antigen instructions: When exposed to a COVID carrier, people should take more than one test or at least wait three days since exposure before testing with rapid kits, top Israeli health official… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eritrean infiltrators rape special-needs woman in Tel Aviv: 22-year-old woman raped in Tel Aviv by two illegal immigrants from Eritrea. 'The silence of feminist groups is deafening.' #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The Jew is the devil' — Neo-Nazis rally in Florida: "The Jew is the devil" and "Jews rape children and drink their blood" were among slogans chanted at a rally in Orlando held by the National Socialist Movement. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ukraine and the American crack-up: Not only is the Biden administration enabling the NATO break-up, it is destroying America's deterrent power and superpower position.Op-ed. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rabbi Chaim Druckman joins rabbinate opposition to conversion reforms: Leading Religious Zionist rabbis sign letter opposing any reforms which do not have the backing of the Chief Rabbinate. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Yad Vashem donation decline, Gov't to transfer NIS 29m -report: The World Holocaust Remembrance Center has experienced severe difficulty in raising funds over the past two years due to the COVID-19 pandemic. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel to ease COVID quarantine rules for vaccinated amid Omicron spike: Revision comes amid growing fears thousands of Israelis will be sent into isolation in wake of spread of highly contagious variant; vaccinated Israelis over age of 5… #URL# Ynet-Culture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli study shows 4th jab provides 3 times the protection from COVID complications: Health Ministry says preliminary analysis of study conducted by Weizmann Institute, Hebrew University and Sheba Medical Center also shows 4th jab to… #URL# Ynet-Culture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hapoel edges Maccabi in derby once again: Tel Aviv painted red after tight triumph • Cellar-dwellers Rishon and Eilat making moves #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FM Lapid, French Pres., discuss 'regional challenges' in lengthy phone call: French Pres. Macron speaks at length with Israel's FM Lapid, focused on 'regional challenges.' #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syrian air defenses report Israeli 'aggression' on Latakia port: This is a developing story. #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jewish museum in Oporto, Portugal, building 'antisemite room': The Oporto Jewish Museum in Oporto, Portugal, is building a room to spread awareness of modern antisemitism. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opposition slams government for fast-tracking Knesset vote on unrecognized villages: Opposition lawmakers plan to boycott debate on connecting Bedouin villages in the Negev to the electrical grid over what they see as excessive use of… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taliban hold first talks in Europe since Afghanistan takeover: With about 23 million people, more than half the country, facing severe hunger and nearly 9 million on the brink of starvation, the Taliban is expected to demand the release of $10… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Researchers lay groundwork for potential dog-allergy vaccine - study: Allergies occur when a person’s immune system perceives certain molecules known as antigens as a threat. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rapid tests at nursing home entrances - even for the vaccinated: PM Bennett holds telephone conference on Omicron, orders increased protection for Israel's elderly population. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ukrainian president downplays talk of Russian invasion: After reports that Biden told Ukrainian president an invasion was imminent, Volodymyr Zelensky accuses US and NATO of stirring up a panic. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radical cleric: Selling land to Jews is a betrayal of Islam: Al-Aqsa preacher calls on Muslims to refrain from any involvement in the sale of real estate to Jews. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Gaza, it continues to be what it was - analysis: It may be quiet along the Gaza border, but unless Israel truly commits to its new harsher policy, the next round of violence is only around the corner. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apartments sold and rented: A selection of recent real estate deals in Israel including in Jerusalem, Beit Shemesh, Tel Aviv, Ramat Gan, Ra’anana, Hod Hasharon, Kfar Saba, Or Yehuda, and Sderot. #URL# Globes #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea confirms latest missile tests: Meanwhile, North Korean leader Kim Jong Un visits munitions factory producing a "major weapon system". #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cities have no plans to hike curbside parking prices: Putting up parking prices might prove unpopular but elsewhere in the world they have been effective in reducing city center congestion. #URL# Globes #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PM calls Netanyahu 'anti-patriotic' for mocking antigen tests: Likud responds: Israelis being forced to pay for unreliable tests Bennett has lost control of the situation. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel reports 45,258 new COVID cases as R number falls below 1: Health Ministry says virus' reproduction number stands at 0.95, lowest the figure has been since November; 1,069 coronavirus patients are currently in serious condition, of… #URL# Ynet-Culture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: Gunman holding hostages at Beth Israel synagogue in Texas: According to reports, a gunman is holding hostages at Beth Israel synagogue in Colleyville, Texas. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Movies of 2021: Podcast: Our movies of the year. View Post #URL# Commentary #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rise in IDF fatalities to 31 fallen soldiers, suicide remains leading cause: Suicide has remained the leading cause of IDF deaths in 2021, with a third of Israeli soldiers who committed suicide in the past year being Ethiopian. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This German historian is rejecting the 'easy' explanation for the Holocaust: She disputes the anomalous image of the imperial Reich, likens the history of Prussia to that of the U.S. and is even intervening in formulation of domestic policy.… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court to State: Explain why vaccinated can't travel to red countries: Supreme Court demands government answer, within one week, questions on legitimacy of travel rules for vaccinated Israelis. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC demands identities of Jewish teens it libeled: BBC accused of attempting to intimidate teens it falsely claimed uttered anti-Muslim slur while enduring an anti-Semitic attack. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior health officials slam Israel's plan to cut COVID quarantine to 5 days: Infectious disease expert Prof. Galia Rahav says people infected by COVID can still spread disease 5 days after exposure; Prof. Doron Gazit, who advises cabinet,… #URL# Ynet-Culture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simon Wiesenthal center calls on Amazon to remove Nazi films: “Americans Against Anti-Semitism” found 30 classic Nazi propaganda films available for sale or streaming on the Amazon Prime video network. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why I got the fourth Covid-19 booster, despite my ambivalence: Israel was the first country in the world to authorize a third and fourth dose. Pioneering is central to this country’s DNA. I don’t mind being a guinea pig if it means keeping… #URL# ISRAELITY #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samaria residents to demonstrate against terror wave: Hundreds of residents to demonstrate at site of attempted stabbing attack in light of growing number of recent terror attacks. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sleep, social life and exercise linked to good mental health among youth: Positive relationship variables – such as making plans with loved ones – was the primary predictor of positive mental health, followed by physical exercise. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darrell Blocker, who could lead Biden’s CIA, is a Black Jew known as a ‘spy whisperer’: If selected, Blocker would be the agency’s first Black director — and the third Jewish one #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel to approve NIS 1b. plan for Golan Heights, build two new towns: The approval of the NIS one billion plan strengthens Israel's presence in the Golan Heights territory. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erdogan looking to cash in on economy gains with early election, analysts say: 'For Erdogan, a "last minute" success story emerges before every election' #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia threatens retaliation if Ukraine allies refuse demands: 'If the West continues its aggressive course, Moscow will take the necessary retaliatory measures' #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Half a million shekels of property stolen at Jerusalem wig store: The suspect, a Jerusalem resident in his 40s, was found by police detectives and began to drive away while violating traffic laws. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Majority of Israeli public believes conversion process needs a change: A survey was published that showed the opinions of the Israeli public regarding conversions. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Large asteroid stronger than nuke heading towards Earth late January: 2017 XC62 is estimated to be as much as 190 meters long, similar to the Tunguska asteroid, meaning it would be far more powerful than a nuclear bomb. Fortunately, an impact is… #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[German Jewish org slams court ruling in support of BDS events: Central Council of Jews condemns ruling by an administrative court that the city of Munich cannot ban the renting of rooms for BDS events. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gantz: rock throwers are terrorists, whoever they are: Gantz spoke out in the aftermath of a number of highly publicized incidents of violence against Palestinians attributed to settlers and or Jewish extremists. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shrimp superfood is coming to Israel: ECOshrimp aims to reinvent the shrimp-growing industry by means of a closed growing system. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden and Putin speak for 50 minutes: White House says Biden "urged Russia to de-escalate tensions with Ukraine" in phone call. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netanyhu trial must be seen through in the interest of Israel's democracy #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why flash floods are intensifying and what to do about it: Flash floods can’t be prevented or even well monitored, but there are ways to protect people and property from their deadly effects. 

The post Why flash floods are intensifying and… #URL# ISRAELITY #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uganda: Positively considering Israeli request to take in 500 Eritreans &amp; Sudanese refugees: Israel says it plans to deport the Eritrean and Sudanese asylum seekers to Uganda - but senior Ugandan officials have repeatedly denied the claim and… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magen David Adom CEO takes shifts at Covid testing sites: Eli Bin, head of the national emergency response group, joins managers pitching in across Israel due to the unprecedented testing demand. 

The post Magen David Adom CEO takes shifts… #URL# ISRAELITY #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A trigger warning without a trigger #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New daily COVID infections tops 10,000 in Israel: 10,644 new cases of COVID diagnosed in a single day, the highest number since September. 117 patients listed in serious condition. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate shock 8,200 years ago may have brought out the best in Russian hunter-gatherers: An anomalously large prehistoric cemetery in Russia precisely overlaps a 160-year cold spell in the Early Holocene epoch #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 15 myocarditis cases found among Israeli adolescents vaccinated against COVID: Hundreds of thousands of Israelis aged 12-15 have received a coronavirus vaccine shot, and a new study shows it's very rare for them to develop myocarditis #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia to repatriate 106 children from Eastern Syria: Russia plans to repatriate up to 106 children from the Al-Hol camp in Syria, known as a dumping ground for former ISIS members and refugees. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel sees fivefold increase in homeschooling requests over last decade: Close to 1,900 kids in Israel receive homeschooling, with the coronavirus pandemic accelerating the number of applications by parents #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security forces attacked by settlers over evacuation of illegal structure: Israel Police forces were attacked by settlers throwing stones, after arriving at Kumi Ori, near Yitzhar, to demolish an illegal structure. A number of police officers and… #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fourth COVID shot 'only partially effective against omicron,' initial Israeli findings suggest: Israeli researchers identify rise in antibody levels in people administered a second booster of the Pfizer COVID vaccine, but not enough to block the… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pregnant woman and baby injured in car explosion in central Israel: 29-year-old woman and her baby girl injured after car explodes in Rehovot. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spanish towns unearthing ancient synagogues for historical value, tourism: The goal is not only to preserve and foster Jewish history and culture, but also to draw tourism to small Spanish towns that lack tourists. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syrian refugees deported from Turkey for 'provocative' banana-eating: 31 suspects were investigated by Turkish police on charges of "provocatively" eating bananas in social media posts. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sudanese refugees in South Tel Aviv celebrate fall of Omar al-Basheer: Faiz who grew up in Darfur said he remembers clearly the day that the militants loyal to Bashir, known as the Janjaweed, arrived in his village in Darfur. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID-19: Pfizer and Moderna prepare vaccine against Omicron: The CEOs of Pfizer and Moderna say they are preparing a booster targeting Omicron. Pfizer CEO Albert Bourla is still unsure if there is a need for the fourth booster. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caroline Glick: The escalating international war against Israel #URL# ArutzShevaOpinion #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Their Warm, Healthy, Fully Vaccinated Hands: Podcast: Where does the masking debate go from here?View Post #URL# Commentary #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Israel's system will collapse': Top COVID officer warns of impending mass omicron infection: 'We will reach tens of thousands of infected people a day. People will not be able to be hospitalized,' the head of Israeli army's COVID task force said… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man and a dog, tsunami victims, found 3,500 years later: Israeli and Turkish researchers dig up remnants of massive natural disaster set off by a volcano, leaving a coastal community dormant for a century. 

The post A man and a dog,… #URL# ISRAELITY #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting to know you...: What is the antidote to polarization? Pharaoh and Joseph are a case in point. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lebanon's cabinet meets for the first time in months to discuss budget: The 2022 draft budget is expected to include tax increases in a country struggling to deal with soaring poverty levels and hyperinflation, also proposing deficit spending… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deri should be barred from politics - opinion: Preventing Deri from once again returning to a government position, following a repeat offense involving monetary misdeeds, would be a step showing that the country has had enough of corruption. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tnuva and Pluristem set up cultured meat joint venture: The joint venture aims to launch its first cultured meat products in 2023 and may also expand to cultured fish and dairy. #URL# Globes #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel Police solve rape case with DNA sample from used mask: A Jerusalem resident in his 30s was arrested for raping and physically assaulting a tourist back in 2009 after police took a DNA sample from a used mask. #URL# JPost #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Polish Foreign Minister warns of war in Europe as Russia-Ukraine talks hit dead end: Russia said dialogue was hitting a dead end as 100,000 were deployed within reach of Ukraine border, U.S. claims proof Russia is inventing pretext for invasion #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maggie Gyllenhaal only dreamed of directing. Two Israeli women made it possible for her: A pair of Israeli producers, who put together the critically acclaimed film "The Lost Daughter," recalls their first meeting with the actress turned director… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to cut ourselves some slack during a global pandemic: Be generous to yourself, avoid too much news and remember we are dealing with an unprecedented situation, says expert. 

The post How to cut ourselves some slack during a global… #URL# ISRAELITY #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defamed by the Anti Defamation League: If the ADL sees its role as policing how Jews defend themselves, their credibility will fall as fast as it did over this past week. Op-ed. #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four Syrians die after burning coal for heat in south Lebanon: Lebanon is home to 1.5 millions Syrian refugees, with the UN estimating that 90 percent of them live in extreme poverty #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superhumans, scapegoats and the far right: Busting the myth of Europe's 'migrant crisis': Migration is not a crisis unless we are willing to call most of human history a crisis, from Abraham onwards. Casting migration in a hostile light is still… #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haredi MK rips Avidgor Liberman: You're a borderline antisemite: UTJ chief Moshe Gafni excoriates Liberman, Yoaz Hendel over their calls to fire Chief Rabbi David Lau. 'Liberman learned only how to steal.' #URL# ArutzSheva #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands flee armed clashes in South Sudan: An estimated 5,000 South Sudanese refugees have made their way to Congo, and about 8,000 more are internally displaced, UN says #URL# Haaretz #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>