<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Dori: Seattle K9 killed in line of duty mourned; loss triggers memories for dog owners #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State failing to protect sex workers – Amnesty #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stavanger-studenten Khatireh (23) flyktet fra Afghanistan: – Fikk sjokk da jeg så at Taliban var i Norge #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covid-19: Omicron cases could double in days – modeller #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indigenous, Native American tribes are pushing for voting rights #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHOTOS: Winter storm pummels East Coast with high winds, deep snow #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slain teen who performed at Obama’s 2nd inauguration to be honored with presidential center garden #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carbon monoxide poisoning at hotel; 7 in critical condition #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detroit Man Charged In Livernois Avenue Shooting Killing 1, Injuring 2 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arlington police make arrest, recover money after Saturday bank robbery #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Altadena Man Arrested On Federal Gun Charge In Connection With BB Gun Shootings At Planned Parenthood In Pasadena #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chicago Bears Hire Colts Defensive Coordinator Matt Eberflus as Head Coach: AP Source #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Everything old is new again’ with feminine men trend #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold demand rebounds, but headwinds loom | Fin24 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kimmel Hits Donald Trump Jr. With The 2024 Campaign Ad Of His Nightmares #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 650,000 packages of Girl Scout Cookies were distributed in Anaheim to kick off cookie season #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[142 chickens confiscated from two Cape Town hawkers, SPCA to lay animal cruelty charges | News24 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stocks are turbulent as investors weigh new inflation data. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canceling classes to address teacher burnout, and how trains serve Houston (Jan. 28, 2022) | Houston Public Media #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One-day Coast to Coast event going ahead #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carmen Malijan Arrested after Hit-and-Run on Fletcher Drive [La Mesa, CA] #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peloton die-hards are sticking with the flailing company #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This New Taproom Will Never (Well, Rarely) Serve the Same Beer Twice #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion:  For students to flourish, teachers also must flourish. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Long Wait for Your COVID Test Results is Getting Even Longer #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tribal eviction plan pits Native American authority vs. civil rights #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Russia-Ukraine invasion may mean for Irish economy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In reunion, Ravens make Michigan’s Mike Macdonald, 34, youngest defensive coordinator in NFL #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Los Angeles to receive $53 million as part of California’s new youth jobs program #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[University apologises to students over celebrated composer’s alleged sexual assaults #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Industry experts reveal how more New Yorkers can prepare for tech jobs #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Best Redhead OnlyFans (Top Only Fans Red Heads)  – LA Weekly #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Northwestern Medicine Launches Nation’s First Urology Clinic Targeted Toward Needs Of Gay And Bisexual Men #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 priests, 2 lay people to be beatified in El Salvador #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rafael Nadal vs Daniil Medvedev, Australian Open 2022 men’s final: What time is it and where to watch on TV #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McDonald's Happy Meal earns nod for 'most memorable fast food' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oliver M. Brandes and Rosie Simms: Securing and protecting our water, its natural habitat both a practical and policy priority #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adams Once Lobbied For Raise The Age Law — Now His Push To Roll It Back Faces Headwinds In Albany #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia says wants ‘respectful’ ties with US #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The World Can’t Go Green and Nuclear Free #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadian athletes begin to arrive in Beijing for 2022 Olympic Games | CBC Sports #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Around 114,500 people believed to have had or will get long Covid | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Dry toast and Marmite’: Tamaki on time in jail, losing 7kg #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High Speed Chase Leads To Elk Being Euthanized In Garfield County #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU Chief Slammed For Secret Texts To Pfizer CEO, Ordered To Turn Them In #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sarah Palin Spotted Dining Out in NYC Again, 2 Days After Positive COVID Test #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Hospitals weathered this storm’: Doctor discusses future of pandemic as hospitalizations decline #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Symphonic Exploration of That Time the US Kidnapped and Imprisoned More Than 100,000 Japanese Americans #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dave Hyde: Miami wants a diminished coach, thinks it’s close to contending — and (sigh) still looks like the Dolphins #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘The board put it on me saying, ‘You’re the one to do the job, you’re after saying what needs to change’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. East Coast plunged into deep freeze, mounds of snow after powerful storm – National | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction begins on 'unicorn' industrial site in south Phoenix #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A quiet end to the weekend, but a messy storm threatens midweek #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ash Street lobbyist ordered to appear for deposition next week #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petrol, diesel and supermarket shopping among the things likely to rise in price #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victoria announces additional kinder year #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Denver Animal Protection seeking information about man who dropped off ‘severely sick’ dog #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flash flooding closes section of Stuart Highway in South Australia #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Supreme Court Will Soon Have Its 1st Black Woman Judge: Joe Biden #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boris Johnson reportedly considering delay to tax hike plans as public awaits publication of Sue Gray report #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harry and Meghan weigh in on Spotify row saying they expressed concerns about COVID misinformation last April #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xiomara Castro becomes Honduras’ first female president #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayer and Prostitutes: Redeeming Love Tackles Faith-Based Romance – LA Weekly #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Water Main Break Floods Cahuenga Blvd. In Hollywood Hills #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kourtney Kardashian and fiancé Travis Barker mocked for ’embarrassing’ PDA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adams to NYPD’s 35,000 Cops: ‘I’m Here for You … New Yorkers Are Here for You’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six arrested after investigation into robberies targeting Asian women in San Jose #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oklahoma executes man for 2001 slayings of 2 hotel workers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Much Snow Did You Get? Latest Snow Totals #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oil executives barred from leaving Peru after massive spill #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sutton Stracke re-follows Erika Jayne, wants to be ‘the bigger person’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Houston eviction courts are packed again as numbers return to pre-COVID levels | Houston Public Media #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matt Gay’s 30-yard FG lifts Rams over Tom Brady, Buccaneers in NFC divisional round #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Councilmember Campillo Urges SANDAG to Prioritize Suicide Barrier on Coronado Bridge #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Magnolia Bakery location opens for business in Hudson Yards | amNewYork #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taliban hold first talks in Europe since Afghan takeover #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden leading Trump, DeSantis by similar margins in new poll #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coloradans Wake Up to More Snow and Low Visibility as Cold Front Moves In #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Culinary Arts Students Deliver Tasty Fare at Great Prices at These College Eateries #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homeless Encampment Sweeps Begin Near SoFi Stadium Ahead Of Super Bowl #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Star-studded LA Rams host surging 49ers in NFC title game #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wall Street split on ‘buying the dip’ in whipsawing US stock market #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mesha Maren describes how novel ‘Perpetual West’ explores lives across the Mexican-American border #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sotheby’s Just Sold a Botticelli for $45.4 Million #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hero mail carrier saves elderly woman’s life in New Hampshire #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staycation frenzy spurs Center Parcs owner to prepare £4bn sale #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Austin tenants without gas, hot water, heat for a month #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon Leases 202K SF Warehouse In East LA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Prioritizing Antiviral Pills for ‘Non-White’ People #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mask Mandate Exceptions for Offices and Gyms Return Next Week In SF As Omicron Surge Dissipates #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York college student dies after being found unconscious outside in extreme cold: Police #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State of Texas: Amid concern for soldiers in Operation Lone Star, leaders work to address issues #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the pandemic’s unequal toll on people of color underlines U.S. health inequities – and why solving them is so critical #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom Convoy 2022: Police report no injuries, ‘no incidents of violence’ after first day of protest #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neighbors Hold Anti-Violence March, Vigil After Similar Shootings Of Two Young Girls #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coach’s classy response to player’s pride jumper stance #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Garland Shooting Victim’s Family Continues Grieving As Suspect Abel Acosta Remains At Large #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rams Fans Prepare for NFC Championship Game #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kokkinakis &amp; Kyrgios beat Ebden &amp; Purcell to win Australian Open men’s doubles final – as it happened #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fishing warning: Mega-red king crabs from Norway invade Britain – threat to local catch #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Polar bear skulls shipped to New York by boutique owner from Canada, feds say #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FDA bans two monoclonal antibodies over Omicron variant. Here’s why. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newcastle agree fee with Brighton to sign defender Dan Burn #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ed Sheeran On ‘The Best Thing’ That Comes From Not Having A Phone #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French Bulldog Owner Pleads for Return of 2 Dogs Stolen in Oakland #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill to ban transgender students from school sports passes Indiana House #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pharmacist helps people of color get access to COVID tests #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Projection mapping: Art and technology illuminated #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IRS Website Will Soon Require Facial Recognition To Log Into Your Account #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hubble Contacts accused of ‘creating needless risk’ for customers; agrees to pay millions in settlement #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel president on 1st visit to UAE amid regional tension #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Draymond Green signs first-of-its-kind media deal with Turner Sports #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prince Harry, Meghan Markle threaten Spotify over COVID-19 misinformation without mentioning Joe Rogan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swedish dishcloth review: An eco-friendly paper towel | CNN Underscored #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Ku Klux Klan Hall In Fort Worth Being Turned Into ‘Arts And Community Healing’ Space #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lashley NEW WWE Champ after Brock Lesnar was screwed by Heyman and Reigns #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men’s soccer: After Canada’s historic night in Honduras, now all eyes are on Hamilton #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bayou Bistro and Bar owner killed in Texas City shooting #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Changes ‘Fight Club’ Ending To Have Authorities Win #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Open men’s final live: ‘Insane’ Nadal has turned final on its head #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are Asian women the target of xenophobia? – The San Francisco Examiner #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security guard ‘attempts to engage’ gunman during fatal shooting of man trying to turn his life around through anti-violence organization, officials say #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conservative post-election report says O’Toole was ‘over-managed’ during the campaign | CBC News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What will next week’s Russian manoeuvres off Ireland look like and what’s the overall strategy? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspect Jailed in Arson Fires at El Cajon Bank #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden Resettles 66K Afghans in U.S. with Help from Clinton, Bush, Obama #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In India’s Militarized Regions, Calls for Ending Impunity #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transient on probation arrested for allegedly setting fires to ATM’s in East County – #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IMPD: Arrest made in overnight murder on city’s west side #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4Site Real Estate oversees two mixed-use projects being built in Lincoln Heights #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aziz Ansari’s Nostalgic New Comedy Special #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michigan High School Students Participating In Safe Driving Campaign #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Revolutionary” Estate in Greenwich Sells for $11.77 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perth Scorchers smash Sixers in BBL final #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wounded Warrior Project 5K raises money to help injured veterans ‘Carry Forward’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Irish clowns defeated orange Toronto cops #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AP Sources: Despite Reports, Tom Brady Hasn’t Made Up Mind On Retirement #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meow Wolf Introduces Party Portal, a Series of Immersive Concerts #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Questlove’s ‘Summer of Soul’ soundtrack released on first anniversary of its premiere at Sundance #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kaizer Chiefs’ best signings in the January transfer window #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supes unanimously approve ordinance requiring landlords give 10-day notice before evictions – The San Francisco Examiner #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We investigated injuries at Texas trampoline parks. Here’s what parents should know #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arrest Made In Venice Arson Fires, Investigators Looking For Second Man #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skills shortage and energy costs among biggest concerns of Irish businesses – report | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dallas Police Searching For Answers About A Man Who Died In A Liquor Store After Being Shot Several Times #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Disappointment May Be Coming For St. Patrick’s Day: Corned Beef Prices Are Shooting Up, Some Local Butchers Aren’t Even Carrying It #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Brady to announce retirement from NFL #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justin Bieber becomes the first artist with 10 tracks with over a billion Spotify streams. Here are the songs that smashed records #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coast Guard finds four more migrant bodies off Florida coast #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mega Millions winning lottery ticket worth $426 million sold at Woodland Hills gas station #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nor’easter To Bring Plowable Snow And Possibly Blizzard Conditions Saturday #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Montana curbs wolf hunt after 23 from Yellowstone killed #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scores of guns stolen from trains cause more problems in L.A. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK weather: Storm Corrie set to hit just hours after two people die from falling trees in Storm Malik – as Met Office issues warnings #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan’s Mitsubishi, energy body join Gates’ nuclear project #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[B.C. clerk says she didn’t see rationale for predecessor’s retirement benefit #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pinpoint Weather Alert Day: Expect snowfall until Thursday afternoon #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman who sexually assaulted 10-year-old girl as teen will serve sentence in juvenile facility #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK weather: Woman killed and 62,000 homes lose power in Storm Malik – and country to be battered by Storm Corrie within hours #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mercury Air Cargo Leases 163K SF Near LAX #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daily Cartoon: Friday, January 28th #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women’s Ashes Test match, day three: Australia v England – live! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia could welcome back international tourists by Easter, PM says #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free N95 Masks are Arriving in San Diego: Here’s Where You Can Find Them #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tiger King’s Joe Exotic re-sentenced to 21 years in prison #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Targeted shooting injures two men in Newton: RCMP #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honduras: Chaos in congress as politicians brawl over election of new president #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power Outage Hits Thousands of SDG&amp;E Customers in North County #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘I tried’: Quebec mosque attack survivor recounts fateful night #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How will US respond to 9/11 victims seeking frozen Afghan funds? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pete Davidson sports fake chipped tooth while meeting John Mulaney’s baby #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joni Mitchell wants music removed from Spotify in covid row #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP Sen. Dismisses Black Woman SCOTUS Pick Citing Affirmative Action #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kilroy Realty Included in Bloomberg Gender Equality Index for 2022 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Park is ground zero in Colorado’s wolf controversy. Ranchers want to know if anyone hears them. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Jersey Residents Stock Up On Snow Supplies And Girl Scout Cookies Ahead Of Nearly 10 Inches Of Snow #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State says 225,000 free COVID-19 rapid test kits available to vulnerable communities in 14 counties #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘I feel alive’: Nadal conquers self-doubt as he chases record 21st major #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Catskill zoo hits the market for $3.6M #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West End Coworkers Struck With Car Thefts, Part of City-Wide Uptick #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Basketball Becomes A Place To Talk Mental Health #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auckland light rail tunnel to run to Mt Roskill before following SH20 to the airport #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jacina Ardern in self-isolation as Covid cases rise in New Zealand #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPDATE: No shots fired, Gateway Mall spokesperson says after 5 armed men hit jewellery store | News24 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jogger in NYC’s Central Park finds skeletal remains #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Oakland County Priest Pleads Guilty In Sex Abuse Cases, Sentenced Up To 15 Years #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raanta returns, helps Hurricanes beat Devils #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Court Throws Pennsylvania’s Mail-In Voting Law Into Doubt #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wild Edge Rangers 3-2 To Spoil Lundqvist Jersey Retirement #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little Village Community Groups Call for Mental Health Resources After Gang Shooting Kills 8-Year-Old #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Run-on Review of The Woman in the House Across the Street … #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homeland Security employee charged with molesting young girls in Orange County #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lewis has triple-double, No. 11 Baylor women cruise 87-54 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest on the winter storm hitting part of the East Coast #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upcoming Events: Maize Dinner, Lunar New Year Festivities #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto Catholic board asks OLRB to force union to reveal schools to be hit by strikes next week #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supercross: Eli Tomac wins Round 4 of series in Anaheim #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robinson goal lifts USMNT over El Salvador 1-0 in World Cup qualifier #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the middle of a pandemic, I felt alone and disconnected. A warm and welcoming church in Normal Heights changed everything #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grammy-nominated band urges fans to ‘delete Spotify’ – with message on the streaming platform itself #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>