<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The Shirelles-Greatest Hits
Steppenwolf-Live at the Matrix
3 Dog Night-Harmony
Doors-The Soft Parade
J Geils Band-Nightmares
 Bloodshot
Kansas-Leftoverture
Golden Earing-Moontan
Crosby,Stills,Nash&amp; Young-Deja vu
The Fleetwoods-Greatest Hits
The Golden Earrings-
Boz Skaggs &amp; Band-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear America,
 Fani Willis is the DA of Fulton County, GA. She is not the AG of Georgia. That man's name is Christopher M. Carr. He hasn't started an investigation of t***p. (Yet)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# 
People taking care of people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know if they could reverse Roe, some assholes in the gop would try to make it retroactive, so they could arrest anyone who ever had or provided an abortion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait till Tucker's Qrazy followers snatch the mask off a child who just had a heart transplant.
People wear masks for other reasons besides COVID.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Alainis isn't it #HASHTAG# That Condoleezza  Rice has to tell RW to lay off Susan Rice about bad information on a terrorist attack?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This moron kept skipping every other election. Did you notice? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Amen #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deny him the ability to run for office and he'll just start a Mega Church...That he'll never step foot in.

The Grift is the Goal. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My black cat, Mr. Re]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reince Priebus wants to run for governor of Wisconsin, because their republican legislators aren't bad enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My guess is the 4 Blackwater guys will be working for Prince again very soon. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The sign of a good host.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today was a #HASHTAG# pure and simple.
Qanon needs to be declared a domestic terror organization]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jewish Space Lasers
Italian Ballot Satellites
Forestry Service Moon Movers

Republicans have more belief in Science Fiction than they do Science.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# of all ironies is the #HASHTAG# hates gays &amp; women. The only people who like dicks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Hitler's death, thousands of Germans committed suicide.

After Trump's defeat thousands of maga/Q have committed suicide via COVID.

Turns out they didn't even need the cyanide laced Kool-Aid. They just had to go to a BBQ without a mask.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unemployment just went up.

Lou Dobbs show cancelled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many of you grew up assuming fish breathed by breaking a water molecule into oxygen and hydrogen, instead of taking suspended oxygen out of the water?

How many of you still thought that until you read this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Chicago to Buffalo thru Canada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm waiting. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 4k + tweets in only 3 months is an obvious bot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Madison Cawthorn know how Fascist regimes usually treat people in wheelchairs?
About as well as every other minority.

Pushing for one is like putting a noose around his own neck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She's killing it post Big Bang, with Harley Quinn and now The Flight Attendant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Losing a mobster's stash of bath tub gin to the cops. Yea, I think they did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put it this way. Trump's speech was the Viagra to the mob's hours long #HASHTAG#. The #HASHTAG# is the operation to remove the damaged tissue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sadly, there are more than enough so called 'legal' weapons in the country for them to use. Add in IEDs and the ingredients for a civil war are all in the mix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the fuck did they ever convince people that Health Insurance should be separate from Dental, Hearing, and Vision?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Do we need a RL Arkum Asylum? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, because she also says it when the story isn't stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raise your hand if you didn't spend 9/11 embarrassing yourself.

Uh-uh, not you Donald.

You neither, Rudy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since I won't have internet much longer I might as well be as honest as I can.

Someone needs to beat some humanity into Manchin and Sinema. I have no illusions that the gop is salvageable.

If someone wants to beat them anyway, I'm OK with that too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RW #HASHTAG# insist on kids going to Sunday School.nnCalls Head Start indoctrination of the young.nn#HASHTAG# weeps from the #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many Immigrants are serving in the military right now.nMany #HASHTAG# never did, but think the military should keep out immigrants.n#HASHTAG# alert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always wondered why republicans think its a good idea to keep food servers at slave wages. Do they like the taste of spit that much?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you realize that the Catholic Church's views about the Earth being the center of he Universe have evolved over the centuries.n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arizona gop: After we show the world that Trump won, he can undo everything Biden did.

So he's gonna take back all the vaccine shots?

AZ gop: Damn straight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it possible the reason no one in America recognizes this MF is because he's not from here? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pending may not be pending for much longer. #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2069

Teacher: Who can tell me when they outlawed facts?

Student: In 2021.

Teacher: Report to the Principal's Office for Uneducation. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christians believe someone committing suicide because they can't take the pain of life any more deserves an eternity of torture.n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wholly fuck! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home of the 9/11 highjackers (Saudi Arabia) thinks #HASHTAG# are all terrorists.n#HASHTAG# takes another body blow from #HASHTAG# n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Send in Boyd. He was really good at taking out the competition. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[republicans wanted to send COVID patients to Guantanamo. Then T***p got COVID and they said, "Okay, maybe not."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Killing over 500k Americans and grifting millions of dollars somehow only made T***p the 4th worst president ever.

At least according to the study quoted by Jody Hamilton (#USER#) on the #USER# today.

I demand a recount!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, I wrote what I meant. A sensor. Sorry if you missed the pun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the feds seized my phone, maybe they could find out why two texts won't stay deleted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really want to know how polls are considered accurate, when great swaths of the population, myself included, would never answer their phone for an unknown number.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If I was ever interested in going anywhere, I would.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Now that you mention it, my family had a LOT of cats. Maybe it rubbed off?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the money paid to the families of those killed by police had to come out of the police budget, those in charge might rethink keeping the officers who cost them millions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a shame twitter didn't exist when my mom and all her cats were alive. She could have been a star.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These MFs really only have one answer for anything. And it's never been right once. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They are the #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberals see something beautiful, they want 2 appreciate &amp; protect it.nnConservatives see it, they want 2 exploit &amp; destroy it.n#HASHTAG# name]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have, in my lifetime, eaten an entire large deep dish pizza by myself. The thought of 76 hot dogs is...🤢🤮💀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Molina has always been the Cardinals' catcher, right? I can't remember a time when he wasn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Mr. and Mrs. Maga,
 If the Capitol was attacked by BLM and Antifa, why don't McConnell and the republicans want an investigation to prove it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has Manchin ever used the filibuster, that he's fighting so hard  to keep? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is when bigots come out of the closet while trying to put gay people back inside.n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you name the person who was in Basic Instinct and No Way Out and an episode of Stargate SG-1, without looking it up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fruit Loops Pizza?

What the fuck are you people doing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please tell the RW Fanboys to piss off. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Lindsey, you think the students of Notre Dame aren't religious? 🤣
#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is calling your rivals 'Commies' while revering the former head of the KGB for his stance on gays.nn#HASHTAG##HASHTAG##HASHTAG##HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I'm really disappointed in Richard. I guess he'll have to go by Dick now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four years of "Lock her up" chants and trump couldn't even invent a reason to do it, let alone find a legitimate reason. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You just know trump is gonna have every channel on every tv in the WH, except FOX, OAN, &amp; Newsmax locked out, fight before he leaves for the last time.

Assuming he hasn't stolen them all.

right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forgot one album.

Rolling Stones-Dirty Work (Unopened)
Alternate red cover #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's no surprise that the people who believe rape is fine think their germs should be allowed to go wherever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask RW Christians to stop telling you how to live your life &amp; they'll get offended because you're telling them how to live their lifen#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Others have similar feelings. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born into #HASHTAG# (Greek) for Honoring godnMatthew (Hebrew) for Gift of godnMe (American) for #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are the illegal drugs the only ones whose price goes down?

Oh right, competition.

So the insulin makers are the good guys?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pardon me, Ivermectin. Have to get the horse de-wormer's name right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Manchin is taking political donations like he thinks he'll get reelected.

Magic 8-Ball says... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Insert Mandy Patinkin meme here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Me neither. We're math dyslexic. We can't hold numbers in our heads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything's bigger in Texas, especially the f**k ups. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman murdered her own children because she "Didn't want them trafficked by pedophiles" as she believed they inevitably would be, because she listened to Qanon.
Kids find guns and kill themselves, because their parents listen to GOP/NRA/Fox propaganda and buy them constantly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are Gaetz and Boebert gonna be arrested any time soon?

Well, I should say rearrested. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is happening right now is exactly the kind of madness I expected all along. I am only shocked that it took so long.
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How often did your mom make spam for dinner when you were a kid?

It was at least once a week at our house, which she loved and I thought was way too often. Once a month would have been okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And growing #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American Christians: Hate sinners.n nWorship guys who work every Sunday.n n#HASHTAG# Alert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Technically a drug.

Try hopping. My grandmother bought things and put them in a spare bedroom where they stayed till after she died.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I guess he just didn't have the same connections Rudy had, to get the good stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The vaccine for stupidity is education and the gop has been fighting against that for decades. This anti-vax movement of theirs isn't a new phenomena.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nina Hartley needs to do a Master Class on masturbation for #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really really want an asteroid sized ball of karma to land on DeSantis, Abbott, and of course TFG.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least no one is asking Sean to do a song for the Sputnik 🇷🇺 Vaccine...Yet.
#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're following 500,000 accounts, you're following none. You might as well have all of twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to teach Steph about equine anatomy sounded like a kid trying to teach their parents how to program a tv remote. #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you signed up for the military, you agreed to get shot at, bombed, and possibly gassed. If you're afraid of a vaccination that 12yos aren't afraid to take, you really aren't the tough guy you think you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If they weren't working for corporations, maybe. They are though. Corporations that aren't interested in truth, just profits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rich white people who's taxes go to pay for poor black people to go to ER's think those people having health insurance is a bad idea.n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd think racist white guys would be more interested in minority rights...n nSeeing as they technically are minorities.n n#HASHTAG# hurts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I missed where this whole thing started. Who was the putz?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh. It's the OTHER one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How come the gop is so worried about trans girls playing sports they try desperately to defund, so football can get all the money?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID can cause cognitive deficits. 
Like the maga who refuse the vaccine can afford to lose even one brain cell?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Supremacy
Fascism
Stolen Valor
Corruption
Insurrection
This is what has become of the GOP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simply Red Shifted
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Some people are destined to be Sarah Connor and some people are destined to be Miles Dyson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No species has worked harder at making itself extinct, other than pandas. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to #HASHTAG# list the attacks Georgia republicans made on voting rights, made me want to vomit. The glee with which they will turn this nation into a fascist, one party, white's only state is phenomenal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have never slept with any people, just cats.

I've had sex with 8 people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How does a 19yo become so angry at his former job that he goes back to kill?
How long could he have worked there? I've worked years with people I really hated and never thought about hurting them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It went from bleach, to hydroxychloroquine, to Ivermectin. What's next...Hemlock?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That sucks, but they get to do that. That's why T***p's lawsuit is a joke. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't do the crime (Sedition), if you can't do he time. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That didn't bother me. The monster baby from It's Alive was my nightmare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# that U.S. leads the world in prisoners &amp; yet so many deserving criminals are still free (Cheney, Rice, North,  most CEO's) #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know every device Rudy owned was full of Russian malware, right? He really has to hope Putin never decides that he's lost his useful idiot status.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America...Land of the Free. Home of the BIGGEST MORONS ON THE PLANET. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Person of Interest has apparently been taken into custody in the #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh, I think we've now seen many other republicans are just as capable of being just as awful.
Abbott
DeSantis
Noem
Ivey
Ducey
And on and on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Then: "Who knew healthcare was so complicated?"n#HASHTAG# Now: "Look at how small our plan is." (#HASHTAG# Alert!!)nDemocrats knew Donny. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know, since Bernie isn't actually a Dem, doesn't that make any legislation he votes for Bipartisan?

Can Manchin get off his ass now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You'll be getting those long after you die. My mom's been gone for 2 1/2 years and she's still getting them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be fooled, the republicans are all for CRT.

Christian Ruling Theocracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Normal? You mean back to gun massacres every week?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know at least a couple of these guys are #HASHTAG# for Israel.nBecause #HASHTAG# knows no bounds. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If RW brains were damaged (As studies have shown) before they got COVID, what are they going to be like after the infection adds even more?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnlyFrans is removing The Nanny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[gQp election plan

Step 1: Enact law to overturn elections if there is any fraud.
Step 2: Commit fraud during election.
Step 3: Declare election invalid because there was fraud.
Step 4: Give election to your candidate.
Step 5: Repeat steps 2-4 every election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way I can describe Texas in one word is, RANCID.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Shouldn't it really be Non-social?

We don't want to burn down society.

That's the people going to Trump rallies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[gop senators are holding a life preserver as they watch democracy drown and they refuse to toss it into the water.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The cops who police cops are called 'Rats' by the cops.

Not just by the corrupt cops, by all cops.

So, police reform needs to happen ASAP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think the only reason to do it is if you're older and have no kids or spouse. When you die, no one's getting that house anyway. You might as well get some money back to enjoy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dance studio, Cha-Cha's became a comedy club, Ha-ha's. And then a strip club, Ta-Ta's. Then a diner, Mama's. Then a pizzeria, Papa's. Then a sports bar, Rah-Rah's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True #HASHTAG# is #HASHTAG# praying to god in thanks for a meal composed of #HASHTAG# frankenfood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Enough was enough after Charles Joseph Whitman's massacre on August 1st, 1966. Four weeks before I was born.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not even like Manchin and Sinema are using their reluctance to deal for anything for their constituents. They're just being tools for tool's sake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can understand old white men being afraid of immigrants taking over the nation, when you realize that's how they did it.n#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dems give you healthcare

republicans take your voting rights and electricity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RW christians believe in fairy tales from 2,000 years ago without a shred of evidence, but won't believe facts they can see with their own eyes, that masks and vaccines work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Till the next one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So guys who spend most of their leisure time objectifying women sexually are worried that gays in the #USER# will be objectifying them?n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do actual people still join Facebook?

How long till the deceased out number the living?

The fake accounts already have to, don't they?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So you're gonna stick around for another 40-50 years? Good for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[republicans want a government small enough to drown in a bathtub and voters dumb enough to keep reelecting them no matter how many people thy kill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They really should be called '#HASHTAG#'
Have you looked at who keeps pushing these things?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There is no person in this country more toxic to democracy and our future, than McConnell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They never stopped. It just didn't make the news as often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You all want an edit button, while I just want twitter to stop pushing suggested topics on me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What their behavior deserves

Cuomo Level: Slap/punch in the face

tRump Level: Cut off the balls

That's the difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The people most likely to keep their kids out of schools pre-pandemic are the ones yelling the loudest to open schools immediately during the pandemic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Vocabulary lesson of the day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every pardon is an arrow pointing to a potential bribery charge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've had a Rapture joke prepared for years. Under cover of dark, lay out clothes in front of the house of your religious neighbor and then watch them cry about being left behind when they wake up in the morning.
#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear American police,
 It's not unarmed black men you need to fear. It's white men armed with flagpoles flying Thin Blue Line flags. They literally tried to kill cops with them. Also, white guys with fire extinguishers and assault rifles, both of whom HAVE killed police officers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is why I feed the squirrels around my house. So they won't go carnivore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Russia's got plenty of room. There's only 145 million people there and it's the largest nation in area.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Impeachment Trial has a jury that's half full of the Defendant's gang.

No mobster ever had it so good.

At least until the regular trials start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't they just make you show a membership card to get into the store? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you know who Roy Hinkley is without using Google, Bing, or Ask Jeeves...

It just means you're a nerd. We don't have to be friends or anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Manchin &amp; Sinema actually cared about their constituents, they'd be using their position as swing votes to get things for their states. Instead they are just blocking everything, for no reason other than to be in the news everyday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[republicans keep suing Dem governors to roll back mask mandates.

Has anyone sued the republican legislatures that force those rollbacks, which immediately spike the COVID numbers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The very second the next gQp president is installed through their voter suppression.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know why you don't have a Small Pox scar on your arm, because your parents and grandparents all got them and destroyed the virus' ability to replicate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm just glad our side has Lawrence Tribe and the RW get Dersh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I don't read horror. Not even sci-fi horror. Just not my genre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That clip will be playing non-stop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# GOP: Gold Medalists at the Darwin Awards every year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That looked familiar. Then I remembered why. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump said "Show up on Jan 6th. It's gonna be wild." And they did.
With 'Jan 6th Civil War' t-shirts.

Just because the plan was slipshod, doesn't mean there was no plan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If England doesn't allow Fox (Is Not) News, why allow someone copying their model?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[007 could have stayed, but after living with real life Bond villains in the world for years now, I'm done. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And you were great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[22 of my followers are also following this putz. That makes no sense. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't know I could have less than 0% interest in a show. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#
The Electric Slide Company #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Matthew Firebird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK wait, wait the rebels in the Philippines are called MILF and they're Muslim? #HASHTAG# you never, ever let me down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate Deniers
COVID Deniers
They're all the same. They don't care if they die, so why would they care if you die? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You blame Obama for cops being shot in states with lax gun laws while screaming that he's coming for your #HASHTAG#.nDo you know what #HASHTAG# is?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I still wonder why mom and dad are afraid of touching the kid's underwear when none of them are ever wearing clothes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs no.
republican politicians? All kinds of
Yes
Si
Da
Ja
Hai #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I can't wait for Dr. Z to interview Space Ghost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, please join the site hosted on Russian servers and monitored by U.S. Intelligence agencies. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey maga, if we have the technology to put chips in vaccines to control YOU, why didn't we put it in the 5,000 Taliban we had imprisoned, that Trump released?

Wouldn't that have been a good way to keep them from taking over again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when people were thinking Mitch was getting ready to retire?

Yeah, that was bullshit. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden: Buy American.

republicans: (crickets)

Media: Why can't Biden unite the country?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the thing, if Donald isn't dead or in jail by 2024 the gop probably won't run anyone else in the primary, and in the general they'll just say he won in every state they control.
We have to protect voting and democracy from these  MFs.
Pass #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I didn't hear about it till Watchmen. And I thought it was made up for the show till people on twitter started posting about the real thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, but I bet he likes that people thinks he is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Continuing to work as a journalist for media corporations that helped get a man elected who did nothing but attack journalists is about as dumb as anything I ever heard. Self preservation must be a rare quality in the profession.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[L.A. County has 10 times the population of Wyoming. How about we make 10 states there? Or we could just condense Wyoming, the Dakotas, Idaho, and Montana into one state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know who's busy for the first time in four years?
The people who VET appointees for their Security clearances. The rubber stamp has been retired.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry, I don't play with brain dead trolls. Go forth and be blocked. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OAN's logo might as well be a Silver Death's Head. They're already 99.95% Nazi, they might as well go all the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well look at that, it's dark and quiet. I guess everyone used up all their fireworks last night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeding the Qanon Qult another "We have to protect the Children" piece of raw meat. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They're not racing alone,
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cut off shorts are just sons of britches.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to an unmasked AVI, but I'm still gonna wear a mask in the grocery store. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not getting vaccinated is the new "Drinking the Kool-Aid" #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>