<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember the outrage when a rodeo clown wore an Obama mask?

Fun times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I don't believe a pregnant person can be forced to remain pregnant; that doesn't mean they can destroy the fetus. They can remove the fetus if it is medically feasible and allow them to grow artificially. They cannot intentionally destroy them simply because they don't want it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Much less a war.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how they treat us WITH guns.

Imagine what they'd do if we gave them up? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There's a difference?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think she's been pretty vocal about wasted embryos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What does Trump have up his sleeve? Anything?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Something needs to be done about China. The CCP needs to be overthrown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Will the NCAA also abolish gendered sports? Why have men's &amp; women's basketball? Why not just basketball? Best players make the team. Same for every sport.

Best player makes the team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For supposedly being the most popular president ever elected, Biden sure is awfully insecure, isn't he?

Hey, if anyone's gonna remove him, it's the hyena standing off in the wings like the Grim Reaper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yes. It's not the job of the government to provide housing for people at the expense of others at the barrel of a gun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Robbed of $150k
Makes $13mil/year
82 games in a season
= $158k per game.

Literally one day's work. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow I was a big Montero defender. Kept basically saying at least give him consistent MLB at bats at DH rather than leaving him in minors. Forget that he's slow and a poor catcher. Just give him 4-5 ABs a game and see if he can knock one out.

Sounds like today's game. HRs and Ks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The reverse argument is they should be made to witness an abortion and all it entails. Personally, I don't want or need that, and wouldn't try to force anyone else to see it. If people don't wanna see something, they don't have to. I don't want to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Do you really not see the difference? Choosing to kill a human in utero vs you wake up one day and find your legs covered in blood.

Difference is intent. One is natural, one is deliberate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Ok, so you support forcing birth after 12 weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Appeal to personal incredulity. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Who wants govt to enforce rule?
Not me.
So back abolish governments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Babies have survived being born at 21 weeks. With advancing technology that will get earlier and earlier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Based on games purchased, Assassin's Creed.

NBA2k is up there.
Elder Scrolls and Fallout.
The Sims.
Mass Effect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No, not really. I was under the impression that presidents don't have that much impact, but seeing the absolute disaster job Biden is doing, I'm rather enjoying this. Why go back to CNN getting to crucify Trump every day? Funner to see the media without anything to report.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I have no problem declaring moral superiority over people who are fine with killing human babies in utero. It's an atrocity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, we need to run guns to

- Cuba
- Australia
- Hong Kong
- Taiwan
- UK

Any other suggestions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# well since jews cause all the violence in ME, syria will now be most peaceful nation on earth. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Minarchism is prettier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This whole vigilante accusation breaks down because the case the prosecution tried to make is that the people who attacked Kyle were trying to stop an active shooter. In other words, they were vigilantes, trying to stop a criminal instead of leaving it to police.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Standard election fraud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Will you also stop sales in Occupied Constantinople?
Or Occupied Manchuria?
Occupied Hong Kong?
Occupied Tibet?
Occupied Smyrna?
Occupied Tenochtitlan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The people running it only run it because the people keep electing them. The crux of the matter is, rights and liberty should not be up to a vote. It's a stupid idea, with no upsides.

If ppl really want to vote on something, then whatever they vote on should only apply to them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He's looking worse with each game.

Overthrowing guys.
Inaccurate.
Taking a sack instead of just throwing it away.
Looked like he didn't WANT Metcalf catching anything when he finally started throwing to him. All un-catchable except one.
INT to end game.

He gives zero f****s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government: grants itself monopolistic power over energy.
Public energy fails.
Leftists: see what capitalism does! ðŸ¤ª #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yes, but they mostly fall under self-harm. There are ways in which they affect others. Drinking alcohol while pregnant, breathing (think Corona), smoking cigarettes (second hand smoke). I don't support govt laws against these. Drunk driving I think can properly be illegal,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will anyone ask Biden if he renounces the Catholic Church for its stance on same-sex marriage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Because it is primarily self-harm. Self-harm is not sufficient warrant to use force. There is no victim really beyond themselves. You want to hurt yourself, ok. ðŸ˜• You want to hurt others, no, govt can act.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# baby powder. I'll wait and see which vaccines are most effective and least dangerous. Till then I survived a year and a half of a supposed global pandemic doing most everything I could TO get sick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not going to the gym resulted in weight gain (+15lbs) which negatively affects my health. Also Covid is especially dangerous if you're obese.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# No nation is wealthy. Nations produce nothing. People are wealthy. People produce. Governments only steal and redistribute wealth, often taking the biggest cut for themselves. The base salary for a Congressman works out to about $85/hr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Ppl get sick. It's how life goes. Govt won't stop it.

Wash your hands regularly.
Wear a mask if you have cold/flu symptoms or stay home.
Take vaccines if you want.

But other than that, live. Enjoy life. Don't treat everyone as potentially diseased or medical apartheid/shaming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Same for Red Sox fans especially. Do that many ppl from Boston live here?

I won't even get into the Blue Jays fans. I'll say this, if Boston was the only American hockey team, and I went up to see Boston vs Vancouver or Calgary, I'd root for the Canadian team. Closer to home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I legit thought Tennessee's said incestual.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Your mom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I dunno, I don't doubt the possibilities of science. If I was a bit more inclined and knowledgeable on it, I'd look into it myself. Seems like it'd be something good to research and develop. Would eliminate the whole need for abortions in the first place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Most peaceful administration in 90 years. No new wars. Avoided war with Iran. Smoothed tensions with North Korea, Russia/Ukraine, and China.

Best economy since Reagan. Slashed regulations.

Got vaccines out when everyone said it was impossible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Seattle junior hockey and MLB.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# How do you get money? Through work. Giving up your body.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I dunno why people just stand and watch as people get arrested one by one. Protect each other. Don't let them take any of you. You out-number them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# When else has this kind of behavior ever been acceptable? All these rules are punishing healthy people, while people who may actually actively have Covid are not restricted at all. You could have Covid and go into every store &amp; restaurant in town and no one would know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Why do you think a baby doesn't have a right to your organs, but you have a right to compel others through their labor to provide you with free healthcare? You are claiming a right over others to compel them to provide you with sustenance while simultaneously saying no one can]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well they blindly trusted government.

We've seen what government really does. It's their own fault by losing integrity.

Can't trust govt.
Can't trust media.

They tell lie after lie, and then wonder why people don't trust them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Right, better if cops just go in and shoot unarmed people to death. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full list of American politicians for whom I've mourned their passing:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, theoretically. History shows what evils govts are capable of. Corporations have far less power to harm others, especially without a powerful govt to exploit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't need to show the cats footage of birds. I just let them into the room. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why can't he find another outlet, like beating women? At least then he could get back on the field.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Science so far has said

Humans can't transmit Covid
Told people to go about life as normal
Told ppl not to buy/wear masks. They don't work vs Covid and hospitals need them.
Use sanitizer to stop Covid. Great hand sanitizer shortage.
Told ppl they get it through their eyeballs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "Can't yell fire"
Actually, you can. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So my cousin, 19yrs old, was never a good student, but got an offer to be an optometrist. They put her through school free. She loves her job &amp; works very hard at it. Is refusing to get vaccinated, both because we had a relative (26yrs old) die from a blood clot from the vaccine,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# SK functionally an island.
Japan, another island.
Both with collectivist populations and less freedoms.

Americans aren't so compliant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay hear me out.

If Delta strain is worse and more contagious, then we should have gotten Covid, built up antibodies to it, and then when Delta rolled around we'd be like bitch please! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Government is the greatest threat to people's liberty. Government has infringed on my rights more than any criminal, Nazi, communist or Islamic terrorist. I'm not about to give them an unarmed populace when they've already shown the contempt in which they hold toward us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Obviously she doesn't know that hospitals generally run at ~85% ICU capacity. 70% would be low, even outside a "pandemic".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Same violence exists. Just technology changes. Methods change. Weapons change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yelling "fire" in a crowded theater is protected speech. Brandenburg v. Ohio.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's why I don't really care what group it is, if we are in agreement on any part of an issue, I'll stand with them on it. Don't care who it is. Communists, Nazis, terrorists, vegans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covid: emergency! Impoverish the people, crush the economy, expand govt powers, offer the people "relief", rack up massive debts.

Russia/Ukraine: emergency! Impoverish the people, crush the economy, expand govt powers, offer the people "relief" rack up massive debts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I swear environmentalists have no knowledge of the actual, you know, environment. I mean I'm all for us taking better care of our planet &amp; other life on it, but... I'll just let Reagan say it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Westbrook - should lead the team off the bench mostly. Play whenever Bron or AD are off the court.

Howard - I like him, under-rated for his career. One of the best C's ever. Good backup to Gasol/AD.

Ariza &amp; Ellington - skilled much-needed outside threats off the bench.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for any media stories about the new U.S. war in the Congo. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# For a starter, I'd agree. Good from range, not a weak point like Russ may be, esp in the playoffs. Russ is more of a high risk acquisition. Could help, could hurt. Hield more low risk, high reward. Russ is more of an all-in move, and it could backfire. Hield just a solid piece.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If consciousness matters, then it'd be okay to rape an unconscious person.

And the fetus is the fetus's body, not hers. The host can remove them, medically, safely, but not outright kill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Anti-war.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Just think, for every 250,000 Americans that die of Kung Flu, it's only 1/4th the number of abortions every year in the U.S. alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All they know is everything they believe is justified at all costs, and anything anyone says in opposition is racist. That's their whole ideological platform.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's unfair and absurd that government would raise taxes on anyone due to higher spending.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With all the work done by climate change activists, can they point to any actual progress we've made? Or has everything up to this point only slowed change? Has it even slowed, or are things getting worse at an even faster rate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Love requires consent.

Consent cannot happen if coercion, threats, intimidation, punishment, penalties, or harassment is involved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I don't trust the same government responsible for the Tuskegee Syphilis Study with my health, nor an unknown substance rushed in development by the same people who gave us carcinogenic baby powder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I thought I'd hate Romo announcing. I hate the ******* Cowboys. But he brought something to the booth I'd never heard before and yeah, I liked it. It's unique. I can see why ppl don't like it, but for him, I respect it. Just so long as all of them don't start doing it. Just him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well judging by the last time... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maybe part of it is they're busier. Gotta deal with 40k ppl vs like 8-15k here. Maybe here they feel they could afford to be ceremonial.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Depends on what you're talking about. Procrustes promised a bed that would fit everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's a dig at both Biden and the state media that props him up. Biden himself is nothing. He'll be gone soon enough. It's the people behind him who need to be called out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes. Govt shouldn't regulate the commerce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# After these past two years, leftists can never again be taken seriously when they say my body, my choice. They can't even pretend to be outraged by it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are also millions of Americans trapped in the United States. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Are you sure you want to tweet this?"

Fuck yes, a million times yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No. Why? I expect Congress to reward failure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# True, which is why I'm an individualist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't care where the All Star Game is played. Zero. Move it to New York for all I care. Have Cuomo throw out the first pitch while Harris stands beside Bill Clinton holding a sign that says Believe All Women, and Fauci is in center field 100 ft from anyone wearing double masks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Did he kill anyone or try to kill anyone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If you work for the U.S. govt, you're already in a Union. That's literally what it is. It's redundant for Union employees to have a union.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The irony is you want to control other's behavior, lifestyle and healthcare choices because it's what YOU want. That's by itself self-centeredism. You want to control others. I don't. If ppl wanna wear a mask, get a blood clot vaccine, and hide and avoid human contact all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's because they fully intend to have their people be in control of government by then, and treat them well because they love licking boot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There should be a national weight limit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin: threatening to launch nukes.

American politicians: hey, let's all gather in one place for a few hours into one well-known location above ground.

Putin: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Start with everyone. Don't pick and choose favorites. No prejudice. Ax em all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth reiterating, I was/am rather supportive of the BLM protests &amp; on the side of protesters over police. Same way, I'm happy to see clashes today. We should never fear our government/police/military. They should fear us. It's when we fear them that tyranny takes root.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Government is a domestic terror organization.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah I know, wishful thinking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Chortle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So many VACCINATED players are getting Covid that NBA teams are now reaching out to unvaccinated players to fill out their rosters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hey good, I already deleted the part in my bio where I advocate for the Constitution. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hard to do that when govt has their hands in everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As to it being selfish, people are responsible for their own health, not others. Exceptions would be chiefly around food service. Medical decisions, such as getting a vaccine, are a personal choice and should be between you and your doctor, not mandated. We should not have a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Well they can remove it if it's medically feasible without killing the fetus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It just ain't sexy.

Back to the drawing board.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Why would I do that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Defund cops âž¡ï¸ abolish police âž¡ï¸ let's police ourselves  âž¡ï¸ vigilantes âž¡ï¸ Kyle âž¡ï¸ the racist system did this!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Been chillin' with the anti-war hippies at the courthouse! #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah all liberals are the great Satan. #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There's never any shortage of places to bomb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Whatever firepower government has, the citizens should have as well.

Wanna look at government's track record? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And I was once a firm supporter of police. 2021 gave me the final push I needed to embrace anarchism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pandemic so dangerous we fire healthcare workers but protect Congressmen, teachers, postal workers and illegal immigrants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's not "war". It's a kinetic military action against non-secular individuals that are not Islamic. #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Better that than to get Coronavirus from an unmasked customer.

â˜ï¸ may have saved that server's life by walking out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They added the libertarians bit specifically for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Also this. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Question:
Is your college degree going to qualify you for a job that will allow you to pay back your student loan?

If yes, you don't need debt forgiveness.
If not, you chose a shitty degree, dumbass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm ambivalent about the Super Bowl. In the past I hated Brady and wanted anyone else, but I kinda like both teams in this. KC cuz they struggled for years, looking like maybe this year only to fall short, Mahomes is a special talent, and I'm ok with seeing a KC dynasty forming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I haven't read Grapes of Wrath yet. Have it tho. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The ðŸ‘ Second ðŸ‘ Amendment ðŸ‘ Imma stop doing ðŸ‘ cuz it's stupid... applies across state lines. See 14th amendment. Rights enumerated federally apply throughout the U.S. Any municipal or state law to the contrary is unconstitutional.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# nnCuz hes trying to win over Democrats, socialists, Marxists..... Just what the LP needs. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that was some revolution, Antifa. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In an attempt to get immunity
And protect the community
Big Bird did admit
That he got the Covid shot
Now how will I tell my kid
That Big Bird died of a blood clot?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# i have a right to know if my neighbor is a muslim. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But if u oppose abortion, watch how quickly they revert to "u just hate &amp; wanna control women!"
Don't you mean birthing people?

Why does race &amp; gender only exist when you can condemn others as racist &amp; sexist? When not doing that, tho, they champion gender fluidity &amp; transracial]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Traffic does that simply enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am an atheist. I view the police and military as enemy organizations. I used to say I love my country &amp; hate the government, but now I'd lean toward hating my country too. I want out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember those who died because politicians told them to go try to kill people in other countries to distract the people in this one from the politicians swindling the people out of their property and rights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Because TV shows can totally be used in place of facts and reason. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't think government should dictate the health risks people take. They shouldn't have power to force businesses to close with zero compensation. They shouldn't pick &amp; choose which businesses can be open. They can't ban church gatherings, people going to other peoples homes,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Anarcho capitalism
Anarcho socialism

Both fine so long as all human interaction is voluntary, all transactions consensual.

No government can accomplish this.
Only a non-government can do so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# All this makes me wanna do is run for Congress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I could block news about Logan Paul. I don't give a fuck about fucking Logan Paul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Idea, just putting it out there, how about we buy insulin from other countries to avoid the high prices here? What's stopping that?

My guess: govt. But since statism is your religion, you won't admit that, you must create boogeymen elsewhere and have the State save us from them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# and politicians can absolutely not be bought....  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wouldn't even buy a piece of property.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Maybe government shouldn't be in charge of healthcare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Govt gives legal sanction for people to steal. They vote to steal from and disenfranchise others. Anarchy doesn't permit this. So you have crime three ways under statism.

1. Criminals outside law.
2. People casting votes to steal from others.
3. Politicians stealing from ppl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If our fate depends on Republicans in Congress to safeguard us, we're already screwed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I've been giving out free hugs the last three years. I'm not afraid. I'm not gonna treat everyone like they're potentially diseased.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What tragic accident? Reaching for gun, which should be on a diff part of the belt than taser, feel different &amp; require a different set-up than a handgun, and shooting a driver in a moving vehicle with a woman in the car, all over a warrant for carrying a firearm without permit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's someone's carpet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't know!

- Offensive linemen all let Seahawks defenders slip by.
- Every Seahawks defender: I'll get the quarterback! I'll get the quarterback!!

It's ðŸ‘ a ðŸ‘ screen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Ok. So you believe your government would nuke its own civilian population to retain power. Now can you honestly say that that government is good, should be trusted with anything, and has our best interests in mind?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Not as good a ring to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can they accuse him of having a concealed firearm when they also allege it was in plain sight? That's not concealed. And either way, what's it matter to you if it's concealed or not? Go fuck yourselves. 2nd Amendment. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Also don't let that "friend" know you have any LEGOs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Really? I'm sure Democrats were VERY friendly with Bush's guys in comte. #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Personally I like radical free speech. Let anyone say whatever they want. I think it'll create more tranquility among people if everyone can freely voice their opinions rather than having one side free to speak and others on pins and needles or else they'll be shut out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So instead of both sides trying to dominate everyone, and rule over 325mil people, let each city, community, street, household, go their own way. Do not let one rule over another. If two are in agreement, they can work together on their own, not get to force others to join them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Is it bad that I wanted to see a clip of them throwing her out of the airplane mid-air?

Not seriously. Just..  I was hoping it was comin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Don't you remember? Democrats were against withdrawl from Iraq. #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# We're literally talking about make-believe movies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Washington Commanders? So they're named in honor of George Washington, a slave owner.

Political correctness for the win. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I never question peoples desire or un-desire to have kids. That is their choice.

One life is created, choices become limited. Make choices before you get to that point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You can, but then you justify how the Left treated Trump and show yourself to be no better than they are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# to out-do each other, get more famous. Everyone will know what they did. Powerful incentive to disturbed people. But then they may surrender to police without a fight or off themselves. Cowards, afraid when someone is firing back. Also maybe they already feel suicidal but if]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maybe she thinks she can be both a Senator and a Vice President. Get two votes in the senate. And still keep her two votes when Biden croaks/Dems push him aside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a Biden is inaugurated in D.C. but no one is there to see it, is he really president?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know who has no right to guns?

Government.
#USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Neither.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I don't dismiss them. I just acknowledge that there are already laws prohibiting murder. We can do more to protect people, yes. Carry guns. Protect target-rich areas. Have armed security at schools etc. Also end the drug war and reform police, and abolish many unnecessary laws.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To recap the Biden presidency:

Biden: 100 day mask mandate!
States 40-50 days into his presidency: nah, we're fully opening. Wear a mask if you want to.
Biden: Ban Dr. Seuss! Also bomb Syria. Am I allowed to answer questions? No? They cut away from me? Ok. Where am I???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wages are between employees and employers, not govt. Govt has no constitutional power over commerce between individuals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# U.S. moves bombers to Norway, Russia has to move anti-air forces to the border, and likely respond by sending their own bombers near the Baltic States.

Bombers are also offensive weapons, not defensive. They signal hey, we are thinking of attacking you.

That is escalation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have no problem with worker-owner businesses. Anarcho communism. That's fine. My issue is with coercion. Authoritarianism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# don't be asinine, Christians aren't persecuted. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# problem isn't addressed, Russ will want out.

Hope that makes sense. Sorta like dominoes. Need to make changes (O-line). If not, and they keep losing, then unfortunately Pete's just gotta go (again, should be John, but coach is always first in hotseat). And if John doesn't do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you've been vaccinated do you still need to listen to the tsunami warning?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, we have a life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# My +70yr old grandparents (unvaxed) were around three of my family who turned out to have Covid. Around them for days and they never got it.

My uncle &amp; aunt work in a hospital &amp; I hung out with them on days they treated active Covid patients unmasked &amp; unvaxed &amp; I didn't get it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sure.
I'd move if I didn't know anyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tulsi and Booker. Youngish and athletic/combat experience. Rest are old &amp; white. They'd bring Dr Seuss books to a gunfight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# An independent state where communities support themselves. I think that's superior to calitalism, if people consent to it. This is also why I'm fonder of globalism over nationalism. I want us to be one tribe working together instead of vying gang factions seeking selfish aims.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I would say poor taste, but it's NY, so what are you gonna do? ðŸ¤·â€â™‚ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So when UK, France, Netherlands and Belgium had colonies and sought world domination, it was cool, they were good guys, but Germany tries it, nope, they've warmongers.

UK and France had half the world split between them. They were the world's greatest imperialists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Does it? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Myself, I respect ppl who are committed to their beliefs, but I am something of a Taoist. I adhere as much as possible to non-violence &amp; inaction. I think I would sooner be killed than kill. But I've never quite had to make that decision. I try to avoid conflict.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Because the Taliban is so well known for caring for the lives of the unborn. Apparently. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# So Trump is literally Hitler and also pro-Jews. Cuz that makes sense. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wonder if Simmons doesn't have some mental/emotional issues. Hate to say it, but to me I kinda suspect he might be suicidal. Does not like the way ppl view him, just can't stand the pressure, and he's just mentally broken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I like that these ppl aren't even looking. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ppl need to make $ and survive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Says no one needs AR-15s. Also points out the overwhelming destructive capability of the military.

Right, so we can't go up against the military using AR-15s, because that makes too much sense, we're supposed to bring forks to battle them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't agree with all his actions. He's a petulant crybaby, arrogant, bellicose, unpresidential, sure. But a good president, or at least compared to FDR-Obama.

Take Obama. Great talker, terrible president.
Trump, biggest problem is his own big mouth. Best president in 90yrs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Such as?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So wouldn't Wanda's appearance in Dr Strange take away from Dr Strange?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Idea: the MyPillow guy sets up his own social media platform.

MyVoice?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Seahawks: let's not score till the 2nd quarter.
#HASHTAG#: hold my garlic fries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Basically, yes. Potentially innocent civilians matter more to me than cops, who volunteer and train for the job, who should know how to act calmly and logically to de-escalate high-tension situations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't really care, because I don't watch it anyway. Why try to get a show canceled that I never watch? It's not a part of my life as it is. Getting fed up about it would only make it so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Appeal to authority.

And I'm not talking about Coronavirus. I'm talking about all diseases.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# life goals, amiright?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You can't make a single logical argument. That's why everything you do boils down to ad hominems. You can't defend a position, so you just mock and think yourself superior.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If it's MILD why would hospitals be overwhelmed?

If hospitals are overwhelmed, why did they fire thousands of doctors and nurses?

If they're overwhelmed, why hasn't mask mandates, lockdowns, travel bans, vaccine mandates and social distancing kept people out of hospitals?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Mass shootings are already illegal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why require paperwork? Seems bureaucratic. It's not required for moving between cities, counties or states. Why have a lengthy process for crossing national borders? Come and go as you please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deep down, Dems are thrilled with SCOTUS blocking the vaccine mandate. One, they know it wouldn't have stopped Covid anyway, but they can claim they *could have* stopped it, if not for the Supreme Court, so Covid deaths are on SCOTUS. Two, it's justification to pack the court.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>