<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[European anarchists (&amp; like all radicals of the time) were also at times connected to the empires in various ways. 

This is why we need to study them to learn from their mistakes &amp; change so we do not repeat their errors.

Too many people refuse to learn from the Past.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Which btw is another element more self protection courses needs to think about.

The shoes you wear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They are unbearably horny... &amp; it is why they are good.

Just wish it had more Queer sex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I truly cannot express how much this conspiracy theory not only makes no sense but pretends JFK wasn't an imperial anticommunist who escalated the Vietnam war. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[literally land &amp; resources across the world, think he can only pay taxes via selling stocks. Which is not how stocks works.

Sure Elon here is probably lying but... he does not comprehend how economics work. Especially not Elon because he was a econ major.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is stupid as shit. Sure absolutely. Reading what is vanned should be done but it doesn't change that the bans are an issue in &amp; of itself as it is about social regulation &amp; censorship &amp; that by banning it they are making it harder for people to access. It is afterall why it #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[also Vikings is a terrible show. Yeah, it is fiction but when you are depicting the Past, you need to do some bare minimum things &amp; Vikings &amp; probably its sequel fails in every single episode to do that in one way or another.

Idk what happened in the 2010s that made a bunch of #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My comment was definitely about the tensions between the theory or ideals &amp; day to day runnings. 

Because honestly... I do not think one can create proper educational spaces for kids that will not be schools (you get my point here i hope) if not connected to other struggles so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yeah, I too assumed GoW was prowar when i originally played it but having revisited it a couple of years back. It is as blunt as possible.

It uses a thing very common in comics. Which is that at first glance it looks very toxic &amp; having reactionary politics but then you read it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrong. Now I imagine the FAQ used to not be as inclusive as it is an FAQ that started in the 90s. But since 2010 when I first started reading it, it has been inclusive. It only excludes reactionaries like ancaps &amp; "national-anarchists". 

Now my criticisms lie in its eurocentrism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If you wanna doubt some other things sure but this is just not a thing one can deny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know academia is different in US &amp; sweden, &amp; i certainly do not want to imply that Marxism is somehow mainstream academia here. 

But it is imo virtually impossible outside maybe economics or political science to avoid Marx &amp; Marxisms influence on academic research in various #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The sparrows are me &amp; you discussing how to make a killer tomatosoup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I disagree in part. Like sure a huge reason Seinfeld was revolutionary as a sitcom was that it was horrible people. But i think the reason why the finale was poorly received had less to do with them being seen as friends &amp; more that well... most series finales are received poorly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[american colonies could've participated in the protests of british authority &amp; still have been a loyalist during the war.

American "revolution" was always a concept that centered rich white landowners who largely just realised being independent from the empire meant more fortune]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I also took those elements as satire as well as in DKR (&amp; only DKR) batman is not depicted as always correct &amp; is depicted as his vigilantism is not the best option. That it is more about Bruce own psychological need rather than any notion of helping others &amp; so on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Calling it Thatcher Business Education Centre is the same as naming a house in a school after a genocidal wizard imo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Luna was trying to discuss what dialectical materialism means &amp; she did a critique of positivism (that she conflates with empricism). But rather than deal with her arguments he starts by dismissing her sources because... it is a vietnamese source.

&amp; then discusses historical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# OH no... I hope shs got clean Quick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also "radicals" in academia are still mainly marxists of various stripes who outnumber anarchists by a lot. All that has happened is that there has been an increase in 3 things. 1) official academic journals created by amarchists in academia, 2) a more social &amp; cultural #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[running self-organisation &amp; self-management in a struggle against capital &amp; the state. 

Real fascinating &amp; cool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Also a lot of this origin is israeli myth. 

Imi Lichtenfeld did absolutely use his wrestling, boxing &amp; jujutsu skills to street fight nazis.

But krav magas origins lie more in british military unarmed combat that they taught haganah both before &amp; after Ww2. Lichtenfeld played]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He has not been the christmas host for 19 years... I miss him too but omfg... this is the most swedish expression of racism I can think of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok so in that meme rhey have Thomas Sankara, a dude who we have soooo much stuff on about how he opposed USSR. Same with Allende alfhough for different reasons.

But then we also have Nasser who not only was a friend of nazis considering how many of them that worked as military #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing confuses me more than the Euphoria discourse. This is when I realise how utterly disconnected I am with everyone else because I legit do not comprehend any of it.

Now a big part of this is that Euphoria is not a show I am interested in what so ever. 

&amp; I try to not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a coup attempt happens against you so you create a governing body to punish nobles. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok so the issue with what Vaush said was that despite his intentions (I am being overly generous) is that the framework of "jews were over represented amongst bankers &amp; rich folks in weimar germany" is not factual statement. The frsmework of that statement is antisemitic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I genuinely respect the account that started this nonsense. Overall they are one of the best follows but they really really jumped the gun on this, probably out of how well most fiction about vikings tend to be...

But not just the rune being wrong thing at all. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# honestly it might be one of the worst films i have seen. Sure there are plenty more with worse effects &amp; basic filmmaking skills. But none are just wrong &amp; bad in storytelling. acting &amp; directing levels despite being a hollywood blockbuster attempt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It is not comparable at all. "Anarcho"monarchism was all about that absolute monarchy &amp; divine rights of kings.

Peasant uprisings such as peasants revolt were all about fundamentally getting rid of all hierarchies. To them whilst there would be a king, he would till the communal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I fail to see why i should treat MLs as special in the regard to their stated end goals when their ideology is rooted in the notion that hierarchy &amp; vanguards are a must. Today even most MLs think an egalitarian society is one where the State have nationalised industries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what was gonna happen regardless. We have 200 years of evidence showing how electoralism does not work to fight capitalism. Because the moment a left wing party takes power or comes into parliaments, they start to govern. 

&amp; that means to not only control&amp; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Imo I actually see a lot of good stuff where chinese arts &amp; karate relearning the old ways by trying to figure out the forms, drills &amp; sparring.

This is in part due to MMA changing the game of what is necessary for an art to be around.

Also &amp; this is imo a thing that outside]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also overall "elites" is itself a vague as fuck concept that can equally mean a perceived ethnic, religious or racial minority as billionaires. Elites is itself a concept that resists &amp; rejects structural analysis. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As much as I do dislike the Snyder films... Cavill was never the issue nor was he particularily bad when he played Superman for the whole time of 10 minutes in both JL versions. He was pretty shit as angry man who shat his own suit which occupied most of the screen in Snyders #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The british empire would have curbstomped the nazis. They wouldn't have. It would have been a long &amp; even more brutal conflict most likely. But... acting as if the British empire was not the biggest empire &amp; not a small Island alone against Nazis is silly.

&amp; this is not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This... is... is a wild take. This is Peterson doing two incredible wild takes. 1) is that I mean climate is not everything. Climate is a concept referring to weather over a long time in a specific region. Climate is around all of us. Because weather is. But that does not mean #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This whole thread is a mess of wrongness. But this map is spectularly wrong on many many levels. First of "Russia" did not in any way shape or form expand or control Siberian or Central asian regions until late 18th &amp; early 19th centuries. So that is wrong. Secondly it was not #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heck yeah... love this movie soo much. It is a dark &amp; gothic shaw brother kung fu film with great action &amp; some honestly shocking scenes #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I associate it so strongly with hockey that it is legit one of those proustian memory things when I am at a hockey rink]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yeah Criminal informants are commonly what most petty criminals with ties to organised crime do to avoid prison time. It is not working for the FBi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I mean literally in swedish these nations are called Norden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See i could get parts of it if tattooine was mainly just a space hub connected to a massive space station or something &amp; the criminal gangs ran on extortion, various other enterprises &amp; controlling the trade through the hyperspace lane. But since they wanna make it a western they #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dude... Indigenous folks around the world are murdered all the time for opposing capitalism &amp; the colonial states. They are all wanting landback &amp; are being killed. Unlike you &amp; me who are comfortable to express opinions without a death squad after us #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet potatoes in tag is anarchist. Yeah sorry for changing my mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# IMO the issue with swtor has been that it was a mmo. If it had dedicated itself to being a multithreaded rpg where storyline depended on class or something... it could've been amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you use the term immortal science unironically... you are not only an absolutist but you are reactionary. First reference to dialectical materialism as "immortal science" i have been able to find is in the texts of Enver Hoxha. A hilarious shit dictator. Now he is #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yeah, I never see End White Supremacy &amp; immediately think... The jews... that is not what one should do considering how white supremacy tends to look at jewish folks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now if you want good vietnamese theory... read whatever you can by Ngo Van Xuyet, a vietnamese marxist who had to flee Vietnam in 1945 as a result of his marxism.

Now I need to repeat... Vaush is a racist. His criticism of Luna Oi is very much rooted in racism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# abstract taxonomical term. It is not a material reality or a historical reality. Again gonna be honest here... I do not care what people advocate as a long term goal. I care only about tactis &amp; methods for the present. Creating anarchy in the here &amp; now. One does so via]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# act as if the clothes you wear are meaningless.

Sure a t shirt is. A Winter coat is not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Kinda. But also not really as viking wasn't a " job". It was merely an activity some scandinavians engaged in. It would be as if you spent your summers going to another country &amp; did swimming competitions for fun &amp; people started calling being a swimmer an ethnicity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[explainations not only for nazis having advanced technology but for nazis winning the war. Much like how their economy run on the theft of jewish property &amp; so on. Their tech was also stolen from jewish folks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Not that they weren't viable before that... but yes, Guns made swords more common as a main battlefield weapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is either meant to be a knife or a tentpole. but yeah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They were serfs. It is more complicated then this as unlike capitalism manorialism wasn't totalistic. There were many different forms of it &amp; not all peasants were serfs.

But again these nuances is lacking in his statement because he is a christian fascist who wants to depict]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I feel a lot of things are missed with this. Now let me make this clear.... Pascal was a devout man who did it as a sort of gotcha but it also was a struggle for him as his philosophical musings are very skeptical &amp; full of doubt about stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not perfect by far but Excalibur by John Boorman is still my jam tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I love is how Herzog tried to kill Kinski by burning down his house but Kinski's dog alerted Kinski before Herzog could set the fire.

Herzog also tried to shoot Kinski in Aguirre when Kinski tried leave the set. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well mainly because they are either too ancient (middle Roman Empire) or not european or asian (tawatinsuyu (Inca)). 

But also an element is the concept of sea power vs land power that is a part of Dugin's concept that formulates sea power = multicultural &amp; progressive vs land #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 9/11 by all accounts messed him up emotionally real bad &amp; it has taken him a long time to get out of that. Not that any of this excuses his rasism or misogyny ofc. It is just fascinating to see him reflekt on it now in more negative terms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I just prefer various forms of experimental rock tbh.

Then again punk was technically created by black bands as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# eh... I disagree. Ferrer talks about it but like the thing is that Ferrer clearly wanted "schools" to not be seperate from society as a whole. The issue with Ferrer overall is a thing brought up already. He frames things too much around teaching the child rather than the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Central asian steppe cultures through history. They had no frontier because they were free to roam anywhere more or less.

But various East asian empires certainly have had frontiers towards central asia as it is the periphery of the empire.

It doesn't even have to be steppes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all people &amp; non human animals should be free &amp; autonomous in a beautiful &amp; joyful sustainable existence #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I highly recommend Pichon by Charles Moore. It is the autobiography of a cuban black man who was sent to prison for... being friends with gay folks &amp; criticising Cuban regime for its racism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trusting others is kinda the key element that my anxieties makes impossible. 

If I hang out with people I will spend the next day thinking of the "many things I did wrong" &amp; why they must hate me. There is no basis for this. It is just my anxiety.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[there are fewer modern wars due to military training but due to the immense cost of wars &amp; talks about how Germany &amp; France know if they declare war it would ruin them... it is a text written in 1901 but that line just feels like the worst take in hindsight ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[😢😢... one of the greatest ever comic artists is dead.  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do think it is very important to understand how nation-states by structure &amp; form creates homogenous ethno-states.

Post-WW2, the reaction to the holocaust &amp; so on was to homogenize nation-states. Not make them more multi-cultural. Multiculturalism is to a large extent against]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# violation of White bodies from indigenous violence the "horror" comes from.nnIt is Roth talking exception to the film that put exploitation films using indigenous folks on the map trying to frame the colonialism as the issue. Even if again cannibal Holocaust failed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They absolutely failed with vast majority of them but they tried]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is 100% this. 

&amp; I get it to some extent. All I want is honesty &amp; understanding of that position]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# sacrificed themselves for other plant. 

Lysenkoism refers to both his ideas &amp; their adoption by the soviet state &amp; the persecution of scientists who did actual science.

His ideas, whilst not the main cause to any of them, was a cause to virtually all famines in USSR &amp; PRC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It depends but it was a popular mid century claim by some figures like Poppler who connected it to historicism but honestly his critiques kinda makes little sense when applied to Hegel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Congrats on next years pumpinkin patch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Externally supported" is certainly a buzzword for what is a logical development. As Sam Mbah points out, africans have tried "scientific socialism" &amp; it did not liberate them. Therefore it makes sense why anarchism would be on the rise in the various african regions currently #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The society that wants to ban it &amp; fight against it. You suck as a person]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It says a lot that Coffin feels it is important to attack indigenous people's autonomous actions &amp; desires in this nonsensicle meme format.
Almost as if Coffin can still be summed up as a dude who wanted fame so badly they kicked themselves in crotch on tv #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So i just heard Haz spread some of the most batshit historical bullshit i have ever heard...

Fundamentally it was Haz admitting to liking &amp; think Lyndon Larouche was correct on history. This was how Lincoln wanted US to connect with Russian Czar to have "mutual industrial]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like balkans during ww2 is one of the least complex periods of Balkan history because it is quite easy to spot the horrible fascists from the antifascists &amp; liberation movements.nnDespite this too many ww2 nerds being reactionary means they still wanna stan chetniks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No one is saying we cannot give out rough sketches. In fact imo having a radical imaginary is one of the most important elements. If you look through my tweets &amp; i know that is hard, you will know i write quite a lot about rough sketches &amp; ideas about things to function]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[* i feel real bad about the snarky opening line now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok i just saw someone say Tolkien wrote subversions of Chosen One narratives which... is a nitpick on that thing but come on. Aragorn is literally as chosen one as possible to make a narrative around. You can still like LOTR just stop pretending it is deconstruction or subversion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*not write Martha Washington the most misogynistic way possible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I did not see the water until now tbh. Which is why I said wheat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# flexibility &amp; openness when one pretends that somehow statist &amp; vanguardism can be compatible with autonomous actions. 

Same thing... if the state enacts reforms that beneficial to the oppressed that is good but that comes from direct action. It does not come from anything else]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Historical approach to the history of anticapitalism &amp; such that have led to overall re-evaluation of anarchisms &amp; anarchists &amp; 3) bigger &amp; more known anarchists movement after the intense repression of the 1980s &amp; 1990s in various forms including Green scare. Again the fall of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I agree but I dislike the totalistic framing as tho this is inevitable.

Now I imagine you do not think so.

Also this is why imo it is so important to understand that the way to avoid it is broadening the movements. Class cannot be the only element]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[22. Left unity is not just a bad idea that is about anarchists or libertarian socialists of all kinds conforming to authoritarian radicals but it is fundamentally rooted in a concept of "left" that is a fantasy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Honestly in anarchism like socialism or communism in general have no singular founder &amp; are collective constructions most of the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you really want to know or do you want to pretend to be a classical liberal still? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because you gotta debate everything... even settled issues]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&amp; yes, I include the star wars christmas special]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nah this is just how neoliberal technocracy works tbh. It is not incompetence at all. It is just how the Dems work as a governing Party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mainly 3 things... 1) Color in general &amp; how due to the absence of pictures &amp; images, people were concerned heavily with symbols. If you make a medieval film &amp; we cannot see the heraldry, you made a boring medieval film more often than not. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The question they have to ask is... what do they mean by communism? &amp; what does it mean to do good to the community?

These are important questions... because it will highlight your approaches.

I don't give a fuck what anyone calls themselves if they do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is fun. History of concepts is fun. Koselleck especially as his view is more social history where conceptual worlds make up our imaginary &amp; thoughts.

I like it as it can be used to highlight how authority works in folks mental worlds so to speak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I feel like these things prove how political spectrums &amp; compasses are shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since 2008... this has been in evey dvd bin i have seen #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[another hot take I have is that films or tv show should be adapted from outdated or mediocre or bad fantasy or SF books with potentiality rather than masterpieces or good books. 

It is a good thing they are doing this since they are adapting The Wheel of Time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# oh don't get me wrong here... we cannot trust completely. But there is a difference being supicious of how she treats the fact that her grandad was killed for opposing stuff &amp; presenting it as if she just parading around a nazi.

Because it could be worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# autonomous actions such as mutual aid, cooperatives &amp; soo many other elements. This is why i keep saying I do not doubt that MLs want an egalitarian society. I just don't care about their stated desires because what matters is material actions. One is not actually showing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I cannot comprehend how folks do not get that centralisation in infrastructure (&amp; everything else) is regardless of intentions exclusionary &amp; hierarchical. 

Sure hierarchies can be decentralised as well. But you cannot centralise things without some kind of hierarchy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I never said no education is needed. I said it is not my job to teach radical conciousness to oppressed groups.

It is however so that all radicals have a role in sharing Knowledge so people can figure out things for themselves.

But sharing knowledge is not educating people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So are we not going to acknowledge the big dick energy from Jeffrey Combs just dunking on Matt Walsh there? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Even if he missed in in Dune... Computers were definitely a big thing in 1960s so claiming it was written in 1965 is why computers aren't a thing in Dune is silly nonsense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# fascism worships authority even if they claim to for example "oppose rhe state" they worship other forma of authority. But different is more important than amount of it which is just an esssentialist nonsens thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah he is a christian fascist. That explains it. 

Look I am all for emphasizing certain positive things about middle ages but I am doing that to emphasize how different the forms of oppression was &amp; to emphasize how different life was in precapitalism &amp; that progress is not #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wrote. But it is self-organised, autonomous ways of organising that Zapatistas have done. I do not need them to call themselves anarchists or something. 

Because revolutions are not anarchist or marxist. They just are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate myself. 

&amp; I hate myself even more for hating myself &amp; needing to express it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# hierarchy &amp; MLs constantly defend &amp; want hierarchies. It is not weird. It is incredibly basic why any socialist should oppose MLs. They have materially shown through over a century of efforts that their tactics &amp; methods lead to capitalism reconstituted. It is imo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is as always great. Especially takes good examples from your work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12. Eugenics is real bad, folks. It is also a structural part of most national &amp; international policy institutions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Charlie Kirk is a white man so Vaush cannot accuse him of wanting genocides despite Kirk explicitly &amp; publically wanting them.

Vaush is not a good theoretical dude. You don't have to study in a uni to be good at theory. But you need humility which Vaush as a egocentric]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I do agree eith their point about how anarchist library editing core in english is too centralised tbh. Sadly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I keep getting reminded every christmas how we watch Kalle Ankas julspecial there is a real moment of anti-italianness in one of the Disney shorts... &amp; I love it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly one of the wildest thing that white supremacy does on a habitual &amp; unconcious level to us is stuff like making us, white folks, think anime characters are white. Despite literally being created in Japan &amp; just obviously not being codified as white.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is True nazis used it less... Especially as it did not work in the attritional warfare of the eastern front.

Like we know they used speed. It is not why blitzkrieg worked but the nazis absolutely gave it out a lot.
Brits did similiar. US as well.
But the nazis did it the most]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amongst many Social scientists &amp; humanities can use. But it is not scientific practices themselves.

&amp; that is the issue here.... calling themselves scientific is a rhetorical tool to justify their ideology without any reflektion on their own biases &amp; assumptions. Not just that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah... Imo he can be funny in a good way. But also frustrating in others]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It creates explicitly a hierarchy between the vanguard &amp; whatever category they perceive as the rest if that is the workers or the people.

The vanguard is the new hierarchy formed above the struggling masses to "lead" them &amp; manage them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Multiple Shanghai communes throughout 20th century needs to be appreciated more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ridley Scott went from making historical dramas that look like this... To whatever the heck is going on visually in The Last Duel #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30. Esoteric Hitlerism is actually how most nazis engage with Hitler &amp; most antifascists or everyday people are not really engaging with that fact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh he was. She multiple times told cops he might kill her &amp; so on. Cops did nothing about it because he was OJ Simpson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am just shocked someone is openly doing pseudoscience like that #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the US constitution was written in direct response to uprisings from farmers &amp; landless white folks against the government &amp; large landowners. It was purposefully made not just to sign slavery into proper law &amp; its government (as articles of confederation had already had that)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah... it was an issue in all of anarchism.nnLouise Michel being one of the Greats for being in solidarity with indigenous folks when she was in a penal colony post Commune imprisonment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got good grades on my essays from the last courses of the past semester.

I am so relieved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Black... it was truly one of the wildest takes to ever be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot call yourself a "marxist" &amp; then project a notion that people you dislike only keep referring to dead men to explain their ideas. There is literally someone in the comments saying read Lenin or Read on Authority. You are calling your ideas after a dead man. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are really bad at even basic history]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yeah that is what happens when a person fails to defect to USSR &amp; returns to the US. Like you do realise OSwald tried to defect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[as it was an empire led by an ethnic minority where many many different ethnicities existed. European writers actually did use the term "China proper" to talk about like the difference between the core of the Empire &amp; its periphery. nnThis is fascinating to me because it forces]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Honestly... The founding fathers did not want to pay taxes at all. It is why they did it.nnIt is also why the immediate aftermath of the war was filled with armed uprisings against the state for taxing poor folks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing i have said about Tolkien or LOTR are criticisms of his work. It is just what the man explicitly said to believe &amp; the text of his works. 

I have my interpretations &amp; criticisms of him. Some absolutely are part of what I have said in my threads today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What I love is how historically common self organised communal defense is &amp; how these dipshits just constantly want the worst version of things.

We have tried private police or firefighters. Like it has happened historically &amp; if it produced immense issues &amp; oppressions in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hate it as a symbol. It is &amp; always has been a functionally &amp; practically meaningless symbol for actual communism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because lets make this clear.... the UK was the world biggest empire at the time. Even if the nazi somehow magically would not invade or fight the USSR (which just would make them not nazis) then the Uk still had vast more resources &amp; man power to deal with them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Idk why I wtote no here.

I meant thank you.

&amp; again Foucault is right. He smashed Chomsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My fave is the photo collages containing Nasser, Mandela, Sankara, Bhagat Singh &amp; so on.nnAlso when african folks are dismissed as CIA psyops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Danny Devito made a good film there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever read Raymond Williams? His cultural approach to marxism truly helps me in my intellectual history theoretical perspectives. I #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Heck yeah...love mutual respect amongst experts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ok so... Lysenko was a terrible biologist who (extremely simplified) believed genetics, agronomy &amp; virtuslly all evolutionary theory was "reactionary pseudo science" &amp; perpetuated his own batshit ideas on how plants did not die due to stuff like cold or lack of water but]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tbf they literally just named it karate kid in the west for brand recognition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fascinating thing about this imo is how they are framing the issue as being about the depiction of violence &amp; cruelty that children shouldn't be exposed to. 
&amp; an insistence that we can teach out history without it.

But no we cannot. We cannot teach out the holocaust #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[big national holidays celebrating becoming more or less independent is memorials to WW1. Becuase Australians &amp; Canadians (mainly the white portions) did not like the idea of sending their troops to die meaninglessly in the trenches or deserts of ww1 for an empire.

It is why]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Any show going past 5 seasons should be axxed next season.

The only ones allowed to continue beyond that is if it can do almost an entire remake ala doctor who even then... It should end]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ok so... that is just... not how capitalism or nutrition works. Epsecially as capitalism ideological structures keep framing how they are defeating malnurition.

I live in a capitalist country where kids are fed. You do too. 

Are all kids fed? No but that is not what the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why i keep saying elites usually means jewish folks by people who use it.nnBecause it always gets revealed they believe in some absolute horrible antisemitism #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That feel when you are tagging indigenous folks whose opinions you dislike to desperately listen to 5 White nazbols discussing how landback is capitalist &amp; the issue sure as heck ain't, colonialism, the state or so on but just "CaPiTaLIsM" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ultimately I just hate these things on almost every level.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning how to read medieval texts right now. Fun as heck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Honestly the thing i would want to be main story if it had to be one wouls be the spy storyline... it would've been amazing if all you ended up with was either lord of the underworld, the information trader or spymaster of the emperor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is it that it is the 1970s version that knew to not go into that? I wonder... how? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# connections between Holocaust &amp; the ongoing genocide of indigenous folks in the americas. Not because residential schools should be compared to Auschwich. Because it truly is not &amp; one has to understand just why the Holocaust is different in scope &amp; plan yet also how it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[time can be framed as nation-states. OMFG... you cannot be more wrong. This is just pain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. Aragorn invaded The Shire &amp; Rohirrim as a way to expand Gondor's influence like all good kings have.
2. The rohirrim in response went on raiding the the borderlands of Shire leading the Shire to become even more isolationist.
3. Which is why Frodo left. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will admit whilst I do like looking at football world cups &amp; euros, I will forever always be more interested in the club part of football. 

&amp; I think more football fans need to seriously think about how abolishing capitalism would make the beautiful game, actually beautiful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Holy shit that article is so bad.
I only read the first two paragraphs &amp; not only is it filled with just bonkers bad faith shit about anarchism but contains a description of class struggle as arising from struggle against nature &amp; is fundamentally rooted in a lot of 19th century]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# True... lets bring back the union between sweden &amp; norway. *the national anthem blares out in the back ground &amp; a flag appears behind me*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I too take them at their word that they want an "egalitarian society". I just point out that they are never gonna achieve it materially using their stated &amp; held beliefs in regards to tactics &amp; such. We fight each other because as an anarchist I am against all authority &amp;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three Kings is O'Russell only remotely interesting film]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes the tweet is a bad look. However... There is a context you are not including there that does alter it a little.

Again her tweet is real bad &amp; not focusing on this is why she should be approached with caution. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# child learning by themselves so to speak. It is why I am a bigger fan of Goodman's pedagogy overall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I keep an eye on him near any drinks because he is gonna try to drug someone #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Post-racial ideas are about masking racism.nnIt is always about saying that racial minority deserves to be oppressed because they are "naturally" criminal or so on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I just assumed by nations they meant cultures. 

Because I also assumed Earth Kingdom haven't always been united as a empire.

&amp; air nomads were more or less well nomads so they by definitions had multiple polities]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What fascinates me is how he is saying it to obscure &amp; be racist to indigenous folks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do wanna emphasize tho that there are nitpicks then there is just stuff that is creating a false image.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can give a ridiculously easy example... Mo Salah is a muslim who happens to be the best player in England who constantly gets depicted as "selfish" or as a "diver" despite Harry Kane existing &amp; literally being the physical embodiment of both these concepts in football #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfectly into their narrative as a "revolution" where the capitalist class overthrew the feudal one. Ofc that is not what happened as british empire was not feudal &amp; these landowners were not exactly fitting the notion of a "bourgeouis" as rhey were landowners rather than]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Again thank you for your intentions &amp; apology. I want you to not think trying was wrong even if in this occasion it did not help. I appreciate it quite a lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is how all HR departments work &amp; it is why they must be opposed at all cause]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The main issue I have with 19th century american individualist anarchists (american anarchists in general in the period) is the utter lack of analysis of colonialism. There was occasionally a semi understanding about how indigenous folks had been destroyed by the state]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No... I am sorry you cannot accept that "Aragorn becomes king due to his ancient bloodline" &amp; "Gondor is corrupt because it is without their Rightful king" are you know sterotypical chosen one narratives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# she made horny immortal mummies in stories about unknown &amp; existentiality. That is good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# yeah, I know. It is why he sucks. Because he did so in the worst way possible leading to the most destructive battle of the war where he failed entirely. 

I don't know what you think but no one is saying anything about hindsight here. It is all about what he did in the war]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# the US is clear. Part of it is that &amp; this needs to be repeated most MA folks in US are middle class white folks who just want to feel cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Remember how Alan Moore's Tom Strong had one of the first interracial couples in US comics history. In 1999]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# All revolutions &amp; all governments claim to feed kids. It is very common. I don't believe in supporting the propaganda of a state. I look at what people are saying &amp; analysing living in that state &amp; how it is materially organised &amp; functions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna say this basic thing... If your socialism is "nationalisation of industries", congrats you have learned nothing from the history of 20th century capitalism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I will be the Cushing to your Lee... By that i mean i will shoot you with a shotgun in multiple films]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*climate change

Btw whilst I personally think logical &amp; consistent degrowth is anarchism or some form of libertarian socialism. There are a variety of degrowth advocates who advocate for more... reformist &amp; socdem ideas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# already wrote a great thread on why this is just the worst take regarding genocide &amp; language which is why my take is shallow as they already did a great job  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This explains his whole filmography tbh. Also why i love soo many of them #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You are a great person who I know is always doing their best &amp; that is why you are great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The weirdness of SF is what captured it for me as a teenager &amp; why i love it as a genre. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now ofc the reason why it has soo many errors as a map is that... Not one of the states who even were "planned economies" was interested in or could abolish capital. Because they were structurally rooted in capital accumaltion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I quit taking it at the question if anyone not white male was oppressed because none of my option was working class, lgbtq white men are oppressed as well as all nonwhite, noncis folks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why am I watching the Clash of Titans film from 2010? It is the worst. It is terrible on every level.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That black fighters often came from kickboxing or karate gyms whereas white mma fighters came from BJJ (a style whose prime family are far right brazilians) or wrestling.

Because karate amongst black folks in the US was always different than white mall karate for its upper to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want filmmakers to stop making historical dramas with blue filter &amp; muted colors. Note how the art from the era doesn't skimp on the color. This is literally a miniature of the duel the film depicts. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember to help your friend by poking them in the nose to clear sinuses #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Embrace being an upprooted iranian like your ancestors... The sogdians]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ok It changes nothing. An M16 round does not do that damage as it is a intermediary round. It was not matching an M16 caliber. It has matched a carcano rifle from ww2 which Oswald bought]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Centralised states around. US is so centralised that its regional state governments are centralised as fuck as well.

There is absolutely hierarchies possible within decentralised lifeways (hint: it is why anarchists emphasize how authority is qhere hierarchies crystalise from]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[battles of the 19th century, it is virtually bloodless. Which makes it seem less a film about brutality of war &amp; suffering but more a celebration of military victory. Second is that the notion of "accuracy" the film focuses means it takes preferential treatment to a notion of]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>