<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Leftists are always seeking to suppress or purge this reaction (grooming you) to their profligacy. Do not let these reprobate shits rob you of your disgust.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The public forum would effectively be privatized and therefore governed by completely subjective and arbitrarily enforced standards. (4)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Christians have always done this. Frivolous bickering should be avoided, naturally, but castigation is also the means of exposing and correcting error.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# William Eaton said something very similar about the Muslims.

"We find it almost impossible to inspire these wild bigots with confidence in us or to persuade them that, being Christians, we can be otherwise than enemies to Musselmen."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The longer I live the more pessimistic about the future of the country, and mankind in general, I've become. As I've said in the past, said for years, anyone whose read the Bible would recognize we're not "evolving," or even "progressing," at all as a species.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Another banal commie strawman. Female commies ("feminists") always portray burdens as "privileges" when vilifying men. Show me anyone who thinks being the head of a household, for example, is anything but a huge responsibility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me tell you how depraved the modern left is. They were outraged at Rogan for not supporting child transvestism. Not adult transvestism, which he endorsed, but CHILD cross dressing/genital mutilation. Openly endorsing Socialism is not remotely enough for the modern Sodomite. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They're just put into that position for being the previous pastor's favorite, being that guy that talks about Jesus the most/loudest, etc. The consequences of which, for the Church, has been rather catastrophic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# At this point I'm immediately suspicious of the word "ally." It's commie nomenclature.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jack Murphy is the Dale Brown of masculinity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Women are meant to nurture children. Their emotional disposition makes them better suited for such than males. As a general rule, one gender will never perform the role of the other, as well as they do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear RINOS. If you compromise on principle to gain new supporters, you didn't convert them, they converted you. Pandering to leftists to win votes serves the left by diluting your own platform. They're pushing their platform, and so are you to some degree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Every time I hear about this I remember this article. One of the best I've read.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't know anything about this Jack guy. But I saw this alleged cuck post. And all I have to say about that, is any man who shares his woman, is a b*tch. Don't like it? Don't care. To think it conveys anything other than weakness is abject delusion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I read the Bible (KJV), unassisted, when I was ten years old. And I would contend nothing else I have ever read, or will read, has been so beneficial and useful as a bulwark against the intellectual and moral malignancy of Socialism, to which it is both a cautery and cure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Long before any of us was born. The Republic the Founders established was destroyed by the Civil War (which resulted in massive augmentation of the federal government). But even before that there were those trying to ruin it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Americans could turn off their sports ball long enough to read a fucking book that would be obvious. As I've long said, ignorant immoral men without principle in office, are a product of ignorant immoral men without principle in the voting booth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those words don't even mean the same things to leftists. "Justice" to a leftist, is a system with an inherent prejudice against Christians, whites, men, heterosexuals, citizens, etc. When a leftist says they want "justice," that is to what they're actually referring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do NOT make idols of these men. They were never intended to play a significant role in your life, and if they do it means our country is broken. To ascribe to them messianic attributes is repugnant. True Americans have only one "Messiah," and He was crucified two millennia ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone not a vegetable knows that abolishing imaginary "racism/misogyny" is a pretext commonly used by Marxists to take over an institution and purge it of ideological dissidents. But these clowns don't. "Allegations" were all they needed to go all in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They have no problem with tyrants flouting the Constitution, so long as it's their tyrant doing it. If Biden imposed a gun regulation in the same manner, all the Trump shills would be calling him Hitler/Stalin/Antichrist incarnate. But when it's their bureaucrat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These guys never learn. Why would you yet again give a duplicitous reprobate a forum to peddle his grift? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was never a fan of Tomi Lahren. She's just one of the many leftists in denial that subscribe to a hodge-podge of ideologically contradictory and incompatible ideals.

You're not a "Conservative" if you reject the basic precepts of Conservatism. ↓↓↓↓↓

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The worst part is they basically abandoned their Messiah. I was never even a "Trump guy." Was a rather vocal critic even (e.g., his unconstitutional bump stock ban, war on Syria, etc.). But he deserved better than what he got in the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh look. It's Dan Fuddshaw, doing big government things again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No, you quote the Bible only when it suits you, to push your Marxist worldview. Let's quote the Bible shall we? The New Testament affirms the Old. The only contradiction/incongruency here is you; because your position is derived from Communism. Not the Bible. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why would I fight to save a government that abandons its own people/allies to terrorists? I would more upset about the attack on the items of historical significance than the bureaucrats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disagree. Have been hearing stuff like this my whole life. What the average person calls "hard right" is but a diminutive lull (not even cessation) in our slide to the left. A hard right turn would be abolishing large portions of the bureaucracy. Which almost none would support. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And that wasn't just true in the 1800s, it was still true in the 1900s, in the Jim Crow Democrat south that comprised the confederacy. Condoleezza Rice's father registered Republican in the 1950s, for example, because the Democrat Party would not have him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is nothing which I dread so much as a division of the republic into two great parties, each arranged under its leader, and concerting measures in opposition to each other. This [...] is to be dreaded as the greatest political evil under our Constitution." - John Adams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If she takes pictures like this she's trash. When a woman tells you she has no problem sharing her body with the world, listen to her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# As seen in the upper left corner of the previous image, in which you construe disparity with the COMMUNIST platform, to which you blatantly subscribe, as violating the laws of God. The actual/correct Biblical position can be seen in this accompanying illustrative aid. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've said it before and will say it again. The time for cordiality, discussion, &amp; debate, etc., with these people has long passed. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Constitution, the language of which is broadly unknown, disregarded, or distorted to facilitate the exigencies of the moment or partisan interest, could be efficacious. It doesn't work because most Americans openly support their government operating extra-constitutionally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know, it sucks being right all the time.
↓↓↓
See:#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A city of 9 million would produce literal mountains of horse shit. But no one rides horses anymore. It is the height of intellectual dishonesty and pretension to judge the people of the past based upon the circumstances and values of the present.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Language controls thought. Subvert a people's language &amp; you also subvert their minds. They cannot change reality, but they can change PERCEPTION of reality, which the corruption of language induces. 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I like how dumbshit leftists often try too construe being utterly wrong about something as merely having a "different opinion." (Usually as a specious means of avoiding concession.) They're not the bad guy for being an ignoramus, you're the bad guy for being intolerant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Quite to the contrary the GOP has been electing black people for a century and a half. All of the first blacks elected to office were Republicans, because the GOP was the anti-slavery party, and the racist Democrat Party flat out wouldn't have them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like I said. Socialism is the sin of covetousness masquerading as altruism. All leftists are thieves posturing as philanthropists. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crazy idea. Don't do pervy weirdo shit and things like this will never happen, Jack.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They didn't want to hear about such things. They just wanted to sit there and emote, and act like emoting is doing something. Or "pray" about it, which seems the "Evangelical's" preferred way, of construing being an apathetic pussy as virtuous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Democracy" is old as fuck &amp; had long been established as a garbage form of government that inevitably culminates in tyranny by the time of the Founding. The Founders "liberally" denounced it as trash, and basically designed the Constitution, with preventing "democracy" in mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are the same people that want gun manufacturers to be liable for harm caused by their products, opposed to vaccine manufacturers being liable for damage caused by their products? If I had to guess, it's because one is paying them off (they're complicit), and the other is not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, leftists are psychotic. So it would sound crazy to any normal human being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Feminism" has always been for the purpose of destroying the traditional western concept of liberty.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just another variant of the all too common specious, "Jesus would want you to be a useless wimp that allows your enemies to do as they please," rhetoric.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All that time Googling and this is what you have to show for it?

You bore me, sir. This is a fruitless dialogue I shall move on to other things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But if they're all here, who's arresting 9 year old girls, for not having their vaccination papers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's precisely because it's being done slowly that they don't notice. What we're seeing is basically the Fabian Socialist model. Rapid, aggressive change, produces ardent counter-revolutionary movements. Incremental change stifles such movements.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crap like this is why I don't subscribe to a "personal relationship" with God. It's just a specious appellation for religious relativism. As I've oft queried, if you have a direct line to God, then why are you so Biblically ignorant and wrong about everything? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even if you don't believe the supernatural aspects, it's undeniably true in substance. I have said for many years, if you ever wondered what it was like living in Sodom &amp; Gomorrah, simply look around. You're living in it. Same pagan depravity, new specious &amp; "scientific" labels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is of course changing as Republicans are increasingly becoming culturally left also. Our society is constantly moving to the left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As usual with leftists the complete effing opposite of reality. This country is so damned far left of its Founding principles, it would be completely unrecognizable to those that established it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Anything claiming to not be right or left, in my experience, is always left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The left are fascists (racist Socialistss). If you ever wondered what it was like in Nazi Germany, you saw it throughout 2020, when the American Brown Shirts (Antifa/BLM) were doing the same thing the German Brown Shirts did: vandalism, arson, assault, murder, etc. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Know what's even more effective than "trucks" at deposing tyrannical states?
↓↓↓
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't agree with the comments regarding "vulnerable" groups but am on board with the rest. Liability protection is the bureaucrats indemnifying the special interests enriching them personally. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem is not that they don't understand. The problem is you lack the balls/spine to impose your values. If you refused to impose your values on your children they would walk all over you &amp; end up heathens. Refusing to impose your values on leftists has the same result.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The left has done a phenomenal job of convincing black folk that the principles of freedom are "white" culture, "supremacy" even, to induce aversion to if not loathing for such, &amp; to keep blacks subscribed to a mentality of subjugation &amp; failure they construe as "black culture."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our government, the powers of which are explicitly quantified in the Constitution, was never meant to operate that way. The specious equation of the pandemic to a "war," is purely for the purpose of illegitimately conferring to the state war powers, in a non-war setting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little discourages me more regarding our future than the fact Americans simply cannot grasp the significance of language. Here's an apparent doctor, presumably far more educated than most, that fundamentally fails to recognize one cannot denigrate a thing by complimenting it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Even the smartest of men are made fools by the female form.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Partially agree. One cannot attribute all blame to Christians however. People have their own agency and make their own decisions. Telling a commie about the Gospel is no more likely to make them a Christian, than telling one about the Constitution will make them a Conservative. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you look at the Socialist Party platform, for example, is calls for the "repeal of all sodomy laws" &amp; laws against "same sex marriage." Why would it do that? Because both used to be illegal, and now aren't, indicative of a society that's becoming less Christian. Not more. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Democrats have a long history of harassing political dissidents, showing up at their homes, burning crosses on their lawns, etc. Same party same tyranny.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So basically just like being a Conservative on Facebook. Sweeping "automated" censorship and bans and a reporting system systematically abused by leftists to silence dissent. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You guys just don't understand what it is to be an alpha. You beta losers probably don't even urinate on your women. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again, anyone with a modicum of historical knowledge knows that the destruction of idols indicates conquest. Our idols/banners being replaced with theirs, indicates a conflict is taking/took place, &amp; our side is losing/lost.

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Accusing other people of doing what you do (subjectively interpreting Scripture to serve one's personal interests). Anathematizing Christian tenets you don't like, e.g., complementarianism, by equating it to misogyny. You even conflate it with "racism." (A staple of commies.) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But to acknowledge these truths would contravene the commie mythos that all white men (particularly the Founders) are racist. Our Patriarchs were noble men with noble aspirations, not to be conflated with the commie excrement masquerading as "rights" movements today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh look. Another Communist construing the Communist platform as Christian dictum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Basically, whatever is "virtue" in Christianity (e.g., patriarchy, traditional gender roles, monogamy, etc.), is sin to leftists. And whatever is "sin" in Christianity (e.g., whoredom, sodomy, transvestism, covetousness, etc.), is virtue to leftists. They're complete opposites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh, he's not "my" pastor anymore. And the "modern" Church, like everything else, is full of Marxists.

See:#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I've said for many years, all of the people you call "Democrats" are COMMUNISTS. Call them what they are. Not what they call themselves. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, but he got to virtue signal and declare his fealty to the Communist Party, which was the point. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What did you expect? He foisted this shit on us (Fauci, the vaccine, etc.). To denounce the vaccine would be to admit failure, &amp; put liberty/people above his legacy/career. Let's see how many partisan shills start saying the jab is not so bad after all.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We're not going to have a "debate" about my liberties. You're not arbitrarily abridging them. Period. Go fuck yourself. They're not subject to revision based upon your emotional disposition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, that's precisely why being dependent upon the state is so dangerous. If my choices are hitting you in the head with a baton or my kids starving...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot effectively prevent, or treat HIV, if you think it's a sinus infection, or worse, something good for you ("progress," "anti-fascism," "equality," etc.). When people call Communists "liberals" they are misdiagnosing the enemy, &amp; thus suppressing effective resistance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The country is too subverted. Most "Republicans" are actually Socialists; they're just too stupid to know it. There is no "Conservative" party in this country any longer. I've said it for years. The present day GOP is to the left of Bill Clinton's Democrat Party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why? I've never been to Europe. And I have, for many years, likewise opposed the designation "African American" for the same reason. It conveys bifurcated loyalty and is a form of auto-segregation. "American of African descent" would be a more proper expression. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah, and one of the things we learned from the Black Death, is that having people cloister in their homes is one of the worst things you can do. People univariably have to go out to some degree for necessities, get infected, and then transmit it to everyone at home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't support any measures to "protect" women in sports, or anywhere else. We're either equal or we're not. If we're equal then you don't need help or protection. If you need help or protection, then we're not equal, and you will acknowledge such. Pick one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make federalism great again. Centralization is a staple of tyrannical states, and fundamentally un-American. There are two kinds of Americans. Federalist Republican Constitutionalists, and traitors. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Church is where the original movement for American liberty was born. Today it's a "safe place" for bearded women to rationalize they're apathy and indifference to pagan tyranny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People think it hyperbolic when I say Communism is everywhere. But Communism is everywhere in the west; it's permeated everything. The "systemic racism," "everything is racist," "all cops are racist" rhetoric, to give but one example, is taken directly from the commie platform. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But they're not Nazis, you see, because they don't claim to be or call themselves Nazis. Nevermind that everything else (that matters) is the same. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I said 20 years ago, we're not "progressing" under the left, we're regressing. Everything the left believes and promotes is rehashed &amp; relabeled pagan depravity. "Homosexuality?" "Transvestism?" All staples of the defunct pagan shitholes of antiquity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I drank out of a water hose, so... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Necessity is the plea for every infringement of human freedom. It is the argument of tyrants; it is the creed of slaves." - William Pitt.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah, exactly. Incorporating Cultural Marxism ("wokeness") to engender favor with the left. Anyone who does this is a fuckin sellout.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Totally serious. I can't even talk on FB. I get banned constantly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Church is being walked on for the same reason "nice guys" get walked on in relationships. No one respects weakness, and the Church is, conspicuously, the most timorous and deferential guy in the room.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's not "mean/ungodly" to make a germane observation. I thought the same thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Classical or cultural? So, just out of curiosity, do you support equality of the sexes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But I heard from a lot of people with no medical training whatsoever on the internets that he's "debunked."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When do these people exhibit anything but maleficence toward you? When are their pronouncements anything but invidious? When are their policies anything but deleterious to your interests? Your smiling Democrat "Christian" friend at work, goes home &amp; prays for Jesus to rob you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta be shittin me. It's not "brilliant." It's simple sense &amp; I've been saying to do this for many years. It's also not enough. Any law you pass will simply be repealed by the commies as soon as they're able.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've watched "Republicans" barter away my liberty to preserve their own station, to remain in the good graces of leftists, etc., my entire life. If you think the solution to that is electing more Republicrats, or cordial conversations with Marxists, you're a fucking moron.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun fact: None of the Founders were Socialists, and Socialism has no basis in the Constitution. In the very work advocating for its adoption, Madison calls "a rage [...] for an abolition of debts" and the "equal division of property," an "improper" and "wicked project."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The president has never been elected by popular vote ("democratically") here. Next commie straw man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You know who doesn't get tips by the way? Health care workers. You can do CPR on someone with a GI bleed, that has shit literally coming out of their mouth, for half an hour and get nothing. But the blue haired lesbian that stirred some cinnamon into your latte deserves $5.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This interminable assumption on the part of the right, that leftists are ignorant of the ramifications of their beliefs and policies, merely serves the left &amp; illustrates the stupidity of the right. Stop treating them like fucking children, &amp; recognize they're volitional enemies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It should be obvious to any thinking person, that the left is using "private" social media platforms, to do what they cannot through the state. The First Amendment prevents the government from regulating speech. (2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I predict Tim has Jack as a guest again, after the latter tweets "new year new me."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You appear to be an apostate Marxist, so I'm not going to waste my time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those in law enforcement who will not get jabbed almost certainly will not comply with a disarm/apprehension mandate. Those in medicine who will not get jabbed almost certainly will not comply with a euthanasia mandate. There's a conspicuous culling occurring both here &amp; abroad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't ever want to be tested for anything of this nature again, because it went into a database, and I started getting calls from the government. I didn't ask to be contacted. I didn't ask for your advice. Leave me tf alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Federal control of elections is the Communist agenda. Socialist magazine article openly called for it.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The notion that "PoC" are being denied voting rights, that illegals and felons should be given voting rights, etc., is derived directly from the Communist Party platform, and is solely for the purpose of manipulating the outcome of elections through "expanding the electorate." #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leftists are always aggressors posturing as victims. Assiduously attacking in response to illusory transgressions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep. The old robbing the young who are too ignorant to know they're being robbed. Combine this with the disintegration of the family &amp; you've got a formula for inevitable ruin. The secularists want government to provide ever more, while producing ever fewer taxpayers to fund it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CRT is the name for Cultural Marxism among those who cannot recognize it.

See:#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've already been boycotting Starbucks for years. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Your sentiments are, as usual, naked Communist rhetoric, which you regurgitate by rote (while farcically claiming not to be a Communist). You're either a cognizant subversive, prevaricating, or an oblivious lemming utterly incapable of deductive reasoning. Both are trash. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Come back when you're not abject ignoramus. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There were also droves of ostentatiously unwashed drug addled reprobates. (Augments numbers.) I vividly remember filming a guy, blatantly high, dancing with a bread role within a drum circle of dirty hippies/junkies. The media coverage of all this? Unadulterated prevarication.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even if changes to the document induced reform (they won't), our own history has utterly evinced that, at best, that amelioration would last approximately 200 years before degrading once again to our current state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As always I pose this query. Are women "equal" or not? If they are, no pity, no concession. And "feminists" say they are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utterly vindicates my subsequent remark. You will constantly see this from leftists. They will blatantly have the same world view as Communists, and use terminology in the same context to the same end, etc., but claim it's just a "coincidence." ItS nOt ComMuNiZM wHeN I dO iT. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blows my mind that anyone claiming to be a "Christian," in particular, could support blindly following government mandates. By that rationale Christ should have been murdered in the womb. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This guy is incorrigible. His excuses are laughably disingenuous. Says he did it because he fell on hard times. I've literally had well less than $100 left and didn't resort to this crap. I'd rather starve in the fuckin gutter with my dignity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop using the words these people use for themselves and their beliefs. STOP. FUCKING. DOING. IT. Stop making up new names for this shit. You're only helping them by doing so. You are ONLY HELPING THEM by doing so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To say we want the same things conveys an almost incomprehensible divorcement from reality. It's kind of like saying Conservatives and pedophiles want the same thing because they both like children. The "security," "justice" &amp; "fairness" they want is totally different in nature.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was the only person that refused to be subjected and walked out. And even that was a strangely Orwellian affair. Student staff literally intercepted me, stood between me and the door, and repeatedly emphasized it was "required" and that I "have you stay."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Far too many of you are literally talking yourselves into slavery every time you open your mouths.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're seeing half the court repeatedly denying even unalienable rights, e g., life, and fabricating new ones out of thin air. The SCotUS violated its own precedent, for example, when it legalized "homosexual marriage."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I've never really been convinced chips are the "mark of the beast." Nor do I understand why they need to be. They represent the eradication of privacy; being monitored everywhere &amp; at all times. And that in and of itself should be enough to oppose its implementation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I like how every time a commie loses an argument the opposition is a "troll." You got me, Circe. I mean, even Robert Malone says it's nefarious, but what does he know. He only played a pivotal role in the development of "mRNA technology."

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats &amp; Libretardians are both leftists, working to the same end, they're merely taking different routes to get there. The Democrat seeks to empower government to impose their depravity on you. The Libretardian seeks one too powerless to stop them from imposing it on you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rand's sentiments do not supersede or efface those of the Founders. Nor the Apostles. Because that's something else I've seen; "libertarians" literally substituting "libertarian" precepts for Biblical precept; typically suggesting a Biblical basis for amorality/immorality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When are we gonna have a vaccine against leftist shit bags experimenting on deadly pathogens? That's the real problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If you resort to relativism to remove (discredit) an obstacle to your own impropriety, you remove it for everyone else also, and extend to them the same privilege.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Because "all experience hath shewn, that mankind are more disposed to suffer, while evils are sufferable, than to right themselves by abolishing the forms to which they are accustomed."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You're not only not a Christian, you conspicuously harbor abject antipathy, for one of its core precepts. Patriarchy. To say you're a Christian that rejects patriarchy, is like saying you're a capitalist that rejects profit. It's a de facto renouncement of the belief system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because that's how it will be construed. The rhetoric will be that "only fascists don't like riding in train cars," and an aversion to camps is "coming from a place of privilege." Black Conservative? Your ass is coming with us, because "you ain't black" if you're not a Communist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thomas Jefferson personally authored a bill punishing sodomy with castration, and today people not only turn their genitals inside out, but are celebrated as heroes for it. But "far-right theocracy" looms to hear AOC tell it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As usual leftists excise the moral component of a thing. Yes, you are supposed to be disgusted by depravity. The Bible (in its sublime utility) refers to transvestism, for example, as "abomination." Abomination essentially means worthy of disgust/hatred. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anti-medicineb or anti-doctor. But these people are Socialists, &amp; Socialists have perpetrated the greatest genocides in history. There were doctors complicit in Nazism (Karl Brandt), &amp; and there are doctors complicit in the CCP's genocide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These "Christians" today, that cower at the prospect of offending anyone (even the most irredeemable reprobates), are nothing like him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# As can be seen in the provided illustrative aid, you bitch about patriarchy/misogyny so much, one might assume you're a staff writer for CPUSA. You equivocated on my last query because you knew what the result would be. But as I said previously, it wouldn't help you. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# True story. Some guy literally fooled scientists around the world into believing he'd found the "missing link" by mismatching some primate bones. He even got an honorary induction into some scientific society.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Told my friend I didn't like him, and was basically skeptical of anything he had to "teach," because he struck me as effeminate. Got vilified (naturally) as being judgmental, placing appearance over substance, etc. 

And then some time later this happened: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deer "modern" Christians. The Old Testament is part of the Bible. Jesus himself references it. It should probably matter to you too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Libertarians" are some of the dumbest people I've ever had the misfortune of encountering. They usually hate me, and I've been banned from multiple lib pages, for pointing out the fact they've adopted the entire Marxist cultural platform. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I already did. They consolidated power, by eliminating competition (including other Socialist rivals; e.g., Night of Long Knives), as has been done repeatedly by Socialist shit heads. This notion that Socialists never disagree is one of the most absurd and trite commie strawmen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which, as one can see, is our nation's biggest problem. An abundance of morons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To accept the diminution of Christian religious liberty at the hands of government, is something that should induce revulsion in any American, particularly a Christian American. The United States is not and was never intended to be another Rome. We were not meant to grovel here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to keep the truth from an American just hide it in a book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He's under some kind of directive to interfere as little as possible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 100% correct. We need to get people to stop calling our country a "democracy" too. That is likewise commie drivel.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What other purpose but aiding and abetting tyranny could FB have for removing such a group? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The United States was never intended to be a "democracy." Educate yourselves.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# But the fact is many have chosen to do so. Because they can. Because it's of little (if any) consequence. And because they cannot grasp the folly of trading perennial benefit for (perceived) ephemeral gain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you hear the constant comparisons to Reagan, that merely illustrates these jackasses only want to revert back to a few decades ago, as opposed to restoring Constitutional limited government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I saying it's a sin? No, not per se. But it always struck me as indicative of a deep seated problem in the "modern" church. Their lives, and thus their views, were devoid of austerity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# These bureaucrats brag about how they redistribute wealth from other states to their own. That was not the purpose of our federalist system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# While you're at it throw things like smoking and obesity induced maladies (e.g., COPD, diabetes, etc.) into that category also. All if these people who choose to be unhealthy are a waste of resources.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Of course. Broadcasting your conformity is all the rage with pretentious commie know-it-alls. Truth is they're children. As evinced by the degree to which peer pressure still directs their lives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just another old whore that won't grow up. She should be baking brownies for her grandkids, and instead she's still going to parties. Did you want to hang out with your parents with you were young? Your grandparents? Dumb bitch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The government established by the Founders was republican at every level, from the federal government, to its smallest iteration the nuclear family, of which the father/husband was representative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When sexual deviants had power millennia ago, they used it to brutally repress Christian virtue. When in power today they do the same thing. No sooner than we afforded them "rights," did they set themselves to destroying ours, prostrating us, and corrupting our children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun fact: Washington refers to the duopoly we have today, i.e., the "alternate domination of one faction over another," as a "frightful despotism" that destroys liberty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# "I like a good attitude also. Omg we have so much in common! Welcome aboard." - Tim Pool (probably).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not only don't uphold it, but openly view it with animus, considering it an impediment to "progress" (Communism). #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, they're not. They're opinion is shifting with the narrative shift; i.e., they're still just being sheep. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This caused me to begin questioning the narrative, &amp; uniformity of the response (similar/same restrictions for rural areas as large cities) early on. Within months, observing that infection was essentially a two week (often paid) vacation, staff began flouting safety measures.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any efforts I made to counteract this were obstructed. I eventually gave up in abject frustration. It felt like I had to leave both my brains and balls at the door to participate, and I simply refuse to do that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton signed DOMA. The present day GOP has completely capitulated on sexual ethics, and openly brags about how "tolerant" (left) it is. We have a two Socialist Party system in this country now. The hardcore Communists (Democrats), and the Fabian Socialists (Republicans).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The GOP's messiah complex is a huge problem. Reagan is dead. Do you understand that? There will never be "another Reagan." Nor is he the standard. He was a moderate/centrist at best (gave us amnesty, Czars, 2-A infringement, etc.). We need another Washington. Not another Reagan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Why "debate?" Debates accomplish nothing in my experience. Neither the participants or spectators' minds are changed, the latter of which only attend/watch for the spectacle and bias confirmation. Why waste your time on something that almost certainly has an ulterior motive?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This sounds nigh identical to the leftist/effeminate spiel against spanking. And if that's the case you're not a coach of shit to me. Anyone not a godless commie would know full well. "He that spareth his rod hateth his son: but he that loveth him chasteneth him betimes."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Years ago I became unofficially persona non grata at the local churches. The pastors wouldn't say hi to me, or even look at me, at the grocery store. Why? Because I was a vocal critic of what I called the hyper-effeminacy of the "modern" church.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So just another stupid commie cow too stupid to know they're a commie.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conversely, if I farted and it sounded like the fart of a German National Socialist, "OMG FASCIST/NAZI!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Libertarians" often don't like me. They've gotten enraged when I point out that, however sagacious she may be, she was not a Founder or an author of any of this Nation's original documents. She is not the "authority" on these things and never will be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would love to be wrong but I felt from the outset Trudeau would just wait it out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look, if the Patriarchs of the church had been like "modern" Christians, there would be no Christianity. Because they'd have passed their days puking specious validations for their apathy and indifference. Offend a godless commie reprobate today. It's what Jesus would do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The people who think they can fix a corrupt system through that system are deluded.

"It is so easy to lull the conscience by the delusive idea that the best way to reform a government is first to swear to support it, and to take a part in its operations." - James Willson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It seems completely forgotten today that the men who Founded this country rebelled against their own government. And that they were called "traitors" by their Tory brethren, just like we are today by their modern Democrat and RINO equivalents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure, Christ was crucified. But have you ever had chaffed nipples?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's my experience that people tend to emphasize their own attributes and diminish those of others. E.g., weak men will portray their weakness as a virtue and strength as a flaw. Can't tell you how many times I've had my literacy construed as a character flaw by morons. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah, okay Yawny. Clearly the deductive prowess of a radish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a difference between serving your country and serving your government. Stop conflating them. One can do the latter without ever doing the former. And this should be known, given how the men who devised our Constitution, explicitly warn us about such in the Federalist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My motto has always been deal with them before they deal with you. Because you better believe they'll deal with you as soon as they're able (e.g., disarmed).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As we convoked on the sidewalk that morning, passing "homosexual" men would stop, and talk about raping us ("Nazis"). At one point a pickup came to a screeching halt in the middle of the street, &amp; the driver screamed out the window, "I hope Al-Qaeda cuts your fucking heads off."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blaming guns for homicide is like blaming airplanes for 911.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not to mention he was a big government/spending Republican. The GoP electorate doesn't want genuine Conservatives anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least he dispensed with the pretense. "Permits" are a tax; the monetization of liberty. It's always been about the money, and always will be, with these bureaucrats. They're perpetually seeking to fund their decadence at the expense of your liberty.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've been pointing this out for a long time also as well as the cause.

See:#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Like all modern leftist made films, its purpose is not to entertain, but to indoctrinate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Will you tell me how to prevent riches from becoming the effects of temperance and industry—Will you tell me how to prevent riches from producing luxury—Will you tell me how to prevent luxury from producing effeminacy, intoxication, extravagance, vice, and folly." - John Adams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was never about "science." Anyone who thinks people that believe in multitudinous genders care about "science" is clueless. The virus served it's purpose: ousting Trump. Everything since/else has just been icing on the cake. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each believes they're better administrators of a bureaucracy that neither wants to eliminate. Every election we see two parties of Socialists, arguing they can better manage an unconstitutional bureaucracy that shouldn't exist, and every election "Conservatives" fall for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The free states should have already seceded. Blue states cannot be allowed to subvert the whole union in this manner. If nothing is done this WILL ultimately result in the subsumption of the red states into a Marxist nation state. Elect governors will balls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Christians should grovel to a godless state is the creed of deluded apostate pussies. Christianity has been propagated against the wishes of "authorities" since its inception (Act 5:29). The U.S. Seal proposed by 3 Founders stated "rebellion to tyrants is obedience to God."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The bearded women in skinny jeans that throng the "modern" church.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The point was to get Trump out of office. The Democrats used these Marxist revolutionaries to create havoc, for which they blamed and vilified Trump ad nauseum. Trump's gone. They're no longer needed. And thus you don't see/hear shit about them anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't either. But going "bigger" than 9 is just a pointless waste of money in my opinion. As someone that's seen multiple gunshot wounds, you can't tell what "caliber" it is by looking at the wound.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>