<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# After their abstention yesterday, they nailed their colours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Deffo mate.
You have nailed your likeness there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boris falls on his sword.
"Playing Politics" uttered ad infinitum.
That 18 mins was EXCRUCIATING!
Faux apologies.
He doesn't give a single pico of a...
I dunno if it's my hearing, but I'm sure I didn't hear "resign prime minister" from KS.
Did any of you?
1/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# *weird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They are.
And yet are treated like dirt under the carpet!
Makes me beyond angry they get scapegoated by this miserable s**t of a government.
Every hospital stint, I've always brought a thank you card.
Their job is thankless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# (Cont)
Love the stereogram.
What is it please?
Used to have a Ferguson.
Loved that thing.
It was collosal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Daria knows her stuff and is very knowledgeable. And VERY passionate.
Matt had no answer really did he?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# WOWnDangerous cycling.nYeah, well that makes gig economy workers like Deliveroo fucked then ey?nNothing about feral gangs and moped theives who shake people down.nAfter all. Cyclists are bad people arent they? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And to you Binkers.
I hope this year things finally change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hit back with Pythagoras Theorem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I don’t even think they can hold a fountain pen the right way up.nThey are so bloody inept.nThey would skewer their own eye with it.nWith the Keystone Cops in charge of us all.nHow nice to feel safe and secure!n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You forgot to put #HASHTAG# at the end of it.nA head's up..nRW dyed in the wool Tory voters are not your enemy.nWho they have no choice to vote for, are.nOur brains are all wired different.nSome wired are  lefties.nSome RW.nSome centrist or politically homeless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatdya reckon?
Lockdown in the coming week's?
The Jerk doing the kneejerk?
Polling not as good, let's kiss off the nation.
Ioathe that man! 
#HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "You are standing in the way of my wheelie case!
No, I'm not going to explain glass chinking.
I didn't hear anything".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thank you.
I have a bacterial chest infection as it is.
And even though the mucus is a more acceptable colour (sorry if it's TMI).
My chest still feels heavy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That's how you tease the freshly caught mouse.
Anticipation is half the fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not been in an actual restaurant of theirs since '04.
But I do like their marinades in supermarkets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 
Well done Jessie!
Glad you kicked the skag.
Cap Doffed.
#HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fucking dalek in #HASHTAG# pushing #HASHTAG# to "extermin8" us #HASHTAG#.
You don't send an intoxicated  sheiße to deal with #HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fantastic pic Goosie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Death: "will you stop repeating the words "playing politics over &amp; over? At this rate I will miss my appointment with Bill And Ted later!".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I don't like the Cayman.
There's a cpl driving round here like some quasi Chelsea Tractor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As soon as #HASHTAG# is deposed, she will go back to mediocrity.
She will be just another journeyman like Jerry Hall.
Where who is on her arm keeps her in the spotlight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It was actually having to phone environmental health here in the UK.
Cos the neighbors who moved in next door were making so much noise at 2am including playing dubstep at D.E.S.T.R.O.Y. volume.
Keeping my two year old awake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They don't change do they?
Only physical.
Doing creatine.
Getting pilled up.
Fucking loathe them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thank you.
Took a bit of time, but it's steady.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I Want You is my favourite Utah Saints tune.
Came out when I married my second ex wife.
This is good tho.
Love the use of Kate Bush - Cloudbusting sample.
Classic #HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And to and yours mate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Did you know you can get those as ice lollies.
Think Iceland sell them. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm so sorry dude.
The government are more tight fisted than Arthur Daley.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Who doesn't love a Cossie?
On eBay, they are going for stupid money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Brains remain sharp until 60, study suggests
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It'll be nice mate but I think she has already made the choice (she is on twitter).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One of my ex father in law's came from Preston.
Always brought back down Stoke Meat &amp; Potato Pies.
Wonder if that is still a thing there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No Kubrick this time tho.
Ridley Scott?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was right!
My music memory better than my normal recall. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I know what the "C" in #HASHTAG# is.
And it rhymes with runt.
Because plan c is going to be cancelling everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wish the Murrayfield crowd give more voice.
Scotland need a mental pickup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else got their #HASHTAG# hands in the air like I have #HASHTAG#?
Avin' it! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wish it would hurry up and land on #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# His Berlin period isn't for everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 3/3
Here is the thread.
Remember, these were my thoughts in '19. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm actually in a very rare good mood mate 😱
And have a little bit of NRG this evening.
So I'm multitasking.
Thanks for asking mate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bottom.
Although I’ve just gone into the photos I’ve taken and found these. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Was playing that just the other night.
It's certainly a favourite of mine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is called that.
Morrisons stores do a microwave version in the chilled veg and stir fry section for about a quid or so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Haven't got any mate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kirsty is so sorely missed.
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best #HASHTAG# present to be given is an end to this #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# nightmare.
Only cash blown on dodgy PPE contracts minus tendering.
And investment in propaganda to shook nation's isn't actually ending this crisis.
Christmas can GFY.
We want our lives back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Jack Daniel's and #HASHTAG# are festive "spirits" right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sheer Heart Attack
Never Mind The B******s
Bat Out Of Hell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And it's still horrible.
It's got too much chicory in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They are very strong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# (Continued)
And the very first Tomb Raider too.
Marvelous game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Seconded.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Haven't found any SACD in the charity shop wilds.
But I have found a cpl of Japanese HQ ones.
Including Page Plant - Unledded.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Looks like Chris Tarrent in that pic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's how it works isn't it?
You can be the biggest bastard &amp; get rewarded.
I bet #HASHTAG# or if Starmer was PM - #HASHTAG# would be made a lord.
And there is Assange in nick, wasting away.
Cos he dared to show the truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot dog.
Jump in fire.
I've burnt bollocks.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That will be the lifting of restrictions to get a "Boris Bounce" to get those figure's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Traffic light system using coloured hearts from the emoji tray?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's a great live album.
Better than '79.
There's an '81 one as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3/
"Paper's Please" via digital.
Becoming North Korea and the former East Germany.
Via an oppressive &amp; Stalinist form of rule.
Your freedom?
Forget it!
It's gone.
It's over.
Free choice being curtailed.
Free speech being silenced.
Your piddly little vote meant nothing. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Piano House / Rave 
Fantastic.
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hope the move goes well mate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I already have all that.nShame you haven't!nLook how many follows I have including writers, doctors, musicians and politicians.nSo myself and my follows are obviously dumb compared to you who has a brain like Megamind oh great one!n#HASHTAG#, what's the answer to my question?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 
(No words)
#HASHTAG# 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah, I've seen in looking through the web &amp; I weep inside for what's happening Claimy.
And the kicker is we are powerless to stop it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is now a free game on Android.
Give it another blast. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I don't want a new one.
I want a complete remaster of the original prime.
But I want its original music kept.
The music especially Phenandra Drifts and Chozo Ruins are so atmospheric.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Halcyon by #HASHTAG# samples this Opus 3 tune.
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Funny with the liberals innit?nThorpe affair.nCyril Smith.nCoalition with the tories.nYeah. Great bunch of lads.n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They put him forward for a few reasons.
He is the easiest to market.
Easiest to achieve popularity by people falling for his "Act" of bumble &amp; bluster, making people sorry for him.
And easiest to be be a Patsy when it all folds in.
If he goes (hopefully), who can they "sell"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 
Someone has kindly found the #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hopefully Agnes this helps
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Having a botched birth including a forceps cut on my head and a life of mental illness is enough to say I'm unlucky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Grandstand taught me well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Vodka is like paint stripper.
I like it but in moderation.
One night in 1998, a friend sent me round an Alldays (remember that convenience chain) for a litre of Smirnoff Red.
My god, did I feel so I'll after an empty stomach and the lurching...
Eeeesh.
I was such an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's bringing great memories for me.
I left someone that year cos the relationship was dead.
So rebounded and enjoyed life a bit.
New person.
Spectacular sex (we broke the bed - ooops 😂)
And she was pretty - win!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# *The calling of favors
(I could happily shoot Autocorrect grr!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pretty much.
But a war this time will take weeks rather than year's.
And we will LOSE while Truss &amp; Co are safely in the bunker's.
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# 4/
Why should I support a man who won't throw a warmonger out the party?
Because said warmonger with Dubya upset the planet natural balance via a false flag, the murdering of Dr Kelly.
And the Iraq invasion killing over time 1m people?
Unlike you, I actually have principles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I would strap the perp to a gurney in a room with blunt instruments.
Then let people loose on them.
There is too much child murder and cruelty these day's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I remember it but I didn't buy it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Great tune with Grace Jones guesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I just think he is an annoying little boy in short trouser's who goes around prodding people, then runs off.
One thing we can agree on.
That he despises anyone a pico to the left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Been listening to the egregious ERG and short trader's so they can get their huge dividend.
It's all about cold hard cash.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I know.
And she was a friend of Pinochet.
Then there was the protection of Slug incarnate Cyril Smith.
What a piece of filth he was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Then if you think about it right?
Them lot getting their Jollie's is a bad example to the nation.
And trivialising the whole Covid thing.
People will see this &amp; think if MPs are doing what they are doing, then this pandemic isn't as serious as made out.
1/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know #HASHTAG# are a bit marmite to people.
(I still think Origin Of Symmetry is their magnum opus).
Here is their new one.
Give it a chance Music Twitter.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Got a taste all of its own.
Has to be with Daddies sauce #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# OUCH.
If you lived nearer, I would happily give you a bottle of oral morphine I have on perm script.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm 56 this year.
All I know is cos of those station's, Alan Fluff Freeman, Stuart Henry and John Peel - that my musical taste is partially shaped by them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[France out the gate this second half.
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My Bessie does the worst farts of all.
FFS don't give him anything with fried chicken or chicken kebab.
Cos when he guffs, it's like a nuke fallout zone.
Worse if he has been out on da razz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# nI think Harris dying in prison would be a fitting accoladenDescended from prisoners to actually being onen#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW!
Well done #HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There is a white one that drives round where I live.
Always loved a Countach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Me too!
Totally avoiding the spoilers on the tech channels I watch.
It feels like Christmas present"s opening early.
I can upgrade my Air 4 in November.
So I wanna know what to expect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The cd seller's are good.
The more you buy from them and give quick feedback - the quicker the next order.
One seller made me feel sorry for them.
Full of thank yous that I paid quick.
Apparently they are genuinely struggling and selling their prized albums.
Made me really sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 2/
.. Bastard's.
There were different races in our cliqué.
Those filth took expressed jollification of giving us a slap around.
In forty year's, nothing has changed.
Another Tory government.
Another overuse of authority overkill.
It's institutional.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Nightingales.
Each with their own set of TV cameras, a TV control room, actors playing patients and simpering lickspittle "journos".
For the next month's till march fgs!
That money cuda ended this nightmare but no.
The Tories use #HASHTAG# to stay in power.
#HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Beautiful cat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As I.
2019 was the last loan of my vote.
And then I will be dubbed "Tory Enabler".
Well that is bunkum, cos I didn't vote Tory.
I do feel we have nobody on our side.
What #HASHTAG# did was unforgiving.
They always sell out.
Every damn single time!
Who can we trust?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Look at his face...it's heartbreaking.
Depher, when I was in hospital / rehab last year, I experienced first hand some poor people with dimensia.
Was talking to their rellies / carers / other &amp; finding out just how outcasted the clients are.
They are human beings but..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL#
At least 17 dead after consuming 'poisoned cocaine' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I know!
One of my following (who I won't tag) remarked on him before.
Maybe it's the aircraft carrier runway forehead he has.
Btw, you just got a fifth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The VLT1 was before it wasn't it?
Used on Get Carter and Open Your Heart off Dare.
And on Da Da Da by Trio.
I love these synths.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Politics should stay in politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Blackpool promenade shut after building partial collapse
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm no fan of them neither.
I have the hotel of death (Sister Meg dubs it that cos they murdered our dad) in the morning for a pelvis x-ray and orthopaedic after.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There are some challenges to smash things up for a high score mate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Have you tried putting every cart into the Sonic And Knuckles cart (which really was just an interface).
Pressed A.B.C. on the pad the same time and played the unique blue spheres subgame if it worked? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW!
#HASHTAG#

BBC News - Essex photographer paints Christmas scenes in light
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fiat Strada?
No.
Remember the ad to this day.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sub to this channel.
Check their remakes of the levels.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why don't you convert the tapes to digital so you have them in the cloud forever?
Tapes are making a huge comeback currently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Till we know the facts....
Well he admitted he was there.
Rules were broke.
What else is there #HASHTAG#?
Its buying #HASHTAG# more time for Gray to get him off. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nah, he was wrestling with an Action Man while jumping over a doll's House.
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Like most of those.
Buzzcocks - What Do I Get is the best one in that list.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's a toughie.
The Stratos.
Blue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toni Halliday&amp; #HASHTAG#
Pure brilliance!
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 5 for me.
But then, my life is a saga.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've had booze every day since at least early December.
After year's of just the odd #HASHTAG#, I've got a taste for it again.
I've been ill with this bacterial chest infection since late November.
The booze is a coping mechanism.
But...I don't drink to get drunk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know why there are anti homeless spikes?nBecause those who thought it a good idea are spiny PRICKSn#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just asked Siri who the scorer's are.
Sounds like everyone has had a go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Honestly mate?
No.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm very much not a people person. (Reasons &amp; fully justified)
But...
I do care about their right's &amp; freedoms being ripped off them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My neighbor upstairs is a chef of 20yrs.
Before the pandemic, he had a comfortable job over in Norwich.
(We live in Gorleston)
After being laid off, it's hard to get work for him.
So he has to go away out of the county weeks at a time.
Hospitality has hit a MN assive crash.
1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's the "get used to it" that annoyed me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't Dream It's Over was a better tune.
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One that him &amp; Wilfred build out of Lego.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Anything is better than Boris right now.
He is a flesh eating parasite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There is always someone bigger than them.
Ever watched Women's MMA?
Now they are super hard.
There is one called Shepshenko or something like that 
Wow mate...just wow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You just cancelled yourself out by not going into Google to see for yourself.
Why should we do all the legwork for you?
Your problem is that you only care for your overinflated six figure wage coupled with your overinflated ego.
FGS Dara! Take a day off!
The corporation is done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Think how much the #HASHTAG# and #HASHTAG# problem could have used with that money?nBut hey. nIt gives our ringpiece, cuckold defense secretary a semi hard-on so that must be a positive right? n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Collecting music is a scratch I need to fix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's on iPlayer on BBC now if y'all wanna watch it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Miss my cd of that.
Have it digital somewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I tell you.
This vaccine pass thing will ruin more businesses.
Cos people to won't wanna eat out if they have this extra pressure put on them.
So fast food corporates rake the bank in cos people will be order from home.
It's killing the human race
We need to talk to eachother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Didn't her and Cathy Dennis go on to write for other people?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The sound design is fantastic.
As soon as you drop out the pod, the music, atmosphere and lack of people set the creepy mood.
It's quite disturbing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actual LOL
#HASHTAG# 
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do you think he is embarrassed by it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You did well Young Padawan.
There is a track on the Sting album called It's Probably Me.
It was pointed to me about 4yrs ago.
There was a bunch of us on a thread talking about great songwriter's.
And a link to the song was posted.
You know the rest.
***Not Addicted*** 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Best version is on the GameCube.
Seen the ex tear it up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Do you agree with me that Somebody Up There Likes You is one of the best instrumental's ever recorded off NGD?
Simple Minds songs, some need more love.
Scar off the Reel To Reel Cacophony album certainly does.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's going to be a tough day for you all.
You have my birthday wishes mate.
But it seems pretty futile as today is going to be as tough as they come.
Life is precious, yes.
We only have one chance at this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I can bet he also blamed the Brits as well?
Because the Tories won't take blame themselves...for anything.
Such blatant narcissist aloofness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Obviously they're a sensitive soul George 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Being lazy bathbugs and getting paid for it.
You joined your local FB page?
You will get it to the owner quicker.
Obvs keep sensitive info redacted. 
Get anyone to DM you via your page regulators for safety.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, it is serious.
And so are #HASHTAG# lives.
Of which him here is in no position to make comments as he is just as useless as the rest of the Tory ingrates.
Ergo, he DGAD about lives.
Hence my question.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I blame the UHD rectangular of Doom (when they aren't watching boxsets)
And the squarking DAB radio propaganda.
I tell ya right?
You could kneecap #HASHTAG# support with a SPAS 12 and exploding shells.
And they STILL would hang in every blubber of blootered babble.
SMH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is fucking genocide.
#HASHTAG#

BBC News - Kazakhstan unrest: Troops ordered to fire without warning
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ok.
So I may have got it wrong.
I do think tho the bottom menu across the screen should be up top.
The top line seems to be geared so you stumble into the store.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done #HASHTAG# way you treat people who want to work is exemplary.nAnd that, btw is #HASHTAG##HASHTAG# nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# should have been stalled after #HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG# 
More useless than a chocolate chip pan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've got both the puyo puyo Tetris ones.
And puyo puyo champion's on Switch.
So addictive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Isolating sux innit.
When I was in rehab with my hip, I had to do ten day's of it in my private room.
Wasn't all bad tho.
Was waited on like a king.
And had frequent visits by staff to keep me company and chat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right, it's on.
Looks like vomit. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I read a thread early this morning with this "Christmas Miracle" birth the subject.
A cpl of commenters suggest surrogacy.
A girl &amp; a boy for their perfectly Hollywood scripted utopia.
This is #HASHTAG#
Everything has been a lie or a living as one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Look at that pic.
Her aloof with her pet monkey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Removing Dorries will give us one thing.
Her replacement will actually possess a Braincell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'll give them their due.
They know how to protest.
Unlike boxset binge watching Britons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You have gave me some ideas.
Looks like list three coming up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I get fibre plus 36mps.
A new Apple TV box on its way so the current one will be my bedroom one.
Apple TV free for a year when it arrives.
BT Sport for two years.
£40pcm
Works for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But....nBut....n£1bn was given to gay hating, batshit crazy unionists.nSurely they need that more than #HASHTAG# needed £30m to keep floating?n#HASHTAG##HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The fact Blair gets one at all fills me with rage like Yosemite Sam. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's partly why I brought a disc version PS5.
Cos a 4K disc player would have set me back £200 for a Sony
You looked on Richer Sounds site?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Innoculated or "out of pocket".
Brought some Martini Bianco yesterday to go with the Crissy drinks.
Not had none since '03.
And I used to love it.
It won't last long....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Quelle Suprise!n£154.50pa by the mafia to pay for more bias.nHow about putting #HASHTAG# in a pink kimono and praise the great leader?nHeck, why don't we have full military parades to show off ordinance we proudly build to vaporise Yemeni kids?n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There is hate in her face that needs to be reined back.
And I agree, she isn't right in the head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Double Dash for me.
Do have fond memories of F-Zero GX (AX was the arcade version).
This tune right here off its OST is a stormer.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well I'm in the town for them for sure.
I've got nobody to go with.
I don't fancy my stoma going BRAAPPP at some moment.
Same as I don't go to da flix.
Can't say "pardon my a**e, it's a friend", when my a**e is on the left side of my stomach 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tense moments for Chelski there.
At least I didn't have to sit through another Pen shootout as a neutral.
This win will please my eldest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# gave back over £800m + he was supposed to use for more #HASHTAG# 
Now he is at health.
And he is going to build 40 new hospital's?
Nah.
Never will happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 3/
I'm not afraid to speak out because I have the intelligence to understand the differences.
All we hear are deliberate misinterpretation's.
It's being used as a political weapon.
Forced Aparteid is wrong.
Internment is wrong.
They forget South Africa pre Mandela release.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I honestly didn't know when I picked these up today it was the anniversary of his sad death.
RIP #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Persona 4 is one of the best games ever made.
Have you played the Persona 4 Dancing All Night game or the Persona 3 &amp; 5 which accompany it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ha!
Brilliant!
Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Still getting annoyed aren't you little bear.
To think you were the tadpole that reached the egg?
By luck obviously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's the innocent orange juice with bits in I like.
I keep the empties which I fill with squash diluted and put them in the fridge.
Apparently in middle age, men need some hydration by them while asleep so they can wake up for a period and have a drink waiting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# (Cont.)
I'm double jabbed.
Very much under protest because my body is a Trainwreck &amp; my surgery advised.
Thought after the initial two, that's it, no more.
Schoolboy error.
I won't be having the booster as I've not been right since the first jabs.
My choice until full enforce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# is a marketable product like detergent.
Only this time round, it's harder to rebrand when people have buyer's remorse.
People are going to point at DC and declare "dare he tell us what we don't want to know".
Well the public have the right to.
And they are VERY angry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# (One of the best films ever made) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Very sad.
I've not heard the Brainwashed album that came out just after he died.
Thought Cloud Nine was good tho.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They did.
Especially the last two album's which sound very strong in these times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I've played it on 3.1
3.11 workgroups.
Win 95 and 98.
Used to play it when I finished my coursework for the day.
Or myself &amp; friends would be writing text RPGs in Excel via the Macro function.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# As seen in the Rosie &amp; Jim kids show.
Rip fizzgog. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Now Authority have taken the fun out of everything.
I think we were lucky to be so carefree then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Storm Arwen: Two men die as gale-force winds hit UK
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Energy firm Bulb set to go into administration
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold tight!
So if there is Russian and Belarusian are on the border?
Then Belarus could invade and they will be seen as the cause #HASHTAG# 
The next week will determine the fate of the planet...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We used to say Love, Sex and twenty pence when it came out.
The Shamen's Boss Drum album with LSI on it is worth a buy or stream.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The capture / peacekeeping was a ruse.
The next week will determine a next move...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is mate.
Although sadly my cd has the shorter version.
It's on this.
There's a cpl of album's in the series I need (although I have digital but not FLAC format)
Album's are worth your time Mark. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This particular government (?), a lot more than the previous two "attempts" seem to get off on trolling the nation.
We are a mouse caught by a cat so pleased with themselves of the suffering the mouse will endure.
No curve flattening.
No tackling the virus.
No endgame.
1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I won't buy it when it's in that state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The best TV for gaming / entertainment for you is the LG C1.
Gsync compatible.
The 55 is 1300 quid at Argos.
Look on YouTube for reviews and most will gush over it.
And the panel is so thin.
The 48" is a grand at Argos.
Perfect as a computer monitor too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great try by #HASHTAG# !
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>