<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Many times, more often than straight people realize, it's happening in the heart, in the eyes, in the brain, and in touch.  It's happening in character. It happens in good times together.  In laughter. It's always happening in what they describe on movie screens as "chemistry."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's one reason I haven't gone out of my way to contact any of them, much as I miss Boyfriend.  I'm just not willing to tolerate that level of IGNORANCE in my life anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HE'S NOT AFRAID!!!  He's EMBARRASSED about something!  That's all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can always say a rabid zombie kidnapped you for three hours on your way back from the store.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my family members were the only people of color on the ice.  And, even though we were having fun, being tokens made those memories painful in certain ways.  Same as hiking the Appalachian Trail with the Mennonite Church when we were kids.  I don't remember having seen any other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Um-huh.  The standard daily news story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow!  Powerful report by CBS News Sunday morning on Bryan Stevenson and the teaching of American history and the pursuit of justice!  Many kudos!  A lot of nails on the head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the same few minutes, I watched an uplifting report on tv this morning about survivors of the Holocaust returning to concentration camps, and then, reports of swastikas being spraypainted in D.C.  Nauseating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then, there's the cutting the tv cable thing.  That totally shocked me!  So, he has PLENTY of reasons to hide!  I just don't think they're as bad as he's making them out to be in his own mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He used to work his ass off just to keep me entertained and from being bored!  Why shouldn't I do the same for him on Twitter???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG!!!  White people love using systems they put in place to claim reverse discrimination!!!  It's INSANE!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did someone threaten them???  Warn them to play nice or something???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You love being Alpha.  And you love thinking I'm your proporty.  Even if it's from a distance.  But you're expecting me to STOP on a dime???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any time I see news stories of some group of people hiding away in a compound and staying in there while it burns to the ground, or a flock of idiots smashing their way into the Capitol Building, Scientologists are the first to come to mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone help me understand how a bunch of seditionists and insurrection fomenters and election lie promotors can be allowed to vote down equal voting rights in our own Congress???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They want a civil war, do they???  They may only be considering racial minorities.  But numerically, they may be fighting two thirds of the entire population of the United States of America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I laugh almost every day thinking about what would have happened had I said to him, "Take off your pants and let's wrestle!!!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Members of the Harvard branch of the Ku Klux Klan pose for a graduation photo on Class Day 1924 at the foot of the John Harvard Statue in Harvard Yard. By Courtesy of the Boston Public Library, Leslie Jones Collection #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love these people.  But I need folks around me who THINK better.  I'm trying to stay OUT of trouble.  Which means not constantly having to try to keep THEM out of trouble too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hell.  You never know what folks get away with in IHOP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, please stop asking me to have faith in or hope for some kind of miracle that will suddenly make masses of people come to their senses or be kinder.  It's just not in the cards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure, but I think the "FBI" tried to let me know they're still around.  Not that I really care.  I'm stayin' at home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their heart would virtually stop pumping blood if they did!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All it takes to dispel the truth in this country is to call it a hoax or a witch hunt.  Presto-chango!!!  Everybody believes the lie instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well...  My doctor does.  But he's getting paid to.  You guys ain't gettin' DICK!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ya' know...  We had rat mazes in Psychology class.  And I read Psychology Today a lot.  And I've seen numerous television reports and documentaries about cognitive behavior.  Over time, RATS LEARN!!!  But these people don't!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to worry myself sick when you were out in the streets all night until I either got a phone call or you showed up and let me know you were okay.  That's a hard habit to break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their lives and careers depend on stoking divisions.  Honesty and integrity and patriotism don't matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're about to do that ourselves anyway.  What the hell does North Korea or Russia believe they will accomplish by nuclear attack other than destroying us ALL?!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They probably tell their kids it's too pornographic for them to see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate these people when they look straight into the camera saying such noxious things like this is the first time we ever heard them speak.  Or like they didn't tutor the traitorous child king to handle himself during a presidential debate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cross the picket line, I could probably find a flight back to Atlanta for a lot less than what everyone else was advertising.  So, that's what I did.  I got a flight for around $58, got my stuff out of a locker, came back to Atlanta, caught MARTA back to Decatur, and had one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or, even better, a fruit basket.  Surely, they like fruit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give it up, white boy!  Ain't happening!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The white people who never believed in that myth seem to be doing just fine.  The ones who swallowed the myth without question are the ones who are panicking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also loved the report on Architect Frank Gehry.  One of my favorites, along with John Portman and Frank Lloyd Wright.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't see him in the crowd on January 6th.  So, he can't be hiding from Congress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But that's not the reason I'm trying to get you back in the picture.  I'd be happy, even if you just took the class and we didn't hang out together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When we're in public, he's all over me.  When I'm being paranoid about it, he's the one who tells ME to relax.  When we go to the movies, he always sits right next to me, no matter who else we're with.  Same deal on rollercoasters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now, they all know I didn't forget.  And they know I didn't stop caring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You wanna play it safe on everything and then blame me for having FUN however creatively I can think of!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why don't you just call a spade a spade and introduce the people on one side as American patriots and people on the other side as Confederate survivalists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden hasn't even announced his nominee for the Supreme Court and they've already cranked up the hypocrisy machine.  It's always as predictable as the sun rising in the east and setting in the west.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know what you're dealing with.  But it must be pretty bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had a fucking blast!  And I'm trying to sit here being mad about for some reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Good morning" must be a very menacing thing to say to strangers on the street!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somehow, I ended up right back on the street where the Scientologists where.  There was one of those canopy covers over stairs that lead down below the sidewalk next door.  A man was standing there and saw me looking at the building.  He asked me whether I had dealt with the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ya' know...  I've tried that listening to both sides theory and heard white people say things like, "You're only here because of Affirmative Action" and "Black people weren't built for ballet" and "races shouldn't intermarry because Blacks are inferior" and "All black people eat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish I could find all those white guys who forcefully stripped my pants down to ask them why they were that anxious to see a gay guy's dick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why was my stuff in a locker at the airport?  Because mom had tried to warn me to be careful.  So, when they sent someone to pick me up at LaGuardia, I rented a locker, just in case!  After breaking out of the building, I was walking on the streets, freezing my ass off in a thin,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At his father's wedding to his second wife, I endured one grandparent saying racist things about his aunt's Black girlfriend.  I bit my tongue to keep from causing a scene.  But I know who he is now.  And I just can't abide that kind of talk anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They drive like they don't give a fuck who lives or dies!  Me.  Them.  Or the people around them who don't drive as fast or as well.  Why should I keep putting up with that?!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't even say YES, let's go to a movie or NO, I don't wanna go to a movie.  Not because of ME!  Because of YOU!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one would pass me off as a legitimate brain surgeon just because I threw on a lab coat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I planned to have y'all running ALL OVER the city to find stuff!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually...  I'm sorry I can't do that for you myself.  But this isn't about me today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Except for Boyfriend, his mother and three of four grandparents, they don't LEARN!!!  And they don't LISTEN!!! They tell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They all had to start somewhere.  They weren't born knowing everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's seen me on the dartboard too.  So, he knows I can't accurately throw a knife!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["cult", as he called it.  He pointed to a huge picture window across the street with the words "Open Door" on them.  He said I could stay there overnight.  I went there, but when I looked inside the glass, the place was empty.  So, he shouted for me to go to A&amp;R Studios next door]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I scared the shit out of both of them by remembering the name of a person who used to contact me on AOL all the time decades ago.  That person knew way more about my personal life than a stranger should know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sitting in the living room one day trying to tactfully explain something about his girlfriend when his dad and brother bust out laughing and saying, "He wouldn't know what to do with a woman, even if he had one!!!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 'Dances With Wolves', Lieutenant Dunbar writes in his journal that everything he had learned about Indians was wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, I believed that too once upon a time.  But I know who I'm dealing with now.  A bunch of crazies!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late one afternoon, we were in the first house alone after everyone else had gone somewhere.  All we did was sat out on the deck for awhile.  Then, when we saw the moon, you brought the telescope outside and showed me how to use it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black people have always been the saving grace that White people stumbled over.  That so many still don't recognize this centuries later is astonishing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ya' know...  When Jim Jordan and Alan Dershowitz and those other seditionists were defending that traitor from impeachment so passionately while we all knew they were lying, I DEFINITELY felt better than THOSE folks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It would absolutely kill them to say something like:  We've had six or seven millennia of white men on the court.  So, it's about time to vote for a black female nominee for the position.  OR:  I applaud President Biden for keeping to his campaign promise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obviously, there's SOMETHING about conservatism that turns people into total dumbasses!!!  At this point, all the evidence seems undeniable!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So...  Critical Race Theory is a punishable crime now.  Just like abortion in Texas.  These people are not normal.  They're depraved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not while the majority seem like de facto white supremacists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And just as especially, over the course of a year after an insurrection at the Capitol they incited and are trying to memory hole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What so many propose sounds like saying sex with blonde women is permissible, but sex with brunettes is a sin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They don't have any medical degrees.  They don't like or understand science.  He has and does.  But they just know he's wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanted to crawl all over Boyfriend!  ALL THE TIME!!!  But I always backed off to give him some space and make sure he was in control of what happened.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, maybe he got bored.  But that wouldn't be enough to stop him from saying so.  And he seems to still be following me all over the Internet, no matter what I do or when I forget my medication.  So, the only thing that makes sense is GUILT!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure would be cool if he really was wanted by the FBI.  I'd have something to hold over his head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still think they're secretly trying to find heaven.  But no one will ever admit that openly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the guy they used to expect me to keep in line and tell when to go to sleep at night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In college, I ended up on probation for the remainder of the year because three young white guys stole a P.A. system and hid it under my bed.  I've been constantly dealing with the consequences of befriending that family of white people ever since.  So...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether I did anything wrong or not, that guy made me very happy.  I adored him.  And he's also the most dangerous man who ever comes to mind when it's about sex.  Everybody should get that.  It's not complicated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geez!  They look just like the White guys in my dorm who cut up sheets and pillowcases to make Ku Klux Klan uniforms for my initiation.  It was intended as a joke.  But the school newspaper published an article and picture.  They looked just like that image.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YOU???  Afraid of ME?!?!?  LOL!!!  Yeah, right.  I fell for that one right away.  (Not!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm still waiting for major networks to figure out the "both sides" argument doesn't hold water so they'll stop putting people like Chris Christie and Meghan McCain on television and radio shows.  It's why were this deep in this mess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So's the psycho who lives upstairs.  In fact, if I get up three times a night to take a piss, he gets up too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had the money, I'd make sure he takes the Production Assistant class first.  And then, the media production class.  But I can only help him with one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But clearly, Republicans are responsible.  And I just know I'm better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As long as they all know I care and why I care, that's all that matters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until you tell me the whole story, this is how I remember everything.  I got no choice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, my real life has been so bizarre at times that I don't need to make up the details!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop whatever you're doing right now and take a look at the size of your hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Several social media accounts ago, when Trump was still campaigning for office, he said that people were underestimating the number of folks that would vote for him.  Something in his wording tipped me off to which people he was talking about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What makes me happy right now are all the commercials that are normalizing gay and lesbian and interracial couples across the spectrum.  Seems to me a mission the modern church should have espoused long time ago or we wouldn't be in such dire circumstances.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're sometimes able to MIMICK learning.  But they don't really learn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They've seen that we can lead the most powerful nation in the world. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From my perspective, his hiding suggests either he was involved, or he's trying to protect his father.  Which he's always done one way or other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I walked inside, there was a male receptionist.  He sounded Italian.  White guy with big black curls in his hair.  I told him my situation and he started calling around town trying to find me a deprogrammer.  He said they would pay for me a ticket back to Atlanta.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They know I care about your future.  I'm sure THAT wasn't in the plans!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one else will even know.  Whatever punishment I come up with will be something he has to do when it's just the two of us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They have no discipline.  And apparently, no integrity.  I'm struggling to be a better person.  I need better people around me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They don't recognize evil operating in our school boards and the banning of books.  Nor do they recognize evil happening in white nationalist churches.  Evil only seems to register with most Americans once they've been scammed out of something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After he stopped coming over, I wanted to follow him around, call him, and drag him back into the picture.  But I told myself that was HIS life and HIS decision to make.  Just like I always do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I pass road signs that say 55mph, I expect whoever's driving to be somewhere within 20mph of that speed limit.  They never are!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There was damage done by so many dismissing Colin Kaepernick and the BLM protests that were joined by millions of people of different races all over the globe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know.  It's scripted.  But it's still hard to swallow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans scream more about protecting refugees from Afghanistan and protecting Ukraine than they ever screamed about protecting Americans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, I've been saying that a long time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything's cool, though.  I don't get their jokes either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guy upstairs also has eyes.  And he's gone out of his way to let me know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll wait until nobody's around, just like he did.  And then, IT'S ON!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is SO EASY to blame God for all our fucked up behavior.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They look at me like I showed up to take their Engineering degree back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the part no one speaks about Vikings.  And just barely about Native American Indians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When his girlfriend asked me if we could go somewhere and talk, I cranked up the car and she got in fighting back tears.  I thought she was going to tell me he left her for some other woman.  Or he hit her.  Or SOMETHING!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I just knew what he's dealing with that's forcing him to hide, I'd probably understand what to say and what not to say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[admirers like myself.  Pretty sure that dynamic helps sell movies.  Worship is worship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They were taught that we're supposed to be inferior.  That's not exactly panning out to be true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold on.  Let me make some popcorn before I try to figure out which one will win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He sat on top of my chest in his underwear playing Typewriter at least a dozen times.  I'm surprised I didn't get dick slapped BY ACCIDENT!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's AMAAAAAAAAAAAAAAZZZZING how much Republicans care about "fairness" when it falls to Democrats to select any candidate who couldn't care LESS about fairness when it's their turn in power!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be mad tomorrow.  I promise!!!  (halo)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There AREN'T any 6'7" white guys around here!  I've checked for years!  So, he'll stand out like a sore thumb if he shows up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And those were the white guys who stripped down a black man's pants to see his dick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know EXACTLY what he wants done to his nuts.  And WHY?!?!  BECAUSE HE TOLD ME!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ya' know...  Once they voted unanimously (along with two morons of our very own) against equal voting rights, that killed any chance of me playing the "both sides are guilty of the same thing" game.  No more sympathy for the supremacists, seditionists or insurrectionists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once upon a time, you braced your feet against the inside frame of my car bumper, wrapped both arms around my CV joint, and bent it enough to get it back on the car!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wasn't going to even mention anything about this hour.  But that was egregious enough to set off a hate bomb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone else assumes the jokes are intended racially.  But because he's Alpha, and I understand how it affects him, those jokes are SEXUAL in nature.  Not racial.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably won't find any cave drawings of them wearing face masks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which I never imagined would be this hard for someone whose haircut is that close to the clouds!  But I keep reminding myself, he thinks I can turn him into a frog.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being deeply rooted in Confederate fantasy, mythos and ideology makes no difference.  Men are men are MEN!  They all want to be desired, adored and worshiped for their looks, prowess and/or physique.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[any sounds sitting right at the piano myself.  For some reason, this morning, he didn't stomp on the floor right over my head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think you're LOOKING for an excuse to be mad.  But you're still horny as hell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would have stayed in the house alone bored shitless about 500 times, except for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would happen in his mind today if I unexpectedly backed him up against the kitchen cabinets and pressed my body against his to say, "I would, but you couldn't take it all"???  Could he handle me doing to him what he did to me???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You wanna watch a brotha snap and put your life in danger???  Invite me to church.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the gif someone just sent me of some guy getting pounded mercilessly by some Alpha guy on top of him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which turned real interesting the moment I got to college and white guys told me I was only there to steal their white women.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well...  Married folks and people into livestock medications.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd be like, "SEE, I TOLD YOU HE DIDN'T MISS ME!!!  THAT ASSHOLE!!!"  (Sniff!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, yeah?!?!  Well, my REM must be doing double-duty, since I have a pretty dangerous predator in my dreams!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[later after resting.  For weeks after that, Scientologists kept calling my house trying to get me to come back.  I kept telling them to stop calling my home, but they kept at it.  Until I snapped one day and cursed them out over the phone.  I threatened to kill them if any ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, I went with him one weekend.  His stepmom was really gracious.  Kinda glamorous too.  His dad was decidedly cool to me, but polite.  Once we made it back to campus alive, I figured everything went well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, they seemed sane.  But I'm waiting for the other shoe to drop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everybody's pay a lot of attention to mental health issues on tv these days who don't seem to realize that does NOT look healthy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe if I included a card that reads:  You're the shit!  Welcome to the neighborhood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm trying not to leap to conclusions (other than to give him a hard time) but I think I know him pretty well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conservatives always presume to be better than liberals and radical lefties.  Liberals are likely starting to believe we're better than conservatives after January 6th.  But not inherently.  Only because conservatives keep doing and saying SUCH STUPID THINGS and believing in SUCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow!  Susan Collins is SOOOOOOOOO full of shit!!!  How can she smile into the camera telling such LIES?!?!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's working very hard to be here without getting caught.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also...  Considering the fact that I'M not TELEPATHIC, I don't see any other way to find out how he feels about it until he talks to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes my heart used to skip a beat just because of the way he looked at me and I wondered:  What the hell is he thinking??!?!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's no wonder the country is divided and getting further and further apart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I figure, since he didn't contact me, he had moved on and didn't need a gay guy in his life anymore.  Then, I found out he was stalking me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the way, my brief stint with the Scientologists was way back in the early 70's before people knew how crazy they are.  Back then, the commercials I kept seeing on television were calling it Dianetics.  Sounded harmless enough at the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, I had read those things already.  Which is one reason it flies all over me when preachers obsess over scapegoating homosexuals as the cause of worsening hurricanes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm also hoping to demonstrate how men see themselves as sexually attractive and are just as obsessed with being seen, adored, worshiped and desired as any gay guys are at providing all those things to them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But...  I guess you've got to be an old gay black dude to see it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I sat here for 30 years wondering which one of them killed themselves BY ACCIDENT either on the road or on the lake every time I hear a news report.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I suspect he's still a big kid at heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can't even show up to have one conversation to explain how you feel and then leave forever, why are you expecting ME to take anything you think, feel or say seriously????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ummm...  Doesn't that kinda sorta suggest you may have screwed up somewhere along the way????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fortunately, the holy man said, "Wait!  I think he's trying to tell us something."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then, after I'm several yards away, they look back to make sure they're safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, there were a few dark spots in the crowd.  EXTREMELY few!  But, this is an insurrection of white people who don't want to share anything with ethnic or racial minorities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which is hard to tailor, since you won't tell me what things you laughed at and what things hurt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[people thinking were involved!  And unless I misinterpreted things my landlord said and our boss on the job said, he was telling people we were involved HIMSELF!!!  Even though I didn't know that at all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You had pretty much anything you wanted from me anyway!  So, none of this stalking makes any sense.  Unless you were talked into taking the dumb as hell route by someone else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And...  I had to replace messing with werewolves with something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, so I'm kidding.  But the main point is, if you're not looking for a friend or a wrestling partner or a fuck buddy, all ya' gotta do is stop following me around online.  Especially, when I'm downloading porn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ummm...  I've seen two Republicans on tv this morning who didn't seem rabid and weren't wearing fur and horns.  I'm not sure what to make of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the very least, he could tell me what went wrong and then RUN!  I seriously doubt I could catch him.  But he's AFRAID of something!  Other than glass elevators, the only thing that ever does that is guilt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last thing anybody's going to accuse ME of is ABANDINING a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to feel guilty as hell if I said anything to you that sounded a little bit flirty.  You're old enough that I can say whatever I feel now.  So, all that stuff I couldn't say before comes flooding out the instant I'm having FUN online!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The white people who are just fine have more to fear from the white people who are panicking than they have to fear from black people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Americans cannot and should not hide from these atrocities just as we refuse to allow German Nazis to hide from what was done to German Jews and Homosexuals during the Holocaust.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some white people may not understand that language, though.  So, next time, I'm buying a cake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate feeling like you have that kind of power.  So, it would be much easier on both of us for you to break that link somehow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Especially, when evil shows up on Sunday mornings dressed in suits and ties looking for converts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soon as I saw this ad it reminded me of the contraption Scientologists hooked me up to while asking a battery of questions, including the names and addresses of any member of my family (cousins, aunts and uncles included) who are gay and might be enemies of the church. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG, I hope I don't make him paranoid about it the way some other actor seemed and started posting stories everywhere with pictures of his wife.  I know Hemsworth is straight and married with kids.  But, like Chris Evans, he seems VERY WELL AWARE he has more than a few male]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe had they not raised up a clone army of rabid, cannibalistic, extremist constituents, they could answer questions more truthfully.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're working their way around to Hitler Youth, I'm tellin' ya'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But what's truly amazing is, in spite of copious reporting on how red states are suffering the most hospitalizations and deaths because of Conservative conspiracy theories and misinformation, THEY STILL LISTEN TO FOX NEWS!!!  And they haven't changed their behavior!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know that Indian at the end of Dances With Wolves shouting at his friend from the top of the mountain because he didn't want the white guy to leave?  That's me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obviously, the frog spell must've worked!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So...  ummm...  You're here 24/7, every time I show up, huh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They never learn.  They never evolve.  They never get better.  Seemingly, those who were born with compassion and understanding can go either way.  But those born without it never, ever get better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It took several days with them in New York before realizing they had no intention of flying me back to Atlanta.  In fact, they were trying to talk me onto a plane to London, which is where they claimed their "Music Division" is located.  Twice, they had two security guards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But...  You look kinda cute that way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While his partner in crime is running around without handcuffs campaigning for another robbery?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One more quick memory and I'll stop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust me.  If Jews can put lasers in space, so can homosexuals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They never learn.  They never evolve.  They never get better.  Not in this lifetime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one seems to be accounting for the fact that at least two or more individuals on each panel have been a racial minority their entire life.  They probably spent most of their career covering minority issues as well.  And yet, on the other side of the desk always sits some white]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, now...  You expect me to wipe all those movies out of my memory and all the reasons I ended up seeing them???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, it's obvious we're stuck there because I sound like a narcissist on Twitter.  LOL!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't mind if he's your hero.  I just want you to know who you are too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was pretty simple and straight forward!  It's hard to imagine there are millions of people protesting and assaulting little kids on their way to school over stuff like this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then, you turn on the morning news to see folks laughing their hardy asses of like they just finished smoking something and came to a 'Don't Worry Be Happy' party.  It's kinda hard to feel along the ground to find out where the sanity markers are.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>