<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# African kids develop speach and learn to walk early but after they start eating (mainly carb diet)  plus other environmental  factors they lag behind East Asians whose main diet is flesh and a little grain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the end of this scamdemic GOK will lose billions in settlement
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lamu is beyond salvage through diplomacy.  Mujahedeen have inflitrated local mosques,schools and social life of natives. Islam offers them sanctuary against the "oppressor" which is the government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A link to this study and if its true we are getting recommendations from a group with diminishing cognitive abilities. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# All those problems are political. Infact 90% of these problems can be solved if MPs did their job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How you interpreted that messge is up to you. There is a reason why we fight male feminists because dee inside we know they are closet abusers and we have proved it multiple times here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The Hamitic theory is based Jewish mythology which is the first red flag. Anyway between Tigray and Amhara which ones are from Arabian peninsula? There was an important of sabaens Axumites]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am seeing Kisa and Banyore dudes in that party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A balance must be created between good and evil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another reason why Judaism should not be introduced to black communities. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Everything is paid just like South Sudanese refugees here who live in expensive apartments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Over 60% of slave owners were white females. We usually blame black men for mistakes made by their women.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She is bleeding from the mouth but no signs of physical injuries. Anyway black boys must learn to date within their groups]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# From 2012 Nairobi Nightlife iliisha kabisa. All I am seeing is more stalls and Somali coffee shops. Hata kupata live band Nairobi ni shida. Anyone born and bred in this city knows its not what it used to be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bantus from the South still don't get it, we are already struggling with Judaism and now they have introduce Shaolin temples.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# No slave owner  makes murals of him worshipping the slave or statues to immortalize the slave. Infact no Nubian can claim he doesn't have Junubi blood in his veins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I see you don't understand why Kibaki preferred Bukusus over Maragoli.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You literally add no value to his course. I saw Kibaki groom Uhuru from 2007 and laid out framework to help him succeed him but somehow you still think you meet the threshold to overcome an incumbent presidents wish?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Wtf is 'cis gender'? We just want binary gender, anything in between and should be treated as a flaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Male feminists don't learn. Ukiona ngeus amereport twitter first na hadai kwenda stenje jua tu hio stori ya abuse or assault ni vako.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Then stop flirting with the idea that liberalism is permitted in islam. What I am seeing here is guys bearing Arabic and Hebrew names claiming to be muslims or christians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ ANC needs a strategic leader not this jokers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Arabs don't care about SSA. To them we are an inferior race]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If you are not a thief even in poverty or riches you won't steal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[False, even a male lion in its prime can't challenge a nile crocodile in its territory. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I see failure by the government and innovation by the citizens but still nothing to smile about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It only our military that does not do research on how to create new weapons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Have you seen any of my people working as guards or drivers for Muhindis?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Archeology, linguistics must go hand in hand with genetics.  Eurasian  gene flow in Africa came in through the east and North African Coast. What we call cushite today is a Creation of the Hamitic theory and has nothing to do with the ancient cushite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The pics you shared are of two sisters not one person but I wouldn't mind dating either and rub it off your face and if possible upgrade to something better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# As long as there are no exchange of women between tye two groups, I dont see any meaningful outcome from this plus Nilotes already enjoy good real-estate in shared territories shared with Bantu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like ghost. Either a fellow motorist robbed by thugs ot thugs posing as ghosts so that they can rob you if make a dick move behind the wheel. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Domestic tourism accounts for over 60% of revenues from that sector. I don't who advices GOK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You just proved my point. We heterosexual men are hated by everybody. From government, NGO, LGBT and male feminists. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# These are the people who are trying to implement vaccine passports]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's not the case. Infact it opens up doors for predation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The horn depends on Bantu EA for survival.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If you are a wokie keep off my lane, infact block me as early as you can. You are triggered about Brits/Portuguese and not Arab/Muslim crusaders?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Killing a fully grown adult human is not an easy task for a leopard. Very few deaths have been recorded from a leopard's encounter with humans but the injuries inflicted may be permanent or take time to heal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't have one except I take beer at 4pm everyday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Maragoli have always maintained they are not Luhyas starting with the late Hon Otiende]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Remind again on why they had to rig 2013 and 2017 elections? Mouny Kenya is only good as a swing vote not the main vote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Brother Obama and Clinton are known male feminists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I saw reparations mentioned in some of those tweets and it reminded me of a Tunisian girl who is a friend to #USER# was using the AA identity to get access to the welfare monies
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ what DNA. It is easy to lie when you are living in America. I am closer to Somalis than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kula your dose of steel wool mzee. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Muite was torn between supporting Odinga his party and Matiba. Ilifika mahali he decided to concentrate ok himself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's what the Qur'an says not unless you want to argue like an islamic scholar which you are not and neither is your explanation valid on based on any islamic text.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Look at Nandi + Luo how they all lost to Brits. Nandi had tye advantage of the highland terrain and Luos had huge numbers experienced with lowlands combat. Instead of working together they both aligned with Brits to fight each other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either you were not born or you have deliberately decided to be stupid. Anything YK92 was law unto themselves. Our fathers were terrorized, mugged and robbed by members of that group. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Nikipata job westlands, Mwimuto would be my most prefered residence as compared to over prized and crowded Kangemi with low quality houses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Patchy wants a Banyarwanda but he is settling on a Baganda to keep his hopes alive ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You have one the most complex voting pattern. There are no favourites in Maragoli politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's being a pussy. Do your thing on the pitch and go home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We all want power decentralized but these people at the ministry of education want to concentrate power at certain offices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not all of them support him. Remember not all workers needs saving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is more an African phenomen, where governments are obsessed with mega projects while completely ignoring the wellbeing of their citizens. RSA,KE, Ethiopia, Ghana and Nigeria.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nigr I am not interested in your BS. I clarified why the burrial happened within 24 hours but nikama uko na maneno ingine. Senji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Onsi is going for a booty call not historical expedition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a lot they avoid talking about so that the focus remains on jews. Did you know they killed almost all biracial people and castrated or sterized blacks? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# From previous cases, majority of self declared male feminists on KOT turned out to be abusers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We are already have one outlaw and his name is Kimuzi, who the fck are you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Maybe Moyale and partly Marsabit which have extremely low population.  People follow money not empty sands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You just confirmed I don't switch sides but there is zero evidence am a liar. I will call out any male feminists on my TL regardless of who they are. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am not looking at the moral angle of it. Armies must be constantly supplied with soldiers and going recruiting children means active adult population is low or weak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Teachings of Christ are not good for the black man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# We have beautiful dark skinned women and that one is not one of them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mandas na githeri asubuhi is enough proof you need a woman ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Diet plus admixture with hunter and gatherers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You said my senator is not one of us. Atwoli just confirmed it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The South is inclined to African religions than Christianity. Christianity is more of an East African and a few west African Nations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The government was brutal with SLDF and its sympathizers but somehow linient on zoos. Do you think if it was Moi, we would still have the nonsense going in NFD? The same approach used against SLDF should be adopted in NFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Zii, iko baniani huclaim half of eastlands ni yake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ADOS are more poor than they were back then. The women and rainbow movements were used to infiltrate their inner circle. Now there are more fatherless kids and uncontrollable single mothers and irresponsible men.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Hata hapa home watu wa IEBC wako idle kids are not interested in voting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most Pro  rainbow men huwa closet male feminists #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# another case of east Asian gene dominating the negro. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Last time NASA went to court to change that, someone made a ruling at midnight while on holiday. You guess is as good as mine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ðŸ™„ uko serious? Would the Arabs do the same if the river was in their territory?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# On this case between Atuoli and the 3 traveling friends, it is not that easy. There is a confession by COTU SG but the victims can't press charges for fear of confirming what he said is true regardless if its valid or not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# What were you saying here? Have you ever heard of poaching skills?
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Males naturally wants to procreate with healthy females in their prime though there is a cap to it. No males have sex with females who haven't reached sexual maturity. Pedophiles defys this rule]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My experience was worse. I looked different from my classmates and close friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# He was against converting agricultural land to residential/commercial buildings. The single mothers nonsense against him was coined by the same people who were against his policy on land]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# For hundreds of years, we have always made sure undesired traits are not passed down to new generation.  Explain why I should accept a flawed kid in my bloodline?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# KE universities should be scared with their exorbitant fees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If the PCR test couldn't differentiate the common flu and other respiratory viral infections from COVID-19, how accurate is your source of data? Did NHS or CDC inflate their figures?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Anything feminist kwa hizi streets ni bitter frauds ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ including male feminists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They are trying to hold anything that can keep the sheeple under control but its not working]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I doubt. Most of these monies ni watu wa writing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Kuffar should be killed on sight. What's preventing that from happening is the secular state and low numbers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Family, clan,tribe, ethnicity/race, nation, region in that order.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You always waiting to strike Bantus on trivial stuff but when one digs deeper you brand them "hotep"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Somalia would colonize you in the 1st 3months of independence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Thats archaic approach. Play music from your phone,laptop, desktop PC or TV. Do you carry your game console outdoors?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Samburu women rep aspirant "the queen of the North"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Han are invading our territory with ugly babies ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why do you always mention an Arab in African business?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Those parcels of land should be reclaimed. Same thing happened to railway land in parklands (ojijo road)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# They despise these characters. #USER# touched lightly on this  but his focus was on east Asia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If Kenyans can consume maize laced with afflotoxins without demonstrating, dont expect much from them if you follow CCP's approach. Anyway it worked against mungiki who had better network and well organized that al Kebab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I thought my statement was self explanatory. Our people got my State jobs only through RAO and Moses Mudamba. Any other person claiming he has the interest of our people at heart is a fraud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My sister don't out your hopes high on that man and his drug. He is the second person in our country to create covid-19 drug. Our government won't appreciate or acknowledge his work. Madagascar tried and their president got a warning shot through a failed coup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# We are already defaulting on our loans. What happens when the government can render any of its services and citizens in the informal sector of the economy have refused to pay taxes or closed their businesses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Infact RAO should oay more attention to Ukambani,Maasailand and Coast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# If Kalonzo jumps ship, RAO will have to go for the mountain or step down in favour of someone else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is Kibaki a joke? You serious think Uhuru made himself the president? Kibaki laid ground for uhuru to take over from him right from January 2008 to August 8 2013. Follow major appointments from 2008 in security and judiciary and even cabinet ministers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think your in US where this data is publicly available through National health system/service main website. Kindly start from there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good luck with your Kagwe. For now we are Following KEMRI. Kagwe is just a policy maker not scientist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I support him hata kama his chances ziko chini. I hope ODM will field candidates across central. We cant missout one or two seats hata kama ni MCA that's progress in the right direction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Amerix huwambia kila siku, most male feminists ni closet abusers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Daktari from Idakho is keenly following Malala and when the right comes he will go for his jugular. Its too early to start making enemies when your boss can switch sides anytime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Onsi is a certified coon. If you want unbiased discussion as long as Bantus are not involved listen to #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ typical zoo but we both know your place either in the past or present]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# If it was a North African or Somali Murtad, you would have made an excuse for them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why to yo the West instead of their immediate neighbors Ethiopia or Yemen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We must be realistic with our demands to the government. We want an upgrade from those Diesel locomotives to fully functional electric rail system without changing much on the existing infrastructure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because no one has challenged it in court when the constitution is clear we are a secular state and no one should be discriminated based on their religious beliefs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Claiming anything related to you is an insult to my bloodline. How can a genetically superior being want anything to do with a vermin from the desert.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There are many westerners in Kiambu and Murang'a. Some are 3rd or 4th generation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You see how it quickly turned into an ethnic war. Zoo were trying to access Arabs space and got reminded their place. Do you think Bantus can do that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Huwa mnalipa spotify premium while we get it for free?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The Hamitic theory had to many questions than answers. There are two East african communities that holds the Hamitic theory close to their heart because it gives them legitimacy to power]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Asome katiba ya chama. If he is not the party leader that's null and void, atafute kiti ingine kwa chama ama akuje kwenyu mumpatie the top seat for the same amount]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ assimilating Gikuyu is next to impossible. We have tried countless time without success. I think bordering smaller communities is kinda advantageous to them. It shields them from invasion or assimilation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reintroduce mandatory NYC for everyone after high school #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# People rape because they want to. Their haven't tamed their wild side. It has nothing to do with dominance or availability of sex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Second option has better outcome only if its not countered by a similar unorthodox move]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# In your dreams. You are tweeting from Eastleigh because you trust KDF more than SNA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's why Arabs in the North want to redirect it northwards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You pulled that from feminazi book 2. If you disagree with someone you don't report their account, just say whatever you have to say to them directly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ No am just concerned on the faces I am seeing on that young party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah but it is not the same as Baganda. Kabaka utilised his position in the colonial government to suppress Luos. Banyarwanda were just caught strays maybe for association with Buganda Kingdom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# By 1400 CE Portuguese were just traders and didn't have any power to colonize any African state. Their main trading partner was Kongo Kingdom. Even their ranking in Swahili city states was lower than half breeds and Arabs. You want to make raid to their caravans by bandits a war?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How? You better give MaDVD something worth the risk or we will cook him without mercy if he doesn't bring the trophy home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Usilete daddy issues kwa viti serious. If your parents didn't want you at that age don't discredit other people's experience. At 9 years tulikuwa tuna chunga ng'ombe. Who the fck dumps their children in a boarding school at 9 years? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But we have. An oversupply of waru from RV and parts of Western Kenya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# claimed that their boy scout unit stood a chance against our men in uniform]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Tito Okello day should be celebrated each year in Zanzibar #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ðŸ¤ plus the people there are cultured, in Nairobi everything and everyone wants to rob you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# On very rare occasions would a leopard try to kill a human or any member of the ape family. Remember an injured "predator" is as good as dead predator.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# To fight evil you one evil by your side - Klaus Mikaelson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Explain why people with more Eurasian component would draw murals of them looking like Junubi and make a clear distinction between them and lighter people in those murals?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I did try doing that in 2010 with my best friend and we closed shop in less than 6months.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Khamisi has a chapter on this. Read the Book of Jomo Kenyatta from Looters and grabbers. James Mwangi was part of the youth Jomo was preparing to take over Banking, insurance and all other business run by Whites and Indians. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# If she was a little bit darker she would3 have scored an 8 for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I just made a comparison but it seems it hurts if we put you on one side of the equation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not every government can afford to play along. If you push too hard, you risk starting a war]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The discussion is moving away from vaccines. It is risky health wise and economically unsustainable. If we couldn't manage the pandemic itself imagine how it will be when the pandemic of the vaccinated starts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Pete is a good program with good actors but little was invested in researching how a Swahili medieval island state would have looked like with a little bit of modernity in it.  From accent, cuisine, dressing and architecture and animation Pete would have achieved more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Expect vaccine dropouts after every booster shot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Even Chinese label all black Africans as Bantus ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That description doesn't suit them. Their problems are self inflicted and neither do they own any tech alien to us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# From 2019 up-to-date, have there been an increasein number of deaths in any country outside the normal range? In Kenya we had less deaths in the last 2 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# People must battle it out as men. We will follow the winner. No one created RAO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That's why I used "most" and not "all".  I have of stories from Buganda but I have no evidence if it's true because all Baganda affiliate tribes don't practice it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The resistance is growing and people are switching teams so are media houses.  Prepare for something else this "pandemic" is done and dusted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Many Gusii who got scholarship to study in india between 70s and late 80s never came back. They all settled with Hindu women. Marrying a Nywele Ngumu doesn't affect social ranking of an individual]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lawyers, politicians and activists cannot talk about corruption in 254]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A couple of drones can sought this nonsense for good. If possible relocate the resulting communities to NFD and let two problems take care of themselves #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Black and white share a common history dating back 400 years. Regardless of their nasty past encounters black people should never side with East Asians in fighting white people because there is nothing to gain at the end of it for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# the race to replace RAO has begun. It seems Bukusus have  an upper hand followed by marama. Gusii and Luo are still yet to settle on anyone. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In 10 years time, we will colonize either UG ama Nandi county]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ukinipa kazi, sit back and relax and let me do my job, kama kuna kitu hupendi say it to me maturely and I will make changes as per your wishes lakini usilete dharau juu umenipa kazi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Major airlines in Africa are all making loses. Even Dubai based Emirates is struggling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I don't there is any Nilotic group foolish enough to submit to horners. Look at how they hype Maasai and Dinka and even try to draw in existence similarities in their struggles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ODM has a party constitution, it's either Wanjigi didn't read it or he is intentionally being petty. The PL is the sole Presidential candidate in the party. Mudavadi was also there and that claus locked him out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Kuna pandemic ya catfish across African continent.  KE and SA leads the pack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They sound like vampires from Elijah Mikaelson bloodline.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I was just having problems installing Zorin on my computer using bootable usb stick and the process was kinda frustrating. Took me 6 hours to finally do it right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I love this assumptions you ate making if Qassim has 1/4 of Mount Kenya that is better than ðŸ’¯ of NEP. You also acknowledged WSR has no grip3 in the capital which cancels the remaining 3/4 of mount Kenya. We can go on with the list if you have time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Kindly research where the name sulwe originates from.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Replace quality with IQ. Anyway I am referring to IG models and men running catfish accounts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We are born wild. Some self domesticate successfully while others succeed up to certain levels.  The urge for sex is natural for men and women alike and brutality is part of it. Difference between rapists and non rapists is how we respond to the natural call to procreate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am Egyptian or rather a North African runs this account. Any fellow black man who still thinks that fraud didn't deserve clipping needs to get his head checked. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This nonsense ends if we reciprocate BS with BS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You keep dropping excerpts without links to their sources. Portuguese in Africa prior 1800 were simply traders and nothing more than that. Them dominating sea trading routes from 1400 doesn't make them superpowers.  I see they have been teaching you history according to Americans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Patients have been dying even when we hadn't seperated from other apes. If you read any data before influencing you would have noticed that Kenya recorded less deaths last years as compared to 2019. What deaths are you speaking about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Also note Bantus from West Kenya are significantly taller and mascular than those in the East due to genetic admixture with nilotes and availability of protein such as beef, mutton, fish, termites and locusts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Destructure GOK and you will get the who exactly wanted BBI and Huduma numba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2% of us Kenyans are vaccinated. Majority of us have no intentions of getting vaccinated and we have less deaths or hospitalization than your country. We rarely wear masks or follow any WHO guidelines on Covid-19. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# said something about children of politicians vocal on social media]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Misss KU 2010 wa beautiful than this and she was a Kale. By then I was a trophy hunter but I was into easy prey(Bantu)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Most elements of Christianity are of Greek or Roman origin. Its just the Gods that are borrowed but the core is eurocentric]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To all designers who post your work on Pinterest, thank you very much for helping us the back-end guys  navigating  murky frontend to access sleek designs for free. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Look at the ranking of the captured half breed. Skin tone, ethnicity and affluence comes first before islam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why not enrol here to a public school? Something not right about this appeal for help #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The article focuses on educating girl child in relation to Infant mortality rate and it doesn't touch anything on educating the boy. How did you arrive at that conclusion that educating/empowering a woman has more positive impact to community than a man?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The same is true with Somali in diaspora, majority are used to chaos at home and the same is also true in their host countries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# and #USER# Aldai constituency should be a contest between us. Don't let UDA capture that seat #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I saw both Mahindra and Land Rover, then came land cruiser, grand tiger and now Ford ranger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It usually don't end well for male feminists. Learn to address people as individuals #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One major challenge is how, the app will generate revenues for its creators and what problem are you actually solving if the tenants and the landlords dont trust technology]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Same problem they have with Kalenjin and Maasai.  Adding another community to the Island kinda equalizes this but only after resettling natives which will only take 300km2 of land out 6000km2. Lamu should be our Milan but we are handling it carelessly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# We also plan on closing ours so that they can get aid from their countries. South Sudanese refugees will be intergrated into our population. They behave well here and dont bring their differences on our country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hao  nao ni worse kutuliko yet their GDP is twice ours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I have no interest in Nubia or Egypt but at least I can put up a good defense backed by existing evidence. For you need this to boost your self esteem since you are regressing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Our grandparents were business owners in that country and the writer didn't write about them so as to sell the false narrative of lazy natives. During the holocaust they didn't mention blacks and biracial people who lost lives and property. Fck that racist article]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Anyway central doesn't have 4M registered voters. The number is lower.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We dont consume coffee na makorofia has better ROI than coffee. Uproot the damn bushes #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>