<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow #USER# mock Hillary for attacking the media, the same thing they applaud and encourage Trump for doing #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Mike Pence say his vote for Iraq War was a "mistake" last night? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neighbor got a new computer so gave me his old one *(2 years old) and told me I can give him 100$ when I have it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah you're right - African Americans have it great and cry to much but Christians are oppressed #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't have anything nice to say -- you're probably talking about Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update from the kidney specialist and fight to get Roberts pills refilled AGAIN #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow that's brilliant and what percentage of rape in America is Muslims?? I'll be most rape in Canada is by Candians #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# When I stopped caring about others and only started caring about others #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I guess I should just forget about her because it's been a year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope (Fathers dog) had a small seizure a few minutes ago, usually sign of a larger one to come.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect time for Bayley to crash the championship crowning of Charlotte #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sheriff Clarke - is that the Fox News shill always blaming Obama for everything.. Surprised he was on CNN and Don Lemon usually Hannity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[woop there it is, got TV working again 8)-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes I did, never heard of it until your facebook post..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Possible 4 RT 4 my disabled veteran father who lost his wife recently no might lose his home #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family Matters - that's the show with the "Did I Do That" kid, not the drug/rape women father isn't it..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# just tired of it, they're getting to be a disgrace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't want free college but do want the same interest rate that banks and business pay with their loans #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He had them kicked off his street for lowering property values, never gave to them before running for president #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superman finding a new place to change after invention of cell phone #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the #HASHTAG# response to the mentally ill person who shot up Pulse is that they wish more drunk people were armed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's Trump - oops it's just the back side of a police horse #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hornquest has been playing really well, Sid is choking for another year making several in a row]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# not anymore but I am with Gabby Giffords, Christine Leinonen and others who truly know real suffering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Donald Trump's history of hypocrisy on releasing his tax returns #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sounds like Ted Cruz is voting Gary Johnson in November]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP senators continue to collect salaries for not doing their job #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You really love putting women down and treating them horrible don't you - guess it explains the 3 wives #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How are you delivering jobs? Will you give people plane tickets so they can fly to China, Mexico etc. 2 work 4 you #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ran to the bathroom and yelled "are you OK" he said yeah, I hear the Ice Cream Truck outside want to go get me something lol 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like it's back to the hospital with my father - having issue with his disabled leg  #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The melting of Greenland and Antarctica is changing the Earth's rotation #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# he's had a rough couple days, I'm just going along to make him happy right now 8)-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House GOP Knows What’s Worse Than Deformed Zika Virus Babies, And It Is Planned Parenthood | Wonkette #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I let my father have ice cream tonight instead of fruit .. His sugar has been in the 120 in the morning / used to be 175 on old meds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tax Reform Proposals In Approved Draft Of Democratic Platform Are Most Progressive In Modern History #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# oops yes sorry was thinking about this #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's out of town today but dog is sitting on mothers bed looking out window waiting for him wondering where he is...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like crap today 0- don't think I can take another Trump win so #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can listen to #HASHTAG# than throw her parents out of the country #HASHTAG# or #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess Wisconsin wants to start looking like Kansas and Mississippi #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really #HASHTAG# - Maga
A micropenis no bigger than the size of a baby carrot. #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm guessing anyone who would buy George Zimmerman gun isn't mentally fit enough to own one in the first place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has right wing media apologized for reporting a lie as facts? He admitted under oath he lied about hacking #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe they should just fine her like what happened every time #USER# broke the law w/out prison #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when Donald Trump called disabled veteran peddlers and "eye sore" to his luxurious property and wanted them removed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans will earn 24,000.00 during their 7 weak vacation starting Friday or 8,000 more than a person on Min. wage makes a year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Loyal - stuck by her man through hard times -- how many of #USER# wives can say the same thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police Investigating "Execution-Style" Murder of 3 Muslims in Indiana #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've lowered the goal to 4,500 after getting in touch with our mortgage specialist.  It's... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Mississippi are you going to turn away Bristol Palin (Unwed mother), Donald Trump (adulterer) or is it just bigotry freedom?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# &lt; now that's a party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# why do you tell so many horrible people like George Bush and Ted Cruz to run for president]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy sh*t it's hot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How dare Obama appoint people who have military service instead of using their dads money/power to avoid it like republicans #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stand by them with love #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would love EVERY one of these republicans to turn over their emails to see what they shared #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help Robert Streich Stay Home #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# read/heard about one of the "alleged" women Katrina Pierson a while ago looking at ted though "no way"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So #USER# wants blacks arrested for their speech but supported armed rednecks at the Bundy Ranch but he's not racist #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I had a Cruz supporter attack my deceased mother and applaud fact my father was disabled because I spoke against Him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well FINALLY some positive news after a month from hell. Just got back from the Kidney doc... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There are no homeless Veterans - I know this because Bill O'reilly tells me so #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well since you call 10 million in handouts from your daddy a "little" help #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Think positive if Lebron leaves they're getting Donald Trump next month #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Court: No right to carry concealed weapons in public #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out BENCHWARMER VEGAS BABY STACKED DECK SHAY LYN VEASY  ACE AUTOGRAPH 03/21  #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes #USER# our 1916 Air Force was much bigger than it is today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump was sued by the justice department TWICE for refusing to rent to African Americans  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Doesn't matter, Trump will go to court so he doesn't have to pay them anyway #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you also]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Donald Trump #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last night made 1,500 straight w/out a good nights sleep (less than 4 hours) and it was a rough one #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# porn and pork - then when ISIS looks at it they have to kill themselves for not following their religion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure Texas / Christians / Fox would be fine with an even mocking Christianity and Jesus Christ #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now you are FOR a Rigged system? Do you honestly stand for anything #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[your donation to help my father(disabled veteran) can get you this  #USER# auto #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saving Private Ryan from STDs #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christian groups protest people who advertise during a Muslim tv show - bet that will make Fox "News" #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got some more news on my mothers passing (and brothers) #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. #USER# then ban gay people from adopting because you know having no parents is better than 2 of the same sex #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# if you're an illegal building his hotel in D.C. if you don't work for him get out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you have a DM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well its' been a good couple days (knock on wood).. 

Robert is on a new diabetes pill a... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are being Foreclosed #HASHTAG# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just woke up - did I miss anything #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there is a god I'm sure he approves of conservatives passing laws that take from the poor while making the rich richer #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I #HASHTAG# and am scared of the scary black racist American hating Muslim from Kenya being in charge of drones #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[of course #USER# isn't releasing taxes so we can't see he's not nearly as rich as he claims and probably doesn't help veterans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's now harder w/ a longer wait time for a single mother to get an abortion in Florida than a terrorist suspect and AR-15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I LOVE LAWYERS #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what our kitchen table usually looks like (3 glued and one not complete) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# I'm already broken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# tooth? There is no damage to it, comes from grinding in my sleep from stress..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# and they want to block grant education funding to states which would be used for more tax breaks NOT education]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["to worried about restricting womens right then the economy" That is a republicans take on The Muslim Brotherhood in Egypt #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's already lied multiple times so I would say yes he'll lie to us #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet Deadeye Donald &lt;- Just don't bring guns onto his properties because most are #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# to help a veteran #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iowa Democrats wish Hillary was as accomplished as Rand Paul, Ted Cruz or as honest as Jeb Bush #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact that Coal workers think Trump can save their job shows how stupid people are - CAPITALISM is killing coal ..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is #USER# hair orangutan orange or is that his skull showing through the comb over?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Community Nurses - have been caring for parents for over 10 years and getting good at it #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After seeing the #HASHTAG# and how scared and fearful they are I now understand the obsession with guns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let the door hit ya where the good lord split ya #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When #USER# discusses family values -- I can't help but wonder which his 3 families he's talking about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've honestly had enough, wake the *$&amp;% up #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Reagan lived those words being the worst, weakest and most dangerous president in my lifetime we're still paying #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While we voted Hope slept #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm raising money for Robert Streich Needs Your Help . Click to Donate:  #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To those who don't have horrible St. Patrick's day memories have a good day tomorrow - see y'all on Friday #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She’s 86. She can’t get a photo ID. Look at the voter fraud we’ve prevented #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton found not guilty of any crimes by FBI and republican #HASHTAG# panel - has the army assembled yet #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I swear you would think #USER# is married to Ivanka - does he go anywhere without her?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not surprised Donald Trump is the republican nominee in today's Kardashian / Honey Boo Boo / Duck Dynasty America #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends Without Benefits #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shep Smith just used Right Wing Gunman to describe the German Shooter - Ailes isn't even gone one day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course you do, being owned by the #USER# prayers is all they allow you to offer as a solution. Didn't stop shooter #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Bernie Sanders / Supreme Court Justice Elizabeth Warren #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh I knew he didn't die, just commenting on his career or how I see it 8)- He's Adam Sandler with none of the charm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[can you imagaine if Pres. Obama pushed his Muslim beliefs like Santorum does his Christian ones #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stacey Dash Calls Jesse Williams a ‘Hollywood Plantation Slave,’ Says His Powerful BET Speech Was... #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes Dogs are way 2 smart - mine plays with little rubber balls until she tears them apart, I bought 8 and hid 2 under my couch 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#  Christmas Morning - before all you damn liberals started waging a war on it #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW! My Twitter is worth $1,090,103.40 today. Find Out Your Twitter Fantasy Value Free! Click Here ==&gt; #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so sick and depressed w/ the news I'm about to watch a "reality" TV show because I can't take any more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Ryan can't even get congress to work how would he be president, still waiting on a war authority vote against ISIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How about removing the FICA cap that allows rich people to pay a lot lower rate than poor people #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well just got my father home and #HASHTAG# and so did he #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sexual predator Roger Ailes got 40 million for leaving Fox News - here's hoping Gretchen C. sues his ass for 80 million]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chance for #USER# #USER# to help a disabled vet w/ a RT and read #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You cry persecution when it has been christians who have been doing the persecution for 2,000 years #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Updated my profile -- my AVI picture,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm agnostic - I have no problem with the idea of a god it's the corruption of the message and teachers that offend me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes Bolling and brunette Beauty queen reject - Atheists have it easy and christians have such a rough life #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out of options, Kobach backs down, allows voters to be registered #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Possible 4 RT 4 my father a disabled vet who lost his wife (cancer) and son last few months #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Negative - I nicked my father while shaving him / positive - it made him forget about his foot being in pain 8)-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada is full of guns but while America has 11K murders a year Canada has 158 - yes it is the type of gun .. The N.R.A.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure there are a lot of "suicides" in the Souths history similar to the person allegedly hung themselves in Piedmont Park]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. #USER# if we could fire incompetent people from government your brother would have never made it 8 years #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# and #USER# want a wall, drones and armed guards at the Mexico border - meanwhile at the white border #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Other than putting names on his building and being a reality TV star what successful business has #HASHTAG# actually built?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again how do you know? He has not turned anything over -- But than again facts don't matter to you do they #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All Gave Some, Some Gave All, Trump Gave Nothing #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuller House - hopefully they do something fun with Michelle like a cult or prison 8)-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The system is rigged #USER# but sorry most of us have been saying it for years long before you threw your tiny hands in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're against war don't take it out on the people following orders, take it out on those who gave the orders #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes Fox "News" Muslims are horrible horrible people - I'm glad Catholics never killed anyone for religious reasons #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So for 200 years were men playing the #HASHTAG# ? #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Must put family first]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st Question to Kasich - next question coming his way in about 1/2 an hour #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In what reality did a speech last week occur before 2010 #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better wake my father up, don't want him to miss his Bones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rubio is so offended that #HASHTAG# might close he may actually show up to vote for 1st time in months #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP Cleveland organizers beg Adelson for $6 million  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hate to be a pain - only have 10 days left to save my veteran fathers home possible 4 RT #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yes and I still have my father]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are the shirts #USER# should be selling #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to get father ready for bed and unwind myself - thanks again everyone you guys are amazing.. Have a good night #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[F*ck me this  will be my fathers birthday and mothers day -- both the 1st ones without Ruth #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Cruise is getting another divorce, damn I guess gay people do ruin straight marriages and the GOP was right #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This could be the beginning of the end for super PACs ➡️ #USER# #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# good luck.. Think we're through it just a little breezy and cool out..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - I have NEVER seen a "superstar" who plays so bad for long stretches when it matters like Crosby #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are those offended by the American flag burning also offended when people like Sarah Palin sign it with a marker?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Slave-Gate’ Joins Bill O’Reilly and Fox News’s Ugly History of Race-Baiting #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I might believe the tea party wasn't racist if it had existed for the 200 years that white presidents ran up debt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# I took family for granted - now I regret it #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bob Dole endorses Trump? = Why do I care who the Viagra guy is voting for? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irony Alerts - the #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# party has 3 of 4 candidates who had immigrant parent who spoke no English]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bankrupt Job #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun fact - Mike Pence is full of shit, there is a smaller percentage of Indiana's population is working now than in 2000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I accidentally put on the Daily Show -- yup it still sucks with the new guy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And women will be happy to seek Mike Pence expertise on their health issues - here comes #HASHTAG# again #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So how many republicans are hating themselves right now knowing it was Michelle Obamas words they were cheering #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top GOP Benghazi lawyer: 'Nothing' could have prevented American deaths #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes but they want to end that.. Case of I got mine now xxxx you  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh silly Fox - Obama didn't avoid the draft at 12 years old, they didn't allow kenyans to serve in the American Military #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Possible for RT 2 help my father (a disabled veteran) who lost his wife and son now struggling #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It wasn't #HASHTAG# that left the Bundy ranch and walked into a diner shooting 2 police officers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow Bill O'Reilly and #USER# are tearing down the kid because his poem took off and they can't have that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - How this Socialist, communist, racist, far left, Muslim dictator from Kenya became president #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal investigation of Trump-Bondi donation needed, Democratic senator says #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wow saw on CNN the FBI email investigation is almost done and no laws broken -- Fox will be outraged]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haven't slept in 3 days - pretty soon I'll be brain damaged enough to vote for Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Think it would make a good shirt #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't remember #USER# reacting so harsh to Stone Cold and how many domestic abuses did he have #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. #USER# wants less government except your bedroom, vagina, what you can put in your body, how you can spend your money etc. etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[fair and balanced fox has 10 "democrats" who are no republicans - guess no GOP ever switched to Dem or they would be on #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just got back - Did Jeb Bush thank his brother for f*cking up the country so bad no one named Bush could ever win again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# &lt;- it doesn't bother anyone that Putin is aiding and really wants #USER# president, probably even donated $$ to him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you to Capt. Khan and every brave man and women who has ever put on the uniform of this great country #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# hopefully there is another one in November at #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes Carson there is a place in America for faith but not in government just ask the people who founded this country #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that speech really upset #USER# because it was a Trump ass kicking #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How I left  your mother #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd rather kill jobs than people #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox complaining about someone ripping off a military charity but yet still have #USER# on air who is accused of same thing #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes Sir Rudy was a hero - tell that to the 1st responders who died because of shitty equipt. he didn't update #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>