<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, while alternating between quietly sobbing and insulting Baron.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# White is back. I expected Bolden to gone, but I thought JJ would be White’s backup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Losing faith in humanity one idiot at a time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The US doesn’t run a state sponsored doping program.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are #USER# Kevin McCarthy and #USER# members like #USER# obstructing an investigation with threats of reprisals? Seems illegal. And, you know, like they have a lot to hide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is decidedly not a racist appeal. n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# This is an entire conversation based on second-guessing. That's kind of the fun of it, right?

The Patriots have passed on WRs who became game-changers. We know they're not great at spotting WR talent. So they may have screwed up in choosing an injured ILB in the 5th.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# LOL. If you think there's some alternative standard that absolves your abject stupidity, your problem is bigger than I thought.

Wild guess: You're not an epidemiologist, are you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hilarious that fake farmer and complicit Trump toady #USER# is taking a job at the head of Trump's doomed social media experiment that is ALREADY under investigation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Posting that map as if it means anything is an announcement of just how stupid you are. 

People vote, not acres. Trump lost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's great how he went to Wyoming to announce the First Hunger Games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lying is a sin. I don't think going to a church is gonna help you until you choose to change your ways.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Google is a search engine.
Yahoo is a search engine.

Do I really have to explain this?

Yahoo also creates and curates its own content. Google is also involved in other businesses. 

Neither are a public utility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think #USER# is taking the whole "bad publicity is better than no publicity" thing a little too seriously.

Hard to believe that there wasn't an editor willing to tell that piece of shit that his piece was a piece of shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Your mad because private platforms won’t allow people to spread dangerous lies...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We’re a center-left country. Look at the polls on social issues. 

Further, being more “left” would help us. Look at where our friends and Allie’s are surpassing us and the policies that have advanced them. 

Manchin just wants to keep selling coal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes. Inclusion and acceptance are exclusionary and hateful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So.....it's pretty fucking real then? 

Let's see what the people in Texas have to say about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I have more than five times the amount of followers that you do. So...nice self-own there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We had it in 2013. #USER# and the #USER# wouldn't even consider it.

Remember that, John? Republicans fucked things up on purpose. Again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# LOL. Dweeb Bills fans, never having won a Super Bowl, are desperate for a burn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# From the laziest POTUS in history who was born into money. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The irony of this tweet is absolutely galactic in scale.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No Trump has ever done that. Especially not Ivanka Kushner. nn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That was one of the greatest games of all time. They came back from TWO 14 point deficits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It’s great that you’re leaving this Badge of Stupidity up for the world to see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It's funny that people squawk about the lack of a backup plan and then those are the same people who say they should have kept Brady, when reporting tells us that it was Brady that was pissed about drafting both Garapolo and Stidham, who were both the backup plans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Second thoughts? I don't think Manchin has any first thoughts beyond how do I manipulate government to make more money for myself and my kids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# LOL.

Seriously. The Heroes of the Battle of Alpha Centuri must be really mad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Political push?!? Trump incited a murderous insurrection and an assault on our government. He attempted a coup.

You took an oath to defend the Constitution. If you're not going to do it, just STFU and resign.

I'll remind you of your role in this each and every day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# is a loudmouthed #USER# propagandist calling the truth about a loudmouthed egomaniacal racist a "smear".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And then dipshits like you, who licked the boots of the worst POTUS in history, should stop propelling the narrative with bullshit like this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Tampa Bay has beaten precisely ONE playoff-bound team during the regular season -- Green Bay, who absolutely rolled today. They weren't able to overwhelm WFT last week, and they made the playoffs with a losing schedule.

Green Bay or New Orleans make it to the Super Bowl, not TB.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Def looking in the wrong place. There’s no way he got promoted to manager. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The children of racists start learning about racism the instant they’re born.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I was using the dictionary definition, which involves an act of libel, slander, or calumny. All of which involve lying. 

Truth is the ultimate defense to libel/slander accusations in legal matters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How ironic. Your lord and master thinks the Constitutionally protected free press is the enemy of the people.

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# He’s a murderer. He set out to shoot people. He did. They died.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Though infinitely more challenging.

SCOTUS asked Congress to reevaluate the VRA. Then the #USER#-controlled Congress did....nothing.

It's not a hard fix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He sees everything as an opportunity to be a victim. 

All he is is a victim.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# LOL. You have no idea what you're talking about.

The TB D isn't getting their due because Brady is on the team. I'm not taking credit from Brady, I'm giving it to the defense because they deserve it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They’ll be lucky to get 3 against a fired up Bills team that they can’t stop while also missing so many skill players.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# FYI: self-defense is only a valid defense if you didn’t seek out the fight. He clearly sought confrontation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's weird that both backups are better than the starter, and Flacco probably is too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What a weird thing to say when voting rights are the topic at hand. Do you think democracy is some kind of radical idea?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER#:

- Pardoned murderers
- Pardoned his cohorts
- Sabotaged pandemic aid
- Vetoed the NDAA...
- ...which halted raises for our soldiers
- He did that to preserve the names of Confederate generals
- Then he left DC
- Then he went golfing

Merry Christmas, America]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Actually, Senator Liar, the law in question calls for a uniform standard for voter ID, not the willy-nilly approach taken by vote suppressors in Texas that approved of *some* state-issued IDs like gun licenses, but not *others* like college IDs because of demographic bias.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# This is a lame excuse. It completely overlooks the fact that no rational person would have accepted that alleged advice.

Nobody with the reading comprehension of a middle school kid would have ever believed it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #USER#! Can you please bring Flores back to be DC. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm totally shocked that #USER# doesn't understand what NATO is or how it works and would misrepresent it to the American public like a Putin talking point.n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is anybody else tired of the #USER# constantly trying to shut down the govt. when they don't control the White House?

It's just so obvious and childish. 

Republicans haven't been interested in actual governance in my entire lifetime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Let's get you to make a cameo on FBI just so I can say hi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Who messed up, and how?

Do you always talk out of your ass, or only about global pandemics?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# OA is *definitely* playing solitaire on his computer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough break for #USER#. He's not gonna get to make an even bigger ass out of himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A Trump admin official squawking about the trampling of Constitutional norms is the sound of irony dying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aside from wasting time, what's the point of polling the jury?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When voter fraud does happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# 80k+ positive tests in ONE DAY and you think it's all going to be just fine.

This is why you have to resort to stealing shoe designs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Voting rights are more important, but you don’t care about living in a democracy, so…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Starting to think you don't read well. 

I didn't "penalize" Brady. He threw threw INTs and the Bucs D kept Green Bay from doing anything with those INTs.

Is that not true?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# 

It's time to remove this man from office. We can't wait until the 20th.

This man is a danger to our nation and to its people. This is #HASHTAG#. This is #HASHTAG#. This is #HASHTAG#. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Senator Cornyn backs the Trump coup attempt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# LOL. The Zero is threatening to treat people who uphold the Constitution like the Trumps treat a pediatric cancer charity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is what smart people call a non-sequitur.  

But speaking of border security, tell us all why your party killed an immigration reform bill in 2013 that passed the Senate with strong bipartisan r
support that includes massive upgrades to border security?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They handled it in the same way that they (almost) always handle it. They're gonna let the kid test the market. If they can get him back, they'll try. But they probably can't. He'll be way too expensive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No names. And if they’re old enough to work, they’re probably too old for #USER# anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# LOL. Yeah....because you promoting the fantasy that the election was fraudulent had nothing to do with the insurrection. #HASHTAG# nnThis is on you. This is your fault.nnYou should resign. Now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Umm…Decision? He was recorded while actually committing the crime. We all heard it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What a weird thing for #USER#, a man who both supported and promoted Trump's racist policies, to say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wonder if they’ll ever actually hire a D coordinator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is the very pinnacle of #HASHTAG#.nnMaybe you should DO YOUR JOB and PAY ATTENTION]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's a democratic republic. Being pedantic is a tactic used by those who need to dodge the point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You can stop kissing his ass. He lost and now he’s looking at prison time. Your political future doesn’t exist, toady.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# His good friends at Deutsche Bank have known all along that he didn't have the money he claimed to have. They never cared because....?

Because they were involved in money laundering?
Because his "loans" were secured by Russian money?
Because....?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm shocked that Trump, of all people, would want to debate foreign affairs. Our allies no longer trust us because of Trump. Our enemies have been emboldened. He pardoned war criminals and committed war crimes, and he's also committing crimes against humanity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Belichick, like Brady, is the GOAT. Ask around. 

If you can’t handle that, it’s on you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How did this story get past *ANY* news editor without serious scrutiny and changes?

Florida is among the states taking the *LEAST* serious approach to the pandemic.

Seriously #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Did you call me “Gringo”?  LOLoLoL

You’re projecting hard ignorant child vibes. You’ll have to work pretty hard to marginalize yourself more than this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Day 62, and you’re still a mouthpiece for a corrupt, racist liar who incited a murderous insurrection.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Well done. 

I was just researching it myself and as yet hadn't found a request for the declaration, which is required.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah. The judges just keep saying your argument has no merit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She’s a Republican]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Like....separating children from their families]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# And yet you have seen no explanatory coverage anywhere? That’s shocking. Hey, if you want to start informing yourself, Google is free. 

Here’s my me of the studies cited in the MYT article. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He thinks everyone is a greedy, immoral, unethical sociopath, just like him. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Fuck #HASHTAG# McConnell.

And Sinema can piss right off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER#, who paid **some** of his many mistresses to remain silent and then lied about it, says the Christians who don't support him are "bad" Christians.nn#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How can this person still be allowed to practice law? Her only appearances in a court room should involve handcuffs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Are you saying that, for example, Sudekis didn't deserve to win?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Last year they had the most COVID hold outs in the league and had just lost the GOAT QB.

They went 10-8 with a slew of new players and a rookie QB, all while dealing with COVID and losing some key players to injury.

Not too bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Neil Gorsuch is, apparently, a moron who can't discern the difference between a crowd at a church or movie theater and few people in a bike shop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Flynn got caught. And so did you. nn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# should return to the White House ASAP. There are still some top Republicans who haven't been infected yet.nn#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And #USER# would like to move the capital of Texas to Cancun, because....let's be honest, Texas is a shithole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# WTF are you even talking about? You can’t just borrow shit from a museum like renting a DVD at Blockbuster and then chuck it in the back seat to toss in the drop box when you’re done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# fans talking trash about #USER#  crack me up. Jones had a MUCH better rookie season than Allen did. Everybody thought Allen was a bust after his first 2 seasons. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But there's no doubt that Brady is the GOAT. This talk about how this game would decide if he or Rodgers was the GOAT was laughable.

Pats fans had 20 years of ridiculous dominance. All this soap opera nonsense is boring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There's nothing funnier than a Jets fan saying "have faith."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WARNING: The same people who thought Trump jovially tossing rolls of paper towels to desperate Americans in Puerto Rico was a sufficient response to a devastating hurricane are preparing to criticize Biden, no matter what.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think you’re an intellectual tomato can and she’s going to eviscerate you. You’re crazy if you think debating AOC is a good idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How many McRibs did you cram down your lie hole tonight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Congress makes laws, they don't enforce laws.

I'm shocked -- SHOCKED! -- that a conservative firebrand and intellect like #USER# doesn't understand how the Constitution works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She's almost certainly the first member of congress to ignore basic food safety and give a bunch of people food poisoning when they ate food from her restaurant.

Regulations are for suckers, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It is what it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow #USER#! You think the Civil War was about the refusal to accept the election of Lincoln??nnHoly shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And again, self defense isn't a viable defense if you insert yourself into a situation. 

Kyle Rittenhouse did exactly that. On purpose. With a gun and a desire to be a vigilante.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Uh...."Victory" cruise?

LOL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Words have meanings. There have def been better athletes who have been as dominant in their own way. Bill Russell. Serena Williams. Michael Phelps, maybe.

This is a stupid argument to be having.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mike Flynn who hangs out with Putin? That Mike Flynn?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# These reports mean nothing. We’ll know where he landed soon enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crazy question: Why would we make any concessions about our willingness to allow Russia to invade another country?

What kind of mafioso BS is that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You can’t be surprised. Three of these justices accepted a nomination after Garland was denied the Constitutional process for purely partisan motives. If they had any integrity at all they would have insisted that Garland get his due consideration. They politicized the court.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm sure all the Republicans who got arrested for voting twice think it's pretty hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Confession under duress. Your suspect just got acquitted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# LOL. 
1. It is. 
2. He was. 
3. They don’t. 
4. Insurrection against the Constitution is the opposite of unity:
5. Trump lost. 
6. You suck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He warned us about greed and inhumanity and false idols too. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# nnDude. You've failed on "we" and "projection" so far. Does your stupidity come in threes? What's next?nnWhy don't you work something up. I'll be over here eating your lunch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ....of you and your bullshit.

Why won't you say when you spoke to Trump on 1/6? Your phone recorded the time and duration of the calls, Gym. "I don't remember" isn't a valid excuse, insurrectionist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He helped create the GOP cult, as did Boehner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# More jobs.nBetter stock market.nLower credit card debt.nHigher wages.nLower UE.nVery low new jobless claims.nnYeah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Aren't these the same folks who had a journalist murdered and cut up with a bone saw? They're angered by...barbaric actions? nnIt's okay though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Look at the board. There are several players that could work. There were a few sub 4.3 times at the combine. There are players from Alabama.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Are you mad because I said the Jets were among the worst organizations in professional sports? 

Because I think that statement is not really arguable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When #USER# is right, he's right.

Steve "There *IS* such thing as a stupid question" Doocey is an unprofessional hack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's pretty naive to think that once the men with trucks and guns show up to seize control of voting machines and move them to whatever undisclosed locations the legal system would have an opportunity to act -- or to act quickly enough -- to alter that course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't think that's gonna work out for you, buddy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#_Johnson No, it does not. 

I acknowledges that until now, deserving people had been kept from that position based on the mere color of their skin.

And yeah...washing away the racist bullshit should be recognized and celebrated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, #USER#. Not only was Trump given an orderly and complete transition (nobody but #USER# is to blame for his lack of preparedness), he was even given a pandemic playbook.

But, you know, he's incompetent so it was all for nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Remember that time you got caught committing real estate fraud and your dad bought off the prosecutor?

I do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nobody is pushing for war except Putin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Maybe he’s letting #USER# do her job (which her predecessors didn’t) while he does his (because his predecessor didn’t). 

He does have Trump’s disasters to clean up, after all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I don't know anybody else whose goal is to look like a wax figure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They were building a fence, not a wall. And it would never have been competed in your lifetime. And more people who immigrate illegally arrive in airports. Why don’t you care about that? Or the Canadian border? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# SCOTUS***

* Gorsuch, seat held open for 400 days. Lacked the integrity to insist that Garland get his due.

** Kavanaugh, unqualified and ill-tempered and elevated without proper vetting.

*** Coney Barrett, rushed to the bench in the middle of an election breaking precedent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You’re not going to treat them as special]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's weird because if you just read the words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Are you suggesting some kind passport that vaccinated people could have to prove that they're vaccinated and, therefore, don't need a mask?

Interesting concept.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# BREAKING: Asshole announces he'll be wasting the money stupid people have sent him after he first aided three people to death with a gun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah, you fucking with the USPS was beyond the pale. But...you lost anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The same Doug Collins who voted for the select committee on Benghazi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He lost, despite calling into question the integrity of our system since 2016, even as his campaign worked with Russia to get elected.

 If you want to protect the integrity of our system now, you take the loss and participate in a peaceful transition of power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 2006. Hm. Since then an other-than-white person was elected as President. I wonder if that has anything to do with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Okay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It was your father]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because it was all about parity. 

The Patriots should get their 1st round pick back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Trump killed 450,000 Americans. Actual human beings. Are you ready to hold him accountable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why hasn't he been indicted for the crimes that sent Cohen to prison?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Hey #USER#! He's a Republican, right? Well in this day and age that's pretty much a guarantee that he doesn't give a shit about democracy or the Constitution.

You have no excuse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's hilarious how they're all states-rightsy until they aren't and how they're all small-governmenty until they aren't.

We're originalists! Follow the Constitution! Oh, wait....no. See, because...it didn't work out for us.

Count all the votes! Stop the count!

F'ing toddlers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did Billy Carter ever imply that if you bought/drank his beer you could expect any kind of consideration from the federal govt? Not to my knowledge.

Did Jared Kushner's sister? Yes, absolutely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You’re actively covering up a coup attempt that happened less than a year ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah. A movement to prosecute seditious traitors. Lawyer up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# For some reason, they felt perfectly comfortable telling the white cop all the crimes they committed. Weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Blaming the bank for what the bank robbers did seems dumb.

But sure...let's find out why the Trump administration ordered a change in the deployment protocol for DCNG mere days before their planned insurrection. I think that's a great idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does #USER# know yet? I know cell coverage isn’t great on the golf course. 
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're asking that SCOTUS deny the will of the people. You're asking for autocracy and civil war.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, we call that "counting the votes" or "democracy".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Who is this “we” Joe of a talking about? Had he officially joined the racist caucus?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# who doesn't read and begs for people to search him up on google is judging me harshly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You got off the plane to "Fortunate Son", a song about how the sons of rich/connected people got out of going to Vietnam.nnJust. Like. You. #HASHTAG##HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. #USER# just said on #USER# that "the country should hold him (Trump) accountable" not the Senate.

Hey jackass! He already LOST THE ELECTION!

If murderous insurrection against the Constitution isn't enough for the #USER# to impeach a Republican, what is?!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's an overreaction. Bourne has actually had a pretty good season, but he has basically been WR1 in terms of production for the Pats, but his abilities and stats are not WR1 level.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Did he bring a fire extinguisher? Really? Show me.

Did he EVER state his goal was to put out fires? Did he do so BEFORE shooting three people? Show me.

Because he can claim anything, but we already know he's a liar on trial for murder, so his claims mean nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That he wasn’t violating Wisconsin gun laws because it’s okay for a minor to carry a rifle unsupervised if they’re…hunting?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# If we killed them now we'd be treating them like they treated Ahmaud Arbery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The workers are going to own the means of production?nnThat sounds....familiar.n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# This is a patently ridiculous response.

Of course it helps to have good WRs. The statement was that Mac wasn't capable. His time at Alabama proves that wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Look at the facts? The fact is that he removed classified documents from the White House. That's not in dispute.

The fact is that it's ILLEGAL to do that. That's not in dispute either.

The fact is anyone else would have been arrested.

Garland is the weakest POS AG in history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# just said that removing a federal vaccine mandate would actually decrease resistance to the vaccine.

Translation: Idiot admits that people are refusing the vaccine just because the govt. has made a mandate for public health purposes. People are evil monsters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But the “once lowly” Bucs were stacked with talent. It’s not like he was playing with a bunch of nobodies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes. When we take the names of seditious traitors off of military bases, China wins!

Wait, what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You never tire of people dunking on you with facts and deserved ridicule, do you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Greatest athlete? C'mon.

He has never been the greatest athlete on any team he has played on. Part of what makes him the GOAT is that he overcomes his lack of athleticism with hard work and determination.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah. That would never happen here!n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why hasn't Individual-1 been indicted yet?

Are we all equal under the law or not, #USER#?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trump owns the plane, right? So….why isn’t he doing anything with it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 3,000 Americans are dying every day now.

Because of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm not an expert like you, but....Mac Jones could be a pretty decent fit. Especially if they can get at least one speedy receiver on the roster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bald guy with a pony tail has things to say about science.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Um...there's absolutely nothing in Catholicism about the religious propriety of being vaccinated. NOTHING.

The Pope himself – who, as the voice of God him/herself in Catholicism, outranks Bishops and Archbishops – is a proponent of the vaccine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He's batshit crazy. Obama warned Trump, Trump embraced the crazy.

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He'll have plenty of time to spend with his family after he's disbarred.

You should try to learn to love your kids real quick. You won't be seeing a lot of them after you're indicted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's weird because if you just read the words, she's admitting the #HASHTAG# of the #USER# and is completely and utterly resigned to the fact that she and her colleagues put their #HASHTAG# and she just doesn't care to defend the Constitution. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Laughable.

#USER# incites an insurrection and then, when it fails, claims that it's a time of healing and tries to dodge responsibility?

Pathetic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You lied about a deadly pandemic and 300,000 Americans are dead, so far, as a result.

Millions of Americans are out of work.

Millions have lost their health insurance.

You are the worst POTUS in history. Period. Not even close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Who said he was cooked? The team lacked WR talent, as opposed to the Bucks who have tons of WR talent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...said the actual racist who ran a racist campaign and promotes racist policies while refusing to resign for being a racist.
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# words!nnLOL.nnYou're not worthy of debating. I can keep saying it if you want. No offense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I an shocked — SHOCKED — that somebody like Tom Cotton would misrepresent himself. 

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We voted back in November to send him off.
Then the House voted to send him off earlier this week.

He's being sent off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ham-fisted dolt #USER# trying to manage the most obvious machinations to sideline #USER# -- who is smarter, sharper and has conservative bona fides that McCarthy does not -- is really just a necessary task to further his aspiration of becoming Speaker.
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to know why Acting SeDef Miller issued the order re: DCNG that required his personal approval for their deployment, stripped them of riot gear, etc., mere days before 1/6.

Why would he do that? Who told him to do that? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #USER#! There's nothing partisan about making sure all Americans can vote.

Conversely, making it harder for targeted groups of Americans to vote -- as the #USER# is doing nationwide -- is *nothing* but partisan.

Why are joining Republicans in killing democracy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Uh oh. Somebody's still melting down! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #USER#! It's not that anybody is painting the #USER# any way at all. It's that the #USER# has become the party of racism and white nationalism. 

You allowed that to happen. Your approval may not have been vocal, but your inaction and lack of integrity made you complicit #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find it comical that people like #USER# don't understand the urgency required to remove a POTUS who publicly incited a murderous insurrection.

What's the rush?!? Process!!!

it's just irrational.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You only like this because you know you can't win with ideas or fairness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# What about Afghanistan? What “lie@ did Obama tell? 

You don’t really hold people accountable for doing something based on a lie they’ve been told, do you? How about a series of lies? “We know where the WMDs are” is a pretty big lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# He's not though. Because Biden isn't responsible for the actions of Republicans. They're responsible for their own actions.

Republicans are CHOOSING to cover up a coup attempt and they're CHOOSING to suppress minority voters. Obstruction is their CHOICE.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>