<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Midland Schools Not Putting Litter Boxes In Bathrooms For Furries, District Says | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MBB Preview: Arkansas hosts Texas A&amp;M | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Spread Cream Cheese, Not Hate’: University of Florida Students Give Away Free Bagels to Fight Antisemitism | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From summer student to chief administrative officer, Deborah Martin-Downs completes the circle | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bucks hold off Kings, 133-127 | Basketball | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | How will the COVID-19 pandemic end? WHO’s answer might surprise you #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Ulster County child molesters sentenced to prison | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | How QAnon sex trafficking conspiracy theories forced a butterfly sanctuary to shut down #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than 1,000 students were sexually abused at this university. An ex-NFL player wants their stories to be heard | Crime | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporters of Laurentian green space continue to fight possible sale of lands | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | 3 reasons you should buy a Chromebook tablet instead of Android #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | How to Survive the Most Dangerous Place on Earth: Your House #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Squad,’ Dems mum on police funding as crime continues to rise in major cities | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 500 Madison City students tested positive for COVID-19 last week | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why These Women Met In an Empty Field to Release a ‘Primal’ Mom Scream – SheKnows | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US professor discusses parenting arrangements and children’s emotional security | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | N.B.A.’s Warriors Disavow Part-Owner’s Uyghur Comments #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | ‘My husband is a paedophile, now I need to raise thousands to divorce him’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | Was Dorothy Day Too Left-Wing to Be a Catholic Saint? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kingsport, Bristol TN school districts continue to battle COVID-19 cases, staff shortages | WJHL | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Five missing teenage girls found, 30 sex offenders arrested #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Schools Branch staff asked to work in long-term care homes on P.E.I. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | Day we tested sex aids at Good Housekeeping #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money Matters: Strengthening your finances and marriage at the same time | News, Sports, Jobs | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media Companies Hit With Lawsuit for Teen Suicide | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okehampton teacher plans her climate mission for town | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | Chrissy Teigen and John Legend put their New York home on the market | Entertainment #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kilgore College names new police chief | Local News | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bangor High School students continue to ‘mentor’ younger kids | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Myanmar’s military took control of the country one year ago, but it never expected resistance like this | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Independent Study Student Brings BB Gun to BHS Campus — Berkeley High Jacket #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former teacher facing rape trial | Criminal Law | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Central Florida Boy Scouts executive accused of child molestation, deputies say #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Save Our Children, San Diego Metro Magazine #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here’s how many COVID-19 cases Lancaster County schools reported this week | Local News | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | How to Know If Your Child or Loved One Is at Risk of Being Trafficked #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farmington Board of Education, community members address 21 Day Equity Challenge | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Sex workers, victims’ advocates at odds over Winnipeg’s bid to remove licences for sexual service agencies #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murdered teacher Ashling Murphy tried to fight off her attacker with set of KEYS, police believe | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nature or nurture? Twin study sheds light on the development of callous-unemotional traits in adolescents | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | ‘We go and confront them’: YouTuber finds child predators #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Italian police arrest alleged Black Axe Nigerian mafia members over trafficking | Global development #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Building Apps Help Make the Office Return a Touch-Free Experience #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gun control advocates express disappointment with Biden | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Springfield Board of Education to make student mask mandate decision on Friday | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff member injured, several students in custody after large fight at Meadowdale High School | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let’s go back to some hands-off parenting, please | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Shaq Says He Doesn’t ‘Feel Sorry’ For Kanye West Amid Co-Parenting Woes With Kim Kardashian | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oshkosh North High School opens sensory room | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 found dead in home; no foul play suspected | Crime and Courts | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dallas Mavs Join The NBA To Honor The Life, Legacy Of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Animated film, ‘Ron’s Gone Wrong’ looks at the effects of technology and social media – Massachusetts Daily Collegian | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | In the pandemic’s wake, suicidal ideation among teens is up #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Florida school district banning excused absences for COVID-19 concerns | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sarawak to set up one-stop centre to cater to the needs of disabled community | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Awareness about human trafficking ahead of the Super Bowl #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents of Two Oxford High School Students Sue District Over Shooting | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Convicted Child Molester From Indiana Receives 10-20 Year Sentence In State Prison – CBS Pittsburgh #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Skoda the latest brand to ditch safety tech amid semiconductor shortage #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carson City School District to limit transportation services Monday and Tuesday | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | Winter Olympians Feel Threat From Climate Change – NECN #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School lunches in a COVID era: ‘I never thought I’d hear the kids say Oh, not pizza again’ | Education | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yvette Uwimbabaz is New Hanover County Schools’ Student of the Week | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | This Mom Is Helping Parents Discover Pro-America Content for Kids #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | ‘It’s always been here’: Sex trafficking in Montana an entrenched crisis | State &amp; Regional #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andre Lambe, Adrian Roach victorious at Fight Night Champion – The Royal Gazette | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents turn to school choice after remote-learning disasters | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | 11 Books, Movies, Podcasts, Songs (and More) Inspiring the Fight Against Gender-Based Violence #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gun Control Advocates Hope for Progress, While Opposition Remains | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lifestyle News | Parenting Interventions Support Psychosocial Adjustment of Kids in Foster, Adoptive Families: Study | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID-19 surge surprises in North Andover schools | News | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Cleveland Rape Crisis Center receives $1.3 million grant, plans to work with LGBT youth, victims of sexual assault #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | Calling Civilian Casualties a ‘Failure,’ Democrats Urge Biden to Do Better #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Houston-Area Woman Charged with Obstruction of the Enforcement of the Federal Criminal Sex Trafficking Statute – L’Observateur #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Camera-caught school zone speeders might face $250 fine for each violation | Crime and Courts #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auburn man’s roommate says Downs had gun at time of 1993 murder | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | Why Teen Mom’s Amber Portwood Walked Off the Reunion #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Takeaways from Tallahassee — Celebrating Black History #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Odd News Roundup: South Africa dog hotel offers ‘six star’ canine luxury; Cuban children with disabilities pet jaguars and snakes for therapy | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Men arrested after MPD, TBI conduct human trafficking operation, officials say – FOX13 News Memphis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Josh Widdicombe asked Kate Middleton to be on his parenting podcast | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Coronavirus live updates and omicron variant news #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chapel Hill-Carrboro schools seeing increase in substitute teachers, but still not enough, district says | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jilted Bengaluru man, 5 accomplices held for abducting his girlfriend’s brother | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | Governor Hochul Urges New Yorkers to Prepare for Dangerous Cold Temperatures Through Saturday Morning #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prince William Made a Relatable Parenting Confession About Prince George’s Screen Time | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU announces €175 million in EU humanitarian aid for West and Central Africa – Nigeria | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SCS Adolescent Parenting Program helps expecting and teen moms – FOX13 News Memphis | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paedophile suspected of abducting Madeleine McCann had worked at apartments where she vanished, documentary claims | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New NC House committee looks to reinvent education. Should the State Superintendent lead the State Board of Ed? | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘It’s Just Stressful’: Students Feel the Weight of Pandemic Uncertainty | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many “Parent” Groups Opposing Masks and CRT Are Actually Driven by Dark Money | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | Tax season has begun: Everything to know before you file your 2021 tax return #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alabama: New arrest in connection with Enterprise 9th-grader murder | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Types of parenting and their impact on children today | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | October is National Bullying Prevention Awareness Month, Jehovah’s Witnesses offer online resources #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion split on legislation that would allow 16- and 17-year-olds to vote in local elections | Legislature | New Mexico Legislative Session | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School closures due to rise in COVID cases affects mental health of SC kids, experts say | Health | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multiple New York school districts go remote after online threats | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Kingston man, 30, gets 18 years in prison for repeated sexual acts with two boys – Daily Freeman #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tamil Nadu girl’s suicide: Stalin hits out at BJP, asks DMK cadre to fight ‘sectarian’ politics | Latest News India | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SUNY Oneonta student dies from cold exposure; found miles from campus, police say | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | People with anorexia and bulimia ‘bombarded with dangerous dieting adverts on Facebook’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. Cox resigns from Duncan education board | Community | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Man sends letter from jail claiming to be ‘serial pedophile’ with victims in three states #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RLRS Board Update – Lewiston Sun Journal | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Know how Kate Middleton Gets Her hildren to behave | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More officers were charged in fatal police shootings in 2021. Not everyone sees progress. | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Cancer Comes Calling, Normal Cells Fight Back. But How? | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | What parents need to know about kids and COVID-19 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hollingshead flashing potential early in her career at Georgia | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Tioni Theus May Have Been Human Trafficking Victim, DA Says – NBC Los Angeles #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | La Crosse’s Billings continues to push legislation to protect sex-trafficked minors – WIZM 92.3FM 1410AM #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bulldog Virtual Academy Update Offered to Covington School Board | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Ending human trafficking in Nebraska – Nebraska City News Press #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘I can be a softie sometimes, but he knows not to push me too far’ | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Texas Ranger was celebrated for catching serial killers. Did he also ensnare innocent people? | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Richland Township man heads to trial, facing 320 sex-related charges | News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Community members in Fairfield speak out after council member correlates LGBTQ people with sex trafficking #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | As the new school year approaches in Australia, what are the COVID-19 risks for sending children back to the classroom? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Gun control advocates nervous as Supreme Court takes up first 2nd Amendment case in a decade #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KISD mother: “I’m asking for you to fight for our children” | Coronavirus | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Littleton Public Schools nix COVID-19 vaccine clinics after videos claim kids got shots without parental consent | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These N.J. schools provide COVID vaccines, tests to anyone. Find a clinic here. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monitoring COVID Numbers a High Priority For Mascoutah School District – Herald Publications | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Khloé Kardashian And Tristan Thompson’s ‘Strained’ Co-Parenting Situation—We’re Devastated For True! | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Helpful Winter Driving Safety Tips from CT DOT + More #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teach Your Children’s Well: Parenting Books 2022 | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Addressing the unprecedented behavioral-health challenges facing Generation Z #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunburn — The morning read of what’s hot in Florida politics — 1.26.22 | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to help families of West Valley City shooting victims | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shelton 2022-23 school year to begin Sept. 6 | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MLK’s words can be applied to today’s labor and voting rights fight | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Spencer’s consultant joining city planning board #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 Philly-area dancers get to the pointe with the Trocks, a comic male ballet company performing at the Annenberg | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Systemwide Failure”: Gun Control Advocates Demand New Regulations After Michigan School Shooting | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | ILA | One Week Into Session and Gun Bills Are On the Move In Santa Fe! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Masks on agenda for 2 school boards; All 3 school boards will meet Monday | Education | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eight-year veteran of the Twinsburg school board due to vacancy | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-State Man Sentenced To 35 Years In Federal Prison For Child Sexual Exploitation Crimes | USAO-MDTN | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zoning panel clears way for second group home in Unity | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | 9 ‘Screen Time’ Features Everyone Should Be Using #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NSW unveils its much-anticipated back-to-school plan as state records 34 COVID-19 deaths | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School board meetings become verbal battle zones in COVID era – Orange County Register | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Non-Jewish ASU students need to do more to fight antisemitism | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happened to Ashling Murphy? What we know about teacher’s murder in Tullamore, as Josef Puska, 31, charged | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Park City School District won’t explain new policy prohibiting talk about vaccines | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Group raises awareness of trafficking problem ahead of World Games #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | UM Today | Screaming into the void? Us too. Coping tips for stressed-out families in the COVID-19 pandemic #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American-Islamic Relations Org. Calls for Federal Hate Crime Probe of ‘N***** Lover,’ Fire at Tenn. Interracial Couple’s Home | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Florida Blue Foundation makes $3.8 million investment in mental well-being for children, families and seniors #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pomona Unified schools to start voluntary coronavirus testing for students – Daily Bulletin | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emma Roberts and Garrett Hedlund split – but are dedicated to co-parenting their son | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | ‘I believe that forcing a child to wear a mask 7 hours a day is torture’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After being abducted by his babysitter, a Belgian boy, four, was discovered dead on a Dutch island. | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woodland Park school board approves memorandum of understanding with Merit Academy during special meeting | Pikes Peak Courier | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Virginia schools used COVID mask mandates to ‘thumb their noses’ at new Gov. Youngkin | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Officials say awareness, education are keys to battling human trafficking in Northwest Arkansas ⋆ 4State News MO AR KS OK #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Be a champion for the underdogs: 12 tips for helping homeless pets, rescues and shelters | Interests #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HIV clinicians should ask gay men if they want to become fathers | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parent maces student after fight at Asheville High School | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valley News – Educators call NH’s ‘teacher loyalty’ bill insulting, vague; proponents point to student ‘indoctrination’ | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why The Parents, Wards And Government Agencies Of These Two Southern States Should Be Especially Alert | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Human traffickers now recruit victims through virtual processes ― NAPTIP #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Paediatrician shares important reminder to parents amid pandemic #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Henry County teacher arrested, accused of sexual misconduct with students | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | Terence Darrell Kelly pleads guilty to kidnapping four-year-old Cleo Smith #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Latest COVID Surge Pushes Parents to Next-Level Stress #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oppose the dangerous reopening of universities! Students and youth must take up a fight against the pandemic! | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Without abortion, Black women and children can thrive #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Okaloosa parents are sending Ubers to pick up kids from school. But drivers must refuse #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Opleousas Man Acussed in a String of Robberies in Acadiana #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parenting In Focus: Helping your child deal with stressful times | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plugged-In Parenting: Expert Advice and The Latest Wave of Devices for 2022 | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nick Clegg accused of turning a blind eye to online child abuse over ‘cynical’ Facebook decision | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murder of five-year-old girl sparks outrage in north Nigeria | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elizabeth Holmes found guilty on four out of 11 federal charges | Archive | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adams 14 School District to discuss future | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | E’town Schools receives award for workplace safety | Education #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | Study, Telecom News, ET Telecom #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID-19 cases force Kalamazoo-area district to switch some schools to remote learning | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Glasgow residents issued safety advice in event of power cut caused by forecast high winds #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As recall looms, school board members stake out their positions | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frassati Catholic High School unveils plans for new sports complex | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Braunfels man guilty of indecency | Community Alert | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Dekalb County Sheriff investigators arrest man for electronic solicitation of a child #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents and teachers plan a rally before school board meeting | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | Full text of NYPD Det. Jason Rivera’s widow’s eulogy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CoxHealth seeks help from college, high school students amid COVID-19 surge | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | Jehovah’s Witnesses hope to help families with bullying #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Killeen ISD parents say district needs to do more to fight COVID cases | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Teach Philosophy of Science in High School | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roughly One-Third of Teens in Canada, US Think Holocaust is ‘Exaggerated or Fabricated’ | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPDATE: Teacher left children home alone while she vacationed in Florida with boyfriend, arrest warrant says | | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID rate among public school-aged Cobb residents continues to increase based on January 28 report | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[County sees over 100 COVID deaths; school district reporting to change | News | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kyle and Sam’s motorcycling essentials, Nyoy and Matt’s creative parenting habits in ABS-CBN YouTube shows – Manila Bulletin | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | City committee hears arguments for and against licensing sex workers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teachers of the year recognized by Opelika City Schools Board of Education | Local News | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For second time, judge dismisses lawsuit arguing consumers entitled to costs tied to ComEd bribery case | Crime-and-courts | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>