<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I love bats. Helpful little skeeter-eaters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Dragons are slightly sneaky
Mandalas, Pride art, chic and geeky
Gifts for any fashion freak
To stand out with something unique!

Code FINISHLINE saves 25% on everything until December 7th at #URL#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm so sorry for such a double-punch. Condolences and sympathy for your loss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I like how much the stark black and white contrast in the first one shows off the perfection of the dot-wave pattern.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some fools really act lile size is proof of wealth like it's the pre-processed-food era when only wealthy people *could* be big and ignore that calorie quantity doesn't equal nutrition quality. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No.

If it "happens to all of us," tens to hundreds of millions of us will die, especially if we don't provide vaccines to EVERYONE, and hundreds of millions will be stuck with long-term disabilities we still don't know all the effects of.

Giving up precautions is mass murder. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd get a fourth and fifth and twentieth if need be.

I'd wear a SCUBA SUIT for life to not catch or spread it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's been backtracked a lot. The mission is ACTUAL EQUAL RIGHTS and opportunity, for all races, genders, and other demographics. We made some progress, but now that progress is endangered and being sabotaged.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Agreed that the chances are low, and I'm not going to be promoting any of this person's tweets from here on in, but I'd like an eye on them- perhaps help warn folks who are more emotionally hurt by this dialogue, and such. And help this one IF they start really reflecting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This ties into the fact that there's a war on non-patriarch genders- that is, all non-cishet-men. All women, trans and cis, all nonbinary, all trans men. They're afraid of what medicine can prove about non-patriarchs, that is, that differences between us are insignificant.

13/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ABA is basically "Nonconsensual BSDM training for babies."

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's best to try to build a relationship with followers- tell your story, get their interest, be polite and don't ONLY talk about your issue. Let them get to know your interests and dreams as well. It looks spammy to only ask for help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# A lot of DENIAL of it as well. Denial of the *fact that the Asp word means supremacy to most Auts.* "I use this word to stick it to Hans." No, that's not how it works. Use his name, you're *endorsing his ethics/methods.* You can't just SAY everyone should interpret it your way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I like how smooth the lines of 4 are. I just prefer dark sheets because reflected light wakes me up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# In my case, I also avoid buying plastic when I can. Haven't bought trash bags in years because I have thousands of grocery sacks I can use- and I don't put out lots of trash to begin with. I DIY what I can and avoid harsh chemical cleaners- baking soda, vinegar, and isopropyl do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thank you! Disabled queer artist a whole MONTH behind on rent! If I lose my home, I can't survive streets or shelters, ESPECIALLY in a pandemic winter.

Current numbers $575/1200.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And if a character is only 20 or 30 by the end of a story? They have TONS of time in their life to have whatever settling down they want. Their STORY isn't their whole life- expecting that a story has to include romance implies every stage of a person's life does!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Items that have basically no ethical big name makers OR healthy ingredients:

Potato chips
Soda
Candy

If you still want these but boycott big brands, buy off-brand, or in the case of chocolate, fair trade. Chocolate is more nutritionally balanced than hard or gummy candy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heeere, fishy-fishy! The Pride Koi Mandala is ready to go! I especially love it on the shower curtain- so smooth and soothing.

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# (It's a messed up, codependent love story, but a love story all the same.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Doesn't sound enjoyable for me. I have to micromanage how I wash my hair- it's long, can't stand it short, but also can't stand like, the "pile it onto my head" style of washing that people do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Especially considering that it's LESS expensive to have an adult live with you than a child. If you're not buying them everything anymore like toys, clothing they grow out of fast, school gear, and such, they cost you LESS than they did as a kid.

2/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aspec people are some of the ones who have had the hardest time with people on ALL ends grasping consent. That no means no for straight and gay folks alike, that folks on BOTH ends have treated us like challenges or like we're broken. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My biggest retrieval of would-be-stolen stuff was $1600 of blinds because they acted like their printoff was a receipt and I pay *attention* to details- for one, it was for another store! For another, all the blinds LISTED were the same size and she had several different sizes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sure! It started as a habit when my home was full of other people and I left the bedroom I was sharing with my now-ex. But it just felt *easier* once the home emptied. No door between me and bathroom, mattress on the floor, curtain-cave for darkness, laptop for music out here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Seconded. Mimicking the lemmings is NOT going to lead you away from the cliff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah, thrift stores have such a variety that you can really learn a lot and never get bored. The big issues are the fact that it's retail and therefore you get stomped on, and the fact that they ALWAYS use the charity status as an excuse to pay minimum wage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# A synonym of Asp? A word that has both the meaning of Aut and includes the high-masked aspect?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even a mild case could still result in me losing the rest of my stamina and survivability. Even if it's not the illness itself that gets me, I could end up starving, having heart failure, or neural damage. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I might be inclined to start work on organizing things like this. Both "starting a prototype list /stats format" and in developing a community about it. I think to keep the GM acronym, we'd use Guild Mentor.

1/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonus details! A nonexhaustive list of things WAY more likely to kill you if you can't access a hospital fast:

Spider bite
Skin infection
Broken bone
Appendicitis
Tonsil issue
Car wreck
Burns
Food poisoning
Allergic reaction
Assault
Pregnancy
Frostbite
Heat sickness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# More people would buy books (and whatever other products that we want and capitalism wants to sell us) if we had fair income.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Underrated term to refer to Any Person: Neighbor.

If your neighborhood is Everywhere, then everyone's your neighbor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's used as a bludgeon. "See? There IS no systemic alternative- so you have to settle for the conversion system."

It's SO often used as a way to prevent people from *developing* their own methods or talking TOGETHER. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disabled, Trans history-hermit word-nerd seeks help for rent and survival! Please check out my shops below for clothing and accessories with Pride art, Dragons, mandalas, space and hippie designs!

OR, please consider sending a tip to 
#URL# ! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Same. HOWEVER I cannot stand baseball caps, and almost all places will ONLY allow ballcaps- usually their logo. I HATE being visible as an employee of somewhere outside of work- what if a hostile customer followed me or an out-of-work creep stalked me to work?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ugh, I'm so sorry you've got so much going on at once *and* on a holiday.

Rest and comfort to both of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It disappoints me that society called POOR whites, not cruel ones, "white trash."nnOne should be able to call the cruel ones trash. The bigots, the plague-brats, the predators and the kreepy kongressmen.nnI've met plenty of extremely kind folk who were CALLED trash for poverty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like a game of keep-away- where they dangle the hope of a great time in front of you while they bully you the rest of the time. The carrot-and-stick approach. Making life seem drab and painful by default so  THEIR chosen days are "awesome" when it's just glitz.

26/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# neurotypical."

Your child: "Cereal is just breakfast pasta you don't need to boil. Loop cereal is just chilled milky alphabet soup that can only spell ooooooooooooo."

(Format: #USER# .)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I do indeed! About twenty kinds of shirt (with multiple color options,) mugs and bottles, stickers, posters, magnets, phone cases, and more!

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm MORE likely to need a stick on uneven terrain like beaches or hiking! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But abled folks tend to center their own needs in many cases- and some of them act like the lack-of-pleasure they imagine we have is contagious. That if it's work for us to have fun, it'll be too hard for THEM to have fun.

4/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah- just as it's bizarre to micromanage if people DO want the same bed, it's wrong to micromanage NOT wanting to sleep in a bed together.

One aspect of purity culture is it creates BACKLASH and a culture that considers certain things PRUDE even if it's not from moral choices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martial arts as a method of defense instead of attack, for example. Or criminals deserving compassion in order to reach redemption. Or interdependence versus standalone-ism. (My term for the so-called independence that people claim they have when they won't work together.)

11/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# *sigh*

How about *they* get therapy to *accept people you can't order to behave like you expect?*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many ignore the effect forced relocation alone has on a populace. Sure, Indigenous folks were bound to the land- *their* land, with harvest and hunting they were *used to,* and even if they were shunted onto equal *amounts* of land- they weren't- it was less fertile, hospitable. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My hair can only handle one wash a week. I can muster the energy for a shower every other day if I'm feeling good, but usually it's every three days or so.

It's way more important to focus on HAND hygiene and TOOTH care than daily showers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any employer asking that about a gap that happens between 2020 and (some hypothetical end of COVID) would be Red Flags Galore.

"I like life too much to want to THROW IT AWAY for a job." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Champ, peer, pal, badass one...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# "Beggars can't be choosers" is so often used as an excuse to deliberately give the poor folks what they can't use.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same thing goes for libraries, schools, hospitals, and postal services!

They deserve a fair, healthy share of funding and shouldn't have to beg for scraps or price gouge users. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Anything said to someone else should never be unkind, especially in a public venue. No versions of bigotry are acceptable in a customer service job- or any job.

Probably one reason bigots are rebelling so much lately- more companies *can be held liable* for employee bigotry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Far as I've read even the songwriter can't stand the song anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I knew what to do for the dry, split skin on my hands. I can't STAND lotions, especially pale opaque ones, I can't stand my hands being OILY, either for handling tech or just the feel of being *slimy.*

Have tried: coconut oil, olive oil, medicated lip balm, Vitamin E oil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This! This this this!nnHow much of "overweight people have health issues" is due to diet culture?nnHow healthy is bullying someone? Making them hate themself? Their body?nnTraumatized people have health issues! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Russian Orthodoxy has a HUUUUUGE level of misogyny and patriarchy, rivaling any of the other extreme versions like the most devout Catholics or LDS. Only JWs are significantly stricter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If I had been drinking something when reading that, I'd have drenched my laptop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yyyyyeah-nope. Someone with opposite political views as me *wouldn't believe I have the right to exist as me.* They'd either want me dead or pretending I'm someone I'm not, and they'd likely get cranky that I'm as vocal about my stances as I am.

Bigotry is disgusting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*wags tail* Up to $1085! Could I get there tonight? Any amount helps and I am extremely grateful for all the support you folks have sent! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Playing the world's shittiest RPG with everybody else trying to be the GM and no rulebook to explain all their incoherent, inconsistent rules. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wish it was easier to do when my face won't hold still. And that it didn't feel strange on my face. I LOVE eyeliner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It sucks that the people most likely to WANT to help struggling people are the ones who are too broke to do so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I don't like green bell peppers because they're bitter. The more mature they are, the sweeter they are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Same here. If I had several of my favorite items, I'd be thrilled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stunning kitty, Max is! Happy fluffy birthday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ouch, I'm sorry. I found it comforting to find a special place on my altar for some of my kitty's toys, and make sure I had my pictures of her backed up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And they're trying to make more and more people they don't want voting felons. They already imprison bunches of marginalized people. Abortion bans are a way to take the VOTE from people with uteri.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under half the worldwide population is fully vaccinated. Many can't be, many are still high risk even vaxxed. The more spread, the more variants.

ALSO, wildlife can catch and die from COVID. Farmed animals, pets, zoo animals. Endangered species could be at risk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# : Could I please get a hand towards my rent goal? I'm running nearly a month behind, at risk of eviction, with no other safe options.

Any amount or shares help!

#HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A thank you message and update on my rental situation- I have finally gotten Official Assistance for a few months! Rent is now secure and I only need lesser bill help and to get traction on FUTURE rent. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Like, sure, my art is digital but I'd rather sell it on ITEMS that are comfy and/or useful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ooh, always love seeing David Eddings mentioned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where do people who claim they're pro-trans but still like the TERF author get their magic wands?

.

.

.

.

.

.

.

.

.

Hypocritic Alley.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sadly, until/unless ALMOST ALL Christians (especially the leaders!) TOTALLY stop the aim to convert the world and just BE the kind people Jesus wanted them to be, they're gonna have too many falling for superiority notions and hurting people on behalf of the crusade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh, indeed. It's not that there's NO effect, but society treats those effects as set in stone- therefore WRONG to tinker with hormonally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In fact that strip of land being EQUATED with Jewish folks is a disservice to all of those who DON'T live there, and it was created as a method of apartheid by nations- the US and UK- who didn't want to support Jewish refugees themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing "Social Darwiism" gets wrong is the phrase "survival of the fittest." Now, a healthy body is a More Survivable Asset, but as we see, people who are physically healthy might not still be AWARE of their own mortality/fragility! They are overconfident! Reckless!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just like we shouldn't be saying "post-COVID" yet because we're still smack in the middle of things, I'd like people to stop saying "UNTIL the pandemic ends" and start saying "UNLESS we manage the spread."

It is ENTIRELY POSSIBLE for us to lose all control  of it permanently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Just because conquest and genocide are always wrong doesn't mean it's fair to just say "it happens." None of us alive had any bearing on Rome or Macedon. But many living Americans benefit from land that belongs to still living Indigenous folks. We can still DO something to help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Lemme guess: this idea is REALLY popular among the horse-dewormer-for-COVID types.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# However, one must be careful to not go with other intentionally polluting snacks. Soda isn't meat, but it's a climate killer due to both water abuse and the sheer amount of corn made for HFCS. Monocrops are a BIG driver of forest destruction and they use LOTS of chem fertilizers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't think of a facet of life that isn't being assaulted by the reich-wingers. They've been trying to censor and control entertainment since JOE MCCARTHY. The Cold War never really ended, and neither did the Civil War- they forged a hybrid called "In God We Trust."

15/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish all my

TRANS BUDDIES

A very

GENDER EUPHORIC PRESENT TIME.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We can say the best tool for the job rhymes with "plane saw."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Folks I NEVER follow back include:

Bullies
Supremacists (racial, gender, ability, etc.)
Anti-queer and anti-trans folks
Antimaskers/antivaxxers
Muskbros
Crapto-currency pushers
One-track accounts (where I can't see your political side)
Spammers/scammers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's racist, classist, ableist, and feeds EDs to demand that everyone eat the way you eat- whether that's vegan or not! Just as bad to demand someone tolerate eating meat when they CAN'T!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heck- my dad "tapped" but it wasn't always loud enough to hear AND he didn't give me much time.

I think a parent needs to let the kid give them the go-ahead, or at least give more than a five second warning. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ideal two methods of sleeping: bed-in-a-tent or hammock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Agreed! And if produce isn't edible anymore, they should be required to donate it to local farms for compost! (Of course, enable farms to have big composting capacity.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public laundry facilities are growing more rare, as homeowners are expected to own laundry machines and complexes often offer a facility of their own. So keeping bedding and clothing clean are extra difficult for homeless folks.nn20/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I do a variety of digital art on clothing, tech gear, home goods, and more! I specialize in Pride art, Dragons Of Unusual Materials, mandalas, hippie stuff, and space art!

Code FINISHLINE saves 25% until December 7th! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I think one key step is patience with oneself- working to eliminate ALL self-bullying. Make a mistake? You can say "I goofed up" instead of "I'm dumb." Identifying the mistake as a TRAIT you have instead of a CHOICE you made or a klutz moment is a very hard thing to overcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sooooo handy for when one wants low-effort spuds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Similarly, people who think Freud was right fall prey to thinking LIKE he says people think. It's a self-fulfilling prophecy- the more you're afraid you'll think about sex or violence, the more you're thinking about sex or violence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Being trans, disabled, vegetarian, and not Christian are four- trans is a big social debuff, disability is health, being veg and not Christian are slightly smaller social.nnBut those do me no damage like the "skintone autotarget system" racists have can do to ANYONE not white.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A vacuum that cost more than two of the cars I've had. The only upside I got from that was a decent credit score for paying it off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Israel-the-nation is also America and Britain's idea of Jewish apartheid- they wanted to funnel as many of their own Jews there as possible both to saturate the zone for this crusade AND to get them out of their own turf. They do NOT actively care about the resulting lives.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It drives me up the wall how thoroughly America (and the rest of the world, but ESPECIALLY America) has been fed the myth of the Billionaire Philanthropist.

A short thread on how people were lead to think krapitalism doesn't stink:

1/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I stood out in MANY ways, not just being Autistic or nerdy. I was raised by a single DAD, which was almost unheard of- there were single moms, stepparents, and such, but for DAD to raise me was "weird." I was not religious, asked inconvenient questions of religious folks, etc... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I despise calling. Phone is the *only* contact I have with my dad at all, though- I think by now his eyes are so shot that writing by letter *or* text would be Nope and he is *not* the sort who would be up for using text-to-speech on a phone. He despises modern computerized tech.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "frustrated girl who hates clothes shopping because they can't afford or fit anything" to "frustrated boy who loves clothes shopping but can't afford it or fit anything" pipeline is a lousy one. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And maybe ask people to compare their own needs with each other for videos. Siblings, best friends, parents and kids, and such. "How do you customize life around YOUR needs?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# But we still can't really compare the near extinction of the bison in order to starve the Indigenous folks to mass meat farming- they're both heinous crimes against nature, but the bison extermination was ALSO deliberately wasteful and done to hurt people as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Some places- the US hardware store with the blue logo, for example- also pick an arbitrary number like 7 as the top score, further confusing customers and sabotaging their chances of top scores even when customers MEAN to give top score!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're halfway through January. Why am I still seeing Christmas advertisements?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Whoever inspired that seems to have gotten Indigenous folks mixed up with Amish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Illegalizing queerdom is trying to take the vote from queers. And prosecutions will call the same crime a misdemeanor if someone they like does it and a felony if someone they don't like does it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linguistics are a special interest of mine, and sadly, this includes times when society has used doubled meanings of words to justify their horror or deny it happens.nnI recommend this thread about the doublespeak of the ongoing genocide of Indigenous folks by "saviors." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Thank you for doing so. That's a solid gift to your fellow people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Rabbie's a great person and a fun artist. They deserve as much support as possible and I'm glad they have you looking out for them too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then- AND THEN! the fact that they basically force-feed you (even when you didn't want to eat as much as they expected you to) is treated as a reason to guilt people into losing weight! More misery-out-of-holiday to "pay for" Doing As Expected.

38/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Noto out there to people who DM others directly about crowdfunding:

If YOU are the one who DMs someone ELSE, YOU are in THEIR DMs and THEY have every right to be annoyed and/or advise you.

You have NO idea how people respond to DMs. It's like knocking a stranger's door.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I personally would like folks to adopt phrasing like "I don't care about the gender" without the "healthy" disclaimer. "As long as they make it" is fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*wags tail* Woot! Thank you! Now up to $870/1200 for December! (Yes, it's January now and I'll also need $1200 for January rent.)

Please aid if you can and pass this on! Peek at my pinned for details!

#HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So the Americas were settled EONS earlier, when ALL humans were still in prehistory. Even if the Indigenous folks were only here a CENTURY before others, they still had it FIRST, but their many millennia prior stewardship was interfered with by INNUMERABLE genocidal acts.nn2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plus, hmmm, with all the places that have caught fire, and the fact that EVERY SINGLE BURNING THING releases greenhouse gases, from the fireworks themselves to fires they start?

We need to stop doing things that have temporary "benefits" at huge costs to people and planet. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Chocolate chips! Melt them together and mix cereal crumbs in it for no-bake cookies!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had to spend hours of time and real money just to get a food handler's permit to work part-time, minimum wage in a cinema.

THEN there's hours of safety training, before they even give you hands-on work!

I'm not calling these bad- but they sure don't qualify for "unskilled." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Although a lot of the time there's a sense of piety to it too! A holier-than-thou attitude, which is NOT limited to religious folks- there are a LOT of superiority-complex atheists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Treating someone wrong for being trans is a gateway to abusing people for not conforming to your idea of their gender if they're NOT trans- like bullying hippies or nerds, fat people, disabled people, or more, for not being feminine OR masculine enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Even waking as early as 6- let alone *getting to work by 6*- has always been a struggle for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Both *watching the way demographics are treated by bosses and schools, hired, promoted, and such in person,* and research on the statistics and people's experiences. Feel free to look up the wage gap and such yourself. I'm not here for a back and forth debate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sleepy and/or wired- too tired to do anything, too anxious to actually *sleep.*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planetary assault is genocidal and a tool of control. It will kill way more than just Indigenous folks, but the Indigenous folks have the closest view of it and are fighting hardest. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the core of generational wealth or poverty- the ability to pass on money-making assets to your kids. Systems that charge more for marginalized people prevent anyone from ENTERING the generational wealth cycle. (See: interest rates.)

10/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Eighteen years ago, $400 plus power was a LOT in the area I lived in. I made $6/hr, and that was an area you could find apartments for only $600 at the time. Nowadays, $400 is chump change, rent-wise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If I had a car, AND a home with a garage, I'd be prone to instead using the garage as Tool Zone. Crafting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or like employees being worked to the breaking point for peanuts, squeezing more work for less pay and dangling hopes of more pay before them like a game of keepaway. Healthcare being tied to jobs is especially heinous here.

5/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest Glownoun design- Zie/Hir. 

Eight colors available: link leads to green.

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's also try to reduce *parents being so hostile or controlling to their kids that the kid can't stand staying with them.* #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We had a WHOLE STINKING SUMMER for most schools to adapt. But noooo, everyone was saying "the vax will solve all the problems!"

Yeah? Did it solve the problem we had of WILLFUL NONCOMPLIANCE WITH SAFETY MEASURES in the Q-klub? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Flowers Are Red" is a tearjerker, a tale of a kid whose creativity is squashed by a conformist teacher. Harry Chapin does a great job of exploring relationships between people- including adults and kids.

10/?

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to accept that filling a person's every minute with busy work and demanding they find something to do when it's slow is just bullying. There may always BE "something to do," but then you rush them through it? No! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YES! I can't STAND "brand loyalty" based around superficiality. Like, if a brand proves actual superiority, like sturdiness, sustainability, and style, then I can grow loyal, but even THOSE elements of a brand can be thrown away by future owners.

See the slogan "don't be evil." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hikaru is an excellent given name for nonbinary folks. I hope they like it because I do and it fits so well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is "total war," and are we experiencing it right now in the United States and elsewhere?

I can only speak *directly* to the issues in the US, but we're seeing signs of it in the UK, Brazil, China, and elsewhere.

1/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, you don't *owe,* but if you're going to just complain when people give advice, better just accept that the advice doesn't work for you.

Like I said, gift cards can't buy booze or cigarettes. They can buy food, toiletries, clothing and camp supplies if the store has it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Glorifying aggression never turns out well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# BIG one. I'd go so far as to say if you're locked, you can't QRT anyone who isn't a mutual.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(His kid is a monarch whose magic makes him an "essential asset" to their Empire. There's also frustration that his kid is treated like "a talking writing desk with a lantern feature." If he doesn't have an heir, they don't know how to get by without the monarch's magic.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If I'm estimating percentages well, it seems as though about 70% of Indigenous folks (who have opinions on spiritual appropriation) consider it appropriation to use white sage, as well. A majority, even if some don't agree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Because like all habits, patience gets easier the more often you use it. Being kinder to yourself helps you realize ways you might have been unkind to others. Being cruel to yourself numbs you to cruelty to others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Indeed! How do you actually convince people "it's not you, it's me" when usually the way that's used is "I'm trying to spare your feelings?" Like, you can be someone I love dearly talking about something I'm really into, and I can STILL feel "oof, too much people-time!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's frustrating because they're *technically correct in some facets* and clearly care- they're not necessarily blaming trans men for it, but they're not placing the blame where it belongs- the patriarchy/toxic dichotomy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Has a LOT more effect than jobs want to admit- keeps folks from holding two jobs when they aren't beimg paid enough at one,keeps digestion and diet messed up, interferes with your ABILITY to sleep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have this issue with morning and pain meds as well. "Am I remembering today, or is yesterday's memory still vivid and it *seems* like today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Profiting off of it AND preventing the origin culture from doing it themselves?!? Like Disney trying to trademark Day of the Dead because of Coco? (Or, for a ridiculous non-Indigenous example, the makers of Candy Crush Saga trying to trademark the words Candy, Crush, and Saga.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Agreed. You only have one chance to live, so it can be totally fair to prefer to prioritize quantity and THEN fun- not to shy away from ANY risk per se but to be aware of how risky your acts are versus how fleeting the reward is!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I seriously think the big reason that NTs might outpopulate NDs is through similar "we want people to be tame/domesticated" styles and levels of artificial selection, especially since cultures who once celebrated NDs suffered badly losing artisans, shamans, etc. through conquest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes! My kettle is hugely important to me. So are my microwave and toaster. Any food I can just use one dish for is a BIG time/energy saver. (Or if I can make leftovers that I then nuke.) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If she bought a circular saw with that money, they'd say "you can saw things by hand for twelve bucks."nnIf she paid for thirty meals for homeless folks with it, they'd say "you shouldn't help people who 'did that to themselves.'"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fresh #HASHTAG# art in my shop! This is an upgrade to my Rainbow Diamond Scales- smoother, shinier, and focused on the six-shade Pride rainbow!

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# DING! And accountants, better appliances, and all sorts of time-saving devices!

Some people *have a stay at home person* who does most of their housework.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You can be nontheist and anti-theocrat without trying to force others to not believe. There's a difference between trying to guide them away from irrational beliefs like supremacy or creationism and trying to force them away from all faith.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not only does it mean they can funnel more money away from public schools, it means they can MAKE money on private (often religious) schools.

DeVos may be out of the cabinet, but her legacy is still going and she's still making bank.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Indeed. Disabilities definitely *include* pain, of varying levels of intensity, frequency, and scope, but folks who think they don't have disabilities act like the existence of any disabilities condemns us to life of nothing BUT suffering- as though enjoyment entirely disappears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# All of these reasons and more. What if I don't keep a subscription for life? Then items I've paid to watch- even ones it says I "own"- just go poof. Or if the service goes under or sells out?

Gimme physical items. And libraries for borrowing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And especially with your kids- like, who did they get their genetics from? Who did they learn dietary habits from? You cannot expect that the child of two big people will have an easy time being skinny unless the parents literally feed them less!

6/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's just how the dipstick binary treats ANYONE that doesn't fit into the binary, whether that's trans folk or cis folk who have the teensiest trait not conforming to their gender. It only "has anything to do with it" because the ones drawing cultural ideals make small boxes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And even more importantly, even if it was only TEN YEARS before Euro travelers got to these continents, the locals were STILL HERE FIRST! It doesn't actually matter from an ethical point how long Indigenous folks were here- taking land from its first humans is still wrong!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It's important to learn to teach our inner critic to be *honest without venom.* We must be able to reflect on our actions but not at the cost of *hating ourself* for them. Even if one did something HEINOUS, villainizing ourself only keeps us in villain mindset.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Pixel Dragon- nicknamed Pixie- was a perfect way to lean into the gamer/nerd side of Autism. Pixie is also another term for SPRITE- the term for a pixel-art avatar in-game. We often go through life with others treating us like NPCs when we're each our own player.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New mandala up with a first look through my Patreon! Become a Pledgling for priority access!

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While queers vary just as much as anyone else, there's a bit more outside-the-boxness in even the most gender conforming queers. Bi, pan, and lesbian women are less patriarchy-driven- ESPECIALLY the ones who appreciate trans folk. Ditto for queer men.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't mind *the existence of music" on a hold line but it needs to not be soulless muzak AND ditch the ridiculous "please stay on the line" interruptions. Like, the music is enough clue that their end hasn't cut out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fresh mandala up in a newly public Patreon post! I'll be adding the Pride Koi Mandala to Redbubble in a few hours!

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Bingo. Like, "shoes oiff indoors" has bearing in practicality: keeping outdoor dirt out and floors cleaner. MOST traditions had SOMEONE decide they were good ideas: like salty food being necessary to cure/preserve it before refrigeration. But in excess MOST things are problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I read that there's no sign of it in birds or reptiles, but in almost all mammals, like minks, tigers, and anything in between.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I was in high school during Columbine and it was strongly on my mind because not only was I only a little younger than them, but it happened near the town I was *born* in. (Not raised.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Like I'm gonna trust random people's sexual safety when they've proven they can't be trusted to stay hygienic and safe in a non-sexual pandemic, for crying out loud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The peer pressure I'm referring to is the "score" that most dudes start worrying about in late high school to college- the "duuude, you're still a virgin?" The fact that virgin guys are shamed for "failing" to get laid and girls are shamed for NOT being virgins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yup! Thing is, there are anti-trans folks who decided to consider cis a slur because they're mad we won't call them "normal." Because there *is no such thing as normal.*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But I use the laptop out in the dining room because I don't like being in the bedroom all day. It also became easier/cheaper to only heat the common areas than using the baseboard heaters in the bedrooms. Easier to keep common areas cool in summer, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*sigh* There's snow. Pretty, but my knees hate traction risks, and "to boot," the boots that a friend helped me get ordered haven't arrived yet.

It's not that deep, but it's enough for my broken shoes. I need groceries and I'm essentially snowed in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's annoying that my phone's space is 5/8ths full of SYSTEM, though. I barely have any apps. No music or movies on it. JUST images, less than one gig, even with my constant drawing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The living embodiment of your computer going to a screeching, glitching halt- noises and lights and sensations stop making inherent sense and you lose control of your output, especially when folks don't stop pushing buttons. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very much. Autism is not an excuse for you inflicting abuse. Meltdowns don't change Jekyll into Hyde- you must not feed your cruel side. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I always knew- since studying how zealous and oppressive some religious folks were- that we could go down a sick path.nn9/11 was one wound. 2016 proved the zealots had NO limits to how sick of a person they would follow.nn2020 was their ACCELERATION.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the elitist, everything more mundane than law, medicine, or rocket science is "unskilled." They're not unskilled, they're MUNDANE skills- cash handling, negotiating, spotting illegitimate returns, making product (from shoes to food) properly, troubleshooting faulty machines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to see rich people start hurting in the wallets bigly when people die. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I just caught up with Owl House! Ooooh, good show. Love the flair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# MC in book one is Dan, the adolescent king of the Pheasant Coast. (Pronunciation: dahn, like the first syllable of Dante.)

丹, Mandarin Chinese for cinnabar red. I built my novel geography around Feng Shui, the southern beast is the Vermilion Bird...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Which means I need to be aware I could be in hermit mode for the rest of my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# My stance it to treat all traditions as nothing more than suggestions until they prove themselves. If a tradition has basis in health, hygiene, reducing harm, or reducing waste, it can be beneficial but we must beware of calling ANY tradition set-in-stone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Docs have to use my right arm for blood pressure because my left arm doesn't have the circulation for it- no aorta. (They had to reroute THAT to my legs.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sometimes I wonder how many people were bullied out of extroverted traits and found introversion to be the safer choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think one of the worst things about the world is that not only can we not un-invent a bad idea, we also cannot convince every single person that *any* bad idea is bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'd be the writing type. I MUST not remove my mask outside of my home. But I've always been ready to write for folks with hearing difficulties or use translate for language barriers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I also just avoid going into public as much as possible. I can't risk ANYTHING. I can't eat or drink anything in public anymore because of it- which makes a work day even less possible than it was already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# (I only mourn because it's a tree and it didn't deserve it, and because ANY burning matter adds to atmospheric carbon.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["(Action film franchise) shouldn't focus on romance" sounds like either "women exist to be eye candy for me, not a male character," or "I'm uncomfortable with a male action character having emotions that aren't Macho Rage."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Indeed- by shaming anyone, regardless of staying in a cis fem state or transitioning to masc, treating all who aren't in ABSOLUTE alignment with stereotypes as though we're all trans and making it harder for actual trans folk to have our own voice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Whereas I am transmasc bi- I am attracted to girls in a guy way and attracted to guys in a guy way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Public hand soap and sanitizer

Lotions- I wish there were options to *moisturize* without leaving hands *greasy* or *sticky,* and without medicated smell

Hair dyes

Pain patches or ache gels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you do not *know* someone you care about- including your elderly relatives or friends- who has a risk factor, that means you just don't know they DO have risk factors.

That's at LEAST one in four people, folks.

If you don't *care* about the high-risk, you're cruel. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mine's usually 72% cacao nibs, with some cane sugar but otherwise all chocolate liquor and cocoa butter. So all plant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I dare say we're the round pegs they want to shove in a square hole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Frankly, the point at which it's unethical is when they use advantage against others. Be fast as you want, don't ditch people in a fire. Be strong as you can be, don't beat people up with it. Are you ahead financially or socially? USE that role to advocate for those who aren't!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Many demographics have reason to hate white supremacy and theocratic patriarchy.nnNonreligious folknFolk of other faithsnLGBTQIA+ folknDisabled folknAny non-white racennThe bigots were quiet for a while, but they got louder, we have cameras, and more realized "it's ALL wrong."]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>