<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2022 Wednesday Q: Federal and State Court News- A judge slapped down the child pornography lawsuit slapped onto the band, Nirvana, over the cover of the “Nevermind” album.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2003 Friday: The first secretary of the new U.S. Department of Homeland Security- Tom Ridge- assumed his office today.  A Republican, he served under President George W. Bush from today until February 01, 2005.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1972 Sunday: Exclusive billionaire Howard Hughes, speaking by telephone from the Bahamas to reporters in Hollywood, said a purported autobiography of him by Clifford Irving was a fake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We believe the Rio Grande must be seeded with alligator pups, piranha babies, and that the border must be militarized lest the scenario portrayed in the original “Red Dawn” movie occur only with Chi-Coms in the place of the Russians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1954 Wednesday: Egyptian government declares martial law and arrests 318 Muslim Brotherhood members.  Elsewhere, in Johannesburg, South Africa, future guitarist Trevor Rabin who would perform with Manfred Mann’s Earth Band[ii] from 1980 to 1981 and again in 1984 is born.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1953 Monday: CBS-TV aired the widely watched episode of “I Love Lucy” in which Lucy Ricardo, played by Lucille Ball, and gave birth to Little Ricky.  (By coincidence, Ball gave birth the same day to her son, Desi Arnaz Jr.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, a summit between the Israelis and the Palestinians commences in Paris, France.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1788 Sunday: Pioneer African Baptist Church organizes in Savannah, Georgia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secretary of State Anthony Blinken and Russia’s foreign minister, Sergei Lavrov, on Ukraine must succeed.  Next, the United Nations defines Holocaust deniers and urges all social media providers to get on board and combat the vile rhetoric being pushed by leftists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data compiled with unchangeable fastidiousness by Moses Scharbug III.  Note: we pay the estate of Beverly Carrick an annual fee by which, we can show her paintings to the world.  We make NO money from the estate’s sales of her world-famous artworks.  Total Word Count: 1,176.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2012 Friday: Nearly 2,000 Malawi women protest attacks on women wearing trousers by unemployed youths and street vendors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1882 Monday: The 47th U.S. Supreme Court Associate Justice Horace Gray assumed his position on the nation’s high court on this date.  A Republican, he was nominated by Chester Arthur to fill Nathan Clifford’s seat.  He served from today until 09-15-1902.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1915 Tuesday: President Woodrow Wilson signed the Rocky Mountain National Park Act, which created America’s 10th national park.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hands over frozen Venezuelan assets to the true winner of election, Guaidó.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 772 Monday: Stephen III ends his reign as the 94th Roman Catholic Pope.  He first became the shepherd of the entire Christian flock on August 07, 768, and shepherded them until today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump News, Joe Biden’s Daily Disaster, Joe Biden Regime News I, Political News I, Sports News I, California Lottery Results-Super Lotto and Powerball Draws, Ukraine, Russia, Australia, Iran, Ayatollah Khamenei, President Donald J.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elsewhere, following two blasts suspected to be sabotage which subsequently led to Moscow cutting off supplies of natural gas to Armenia and Georgia, Azerbaijan steps forward and restarts supplies of the life-saving fuel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, it is more contagious but far less destructive so to me, that means hope is on the horizon).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1118 Thursday: The 161st Roman Catholic Pope Gelasius II picks up his Holy Cross on this date and serves all Christendom from today until January 29, 1119.n- 1568 Wednesday: In the Netherlands, the Duke of Alva declares William of Orange to be an ‘outlaw.’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1978 Friday: Former 38th Vice President Hubert H. Humphrey of the United States died in Waverly, Minnesota at age 66. He served under President Lyndon Baines Johnson from January 20, 1965, to January 20, 1969.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WE THANK EVERYONE FOR JOINING US AT #URL# AND FOR AIDING US IN CONTINUING TO DO THE WORK WE TOOK UPON OURSELVES MORE THAN A DECADE AGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Secretary of Defense Frank Carlucci; U.S. Secretary of Transportation Alan S. Boyd; Band of Gypsys featuring Billy Cox, Chuck Berry, the Faces featuring Rod Stewart, Fleetwood Mac featuring Robert “Bob” Brunning, and the Jefferson Airplane featuring Paul Kantner:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elsewhere, “Big Brother Facebook” now is going to ban ads for weapon accessories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disputes arose early over the first state in question- Arizona- which sent both chambers of Congress to debate the election fraud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1878 Monday: The first daily collegiate newspaper in the United States— “The Yale News”—underwent publication on this date.
- 1881 Friday: At the Battle of Laing’s Neck, Natal, South Africa, an inferior Boer army beats a superior British force.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1936 Thursday: The United States Army adopted the semi-automatic rifle.
- 1937 Saturday: Fascist Italy bans marriages between Italians and Abyssinians in conquered Ethiopia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stone and Vinson served from June 21, 1946, to September 08, 1953.  Prior to this, Vinson served his nation as its 53rd U.S. Treasury secretary.  Serving under the same president, he served from July 23, 1945, until June 23, 1946.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We hope you will visit #URL#, Discogs, AllMusic, eBay, or any other place you shop for the absolute best in music and consider making it a part of your listening day- you will be glad you did.  Enjoy. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elsewhere, future drummer with the British psychedelic rock band, Pink Floyd[i], Nick Mason, is born on this date in Edgbaston, Birmingham, England.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BEVERLY CARRICK ORIGINAL ARTWORK OF THE DAY: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[viii] AAA Gas Prices (#URL#)- See this site for nationwide daily gasoline averages.

[ix] Please see the following site for information on global gas prices: Gasoline prices around the world, 26-Apr-2021 | #URL# (#URL#)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[…the raging coronavirus pandemic. Under President Trump’s watch, there were 404,645 fatalities from the Chi-Com Bat Virus.  From this point forward, ALL COVID-19 deaths are atop Joe Biden.  He has surpassed President Donald J.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1945 Tuesday: During World War II, American forces under the command of General Douglas McArthur began landing at Lingayen Gulf in the Philippines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[minister to Denmark (what we call ‘ambassador’ today).
- 1848 Monday: James W. Marshall discovered a gold nugget at Sutter’s Mill in northern California, a discovery that led to the Gold Rush of 1849.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1942 Monday: The first American Expeditionary Force to go to Europe during World War II arrived in Belfast, Northern Ireland.  Meanwhile, the Italian high command demands that Germany dismiss General Erwin Rommel, commander of the Afrika Korps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TODAY IN HISTORY

THE #URL#

Chef Cheryl La Tigre, CEC-ACF

Chefs de Cuisine Association of Honolulu, Hawaii

Honolulu, HI 96782

Contact Me: cherylthetiger81#USER#.com

TODAY IN HISTORY @ THE #URL# @ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TODAY IN HISTORY

THE #URL#

Chef Charles Smithenstein,

Foodservice Management Professional, FMP, Mixologist, Culinarian Extraordinaire

Delano, CA 93216

Contact Me: thechuckster61OOO#USER#.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2020 Wednesday: Multi-instrumentalist with the British band Kaleidoscope- Chris Darrow- died on this date.  Elsewhere, CNN reports that a Delta Airlines jetliner approaching LAX dumped fuel during its descent which fell on local schools.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2022 Tuesday R: Nancy Pelosi’s January 06-2021 False Flag Operation- In Capitol Hill Riots-related news, Stuart Rhodes- American patriot and founder of the Oath Keepers pleaded NOT GUILTY to five charges of seditious conspiracy in federal court yesterday.  Good for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2007 Tuesday: After helping crush Islamists in Somalia in general and in Mogadishu in particular, Ethiopian military forces begin withdrawing from the nation’s capital city.  Elsewhere, an exasperated President George W.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elsewhere, the NFL franchise San Diego Chargers announces it is going to relocate the team to Los Angeles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor Marion Barry suffered arrest in an FBI sting of drug possession charges.  A court later convicted him of a misdemeanor offense.
- 1991 Friday: During the Gulf War, Iraq begins launching SCUD missiles against Israel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1989 Tuesday: A gunman opens fire in a California school, killing five people and wounding 30.   Elsewhere, up-and-coming heavyweight boxing future champion Tommy Morrison improved his record to 4-0 with a KO of Elvin Evans in Round 1.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things are going so badly for the Biden regime that everyone remotely connected to it is seeking a way to escape ahead of the oncoming political destruction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2022 Thursday N: Sports News I- Following last week’s on-field meltdown, the Tampa Bay Buccaneers have parted ways with troubled wide receiver Antonio Brown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can see much more of her work at her website, found at #URL#, or at the blog’s Facebook page.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[x] U.S. National Debt Clock: Real Time (#URL#) See this site for the U.S. National Debt Clock.

WE THANK EVERYONE FOR JOINING US AT #URL# AND FOR AIDING US IN CONTINUING TO DO THE WORK WE TOOK UPON OURSELVES MORE THAN A DECADE AGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most educated people believe the pandemic is on the wane and that what we continue seeing in the United States is little more than politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other foreign and overseas news, fury is growing among the civilized peoples of the world over the Chinese communists slaughtering small animals in Hong Kong, all because of claims they are COVID-19-positive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Original Beverly Carrick Artworks, Beverly Carrick—World Famous Artist, FINE ART, Beverly Carrick Beautiful Desert Landscapes, Just the Facts, Unvarnished Truth- The, American Institute of Culinary Politics-Elemental News of the Day- The, COVID-19 Statistics for The Planet as A…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaking of ‘Beijing Biden,’ people are curious as to WHY he remains MUM on Chi-Com repression as well as its continued lies that ‘Wuhan virus no come from Wuhan but come from outside China.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1922 Saturday: In the 10th Canadian Football League Grey Cup, Queen’s University defeats the Edmonton Eskimos, 13-1.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The other one is in custody.  Normally, things such as this don’t happen in ‘gun free Canada.’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1942 Tuesday: As the Japanese continue driving towards Singapore down the roads of Malaysia, British and Commonwealth forces pull back into the city and then blow up the causeways leading to the mainland.  Japanese bombers continue bombing the city around the clock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2022 Friday G: Illegal Aliens-Invaders-and-‘Refugees’ News- We learned today that just 267 illegal aliens have been returned to Mexico to await asylum hearings following the U.S. Supreme Court’s reinstatement of President Donald J. Trump’s ‘Remain in Mexico’ policy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shocking but not surprising for someone as unqualified as she is but still- the people of California are ecstatic to have made her the nation’s problem and no longer the Golden State’s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1925 Monday: Nellie T. Ross of Wyoming became America’s first female governor.   Meanwhile, U.S. Supreme Court Associate Justice Joseph McKenna, #HASHTAG#, a Republican, stepped down from the court.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1793 Wednesday: The second partition of Poland occurs, and East Prussia and Russia continue to divide the hapless kingdom between them.
- 1845 Thursday: The U.S. Congress decided to hold all national elections on the first Tuesday after the first Monday in November.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alan Dershowitz, Governor Asa Hutchinson, Congresswoman Claudia Tenney, President Donald J. Trump, Dr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[citizens but it’s going to illegal aliens.  This can and must stop.  Next, here is the estimated number of illegal aliens who have swarmed across the border and into the U.S. over the course of this week: 163,484.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2022 Thursday O: Political News I- YouTube has permanently banned Dan Bongino.   In other news, the dog dingus of dinguses, Sandy “The Fly” Cortez, says there’s ‘no reason for Senator Kyrsten Sinema to keep her seat.’  Wow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1621 Thursday: The 233rd Roman Catholic Pope Paul V ends his reign as the Vicar of Christ on this date.  He first became pontiff on May 16, 1605, and guided all Christendom until today.
- 1787 Sunday: Philadelphia’s Free Africa Society forms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next, here are the stats for the United States: 69,582,430 confirmed cases, UP 955,141 from yesterday’s reporting, 880,160 confirmed deaths, UP +3,003,[i] and 43,700,835 confirmed recoveries, UP 405,955.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2014 Wednesday: The Italian coast guard intercepts a boat carrying 900 Syrian refugees and brings them safely to shore.  Human traffickers operating the boat abandoned it after setting its navigational instruments on a collision course with the Italian mainland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Reichsfuhrer may suspect that the war is going against the Third Reich so the elimination of the world’s Jewry- as well as homosexuals, Catholic priests, Gypsys, Jehovah’s Witnesses and communists- must proceed at full throttle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1993 Sunday: In the 81st Canadian Football League Grey Cup, the Edmonton Eskimos beat the Winnipeg Blue Bombers 33-23.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1947 Sunday: V. Vicky Mazarotti—a writer and chef at the AICP-END —was born to J. P. and D. C. Mendoza in Napa, California.  Elsewhere, famed rock-and-roll vocalist Rod Evans of Deep Purple[iii] was born in in Slough, England, on this date.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day Massacre 2018 in Tallahassee, Florida, gun control advocates, parents, teachers, students, and everyone else is demanding something be done to stop this stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2022 Tuesday K: Military Suppliers’ Stock Prices (Follow the Money 2) News- (1) Raytheon: $90.76 (2) General Dynamics: $211.16 (3) Boeing: $225.05 (4) Lockheed Martin: $376.54 (5) Northrop-Grumman: $401.63.  War is coming, buy your military stocks NOW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30. TODAY IN HISTORY—SUNDAY, JANUARY 30, 2022

A thread ⬇️ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t you love these ‘civil rights freedom fighters’ sucking up money and then pocketing it for their own purposes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1917 Thursday: In Washington, D.C., the 36th U.S. Attorney General Wayne MacVeagh died at age 83.  A Republican, then a Democrat, and then a Republican. he served under President Grover Cleveland from March 05, 1881, to December 15, 1881.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1830 Wednesday: The 22nd U.S. Supreme Court Associate Justice Henry Baldwin assumed his position on the nation’s high court on this date.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2022 Tuesday F: The Replacement Theory-  Republican Lou Barletta, running for governor in the Keystone State, told Newsmax that the Biden regime is flying flights full of illegal aliens into the state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile in Syria, Syrian government forces are cleaning out jihadists and other terrorists in Idlib Province as the government makes a concerted push to reclaim towns and villages from remaining rebels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Chiefs finished the regular season with a record of 12-5-0 while the Broncos ended it with a record of 7-10-0 and with yet another loss to their nemesis.  In the late game, the Dallas Cowboys went to Philadelphia to play the Eagles and gave them a good ass-whooping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The price of PALLADIUM is $2,493.40 per troy oz, +102.20 (+4.27%).  The price of Light Sweet Crude Oil is $49.87 per barrel, -0.06 (-0.12%).  Currently, one-dollar U.S. = 6.46 Chi-Com yuan.   Meanwhile, one-dollar U.S. = 0.81 euros and in Mexican pesos equals 19.88.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2020 Thursday: Fighting continues in Syria as rebels attempt to storm rebel positions in Idlib Province.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Note- Joe Biden says it’s long overdue to have a black woman on the U.S. Supreme Court.  Joe- how come you and your boss, Barack Hussein Obama, didn’t put one on rather than Sonia Sotomayor?  You guys had eight years).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1988 Friday: Jimmy “the Greek” Snyder makes racist remarks about black athletes and suffers job loss and exile from professional sports commentary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other foreign and overseas news, North Korea conducted a missile test today with the longest-range missile since 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WINTER SESSION 2022

BLOG POST #HASHTAG#,383 AT THE AICP-END

DAYS UNTIL ELECTION DAY 2022: 296

DAY THREE HUNDRED-AND-SIXTY-SIX OF THE BIDEN ADMINISTRATION

20. TODAY IN HISTORY—THURSDAY, JANUARY 20, 2022, UPDATE A:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1979 Wednesday: An Air New Zealand DC-10 en route to the South Pole crashed into a mountain in Antarctica, killing all 257 people aboard.n- 1982 Sunday: In the 70th Canadian Football League Grey Cup, the Edmonton Eskimos beat the Toronto Argonauts 32-16.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, Congressman Jody Hice, R-GA 10th congressional district, says that the ‘Dems will do anything to pass their agenda.’  Currently, the Dems are going after Senator Joe Manchin, D-W.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[…Island Gas Prices, Global Petrol Prices, South Korean Petrol Price, Fairport Convention, Chef Elvin C. McCardle,

TODAY IN HISTORY, THURSDAY JANUARY 27, 2022, BLOG POST #HASHTAG#,397, UPDATE A

PLEASE READ OUR MAIN BLOG POST, PUBLISHED AT 12:01 A.M.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1991 Thursday: Israel reopens its consulate in Russia for the first time in 23 years.   Meanwhile, freshman Congressman John Boehner, R-OH 8th congressional district enters the U.S. House of Representatives.  He would become the 53rd U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Harry S. Truman; U.S. Supreme Court Associate Justice Felix Frankfurter; U.S. Secretary of State George C. Marshall; U.S. Secretary of War Edwin M. Stanton; the Band featuring Stan Szelest; “Meet the Beatles” by the Beatles, “Mr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats around the nation are beginning to rise up because she promised to retire.  Most of them do not want her in power anymore no more than Republicans do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other news, reports of Omicron cases going up, up, and up have people living in fear.  Drive by any testing center and one will see lines of cars wrapping around the block.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1954 Monday: Future Acting U.S. Secretary of Defense Richard V. Spencer is born in Waterbury, Connecticut, on this date.  He would serve under President Donald J. Trump from 07-15-2019 to 07-23-2019 after which, Mark Esper would take the post.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once again, fascist Mayor Muriel Bowser could care little to nothing that BLM and Antifa trash burn down all manner of things from buildings to businesses or that they beat people senseless in the streets, but a Latino guy burns a BLM banner and goes to jail?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The American Institute of Culinary Politics-Elemental News of the Day #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[…election and then brags about doing so).   In other dire, economic news, consumer prices have shot up 7-percent over the past 12 months thanks to the ineptitude of drooling Joe Biden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, folk singer and far left activist Pete Seeger, 94, died in New York.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1656 Monday: The first Jewish doctor in the U.S., Jacob Lumbrozo, arrives in Maryland.n- 1742 Wednesday: During the War of the Austrian Succession, enthusiastic supporters elected Charles VII emperor of the Holy Roman Empire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1059 Monday: The reign of Antipope Benedict X- designated by us as the 154.1st Roman Catholic ‘antipope’- ends his brief reign on this date.  He first became pontiff on April 04, 1058, in opposition to the 155th Pope Nicholas II.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[iv] We obtain our statistics for the coronavirus from: COVID Live Update: 151,025,351 Cases and 3,176,405 Deaths from the Coronavirus - Worldometer (#URL#) (#URL#)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[…compared to the cases and numbers of recoveries.  What can we learn from this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fourth and final, here is the CONSERVATIVE LOW ESTIMATE for the number of illegal aliens roaming our country: 42,431,220.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Ayers, one of the terrorist group’s founders is a close friend of President Barack Hussein Obama.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[…Hong Kong Democracy Movement Killer, U.S. National Gasoline Prices, Global Petrol Prices, DOW Jones Industrial Average, S &amp; P 500, NASDAQ, Gold, Silver, Platinum, Copper, Palladium, Rhodium, Aluminum, Neodymium, Precious and Rare Metals, Light Sweet Crude Oil, U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The price of NEODYMIUM is $1,110,000.00 per CNY/T, 0.00 (0.00%).  The price of ALUMINUM is $2,946.00 per USD/T, -36.50 (-1.22%). The price of COCOA is $2,609.00 per USD/T, -50.00 (-1.95%).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Calvin “Silent Cal” Coolidge; Vice President Calvin Coolidge; Vice President Walter Mondale; U.S. Supreme Court Associate Justice Joseph McKenna; U.S. Attorney General Griffin Bell; U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At her website, you will see not only more original oil paintings but also lithographs, giclees, prints, miniatures, photographs, and even her award-winning instructional video entitled, “Painting the Southwest with Beverly Carrick.”  Beverly has been painting for more than 60…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1668 Thursday: King Louis XIV of France and Emperor Leopold I of the Holy Roman Empire sign a treaty dividing Spain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1939 Friday: Belgian premier signs the Burgos Treaty which will open up trade relations with Franco’s Spain.
- 1941 Monday: A new law went into effect granting Puerto Ricans U.S. birthright citizenship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s 15-month number by 92,429 Chi-Com lab-engineered virus deaths in ELEVEN MONTHS.  Joe has accomplished this onerous task in 373 days.  He promised that he would lockdown the virus, NOT the country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, as Syrian government troops begin pushing back against the ISIS thugs in Deir ez-Azor, retreating Islamists kidnap 400 civilians to use as hostages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[…in the womb.  Meanwhile, Dr. Ben Carson meets with Syrian refugees in Jordan as he swings through the Middle East.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2014 Wednesday: Brainy History reports that Shanghai and Hong Kong halt live poultry sales after the authorities report a third death resulting from to the H7N9 bird flu in Hong Kong; China has reported 19 deaths and 96 infections from the bird flu at the beginning of 2014.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1913 Saturday: The first enclosed sedan-type automobile, a Hudson, went on display at the 13th National Automobile Show in New York.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1969 Wednesday: Jimi Hendrix[iii] and Pete Townsend of the Who[iv] wage a battle of guitars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian and Syrian troops throw the rebels back, killing at least 50 Islamists dead and another 90 wounded while the Syrian government forces lost about half that number.   Meanwhile, in Wuhan, China, nearly 850 cases of the coronavirus with at least 25 fatalities are counted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2022 Saturday D: Stock Market Closes/Precious and Rare Metals: DOW Jones Industrial Average: 34,725.47, UP 564.69 points (+0.021%).  Next, the NASDAQ: 13,770.57 UP 417.79 points (+3.13%).  Finally, here are the stats for the S&amp;P 500: 4,431.85, UP 105.34 points (+2.43%).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1829 Thursday: In Salem, Massachusetts, the third U.S. Secretary of State Timothy Pickering died.  A Federalist, he served under President George Washington from December 10, 1795, to May 12, 1800.  He also served the nation as its 2nd U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2013 Tuesday: Chinese researchers discover an ancient human fossil in a cave near Beijing; the 40,000-year-old leg bone shows that it was related to present-day Asians and Native Americans, thus the Chi-Coms would have us believe that they have a claim to North America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1969 Monday: Authorities put nine Jews to death in Syria while in Iraq, Baghdad hangs another 14 Jews accused of being spies.
- 1973 Saturday: The Vietnam Peace Accords were signed in Paris.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1807 Monday: Future Confederate General Robert E. Lee was born in Westmoreland County, Virginia.
- 1809 Thursday: Author, poet, and critic Edgar Allen Poe was born in Boston.
- 1840 Sunday: The Charles Wilkes expedition from the United States discovers Antarctica.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2022 Wednesday J: Vaccine Manufacturers’ Stock Prices (Follow the Money) News- (1) Pfizer: $55.63 (2) AstraZeneca: $56.88 (3) Merck &amp; Company: $78.90 (4) Johnson &amp; Johnson: $172.14 (5) Novavax: $122.41 (6) BioNTech: $211.43 (7) Moderna: $215.23.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[…block.  As for holders of U.S. debt, after India the next largest holder of U.S. debt is Saudi Arabia 1 with $180,000,000,000 of U.S. national debt (it is important to note that these numbers vary every day with one nation after another jockeying for top position).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1860 Thursday: The future 51st Attorney General of the United States Harry M. Daugherty is born in Washington Courthouse, Ohio, on this date.  A future Republican, he would serve under Presidents Warren G. Harding and Calvin Coolidge from 03-04-1921 to 04-06-1921.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1099 Friday: Crusaders set fire to Mara, Syria, on their drive through the Holy Land.
- 1128 Friday: Declaring it ‘an army of God,’ the 163rd Roman Catholic Pope Honorius II granted a papal sanction to the military order known as the Knights Templar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1907 Wednesday: Charles Curtis of Kansas becomes the first Native American to win election to the Senate of the United States.  In March 1929, he resigned his seat to become the vice president of Republican Herbert Hoover.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2019 Sunday: In the NFC Championship Game, the visiting Los Angeles Rams stun the home team favorite New Orleans Saints in OT by a final score of 26-23.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAYS UNTIL ELECTION DAY 2022: 290

DAY THREE HUNDRED-AND-SEVENTY-TWO OF THE BIDEN REGIME

26. TODAY IN HISTORY—WEDNESDAY, JANUARY 26, 2022:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1861 Tuesday: The 24th U.S. Treasury Secretary John Adams Dix assumed office on this date.  A Republican he served under President James Buchanan from today until March 06, 1861.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, Britain and France announced their plans to build the Channel Tunnel, which now helps illegal immigrants from the Middle East and Africa cross over into Britain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1958 Wednesday:  Paul Newman and Joanne Woodward married on this date.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2017 Tuesday: In West Palm Beach, Florida, Butch Trucks—longtime drummer for the Southern rock-and-roll band, the Allman Brothers Band[iii]—died from a self-inflicted gunshot wound on this date.  The famed percussionist was 69-years-old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Covid-19 Deaths- Note: since Joe Biden became president on January 20, 2021, there have been 457,577 CHI-VI DEATHS IN THE United States- mentally deficient old Joe, by the end of the year, you will have tied the total number seen by the Trump administration in a year of…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next, the Biden administration has slapped some sanctions atop several Ukrainians who are reportedly working with the Russians and not with Kyiv.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20. TODAY IN HISTORY—THURSDAY, JANUARY 20, 2022, UPDATE A

A thread ⬇️ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor Justin Trudeau- as hundreds of thousands of trucks filled with tens of thousands of angry drivers followed by other freedom-loving Canadians (and Americans) descend on Ottawa, security officials whisked him and his family away to a hidden bunker.  What a flipping pansy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1935 Tuesday: Rock ‘n’ Roll legend Elvis Presley[i] was born in Tupelo, Missouri.
- 1940 Monday: During the opening days of World War II, Great Britain begins its first rationing of the following commodities: bacon, butter, and sugar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National Debt for today: $29,908,195,658,181 and the Democrats are adding TRILLIONS of dollars to it, not BILLIONS but frigging TRILLIONS.[x]  Cloward and Piven causing problems like they always do which is not good- those two bastards should have met their ends on the chopping…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brady; U.S. Senator Bob Menendez; the Guess Who featuring Domenic Troiano, the Kinks, Led Zeppelin I, Mott the Hoople featuring Terrence Dale “Buffin” Griffin, Heavyweight Boxing Champion Muhammad Ali, and the Rolling Stones featuring Mick Taylor:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their losses were appalling and each time the Russians counterattacked with tanks, they crushed the dead, the wounded, and sleds with supplies.  Still, the Italians fought on bolstered by more of their comrades still fleeing through Popovka heading west.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plus, George Wallace was a Democrat as was Bull Connor as was Jefferson Davis.  Dems are party of slavery, separate but equal, KKK, Jim Crow, cross-burnings, lynching, the norther Dems- Copperheads- defended southerners right to own slaves.  Someone must say this out loud!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that Mo has relocated to Israel, let’s look at the statistics there: 463,448 confirmed cases, 3,529 confirmed deaths, and 393,712 confirmed recoveries.  Here’s a laugh: Beijing stooge, Dr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Stinkbug symbol on CDs, DVDs, and Books means “approved by the American Institute of Culinary Politics-Elemental News of the Day” as well as adjusted or edited by the photographic editor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The German defenders were elite parachutists and defended every nook and cranny of the abbey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2022 Tuesday: COVID-19 Statistics for The Planet as a Whole: 295,585,822 confirmed cases, +2,621,969, 5,474,166 confirmed deaths, +8,263 and 256,116,403 confirmed recoveries, +772,060.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2021 Sunday B: We learn today that Instagram is FORCING ALL USERS to ‘sign up’ for the White House account to make it look like ‘President’ Joe Biden- the usurper in chief- has a massive following when in fact, he has NO one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2022 Saturday G: Foreign News-Overseas News I- As the trucker convoys full of freedom-loving patriots bear down on Ottawa, Canada, the government has whisked chicken-shit Prime Minister Justin Trudeau- a son of one of the Rolling Stones (most likely, Keith Richards or Ronnie…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let us look at one other part of the U.S., Veterans Affairs: they have 462,472 confirmed cases, 17,923 confirmed deaths, and 391,227 confirmed recoveries.[iii]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1969 Friday: Led Zeppelin[iv] released its debut album in the United States on this date in history!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secretary of Defense Leon Panetta, DS, says that ‘American lives will be at stake if Russian invades Ukraine.’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2009 Saturday: Israel declares a ceasefire in the Gaza War to be effective on January 18 while the Islamists do the same.   The Israelis should have killed more of this jihadist scum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Kazak government called on Russia to honor the Collective Security Treaty Organization, aka the CSTO, because protests over a massive spike in fuel costs has the country’s populace up in arms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2010 Wednesday: A week after the 2010 Haiti earthquake, a 6.1-magnitude aftershock causes further damage to the island nation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[…outlets.  Next, at a caucus in the Keystone State today, U.S. Senate candidate Dr. Mehmet Oz, GOP, saved a man who was experiencing some sort of trauma.  Good for you, Dr. Oz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[…confirmed cases, 80,064 confirmed deaths, and 7,896,990 confirmed recoveries (since California won’t report recoveries anymore, we are doing it).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, in yet another dagger driven into President Trump by members of his administration, DNI Dan Coats contradicts his boss on North Korea, Iran, and ISIS.  ‘North Korea will never denuclearize,’ Iran is a fine country and ‘not working towards the bomb,’ and ISIS is ‘not…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Third, here is the number of noncitizens who have flowed across the border for the past 21 days: 207,115.  Finally, here is the number for today combined with last year’s number for grand total of 42,561,756.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2013 Sunday: President Barack Obama undergoes his second inauguration in the Blue Room of the White House marking the beginning of his second term in office.  His second-in-command, Vice President Joseph R. Biden, also takes his oath.  In 2020, Biden would run for president.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next, Congressman Dan Meuser, R-PA 9th congressional district, anointed President Biden the ‘divider-in-chief’ following the president’s press conference yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[vi] Commodities Prices - Spot - Futures (#URL#) (#URL#) See this site for much of the economic information cobbled together at this blog.

[vii] (1) Currency Converter - Bing (#URL#) See this site for currency conversions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Australian Dollar, one greenback equals 1.43 and in Azerbaijani Manat, a buck equals 1.69 and in Bahamian Dollar, one dollar equals 1.0 of theirs.[vii]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2022 Thursday B: COVID-19 Statistics in the four states in which, the world-famous American Institute of Culinary Politics-the Elemental News of the Day employs chef-bloggers- California, Florida, Hawaii, and Washington- here are the stats, California first: 7,128,357…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, when combined with last year’s tally, here is where we are at today: 42,157,388.  Remember: this is a conservative estimate, not a liberal one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 817 Tuesday: Following the end of the death of the 97th Roman Catholic Pope Stephen IV, his successor- Pope St. Paschal I- prepares to pick up his Holy Cross on the morn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, it wasn't Tiananmen Square but give the Democrats the opportunity.  Maybe next time, they'll have tanks roll over peaceful protesters. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The price of PLATINUM is $966.50 per troy oz, -6.70 (-0.69%) while the price of COPPER is $4.46 per pound, +0.03 (+0.78%).[v]  The price of PALLADIUM is $1,917.17 per troy oz., +4.53 (+0.24%). The price of RHODIUM is $17,500.00 per troy oz., 0.00 (0.00%).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1919 Wednesday: In Boston, a tank containing an estimated 2.3 million gallons of molasses burst, sending the dark syrup coursing through the city’s North End, killing 21 people.
- 1929 Tuesday: Civil Rights leader, Martin Luther King, Jr., was born in Atlanta, Georgia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2020 Monday: At the Golden Globes, actress Michelle Williams celebrates her abortion before a likeminded crowd of liberal losers and activists.  What the hell is up with the Pro-Death movement?  Killing the unborn is the most sadistic, evil thing one can do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1964 Friday: Michelle La Vaughn Robinson—the future Mrs. Barack Obama and First Lady of the United States—was born in Chicago, Illinois.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, President Barack Obama gives a speech in Las Vegas in which, he celebrates U.S. domestic oil drilling (really now…) and says that the ‘U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beverly Carrick: The World’s Greatest Artist (1927-2012)

Pictures #HASHTAG#-1495

ALBUM OF THE DAY AT THE #URL#: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congressman Ralph Norman, R-SC 5th congressional district, said that Democrats are ‘avoiding toxic Joe Biden’ during his trip to Pennsylvania.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2011 Monday: All bullet trains in northern and central Japan temporarily halted due a computer glitch that affects thousands of passengers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Biden, please defend our borders.  Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, France increases the number of its troops in northern Mali by 1,400, planning to have a force of 2,500 or more to quell the Islamist insurgency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1922 Sunday: The 258th Roman Catholic Pope Benedict XV died; Pope Pius XI succeeded him.   Benedict XV served from September 03, 1914, until today.  His successor, Pius XI served from February 06, 1922, until February 10, 1939.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People screaming, “TRUMP WON,” and other things favorable to the president to give the impression it’s his people doing the rioting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elsewhere, in Nigeria- the so-called ‘religion of peace’- Islam, in the form of Boko Haram, carries out some atrocities in the town of Maiduguri where adherents hack five people believed to be Christians to death with machetes.  Crucify these Islamists… Meanwhile, the U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAYS UNTIL ELECTION DAY 2022: 313

DAY THREE HUNDRED-AND-FORTY-NINE OF THE BIDEN REGIME

003. TODAY IN HISTORY—MONDAY, JANUARY 03, 2022, UPDATE A:

Sandy “The Fly” Cortez sure has an inflated ego- the bug-eyed skank thinks Republicans want to sleep with her…WTF?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is time to eject this senile pretender from office and back to his Delaware basement, there to watch “Matlock” reruns sitting in his rocker, slurping up his Campbell’s chicken noodle soup while Dr. Jill dabs the drool from his receding chin, and dressed in a shawl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1981 Friday: The Associated Press ran its first story about two rare illnesses afflicting homosexual men—the medical world later renamed one of the diseases AIDS.  Meanwhile, the 92nd U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The price of LUMBER is $1,143.70 USD 1,000 board feet -45.00 (-3.79%).[vi]   Currently, Bitcoin, one U.S. greenback = 0.000028.  As for Chi-Com money, one-dollar U.S. = 6.34 Chinese yuan.  Meanwhile, one-dollar U.S. = 0.88 euros and in Mexican pesos equals 20.45.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1975 Saturday: The situation comedy and spinoff from “All in the Family,” “The Jeffersons,” premiered on CBS-TV.
- 1976 Sunday: In Super Bowl X, the Pittsburgh Steelers beat the Dallas Cowboys, 21-17.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National Debt and Gasoline Prices in The Four States in Which We Have Chef-Authors- Thanks to the Biden administration, gasoline prices continue rising and lowering by the day and NOTE- these prices are sans TAXES- in California, gasoline prices have moved to $4.637 per gallon,…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We genuinely welcome COVID Live Update World Meter for being honest in covering ALL the numbers- God bless them.[ii]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Democrat, he served under President Jimmy Carter from today until  August 16, 1979.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The next country on the list has the 92nd HIGHEST gasoline price in the world- Grenada: $4.822 per U.S. Gallon.[ix]    Meanwhile, here is a snapshot of the U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[iii] See United States COVID: 33,033,385 Cases and 589,110 Deaths - Worldometer (#URL#) (#URL#)..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[v] Commodities - Oil, Silver and Gold Prices - CNN Business (#URL#)- see this site for daily commodity information.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, here are the stats for Washington: 935,732 confirmed cases, 10,071 confirmed deaths, and 341,287 confirmed recoveries (same numbers).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1863 Monday: The War Department issues an order that allows Massachusetts to begin recruiting black soldiers to fight in the Civil War.  The 54th Regiment forms with black soldiers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elsewhere in the world, British rock band Emerson, Lake, and Palmer disband after ten years of working together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1944 Saturday: American General Dwight D. Eisenhower arrives in Great Britain on this date.  Planning would go into overdrive on Operation Overlord, the liberation of Western Europe from Nazi control.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1858 Tuesday: The 34th U.S. Supreme Court Associate Justice Nathan Clifford assumed his post on the nation’s high court on this date.  A Democrat, President James Buchannan nominated Clifford to fill the seat of Associate Justice Benjamin Curtis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TODAY IN HISTORY

THE #URL#

Chef Elvin C. McCardle, CWC-ACF

Ventura, CA 93003

Contact Me: venturachefEC7#USER#.com

TODAY IN HISTORY @ THE #URL# @ #URL#

WINTER SESSION 2022

BLOG POST #HASHTAG#,392 AT THE AICP-END]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1969 Monday: The Beatles[v] release their “Yellow Submarine” album.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 1908 Wednesday: Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority became America’s first Greek letter organization established by African American college women.
- 1915 Friday: Japan claims economic control of China.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 2022 Friday C: Foreign Covid Stats of The Day- Now that Mo has moved to Israel, let us look at the statistics there: 1,463,200 confirmed cases, 8,259 confirmed deaths, and 1,365,306 confirmed recoveries (somewhat the same numbers).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elsewhere, Russian military units are entering neighboring Kazakhstan to help the government crush popular uprisings across the country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[…$3.347 in Florida, $4.394 in Hawaii, and $3.954 in Washington state.[viii]    Let us look at one other portion of the United States: Tennessee- $3.094.  We are going to do something else that could be fun- gasoline prices around the world going from cheapest to highest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chase served from December 15, 1864, to May 07, 1873.  Prior to this, Chase served his nation as its 25th U.S. Treasury secretary.  In this role, he served his nation under President Abraham Lincoln from March 07, 1861, to June 30, 1864.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats like ET and me won’t be voting for any Democrats anytime soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senator Rick Scott; Soviet Leader Georgy Malenkov; “We Can Work It Out” by the Beatles, Def Leppard featuring Steve Clark, the Doors featuring Robbie Krieger, Elvis Presley, the Hollies featuring Tony Sylvester, Loverboy featuring Mike Reno, and the Nice featuring Keith Lee…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>