<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Obviously #USER# doesn't care about large families or poor people who can afford movie tickets but can not afford to tack on the huge costs of over priced snacks. ...8)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Titanium (David Guetta/Sia) 2020 Christmas Light Show #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# no longer bother to hide their #HASHTAG#. They spout this bullshit every day now. Yet they won't come right out and admit it. Come on, #HASHTAG#, just say it, admit it, you are racist.
(🦗🦗)
So. Cowards as well as racists. No surprise there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol! They never learn how to be unstuck. Just today, my Sugar (just turned 11 years) managed to get stuck to the red chair for the eleventy billionth time. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# - Photo by New Jersey State Police Mounted Unit #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Beauty #HASHTAG#Leaves #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# Not Furry - Photo by Heather-Chrysalis aka nocturnejewel aka Jewel Moon Silver Knight #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Since #HASHTAG# is a moron who can't even pull off a successful steal &amp; Putin has lost all face &amp; a lot of power, I bet #HASHTAG# is probably crying that he has no way to actually win (ie: steal) the next elections. Bet he drops out in the next month &amp; runs away. 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No worries. Thieves, grifters, &amp; con men will always find dupes. There are still a lot of morons among the #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG#. They all deserve each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Of course #HASHTAG# mocked #USER# even tho she raised $5 million to help people. Hating, insulting, belittling is what the GOP does. It's all they do. If AOC had NOT raised millions, more people would suffer. GOP is fine w/ OTHER people suffering. As long as THEY enjoy vacations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Beauty #HASHTAG#Leaves #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG# - Photo by #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what's the new big TV event? What TV show now unites us? 100,000 people USA-wide watching the new cool TV show? It's a far cry from the 125 million people who watched the final episode of MASH. And then talked about it together around the water coolers &amp; on the playgrounds. 10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No sympathy. I hope they ARE unemployable. There needs to be some repercussions for the #HASHTAG# who aided &amp; abetted trump's many MANY lies &amp; crimes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Trump &amp; his #HASHTAG# want to destroy our country &amp; replace it with what they view as an all-white all-male all-republican paradise: women have no rights to their own bodies, only approved white people can vote, all Democrats should be locked up, no one can speak out, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# If my memory is right, I don't think a ditto machine was the exact same thing as a mimeograph but I think they were very 
similar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because gee whiz those super poor Black people might be hiding a dime here or there. Not like those super wealthy billionaires. Everyone knows they're super honest about their riches just like Trump. And they would never cheat. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#  #HASHTAG#Weekend #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# - Photo by thethirstypug #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mom packed my lunch almost every day from 1st grade through graduation. Baloney on white bread sandwich &amp; potato chips every day because it was cheaper than the cost of a school lunch which at the time was 35 cents a day. If I was lucky she cooked a hotdog &amp; put it in the thermos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Supplies #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG#ueDeBordeaux aka #HASHTAG#   

Good night, all! Good luck with School! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Has any #HASHTAG# raised any money for the Texas relief efforts? Any republican anywhere? Any amount at all?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A year later we, Mom, Dad &amp; Aunt E, drove from Ohio to #HASHTAG# in CA. Mom &amp; Aunt each took a hand &amp; lifted me up over hot sidewalk at a Las Vegas stop. On the way home, I had a little "Indian" drum &amp; stick. I threw the stick out the car window at a kid in a passing car.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I grew up w/ a #HASHTAG# &amp; thought I was a #HASHTAG#. Then I had a 2 yr hospital stay &amp; after I came home, I started rescuing neighborhood strays. Now 10 yrs later, I have 7 #HASHTAG# (4 others OTRB) so obviously a #HASHTAG#. Here are Nixie, Sugar, Lucky, George, Stormy, Mishka #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm not sure who the original photographer is but it really is a lovely #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# logic: we need a gun to go grocery shopping because those foreign fruits &amp; veggies might spit seeds at us. But we don't need to wear masks because it's just good ole Americans spitting Covid-19 at us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Weekend #HASHTAG#Fun #HASHTAG#Bunny #HASHTAG#Egg #HASHTAG#Basket #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# - Photo by everyday_goats_life 

Good night, all! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Got my 2nd vaccine last Friday. Just as I did for the 1st shot, I went to every person working &amp; giving shots &amp; thanked them &amp; praised them to the skies. I praised their clockwork precision (I was in &amp; out in 30 min.), their dedication, &amp; their efforts to help the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol. I hoarded 2 boxes. Kept them in the garage but I opened the 1st box &amp; started to use the TP in December. Just opened the 2nd box. Now I'm getting panic attacks. I think I'll use some of my stimulus $$ to re-stock. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Completely boggles my mind that STUPID people GIVE trump $$. People are out of work, facing evictions, hoping food banks have enough food, terrified to die alone in a hospital b/c some selfish idiot wanted to spew spit into the wind. But those idiots give $$ to a millionaire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# By the way, I have not worn make up of any kind AT ALL since 7th grade which was 50 years ago. So there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Costume #HASHTAG#Fun #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# - Photo of Sugar Bush Squirrel by Kelly Foxton #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# - Photo by Love Your Furry Face Pet Photography #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Normal people show things they're proud of: their family, their degree, their awards, etc. But these morons show guns &amp; ONLY guns b/c the only thing they have in their lives that they're proud of is: I can kill animals (&amp; maybe people) from a long way away at no risk to myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG#  
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# 

Good night, all! And have a great New Year! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Weekend #HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# - Photo by Gentle Carousel Miniature Therapy Horses #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#:
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Wonderland #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#flakes #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# 

Good night, all!
Stay safe &amp; stay warm! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# - Photo by pugdashians 

Good night, all, sleep tight! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Weather #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# - Photo by Freida the Throw Away Kitty #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She's right! I mean, who in their right mind would ever take advice from someone who supposedly has money &amp; connections but looks like that. Maybe he thinks he looks cool? But that questionable judgement just cements the question.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Twitter is #HASHTAG#.
Presidency is #HASHTAG#.
USA is #HASHTAG#.
EVERYTHING is #HASHTAG#.
Sadly #HASHTAG# are too power hungry, greedy, hate-filled &amp; just plain stupid to realize even the #HASHTAG# would be #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I have checked out some of the virtual tours and, yes, they are very interesting. The Theban Mapping Project was very interesting but it was offline for a few years b/c of lack of money. I hear it's back online now but I haven't yet checked it out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Thank you. I think with our #HASHTAG# it's always a 2 way street. We may save them but they also save us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# 15 week old #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# - Photo by Warren Photographic #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #HASHTAG# will eagerly suppress the vote of one of these women if given half a chance. Guess which one the #HASHTAG# thinks shouldn't be allowed to vote: The talented Black poet or the white insurrectionist who wants to destroy our country #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG#  #HASHTAG#Weekend #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# Not Furry - Photo by Turtle Conservatory #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# While Sugar &amp; Stormy were healthy when rescued Mishka was so sick she nearly lost an eye &amp; Bindi was so starved &amp; ill that the 1st few days we really weren't sure she'd survive. People need to take care of their pets &amp; that means GET THEM FIXED!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# *Sigh* My #HASHTAG# want this. Sadly, my credit card does not. 😿😾😿😾😿😾😿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# LOL! I remember that smell! Friends &amp; I used a neighbor's mimeograph to run off the 1st &amp; only issue of our neighborhood newspaper ('60s). In High School, I ran off worksheets for Teachers as a student aide ('70s). And in College (early '80s), this was still taught to Teachers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have had some escape artists in the past. So I gave up on the door fight. Now, when I go in or out of the house, I go through the utility room into the garage then outside. That way I have 2 additional doors to keep the inside inhabitants in &amp; all others out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every Child Leaving Care Matters #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why are traitors who tried to destroy America being honored on American ground? Why should the people hurt the most by these enemies be forced to "honor" them? How can you claim to be an American patriot when you put dead enemies above living Americans? #HASHTAG# 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG#,
STOP LYING ABOUT THE #HASHTAG#.
Come on, just admit the truth: you're all lying, racist, power mongers. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That is exactly why #HASHTAG# will never support this. Have you ever seen a happy republican? Every one I know is busy hating anyone different from them, screaming insults, lies, &amp; conspiracy theories, &amp; desperately plotting to steal rights &amp; votes from their targets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I leaned forward in my chair to work on my laptop. Allie got tired of waiting on scritches &amp; climbed up behind me, so she's nice &amp; cozy warm between me &amp; the chair. Now she's snoring. Guess I'm not moving anytime soon. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have 2 black panthers of my own. Both strays, both approx. 1 - 1 1/2 years old, probably brothers. Little Lael came in last winter, Joey just a month ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# doesn't care if Americans starve &amp; are evicted. He doesn't know anyone who is NOT rich so it's like all the rest of Americans are completely invisible to him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# it's soooooo nice to know that there are Christians who believe in &amp; follow that "treat your neighbors as yourself" stuff. Big time #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I get my checks by direct deposit. The last time trump actually sent me his signature by mail. A completely unnecessary envelope for a completely unwanted &amp; unneeded signature. I wonder just how much trump's little vanity move cost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#:
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# mix - by Kristina Lynn Photography 

Good night, all! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#dy #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# 

Good night, Dad.
Good night, Grandpa.
Good night, all. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I love it when the #HASHTAG# talk to me. We have a supper ritual where I pretend I can't decide if it's time for wet food yet. At least one (I have 7) must either tell me to hurry or lick their chops. We never fail to have well licked chops &amp; lots of meows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is the day!
It's November 3, 2020!
It's #HASHTAG#!
#HASHTAG#! Vote! Vote!
#HASHTAG#BlueToEndTheNightmare 
#HASHTAG#BlueToSaveAmerica 
#HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG# 
This is your last chance! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Poor poor widdle rich people desperately need more tax cuts b/c the upkeep on 5 cars &amp; 3 vacation homes costs $$$.nBut hungry school kids don't need no stinkin' school lunches &amp; poor people don't need SNAP. Going hungry teaches them lazy folks endurance.n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why surprised? Trump &amp; his #HASHTAG# tore screaming children from the arms of their parents, imprisoned the kids &amp; sent their parents out of the country. What's a little pepper spray to people who hate everyone except themselves? Trump &amp; GOP love the sound of screaming children]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Costume #HASHTAG#Fun #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# - Photo by harlowhoff #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Weekend #HASHTAG#Fun #HASHTAG#Bunny #HASHTAG#Egg #HASHTAG#Basket #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# - Photo by #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The big difference between Democrats &amp; republicans. I can imagine MANY Dems saying this including former President Obama &amp; current President Biden. Can you honestly say the same about Trump, Boebert, Cruz, De Santis, McConnell, or any other GOP? So why do people vote for them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 😠 I has one call today &amp; tell me they were canceling my Social Security.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# HE has health care so what does he care about poor people. Maybe he thinks all poor people are Dems &amp; is hoping they all get sick &amp; die. 
What? He's a #HASHTAG#. There's no limit to how low they will go to steal power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# People can't afford food but #USER# Ole #HASHTAG# says there's no need to help working people with stimulus checks. As long as his rich friends &amp; family are doing fine &amp; getting richer Mitch is just fine with the rest of us going without food. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nope, not my party. Not even my species. I'm human.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#yDay #HASHTAG#Coat #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# - Photo by 2husketeers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thanks for the offer but I'm not the owner of this lovely photo. I just collect pretty &amp; interesting photos. Go to #USER# at Instagram for more of this lovely #HASHTAG#. I do have 7 #HASHTAG# but they rarely make an appearance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Phew. Who knew throwing a lying grifting traitor &amp; his worthless family out of the WH &amp; fumigating the nation would be so tiring?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still watch hours of TV a day. I thought I was well versed on modern shows. Until I took this survey. There was literally hundreds of TV shows &amp; dozens of channels  that I had NEVER HEARD of before.  6)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Costume #HASHTAG#Fun #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# - Photo by hankthekitten #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right now I'm crushing on The Affairs of Dobie Gillis, a bit of silly fluff with several cute songs &amp; a very young Debbie Reynolds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# - Photo by Paul Croes &amp; Inge Nelis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
I missed #HASHTAG# Day so I'm doing #HASHTAG#  May 21 #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# - Photo by Sugar Bush Squirrel #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# was probably trying to flush evidence of his many crimes down the toilet &amp; couldn't even manage that successfully. What a moron. Can't even successfully flush the toilet. Even bigger morons are those who follow him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Translation: Thank you for electing me mayor, you stupid chumps. Now, I'm gonna look out for #!: ME! The rest of you can freeze to death &amp; die of thirst but I got the mayor's mansion &amp; slaves...er...companies make sure I get power &amp; water if they know what's good for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They're so fun at that age. I used a pop-up cage for my stray #HASHTAG# so they could safely meet the other #HASHTAG#. Big enuff for a small litter box &amp; small play / sleep area. Their schedule; get up &amp; eat, play like mad for 60-90 minutes, crash &amp; sleep for 4 hours, rinse, repeat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So if they aren't following because they think you, just for being Black, must automatically be a crook, then why are they following you? Maybe they want some of what you're smoking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# claim that Dems are satanic cannabalist pedophiles. Yet again &amp; again they support &amp; vote for the REAL pedos.  Are they stupid? Blind? Maybe they believe it OK for SPECIAL republicans to be pedos but no one else. Kinda like they believe only repubs can vote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# For 30 years I worked at a local bookstore. For the 1st 15 or so years, we carried adult magazines. Whenever a snowstorm was due the men would come roaring in &amp; buy, not one, not two, but whole stacks of adult magazines. We always got a chuckle out of that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Such a lovely #HASHTAG#! Both the #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# breeds just look so stunning &amp; full of character.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Really pathetic that George's murderer felt that $20 was worth more than George's life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trump &amp; his #HASHTAG# repeatedly cannibalise his own henchmen. But some #HASHTAG# are so desperate to steal power &amp; join in on the trump looting of American that they'll take the risk &amp; help trump. No sympathy for Barr or the other #HASHTAG#. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So true. Ex-roommate always used to say I needed to make a budget. I always said: "Pftth. I pay the bills then feed &amp; pamper the #HASHTAG#. Anything left (if there's anything left) is mine."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Weekend #HASHTAG#Fun #HASHTAG#Bunny #HASHTAG#Egg #HASHTAG#Basket #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# - Photo from Nancy Rose #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hmm. So #HASHTAG# admin. was looking into places to set up #HASHTAG# for homeless people while ICE wants to learn "urban warfare".nSo how long before armed ICE agents start hunting those horrible un-American homeless people through the streets? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# McCarthy is #HASHTAG#. They're NOT known for telling or even recognizing the truth so I'll believe he'll meet with this heroic police officer when - rather IF - he ever does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Longest 35 days in history. Can't come soon enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
I missed #HASHTAG# Day so I'm doing #HASHTAG#  May 21 #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostume #HASHTAG# - Photo  by cupcakethefluffypom #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new movie reality is that maybe I have to stop seeing films in theaters. If I can not stand in line waiting on 2 people, I obviously won't be able to wait in a blockbuster film long line....16)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So which one did #HASHTAG# think was most necessary &amp; affordable &amp; urgently needed? Was it the CHEAPER one that would help WORKING people?
Talking about republicans here. 
Of course they wanted the MOST EXPENSIVE one that only benefited the RICH. 
GOP don't bother with the poor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Lovely, just lovely. But I bet all that fur takes a lot of brushing. I just re-homed a long haired #HASHTAG#. She's not ready to let me brush her yet. She's getting there but it'll take some work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I admit I said I would not be "first" in line to be vaccinated mostly b/c I don't trust anything #HASHTAG# had his corrupt &amp; moronic fingers on. That said, It's been months now, vaccines are rolling out &amp; people are fine. My vaccine appointment is Wednesday at 9:30 am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# We had a Woolworth's with a counter when I was a kid in the 1960s. I remember asking my Aunt E why all the ladies eating lunch were white but the waitresses were Black &amp; didn't they want to eat, too. The store was there for decades but they removed the counter in the mid '60s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stormy is next oldest at 4 years. George, a stray Ginger I adopted (now over the Rainbow) brought her home to me when she was only a few months old...3/ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, my Nephew &amp; his GF had it. Fortunately, he is an Army Medic (he was among the very 1st to administer drive-up tests back in the beginning) &amp; was already vaccinated so his case was very mild. GF is Reserve, also vaccinated, &amp; also had a mild case. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hmmm. All those people left trump's Insurrection Rally &amp; went straight to the Capital. I wonder why. Maybe they're having a BBQ. An innocent BBQ. Not a hanging. Surely all those "good people" wouldn't dream of attacking &amp; killing people just because of #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
I missed #HASHTAG# Day so I'm doing #HASHTAG#  May 21 #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# not impressed #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Gee, if only she would teach herself &amp; her children to STOP BREATHING and spreading their Covid-19 germs around we all would be better off. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's not to say I think we should beat them to death with what some may call callousness but I call reality &amp; truth. But a few whacks up side the head might actually help knock some sense into some of them. Nothing else has worked.
end/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well, #USER# is a #HASHTAG#. Just look at the way they all act &amp; hate &amp; try to destroy our country. Bizarre &amp; mentally unbalanced is a given for #HASHTAG#. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# Not Furry - Photo by Heather-Chrysalis aka nocturnejewel aka Jewel Moon Silver Knight #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# - Photo by The Itty Bitty Kitty Committee #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have 7 #HASHTAG# &amp; they follow me everywhere. I "go nap" &amp; 3-4 go along. I sit in my chair &amp; 4-5 sit on me. I go to the bathroom &amp; 1-5 have to watch. I go to the kitchen &amp; they ALL go just in case food magically appears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, maybe don't put your cat of dog out for a potty run. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Actually I checked several sources and there seems to be a disagreement as to whether it was reins, whips, or a lasso, or whether whatever it was was just the riders using it on their horses as they used the animals to corral people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Lael, Sugar &amp; Stormy taking a nap on my chair. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Got a call this morning: I was scheduled to get my 2nd shot Saturday morning but now I'm getting it Friday! Yes!! Can't wait!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really angry. If you want to refuse vaccination &amp; kill yourself: Go for it. The world will be a better place w/o your arrogant selfishness in it. But it's innocent people who die &amp; Healthcare workers who suffer. There's a #HASHTAG# then there's this #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why won't #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# vote for Disaster Relief? Well, Puerto Ricans are brown skinned so they're not human, Californians are Democrats so they're not human, &amp; Floridians are old so they don't matter. It's best to save $$$ for Relief for Billionaires. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Spitting? This is #HASHTAG# you're talking about. The dictionary has his picture under 'mean'. And under 'nasty'. And under 'hate'. He wouldn't just spit, he'd pee. In fact he probably keeps piles of Democrat bills in a corner in his office that he uses for target practice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# - Photo by Roman Reign Greater Swiss Mountain Dogs &amp; Lowchens #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sadly, Lucky went #HASHTAG# in November. She was always very wild &amp; constantly attacked my feet until just a few months before her death when she suddenly became my shadow &amp; glued herself to my lap. I held her as she died. I'll always be glad we managed to connect before she left. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have a Friend who used to have a Daddy Long Legs in an upper corner of his home office that he considered a pet. I prefer my #HASHTAG#, he hates Cats &amp; preferred his #HASHTAG# yet we've been friends for 30 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Exactly. It's Wednesday. If it's coming DD, where is it? It it's coming by mail, then why? And since we live with DeJoy Mail it might take weeks. Ridiculous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Beauty #HASHTAG#Leaves #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG# 

Good night, all! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The numbers say it all. All the #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# want to overturn &amp; steal the election &amp; insert their #HASHTAG# where he doesn't belong. What do they expect those of us who love our country will be during while they try to destroy the USA? We outnumber them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#  #HASHTAG#Weekend #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Meme #HASHTAG# - Photo by The Island Cats #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow! What a lovely #HASHTAG#. Is it #HASHTAG# or #HASHTAG#? The eyes &amp; face are stunning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sister just moved to Texas (Hubby got a job there &amp; she stayed here to sell their house). She asked me to move too but I said no. I've visited Texas 3 times (San Antonio, Ft Worth, Houston &amp; Galveston). Not even the prospect of voting for Governor Beto makes me want to go again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Totally agree! And all those military bases named for Confederate traitors? "Camp Eugene Goodman" sounds real good to me. A true incredibly brave Patriot. Those murderous insurrectionists don't understand the meaning of the word.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm a proud fire-breathing Liberal Democrat! I volunteer on campaigns &amp; everything. I even plan on wearing one of my Hillary T-Shirts when I go grocery shopping tomorrow. All 7 of my #HASHTAG# are also Democrats. I even have T-Shirts proclaiming 'Cats for Hillary' 😺😸😺😸😺😸😺]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#!
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Tree #HASHTAG#Lights #HASHTAG#Elf #HASHTAG#Reindeer #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# - Photo by owner Kelly Foxton &amp; photographer Colby Katz #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have that problem. Mine love to play in boxes but after 3 days the peeing starts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Looks like a lot of politicians who take their masks off to talk. One huge difference: at least she's not repeating lie after lie after crazy fraud lies like Trump and his supporters everytime they open their mouths.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# Graham wants to impeach VP Harris b/c she's:
1) Black (so she knows how to fight injustice)
2) Woman (so she knows how to stand up to men w/ little penises)
3) Democrat (so she supports our country &amp; our people)
All things #HASHTAG# hates &amp; wants to destroy. 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Wonderland #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Fall #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG# - Photo by viktoriahaack 

Good night, all, &amp; I hope you stay warm. Please check on your Neighbors. Don't forget to keep your #HASHTAG# warm, too. Good luck. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hmmm. My youngest, Brindle, who was a starving stray when she was a little #HASHTAG# less than a year ago, is full of boundless energy. She's the jumper of my furry family &amp; can easily clear a room. And she recently lost her best friend (RIP sweet Mishka). Gotta go check prices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Of course Kavanuagh is the real victim because HOW DARE Prof. Ford refuse to give teenage him sex &amp; HOW DARE women today get mad at him &amp; HOW DARE Democrats not hand him Merrick Garland's job. Entitlement Rules! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Special Snowflake republicans are so focused on their own specialness, fantasies &amp; hatreds they refuse to listen to anyone who tries to help/ save their lives b/c it might force them to actually live in the real world &amp; end their belief in trump's #HASHTAG# &amp; all their other lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# has been thrown out of office but he's still trying to loot our country &amp; steal as much of our money as he can. He'll never stop until he faces consequences. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Agree, but, many times I've woke up (either in bed or my chair) &amp; I can't move because up to 5 of my 7 #HASHTAG# are cuddled up on &amp; around me. Really bad when you need a bladder break but it takes 20 min. to get the #HASHTAG# to move. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just lovely! Your family is so lucky to have the traditions &amp; the skills. Merry Christmas!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# was never really the party of "law and order". It was never the "family values" party or the "moral" majority either. Their TRUE debased &amp; dishonorable colors are really showing now. Many of us saw through them years ago. But now even the morally blind can see them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# is enjoying himself immensely. He's busy golfing &amp; having a grand time at his own property &amp; forcing taxpayers to pay for it. And he's sticking it to GOP who won't support his coup &amp; Americans who dared to NOT vote for him. Winning! And #HASHTAG# voted for this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Spirit #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Costume #HASHTAG#Party #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Cub - Photo by Port Lympne Wild Animal Park #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No one ever said, "Hey, Republicans, you need to talk to us &amp; learn to accept our views." 
Frankly I'm tired of trying to talk to Republicans when so many are too stupid or too filled with smug self-righteous hatred to listen. And I'm definitely sick &amp; tired of
4/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Eventually #HASHTAG# will murder a Senator or a Representative. Why wouldn't they? Their orange god will probably never face consequences &amp; will continue to incite more insurrection &amp; chaos. Then what will #HASHTAG# do? Oh. Thoughts &amp; prayers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The school I worked at was originally in a rundown urban area then moved out to the country. I always stayed late in the evening. I never felt unsafe except for hunting season. I would zoom to my car expecting to be hit by a stray bullet from the war in the woods behind school.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Every month is close &amp; there's nothing for unexpected problems. I have a 25 yr old car, a 6 yr old TV &amp; a ducktaped laptop. But my medical bills were all paid by insurance. I know I'm lucky. But -]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Check out the aussie_freya Instagram. Most of their photos are lovely works of art.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I stopped doing treats b/c my oldest #HASHTAG# would throw them up. Instead I increased their wet food to 2X a day &amp; there's always dry food - until this week. I miscalculated &amp; we've had to ration the dry food. Luckily I have an emergency bag arriving today. But that look is the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What a little cutey! I have 2 black panfurrs, too. Lael is #USER# yrs, JoJo is a bit over 1 yr. They were both strays that I caught when they were still #HASHTAG#. They are probably siblings from a B&amp;W feral who has #HASHTAG# every yr but I haven't been able to catch her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I re-homed Allie a year ago. She also loves to sleep by my head. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah, boys will be boys &amp; white will be white. They're good boys there to march in support of controlling rowdy women &amp; taking away their healthcare choices. Besides it was only an old red man, nobody important. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#AndRobin #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# - Photo by thedappernapper 

Goodnight, all, and remember
"A hero can be anyone" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Of course Thune is "disturbed". He's worried there's not enough to benefit his rich donors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm 60 yrs old &amp; have several health problems including lingering effects from 5 operations &amp; a 2 yr hospital stay. I can not stand for long periods of time. I actually start to get sick. It used to be I could just buy a ticket &amp; go in... 3)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Especially if the conversation goes something like this: "Aren't you a pretty little thing. Are you lost? Are you hungry? Would you like to come home with me? I have nice soft Cat beds &amp; plenty of Cat treats."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just to clarify, I don't own the photo. That said, yes, it's a great, fun photo &amp; that pup is all round cute!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maybe Pharaoh. Or maybe Tut. His little white bib reminds me of an Egyptian collar. Congrats, he's so cute!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OooOooo. I've used similar cages in past to help introduce new #HASHTAG# but Bindi tore my last one to shreds. This brand looks MUCH better.

Enter to win a October 2021 Giveaway: Necoichi Portable Stress-free Cat Cage! #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes - Photo by beanbeanji  at Cat Camp-The Mini Indoor Tent for Cats #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not a near neighbor, but the house a couple streets over still has a trump sign in yard. Noticed last week that it was knocked over but still there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Congrats to you! And no worries: I was in &amp; out in less than 30 minutes with no effects at all. You'll do great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There was a time when I was considering whether Lindell's pillows might be worth the price. But I'm poor so I dithered &amp; never bought one. Wooo! I really missed the crazy there. Lindell is such a #HASHTAG# I would be afraid to catch it from anything he's touched.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let a Democrat open her mouth - Bad! Punish her!
Let a republican threaten to kill a co-worker - It's just a joke, no need for punishment. QUICK! Look there's a Democrat who should be punishment! 
Riiiight. "Rules for thee but not for Republicans"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flash back to Halloween!

Rock Out to This Metallica-Themed Halloween Light Show #URL# via #USER#://nerdist.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If the #HASHTAG# gets away with it betcha it won't be long before #HASHTAG# gives it a try. He's been boasting about it for years (shooting someone in the streets). Once he knows #HASHTAG# makes it OK, you just know he'll be all in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Rehomed sisters Bunny &amp; Allie last #HASHTAG#. They are both 2-3 years old. #HASHTAG# Allie got very sick a few months after arriving. But after 3 rounds of shots &amp; pills &amp; months of special medicated food she's skinny but as sweet &amp; loving as sister Bunny...4/ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG#2021 #HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# - Photo by Baggy Bulldogs, Cindy Lee #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Speaking of running away, where will trump run to when the (many) criminal charges start hitting him? Russia doesn't look too good now as trump's future home. They can't afford to gilt his new furniture anymore. The world will be a better place when the terrible twins are gone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# not worried abt white nationalists, thinks they're all good people. Besides they usually kill brown/black people or others considered not quite "white" enough. Fake-#USER# only worries when it's "his" kind of "humans" getting killed. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Gorgeous! While I love my 7 former stray &amp; rehomed #HASHTAG# (proud "mutts" one &amp; all) I admit a #HASHTAG# is definitely on my top 5 list of breeds I would love to have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Of course #HASHTAG# scrubbed all their traitorous tweets. Lying &amp; cowardice are the defining traits of #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Family #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#ss #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# - Photo by Carmen Harriman &amp; Baggy Bulldogs #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Poor widdle white boy. It's not his fault he couldn't keep his own penis inside his own pants. It's the fault of all those evil Asian women who followed him around, attacked him, carried him into their evil lairs &amp; forced him to have sex with them. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, but...but... most of those dead 180,000 were black or brown people who were probably just poor workers or old people who were going to die anyways in 10 or 20 years or Democrats in blue cities or states who wouldn't vote for trump anyways. n#HASHTAG# but not to #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oops. #HASHTAG# is having a hard time keeping all his many lies straight. Just goes to show he KNOWS he's lying, there was NO voter fraud. Except for the fraud he was committing. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Cruz is a typical #HASHTAG#. It's not enough that he deserted his constituents in the middle of a disaster b/c he thought he deserved warmth &amp; comfort &amp; never bothered to think about them. But he even puts himself &amp; his photo op 1st over their health.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#yDay #HASHTAG#Coat #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# - Photo by Max Ellis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Do Cats Like To Sleep With Us? #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, you know Black Women are always stupid because well, black &amp; women. But rich white guys are so special we all should march lockstep with them. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pence &amp; #HASHTAG# are still close friends.
Yep.
Because someone who sends morons to HANG you is definitely on my list of what makes a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So average sane Floridians are exercising their freedom &amp; rights &amp; rejecting the insane stupidity of a #HASHTAG# governor.
Well #HASHTAG# definitely can't have that. Wonder how soon #HASHTAG# will call out police &amp; National Guard to restore his absolute power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I'm sitting in my chair with my laptop. Rather, I'm sitting on the edge of my chair. 2 #HASHTAG# have decided to climb up &amp; stuff themselves at my back. Again, I'm a heat source. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans believe in Freedom. At least that's what they're always screaming. So far it seems they limit "Freedom" to guns, white people, rich people, and idiots who think they're horses, cows &amp; sheep. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I texted my Sister to remind her to set her clocks because she has a very important Monday morning appointment: She gets her #HASHTAG# at 8:10 am!! Go, Sis!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yep, there always is. Don't know what I would do without them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghans handed their country over to their enemy without firing a shot then cried for us to come save them.
Pres. Zelensky of Ukraine says "This is our country... we will defend all of this" &amp; "I need ammunition, not a ride".
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Took a nap Friday afternoon. Woke up suddenly &amp; couldn't move. 3 #HASHTAG# decided I was a nice warm heat source. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# What a lovely portrait! And so much attitude! You were so lucky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My Grandpa, who would be 110 if he was still alive, always said the best therapy was a "good, swift kick to the rear".
But the #HASHTAG# are such morons I'm not sure one kick - or even 50 - would help them reconnect with reality. They've fallen #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#yDay #HASHTAG#Coat #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# Not Furry #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did Newt the Moron really admit to this Anti-American nonsense? Making it easier for people to vote makes it harder for GOP to win? So GOP can only win if no one else is allowed to vote? No one else can vote but them. Seems to be the only plan GOP has.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We used to have "It" Girls, now we have a "Nothing" Boy.  Bet Rick cries he's being "canceled" &amp; "it's not fair". Too bad all the dead Native Americans can't complain about being permanently canceled by Rick's greedy ancestors. Bet Rick couldn't care less about "nothing".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I can understand the self pity after all he works for #HASHTAG# which means trump will never pay him &amp; he has probably ruined his career by trying to defend the indefensible. On the other hand he chose to work for trump so he deserves everything he gets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# doesn't have friends. He has victims, #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG#, brain dead cult followers, wanna-be ass kissers, &amp; those pulling his strings. He will throw all of them under the bus &amp; they will throw him. Trump can't even spell "friends" let alone name one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Weekend #HASHTAG#Fun #HASHTAG#Bunny #HASHTAG#Egg #HASHTAG#Basket #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# - Photo by schmitt.happenss #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If non-white people can't leave their homes for fear of being killed by Police, can't protest for fear of being run down by republican drivers, can't vote b/c their voting rights have been cut off then the #HASHTAG# can ignore them like slave owners hiding their slaves in shacks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really need to use "trump Mental INstability" because we have yet to see ANY sign of stability.

Capitol Select Riot Committee: We Will Investigate Trump’s Mental Stability #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#:
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Photograhy #HASHTAG#Attack #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#sInCostumes #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# - Photo by suzie_and_kushi 

Good night, all! Back tomorrow with more Sharks #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There's an old saying about a #HASHTAG# being able to write a novel if given a typewriter &amp; enough time.
I think that applies here. Given enough #HASHTAG# &amp; 4 years of corruption even these idiots stumbled upon a coup. Too inept to actually pull it off, but they did get the idea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So Dad worked 12 hour days every day. Mom worked 8 hour days every day (she had to pick us up from school &amp; take care of us until Aunt E got home from her work &amp; took us. Motto: if you want it you can do it (usually) without making your workers suffer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# Lael came in last #HASHTAG# &amp; is probably Jojo's older brother since I had seen him w/ Snowflake, too. Lael &amp; Jojo are extremely loving &amp; enjoy belly rubs. Jojo will put her paws up to be picked up. It is my good luck that I am able to offer them a better life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Thank you, but to be clear, this is not my photo. I just collect interesting / pretty pictures. I'm not sure who the photographer is but whoever it is did a lovely job (if I know the photographer I include it in the Tweet).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump will continue his crime spree until we drag him out of the White House.
#URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>