<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[At Harlem vigil for cops shot in ambush, Adams and other leaders pledge to shut down the ‘iron pipeline’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stalemate for Oldham as John Sheridan returns #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Change Moves In Pokemon Legends Arceus #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eir teams up with InfraVia to accelerate fibre broadband roll-out #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Suspects Charged After Police Shooting in Ferguson #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swindlers who conned British home buyers at Murcia’s Trampolin Hills in Spain try to overturn guilty verdicts #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogecoin is more than speculative elements: Shibetoshi Nakamoto #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia reveals whether it will relocate naval drills at Ireland's request #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the truckers: The men and women of the Freedom Convoy 2022 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft fends off record-breaking 3.47Tbps DDoS attack #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea launches suspected ballistic missile in seventh test this year #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coronavirus Conversations: What researchers have learned about the omicron variant #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RCSI scientists find potential way to treat secondary breast cancer #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joni Mitchell Joining Neil Young in Protest Over Spotify #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sources: Brady retiring after 22 years, 7 rings #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officials seize 16 tons of ‘contraband’ beetroot, disguised as potatoes, in Sri Lanka food shortage #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been 50 years since Northern Ireland's Bloody Sunday. The victims' families still want justice #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demand is suddenly soaring for electric vehicle batteries. Can Canada seize the moment? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spain extends entry measures for European countries until 06 February #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[REPORT: NICK CANNON EXPECTING HIS 8TH CHILD WITH BRE TIESI #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waterloo Region high school students are drained, concerned, and resilient #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two-Spirit activists on how LGBT+ community must champion the planet #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bella Hadid Opens Up About Constantly Going 'Back To Men And Women' Who 'Abused' Her In The Past #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like Neil Young, David Crosby wants to remove his music catalog from Spotify. Trouble is, he’s sold it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flights, Auckland Airport lounge listed as locations of interest #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do doo do doo-do… BN biscuits are finally coming back #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 priests, 2 lay people to be beatified in El Salvador #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen’s testimony reflects plight of children held in jails for IS group fighters #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bitcoin Raising High, Is This Another Trap as BTC Price Primed To Fall Below $30K #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covid-19: Prime Minister Jacinda Ardern in self-isolation, identified as close contact of Covid case #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-vaxxers hold emergency meeting to prepare new excuses, after provisional approval of Novavax #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christians must obey government is that really true? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Children sold for £150 to feed hungry siblings as women sell kidneys for cash: The horror of life inside Afghanistan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man died in Goulburn motorcycle crash on Saturday #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrong-Way Driver in Custody After Multiple Crashes in Las Vegas #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Naked Cowboy’ Braves Winter Storm in Times Square #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going cold turkey on Spotify « The Standard #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Croatian President calls PM 'Ukrainian agent’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghanistan's Taliban have started their first talks in Europe since takeover #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot Wheels Unleashed is Getting a Monster Trucks Expansion #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CHP officer cleared of wrongdoing in fatal shootout at O.C. homeless encampment #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Water-Sipping Showers Are the Next Luxury Buy in a Parched World #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britney Spears's Spitfire Spirit, Explained by an Astrologer #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gay NFL player Carl Nassib creates Pride cleats to support LGBT+ youth #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man accused of threatening to kill ‘serpent’ Biden #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gunmen kill Christian minister on his way home from church in Pakistan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nutritional imbalance could affect physical and mental development of Hong Kong underprivileged children, survey shows #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Viswanathan Anand to mentor Indian chess team for 2022 Asian Games #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Would Allow Arizona Legislature to Overturn Election #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Din Tai Fung M’sia prepares for Chinese New Year reunion dinners #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cop Impersonator Casually Tries Freeing Buddy From Missouri Jail: Police #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ratings agency Fitch upgrades Ireland's credit rating #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It should've been easy" – Becky Lynch reveals original plan for title exchange with Charlotte Flair #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 20,000 data center management systems exposed to hackers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vague guidelines, not lack of funding, blamed for Hong Kong schools’ failure to develop ethnic minority students’ language skills #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gamer Spends Months Building The Legend of Zelda Hyrule Map with 25,000 LEGO Bricks – TechEBlog #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘I dated Madeleine McCann suspect Christian B when she disappeared #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go! Go! PogoGirl – A dynamic, cute and wholesome PC platformer is ready to be enjoyed! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No plan to address asylum seeker exploitation #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indigenous people in Alberta get lower level of emergency care #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vega Baja councillors mix with world tourism experts in Madrid to increase popularity of Spain’s Costa Blanca #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[300,000 Russian Priests Were Given a Choice – They All Chose Death (Dmitry Smirnov Video) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seven-time Super Bowl champion quarterback Tom Brady to retire after 22 NFL seasons #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sixers fan who taunted Melo banned indefinitely #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethereum Price Rebounds! BUT don’t be fooled by $ETH Spikes #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had unusual Covid side-effect that lasted weeks after testing positive – my heart rate was through the roof #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I don't fall into male or female': AFLW player Tori Groves-Little on coming out as non-binary #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The New Yorker’s OUTRAGEOUS Climate Nemesis: Refrigerators #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ash Barty becomes a rare champion who is both loved and feared #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nurami seeks FDA, EU approval for soft tissue repair solution #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You Can’t Be Serious – Taking another run at life #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunderland sack manager Lee Johnson #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Pilar school to be completed by March #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris Eubank Jr vs Liam Williams: Date, UK start time, TV channel, live stream and undercard for huge British clash #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Military museum and library curator wants to preserve veterans' stories #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No New Girls; Cosby Talk (and Talk and Talk); Willem Dafoe Is Everywhere #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PICS: Latto Hosts 1st Annual ‘Latto 4 The Ladies &amp; Babies’ Christmas Party for Teen Girls &amp; Teen Moms #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Succulent Arrangement TikToker Has ‘JustSuccIt’ Trademark Application Opposed By Nike #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[November letter from Gaia to Aurora kepler #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honduras: Chaos in congress as politicians brawl over election of new president | World News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scan to scam? QR codes are convenient and everywhere — but there's a catch, FBI says #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American boy dreams of visiting Donegal after message in a bottle goes viral #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK-based fintech Everything aims to reinvent premium bonds with €2m raise #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweden, Finland on edge as old anxieties grow over Russian expansionism #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Conversation with Christopher Priest: The Comic Source Podcast #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Practical Programming guide featured in MagPi issue 114 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘And Just Like That’ Makes Way For The Explosive ‘The Princes And The Press’ Documentary On M-Net #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nibnibs Not Too Naughty cookies announces Booths as first retail stockist #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nick Kyrgios’s many contradictions make him a wonder to watch #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ukraine Calls On Russia To Pull Back Troops Along Borders Amid Tension #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seattle startup Stack wants to help teens invest in cryptocurrency #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SwitchArcade Round-Up: ‘Pokemon Legends: Arceus’, ‘Peace, Death! 2’, Plus Today’s Other New Releases and Sales #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia moves blood supplies near Ukrainian border – Reuters #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Threepio And Solo Back In STAR WARS? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFL reporter Amanda Vance takes dig at Brittany Matthews, calls on Joe Burrow to save them #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RUSSIAN ROULETTE: Boris Urges Putin to “Step Back” from Brink of War #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘SNL' Cold Open Tackles Tom Brady, Aaron Rodgers and Ukraine Crisis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Farming was his first love’ – charity livestock sale in memory of Cork farmer #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benedict Cumberbatch Addresses Backlash Over Gender Non-Conforming Role In Zoolander 2 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ben Simmons trade rumors: 76ers' asking price 'too steep' for Kings #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coronavirus is forever, Americans fear – poll — RT World News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Road’s End for Malaysia’s Reform Coalition? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Media Awards 2022 Scheduled for April 28 in RDS #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cambridge Fire, Ontario Fire Marshal investigate building fire #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beijing’s self-sabotage in the South China Sea #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia should recognise breakaway Eastern Ukrainian republics – Communists — RT Russia &amp; Former Soviet Union #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Directors Guild of America (DGA) Nominations Announced. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rejected by New Zealand, reporter turns to Taliban for help #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadal casts doubt on an Australian Open return after winning record 21st men's grand slam singles title #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Native American tribe's eviction plan raises civil rights concerns. Should US government intervene? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Editor’s Pick – Mark Prince: ‘Every time I lost, I became better’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Early evidence that boosters seem to hold up against Omicron subvariant BA.2 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US President Joe Biden To Send Troops To Eastern Europe Amid Ukraine Diplomacy Push #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shocking moment ‘footie fans’ clash in Glasgow as cops launch probe #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian coach questions ‘American way of life’ as he reacts to non-binary skater scandal — RT Sport News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow ‘Bomb’ Unleashes Blizzard On Eastern US, States Declare Emergency #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kardboard Kings Will Let You Live Out Your Card Shop Dreams When It Launches Next Month #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donegal Gardaí urge dog owners to keep pets ‘under effectual control’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Box Office: Spider-Man: No Way Home remains number one during a weekend with no new wide releases #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As DHBs Die, A Chance To Feed A Starved Health System #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MII to Host Webinar on Diversity &amp; Inclusion #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kody ‘Feels Betrayed’ After Christine Split — Will They Spiritually Divorce? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WSJ reporter Schwartz departing for new opportunity #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nagarjuna asks media to refrain from posting rumours #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clark Ca-Ca: Cooper Kupp Is Underrated Because He's White #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['We have nothing left': Snowstorm leaves Syrian refugees without shelter #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Explained-Scientists on alert over rising cases caused by Omicron cousin BA.2 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gavin Rossdale's new love (FemaleFirst) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Rafael Nadal’s wife Xisca Perello, when did Australian Open finalist marry her and do couple have children? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vigil calls for justice for Jay Abatan 23 years after death #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melbourne Backyard Floods After Severe Thunderstorm Warning #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omicron Hong Kong: ethnic minority leaders urge members to get tested as Sham Shui Po cluster grows, but chief imam warns ‘no community group should be blamed’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elden Ring’s director says don’t pick the naked Wretch class #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Carville Says Those 'Bit**ing About' Joe Manchin 'Can't See Political Reality' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL# | Town in Japan wants to eliminate all of its waste, so it built a stunning recycling centre out of trash #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Wingers Howl About Black Lady SCOTUS Nom, Pat McCrory Wonders How A White Dude Can Get A Fair Shake #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Create QR Codes for Audio Files in Google Drive #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Star Wars Games, Call Of Duty’s Future On PS On BJ Shea’s Geek Nation On KISW FM #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Historic nor'easter': At least 3 dead in New York; over 100K lost power at height of East Coast storm #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dynamic jurisdiction of ITAT, simpler compliance window being considered #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK assisted dying bill hopes to end ‘inhumane’ suicides #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A growing number of politicians run afoul of strict COVID regulations #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Europe Could Live With Less Russian Gas. A Complete Shutdown Would Be ‘catastrophic’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MFS hires Australasia wholesale head; ex Legg Mason local chief bounces back at Allspring; Makao adds analyst #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French unions fight for better wages in nationwide strikes #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No restrictions: Pubs prepped for ‘big weekend’ with 80,000 kegs delivered #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Germany's exports to UK continue to decline in 2021: Destatis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donny van de Beek loan move could prove Man Utd wrong on Bruno Fernandes issue #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The biggest comeback of my tennis career': Nadal celebrates after clinching men's record for major titles #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two-Spirit activists explain why the LGBT+ community needs to unite against the climate emergency #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Results are in: Pleasing results for Goulburn High School students #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parts of Beijing sealed off after two COVID cases found – a week before city hosts Winter Olympics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lisa Smith denied taking part in Syrian fighting in 2019 interview, trial hears #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFL legend Tom Brady will retire: Report #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remembrance walk for those killed and injured on 50th anniversary of Bloody Sunday | World News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Startup Valuations are Driving Company Equity #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 10 Best Saccos To Invest In Kenya 2022 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Beret(Rush'n Attack) – Highly challenging retro classic finally arrives on the Amiga as an Arcade(ish) conversion! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['We feel mistreated': Googong residents eager for new public school #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best THC Edibles 2022: Top Rated THC &amp; Weed Edibles | Paid Content | Detroit #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Florida Deputies Dead in Vacation Murder-Suicide #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National Insurance: What’s the new Health and Social Care tax and what will it cost me? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ramor Macra charity run in aid of ‘Be Buddies Not Bullies’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police make arrest after Manchester United’s Mason Greenwood accused of assault #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HP launches Z2 G9 SFF compact professional PC #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old Grannies- What Is The Reason for Popularity of TikTok Memes? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mini Metro’s First Big Update of 2022 Adds the Nanjing Map, New Achievements, and More #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto scientists are trying to crack one of COVID’s biggest mysteries: Its impact on the brain #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rule of law in South Africa protects even those who scorn it #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Super Sale: Get Windows 10 Lifetime License For Just $15 With Free Windows 11 Upgrade – Month-End Super Discounts Up To 90% #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rwanda to reopen land border with Uganda after three years as relations thaw #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students identifying as furries using litter boxes? Michigan superintendent debunks rumor. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday Thoughts: Atheists Preach No God From Inside a 4D box, More Pseudo-Science? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nurses star in Arcada’s free ‘Salute to Heroes’ ABBA show #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BetaShares prepares PIE wrapper as Aussie ETFs run hot #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wicker, Hyde-Smith, Guest call for Medicare telehealth benefits extension #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meghan &amp; Harry Join Joe Rogan Protest, Slam Spotify ‘Misinformation’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Jaw-Dropping TV Transformations Are Guaranteed to Have You Tuning In #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Than 200K People Sign Petition To Release Texas Brothers Accused Of Killing Stepfather For Allegedly Sexually Abusing Their Sister #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hong Kong Christmas cracker project teaches teens about business, gets ethnic minority and international school students working together #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schumer Vows to Pass Federal LGBTQ Non-Discrimination Bill #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran won’t release US prisoners as part of nuclear deal #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Texas teacher was placed on administrative leave after ranting to junior high school students and calling them ‘complete and utter morons’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ll Pry Fruity Swisher Sweets From Tim Neville’s Cold Dead Hands #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kandi Burruss Invites Fans To Watch Kandi Online On YouTube #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology isn’t ruining lives, that’s the Government’s job #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ben Stiller would love to make a sequel to Mystery Men #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadal comes of age with his 21st Grand Slam #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL# | Six-car Las Vegas pile-up kills nine #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OPINION: Why YOU could be the secret weapon against fugitives hiding out on Spain’s Costa del Crime #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transfer news LIVE: Chelsea line up £50m Raphinha bid, Bentancur and Kulusevski to Spurs, Van de Beek Everton loan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICC U19 World Cup, 11th Place Playoff, West Indies U19 vs Zimbabwe U19: Probable XIs, match prediction, weather forecast and pitch report #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black people have the resources to heal our own communities #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Joker’ sequel to start filming in 2023, and Joaquin Phoenix is not happy with the choice of lead actress #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ko holds off Kang to win Gainbridge LPGA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Russia invades, the Biden administration plans to hit Russian banks harder than ever before. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roundhouse Studios Job Listings Could Indicate Multiple Projects In the Works #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Jordan becomes new NBA meme with reaction to Hornets nearly blowing a huge lead goes viral #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2022 Sundance Film Festival Interview: Bradley Rust Gray and Carla Juri Talk blood (Exclusive) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School zones put student safety in to vision #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>