<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# OH. EM. GEE!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# was prepared to use the pen in his pocket to defend against the terrorists, had they breached the room Congress were barricaded in. People have looked at me like I'm crazy when I say a pen can be used as an effective weapon. I feel vindicated. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Guess he lied about getting career politicians out of there. Shocking. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$500? That's all? Nah, gotta make it higher so it hurts them in the wallet. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nuke. The. Filibuster. Fuck McConnell. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pfizer first round I didn't feel any side effects. Getting second round on Wednesday, so we'll see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm not Jewish, but can I get in on said space laser for her?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I was SO disappointed with those!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[O. M. G.!!! The teeny, tiny ears!!!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Pres Biden has already declared a nat'l emergency in TX, has generators &amp; clean water on the way, &amp; is already sending FEMA in. Fed disaster aid will be separate from the COVID relief bill. Doing it this way, rather than putting it in the bill, gets help to TX now, not in weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I propose a total &amp; complete shutdown of white guys just until we figure out what's going on. (Obviously not the good ones). #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Must be the small business pandemic relief money the Catholic church got. #HASHTAG# Also, we need to start taxing TF out of big churches.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Do basketball player fingers even *have* any ligaments left in them after years of playing? :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I have been kicking people out of the ATR before they even step foot in it if they aren't masked. Thankfully, the ATR I work out of is not on the main campus!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It does, however, make it easier to identify early on who is caustic &amp; who isn't, which is a handy skill to have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When VanDerveer found out, she did not seem mad. Instead, Williams says, their coach was “heartbroken.”  It was difficult to face—and since it sent the players back into quarantine, an even longer one this time, they had plenty of time to think about it." 2/x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Similar to what I just said to my mom in a conversation about this mess. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Who will pay it? We can start by rescinding the tax break Trump gave rich folks, start taxing rich folks at a more equitable rate, &amp; start taxing churches &amp; any other rich "non-profits" that benefitted off PPP loans for small businesses that were hurting due to Trump's pandemic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The look on this innocent baby's face for being accused of such a crime! :D #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a lot of things going wrong in the world right now, but this is not one of them. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Are they mad about your choice of mops? Or was there a movie/series live tweet they did not like?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# In Texas...that's a good bet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# But I've been told PT clinics aren't in it for the $, but, rather, to help the athletes. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If she was a white man it wouldn't be. People suggested Michael Jordan sit out games so other teams had a chance to win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep. pretty recently, but still taken off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wasn't he just calling for unity last week?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's been awhile since I've had a most splendid day, &amp; to top it off with a concert on the day her new record is released was just perfect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a load of crap, &amp; something needs to be done to fix it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# oof....hopefully this helps to right the ship!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very important #HASHTAG# update. Part bags 6-11, &amp; onto instruction book number two. My fingers may have no skin left by piece number 6000. :D #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tweeting about student loan debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Funny thing is, it was a friend/co-worker who asked if I'd ever thought about AT -- well, no, because I had no idea it existed. She told me to call the head AT at a local JC to see if I could late add his AT intro class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monkeypox. WTF?! Yeah, anyone who comes at me for continuing to mask can straight sod off. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# TV show, &amp; you can watch all four seasons on Netflix now. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look who's home from the hospital, w/a new nose, radiator, AC core, &amp; transmission lines! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great use of our tax $ and military resources. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ah, there ya go! All out assault on the allergies, FTW! Good luck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So fast they wouldn't even know I'd been there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It totally showed that you were actually loving that moment, rather than just trying to get into the heads of the Swedes. It was fun to watch. Congratulations on the Gold!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But...but...but...I'm sure anti-vaxxers, who are also anti-maskers, will be totally, 100% honest about being vaccinated when they aren't wearing masks. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make that a permanent position for him! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[William just did the "I'm not a racist" bit, so now we know it was him who was asking about skin color. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# said the same thing last night -- how it could've been an "Okay, it'll be a safe target because I won't be there" sort of thing, That hadn't occurred to me, but now I can't stop thinking about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How tf did I get on a call/text list for the fecking GOP? And for that traitor Dan Crenshaw?! I doubt they'll be responding to what I replied with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The moment cheetolini stole 2016. Actually, before that, because I saw the parallels to 1930s Germany.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Uppity?! Holy crap, do you even know the history of why this is so bad for a white person to call a Black person uppity? Because, damn, this is bad. And WTF does his making $800/yr as mayor have to do with any of it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nah, all good. I read it as an excited "I KNOW, SO AWESOME!!!" :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A topic that really, really needs to be addressed in healthcare. Good on you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Um...kicking them out gives control back to McConnell, because it would give Republicans a 50-48 majority.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The age old AT story! If one of us figures out how to mitigate this, we may win a Nobel Peace Prize! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yep, looks like a terrorist group to me. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Removing military personnel just as he's escalating the war in Afghanistan. Brilliant. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Oh, Nneka wants to participate, &amp; nothing else came up. She's now awaiting FIBA approval to play for Nigeria, rather than waiting around to maybe be called up by the US if someone gets injured btwn now &amp; the start of Olympic competition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# When you join a police department out of the police academy, you still have to go through in-the-field training. You're in a probationary period during that time, &amp; are evaluated by the field training officers before you are left to go solo. Basically, on the job training.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, he's just Ted Cruz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, so Trump got Taliban prisoners released, even though they killed US soldiers? And they were released yesterday? And he bragged about how well we're getting on with the Taliban? The day before 9/11?  Yeah, he loves our military &amp; country. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well, I think most of it is going to slosh out when she tried to lift that container when it's full.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To this day, I keep expecting the colleges &amp; universities to call &amp; demand back the degrees that were conferred on me. We won't get into how stunned I am to have been in my profession for nearly 30 years now. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Me, when 20+ track &amp; field kids walk into the ATR at the same time, all needing some form of treatment. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 57 here. I have toast or cereal for dinner quite often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But, remember, women's sports don't count. #HASHTAG# Double-edged sword for we Stanford WBB fans who are sick of hearing it every...single...year since 1998,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I actually wasn't really aware of N95s *without* valves, so I'll amend to say if ATs are wearing N95s, don't use the ones with the valves. They do nothing to protect others from COVID.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is definitely happening because of the vax. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Please tell me  you demonstrated, on him, how it was done! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For SO many! 1997 team, the sisters Ogwumike, &amp; so on, &amp; so forth. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In all the years I've taken photos at concerts, this is the first time I've ever had something professionally mounted &amp; framed. #USER# at Stanford's Frost Amphitheater, a week before I started a new job. Gift to myself when I got my 1st paycheck. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Costco sometimes sells "moving kits," which is a bunch of different sized boxes, packing materials, &amp; boxes specifically for dishes/glasses/wardrobe. U-Haul sells boxes &amp; packing materials, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So...no spectators because of a COVID resurgence in Japan, but they're going to let unvaccinated athletes come there? Good God, it is beyond idiotic to continue with the Tokyo Olympics at this point. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Exactly what I was thinking. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Huh...camera phones cause police brutality is certainly a...take. Stupid people are stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Was it as hot out at Stanford today as it was yesterday? I think it was close to 90 deg there yesterday. I nearly melted out at Frost Amphitheater. How's that for irony? :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to know how she had any energy left to let out those yells like she did when she knew she was going to medal! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And that associate head coach to her left? Kate Paye. Who was a freshman player for Tara the last time Stanford won it all. :D #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Why are you trying to take credit for something you voted no on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Everyone who declares war on The United Kingdom loses..."

The United States would like a word.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ya know, Andras, a tweet like this actually gave me a sparkle of hope. What a weird sensation. :D Happy holidays to you &amp; yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah, no call on that bloody nose. I thought the saying was "no blood, no foul," not "eh, blood." :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hell yes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I liked when they busted the Netherlands for it a little while ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Sorry, injured athlete, but I can't evaluate your injury because I have to keep wiping down the bench." Um yeah, no.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yep, that last part. That's how Schwarzenegger got in. He didn't even get 50% of that recall vote, but he had the highest % of votes on a very split ballot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And I see you conveniently ignored the part about how it would have a better chance in a standalone bill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They claim to support the military but they don't know the pin that signifies military family? Shocking. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's one of my places I want to visit. Gotta see those Northern Lights! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #URL# She's been livestreaming performances all pandemic. Today's concert livestream will be available to watch until April 11. Cost was $25, &amp; the $ goes to paying her band &amp; crew while they aren't touring during the pandemic. She puts on a fabulous show. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, you have a conscience, so, by default, you couldn't be them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Well, I know the wrestling &amp; men's rowing teams were out there cleaning it up. Point is, it was chalk, &amp; at least some of the involved athletes were out there cleaning it up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ya know, when I saw this video earlier, I thought "that looks like woman, from the gait, &amp; just the body in general." I would not be one bit surprised if this is a woman. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Today was also my first day back after nearly 2-weeks off. I got to deal with COVID mess all day, with some conflicting information thrown in the mix just for fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You know I bleed Cardinal red, but Aliyah just breaking into tears like that was gut wrenching to see. She's a special player.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SNOW 

Dammit

SNOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That's what I said happened to Dunn in that game v Sweden -- she just got left stranded on an island by her center backs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# So the trick is to convince them that ATs can provide that same care on non-sports movies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think this may explain my affinity for tigers. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching an on-demand CE presentation on concussions, &amp; the presenter is talking so fast, it's giving me a headache. #HASHTAG#!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Your keynote basically externally validated my entire career. Have been certified since 1997, &amp; have practiced AT pretty much the way you discussed. I'm guessing my background in Psychology may have something to do with it, but I also interned for an AT who had similar methods.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Gymnastics is probably my least favorite sport to cover, because it gives me mini-heart attacks seeing theirs heads so close to the beam, or falling from the high bar, or a badly missed vault. Always on the edge of my seat when I cover it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I've seen one of those up close &amp; personal with a couple of rugby players, although with one, the foot was completely facing the opposite direction as it was supposed to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I'm in a union. We're still adopting the new CDC guidelines, as idiotic as they are. Oh, and I'm a healthcare professional.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That entire CD is fabulous! Sadly, I will not be going to MT for her shows. I was talked out of it by my BFF, who reminded me about the Delta+ variant, &amp; how MT is one of those anti-mask states.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll always be with you...

Brandi Carlile. :D #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That was my same thought.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Finally, you, sir, are a perfect example of what OG was posting about. Just had to center yourself, rather than saying nothing and just considering what she had to say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nah, we get to see highlights from South Carolina v Texas instead. Stanford getting no respect is nothing new.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to all the new ATCs! Welcome to the BEST PROFESSION EVER!!! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Innocent. That looks like it just up and spontaneously exploded on its own. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Aw shucks. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I just dozed off in the middle of my second one. LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What a difference a little love, nurturing, &amp; the correct food can make! They are precious!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# WTF?! Yet another reason to keep the feet firmly planted on land! Don't get me wrong, I love the ocean, but I do not go IN the ocean. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been telling y'all. pay attention to who around you isn't wearing a mask...and steer TF clear of them! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When I'd travel a lot with teams, gone anywhere from 1-3 weeks, I missed my cats horribly. Those little fur brats had me wrapped around their paws.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem is the assumption that the far left is on "our side." They have more in common with Trumpists/GOP than they do with me/(actual) Dems. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# 1. We can integrate immigrants? How about let immigrants integrate if they want, but let's not force that. That is historically a horrific thing the US has done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "To my surprise, my head injury was more concerning than my shoulder/arm injury." Yep, head injury w/vomiting is WAY more concerning than a shoulder/arm injury. Glad she made it to the next checkpoint, where there were ppl who could help, &amp; glad she's on the mend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER#'s answer re: EBP had me yelling "Yes! Thank you!" at my computer! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hope everything turned out okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Exactly. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just one of the many reasons I love this show, because #HASHTAG# &amp; everyone involved with #HASHTAG# knows that, &amp; was invested in getting it right. Also, if you haven't seem Cam's edits, go check them out. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm DI now. This will be the first time I get more than 2 days off. High schools, clinic/outreach, etc, I only ever got Xmas day and NY day off. Xmas Eve &amp; NYE were 1/2 days. Granted, I work w/sports that are not in season, but still...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, no he can't. Please learn about how our government works, particularly since you're a part of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have it on DVD, but I haven't been able to watch it since I saw it in the theater, even though it was so well done, &amp; Hillary Swank just nailed the role.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure...but let's be real here, I don't put up with crap, &amp; that tends to make me single. :D #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# *whispers* brachial plexus nerve bundle :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# People have gotta stop putting this stuff out into the universe, yo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Use a cat filter, &amp; you can charge more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's what I mostly started doing this past year. Also, I turned off RTs of some of the people I follow, because all the stuff they RT is stuff I'm hoping to mostly avoid &amp; get dragged into.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I knew it straight away when I saw this pic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Safe travels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because you're an Athletic Trainer. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Congratulations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We'll have one again in 10-days. That position has been vacant since 1/20/2016 at 12noon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White folks equate privilege with money/possessions. Can't even count how many times I've told other white folks that's not what white privilege is referring to at its most basic. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait...Kiana gets butt checked to the ground, &amp; the foul is on her? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He has the greatest military mind you know? Knows more than the generals &amp; such. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My eyes nearly roll out of my head when I see anyone going off about trying to primary WV's Manchin with a leftist. Have these people never been to WV? Or even so much as met someone from WV?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# C'mon now, you don't expect them to do something different, do you? It is the women's NCAA tourney, after all. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No. We already pay gas taxes &amp; registration fees that are supposed to pay for infrastructure things. This penalizes people who can't live close to where they work, &amp; who do not have access to other transportation. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 3 hrs of redialing, I finally got through to the #USER#. I was on hold maybe 15 minutes before I was able to talk to an actual person. I have now been on hold for at least 1.5 hrs, waiting to be connected to someone to manually enter my extension info. 1/x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Um...please re-read what I replied. I was agreeing with her. That's what "This! SO MUCH THIS!" means. I was in no way suggesting SHE wasn't vaccinated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Huh...who knew that a program that was created to rate women would turn out to be so scummy? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMFG...now can the #HASHTAG# stay on sides from here on out? Pretty please? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Also, the Sparks have the Sisters Ogwumike, who know how to compete against Brittney Griner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Congratulations on the early finish! I'm usually scrambling the last few hours. LOL #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pretty sure some may have been.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have to say, it's a really nice feeling to wake up, &amp; not have my first thought be "well, WTF did that asshole do today, &amp; are we at war with someone new yet?" I could totally be fine living like this the rest of my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes. Paper towel stops the grease before it hits the jar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hey, DC residents, Mike here says you don't deserve representation. I guess that means y'all don't have to pay taxes now. Not like we went to war or anything with some country over that taxation without representation thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really wish they hold off on these Federal charges until Biden's sworn in. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bill Barr is full of shit. Trump has been fomenting insurrection long before yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stopped listening to people telling me what I should do, &amp; started living my own damn truth. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# OMG typo...another hour &amp; (now) 7 minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, so Trump got Taliban prisoners released, even though they killed US soldiers? Yeah, he loves our military. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nneka hasn't been critical of USA Basketball, but said that when she didn't make the U.S. team, she didn't want to wait on the possibility of perhaps being called on as an alternate...She's been in that position before &amp; said she doesn't see herself as a "second choice."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I was thinking allergy attack -- sneeze all over it. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Damn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Bucky is living his best life! Yay Bucky!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Just a lil strawberry...rub some dirt on it..."

OMG...I love this kid!!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah, I've been a Sports Medicine professional 25+ years, with the bulk of that covering rugby. It's mind boggling what concusses some athletes, but not others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you've never seen this show, your opportunity to rectify that is here! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I know how that trying to type/think pre-fully caffeinated is!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, we really don't need to wonder. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep. Way too many times to count, including some of my family. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep, cheetolini is really helping our military &amp; their families. #HASHTAG#  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Y'all did yourselves proud, Coach. Aari's last shot could've just as easily gone is. I thought it was going to. That it was so close w/her being guarded by 3 players, &amp; her being off balance...well, everyone knows it could've gone either way. Y'all put everyone on notice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Someone told me "They just just pull Trump out now!" Sure, then Dems are the ones overthrowing our government, so no, that won't work. Now, if he attempts to seize power come Jan 20, then he can be pulled out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And, no, I'm not saying that's all undocumented people do. They contribute in many different ways, &amp; they pay taxes here, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah, no, I don't do "local" group BS. If I won't socialize with them IRL, I won't socialize with them on FB, &amp; I stay to myself here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yes, I know how hospitals work, thanks. Never said I resented anyone, but there's got to be a better solution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh, now that is a gooooood stretch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# PRESIDENT Biden is using Executive Orders to reverse the hideous EOs that Trump signed. So it was okay for Trump to govern that way, but not for Pres Biden to? GTFOH with that, &amp; do fuck all the way off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raise the pay, implement protections from COVID, stop treating employees like crap, offer paid sick leave, don't undercut hours. Simple enough fixes, but business owners just want to blame something/someone else. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I absolutely love where I work now. Even with COVID hell these past 3-weeks, I wouldn't trade it for anywhere else. 

And good job on the basketball coach! #HASHTAG#! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not being alarmist if it's clearly spelled out, &amp; you just point out what's up. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# When I fly R/T, I routinely check-in to my flights the day before, &amp; unless I check baggage, I skip the whole check-in line. Could've been the case, or the no-fly list was updated after they checked in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Aaaannnnd my brain just went into "Huh, what are the factors that would go into a study like that?" Then proceeded to think of a few factors. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Anyone but white folks are lazy, remember? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There was a bomb threat at another Bay Area high school a couple hours ago, too. WTH? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Kind of like how we used to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No, Ford *literally* never won a national election. He wasn't even elected as Nixon's VP. He was appointed VP, via the 25th amendment, after Spiro T. Agnew resigned as VP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's truly mind boggling to me, but then again, I never hated myself for being queer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ah, I new that conservative POS was still in there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTF, Georgia?! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "Is the person who is supposed to be doing that job having a difficult time with it?" *adjusts halo*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No, they're not. Fractured sternum is much more serious, &amp; can take up to 8-weeks before healed enough for her to play. Her game fitness will also be affected in terms of cardio. With a knee injury, Nneka should be able to keep her cardio close to game fitness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I hope you told whoever told you that to piss off &amp; mind their own business, that you will grieve in your own way &amp; time. There is no timeline for grieving. None.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am so happy I can avoid people, both because not working right now due to COVID shutting down my job, &amp; because I don't live near people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'd move there or Ireland in a heartbeat. Pretty sure I could find work in rugby either place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# American History Month? If he doesn't like Black History Month, I really don't think he'll like American History Month.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Nah, the country definitely does not need the normalization of freaking Nazis like Gaetz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found a bottle of garlic powder that I'm pretty sure had become petrified. I was going to dump the contents, then clean &amp; reuse the bottle, but it was so solid, I couldn't break it up at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It will come as no surprise that I was the "troublemaker" at that clinic. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There *is* nothing quite like a well executed dump tackle. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My first thought was "And this teacher is still alive?" Second was "Not fired?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It's not at all debatable if Nneka should've made the roster for Tokyo, unless she's not responding well to rehab for the injury, &amp; her athletic trainer would've been able to update USA Basketball on her progress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah, but the women got socks &amp; an umbrella. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yeeaaahhhh...don't get me started on CA's antiquated power system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I'm in CA, so I tend to agree, but it has to be a consideration.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>