<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Awww thanks! All hugs gratefully received! ðŸ˜Š xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I gave up ... he's like a dog with a bone ... I do love him though! ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well of course ... I'm Scottish ... I shouldn't have an opinion!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol We got a sneaky/lucky try at the end! It was nearly much worse!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's the weather .... and there will be high winds in the 'north of Britain' ... isn't that called Scotland? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol I have to say I love it ... but it is a bit bizarre! It'll all come out in the wash as they say!! You can tell I'm easily amused eh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah! They're cute and full of enthusiasm! I like it! ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Travelodge!! trust me I was a receptionist there! You'd be lucky to get a clean mattress protector! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aren't we going to have to wait to see how Covid is before we have big parties for the Queen's jubilee? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Haha! it's a bit like mashed up Irish stew with extra tatties! I'd eat them any way though! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a weird way to organise a jury! Only in America! ðŸ™„ #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's turning into a day where we can show our love for anyone and why not!! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh you wee souls!! ...Yes I'm watching...just for a laugh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ooo I can't get enough of this! It's arrogant of us to think we are the only intelligent life. Just say the word 'infinity' ... that's mind boggling!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think Colin Pitchfork really wanted out of prison! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yay!!!! I love that bit ... that's better than coffee to wake me up!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well the independence voice is huge! Don't hear much noise from you! I'm assuming... though correct me if I'm wrong ... you're a unionist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh I just remembered something else disgusting about you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And all the best to the happy couple ... obviously! ðŸ˜ŠðŸ¥‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I might just do that ... sharing obvs cause I'm a shit eater! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I just need to know what other things I can watch while it's on! Not my thing ... just got bored with it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bet you wish you'd never posted that now! haha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's very important to me! I have to go in to hospital Saturday, Sunday and even more importantly next Wednesday!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol of course the river Clyde is going to be the worst river for sewage in Britain!! ðŸ™„ #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're are lucky there! she is a star and so composed! Can't wait to see her WIN!! ðŸ˜Š #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God -4 tonight!! My heating bill is going to be sky high!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are that woman's friends? 
She shouldn't have been allowed on telly! I found that quite exploitative! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG! they spent half the prog on Scottish Indy!! ...what a waste of time... !! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IMHO honours should be given to people who have proven through hard work they deserve them! None of this wishy washy 'here's an award for sneezing' #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Tory gov and every Tory gov suck up each others bums .... it's embarrassing! The world is laughing at those who voted them in! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There's nothing middle class about Storm! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's true ... there's no fool like an old fool!! ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Never touch them with a ten foot bargepole .... scummy shitholes!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh noooo can't do Eastenders! I like a wee bit of humour in my soaps! Do you watch River City?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thanks! First session so was a bit scared! Went fine though and very quick! ðŸ˜Š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love how #HASHTAG# is obsessed by #USER# and Scotland's approach to Covid!! Boy we really get on their nerves!! Small population ... huge voice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberty X - Just a little HD #URL# via #USER#  I'm dancing for #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes it is good for me cause it's better than nothing! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hahaha yeah I bet I am!! lol #HASHTAG# Yes ok ok you are the best lads on twitter!! lol xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm wondering when someone is going to be harassed for continuing to wear a mask! It's bound to happen!! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't handle this guy today on #HASHTAG# .... I'm off!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# oooops! I hope you're not offended!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've only got the basic freeview channels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James... the best way to look after the vulnerable is for everyone to take responsibility!! Just be sensible and not selfish! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apostrophes are essential! I try hard but I do get confused! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the hell did England vote in these up themselves public school boys? #HASHTAG# ... get it right next election England! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You know it is ... it's the best seat in the house!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Obviously they don't trust the government's recommendations! Who would?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She took the opportunity to save herself and her 4 girls. It's a pity she didn't have the courage to get Billie-Jo out too. ... which I totally get. I hope they've found some peace!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He probably thought lightning wouldn't strike twice in the same place! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ofgs!! Spare us!! Boris couldn't give a shit ... there is no opposition and fine he knows it! He's laughing up his sleeve! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I might be blinded but in my personal predicament health wise I'd rather people wore them! I feel safer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What parent was home minding the kids the night before Mathew died? Nobody asks these questions! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The people responsible for the cladding are the people who passed the health and safety checks! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I do have some and I get by on them. Had my last chemo and on to radiotherapy on 1st march. I'm hoping that won't be so invasive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Och they'd only do one gig here anyway!! in the back of beyond Scotland!! lol xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm watching too much news! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wouldn't wish ill on anyone ... trust me but there's no such place as an ivory tower!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where do they get this 'average' household income of Â£27k from? Cloud cuckoo land? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creme Egg no.2 done .... 1 to go! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It gives them thinking time before they say the load of crap they're going to say! Why bother ...just get on with it! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ofgs Yasmin ... clip your wings just a bit eh!! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I tried looking on Playstore but they were similar but not the same game. I'm ok thanks. Taken 2 wks to get over my last chemo. Hefty stuff. I start radiotherapy on the 1st. God knows what that will bring but there is no alternative!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# *gasps* How very dare they steal you're 15 mins of fame!! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha!! Carole Malone ....  So funny she wastes so much energy hating us!! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Billy Connolly tonight at 9.30 #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sarcasm in this case is not very helpful. Some of us recognise Putin as a new Hitler ... this could escalate so far we need to be worried!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do people want to interfere in other people's lives? I have so much shit going on in my little life, I don't have the time or headspace! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No I have to say I am very distracted atm! I'm relying on you lot to keep us moving forward! ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Going through the same Janey! I feel your pain! All the best to all of us in the same boat! ðŸ˜ŠðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I will cope! it really helps to have lots of support and especially from you who has been there and done that! Thank you! ðŸ™ It means a lot! ðŸ˜Šâ¤ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have I missed something? Why has Alex Salmond suspended his show?  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is! lol I don't know how people end up so totally delusion!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol I think our soh comes from the same place! and all the lowest forms of wit! But funny all the same!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a beautiful sunny day in Perth and the wind has died down!! ðŸ™‚ðŸŒ‚ðŸŒž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to continue to be sensible and set an example to this asshole gov! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Simon - You Can Call Me Al (Lyrics) #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahhh never mind Alby! We'll see you on stage in the West End! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awwww! We all cry at Auld Lang Syne!  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No you're right there Boris the UK is not corrupt .... but Westminster IS!! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeremy would throw you in jail just for owning a car if he could!! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last RT appointment today for 2 weeks ... ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people don't like Adele's lyrics because they tell the truth! ... and the truth often hurts! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well they must've thought you were worth talking to! I tried to get on bbcqt when it was in Perth! I think they check your Twitter first! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Thanks Sheree! x Have a great weekend folks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh you're a clever boy!!! lol ... and i'm sure you would never deny your mum that pleasure when she's around!! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's face it Boris was expecting an easy ride as PM ... then up popped Covid to prove he was never capable of the job in the first place! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's cause I'm a smart ass! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes haven't seen tonight's though so no spoilers! I actually managed it to McDonalds, Asda and the pub!! #HASHTAG# lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh well she would know! #HASHTAG# haha!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes yes yes!!! Teach the children BSL instead of German or French! Everyone should be able to use it! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah that would be fun to watch! I don't like him ... he ooozes arrogance!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh shouty man Mike Parry tomorrow! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Best way to avoid having cats in your garden is to get a cat!! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The moral of the story is ... don't employ a kid to look after your kids! Most people do cause they're cheap labour!! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't like alternative and sarcastic comedy ... don't watch #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol I'm not moving till Tuesday now!! ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe in the 21st century this in Ukraine is happening! It's like the dark ages!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pandemics will become endemic! If you think Covid is the last you're wrong! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where the hell is your support worker Chesney? Get one and get all the benefits you are entitled to! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Haha! Yes he has to mention the 'penthouse' at least once! I live in a penthouse (top floor) but I don't brag about it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And yet they're saying you have to get a job in 4 weeks regardless of where it is!! You can't exactly bike to Glasgow and back every day! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rocco just can't paint but he has to make a living off his parents fame! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catalonia stands with Scotland and vice versa! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol What a disaster .... do we cancel Christmas now too? 
Tbh I've just been to the theatre to see Dirty Dancing ... #HASHTAG# Lets see what my Covid test says later today! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The winner takes it all!! #HASHTAG# 
Probably best ever song!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Look I've got chemo brain! I'm allowed to want world peace before I die!! What's your excuse! lol ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol I can be a bit sick....joke wise! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ouch serious coercive control going on here! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Haha! Typically it would backfire on me and I'd live forever!! ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I get where they're coming from but that's when dealing with normal people! He's the 2022 Hitler and we're letting him get on with it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin knows the world won't enter into #HASHTAG# and that gives him carte blanche! He'll take full advantage of that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And you can shut up too Stephen Kerr! Away and get your own party in order! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If they'd had Nigel Harman in Peaky Blinders I'd have watched it! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Morning CG! Lovely to see the sun! Spring is on it's way!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Before my chemo I could taste but swallowing was agony ... now I can swallow but it tastes disgusting! What is your condition ... it sounds horrible too. â¤ xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hasn't been bad here Terry and it's a beautiful sunny morning! Have a good day! ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...a loan then? ...I can't afford the flight!! hahaha! eh!! xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching 'Married at First Sight Australia' and the prize dick has already arrived! He doesn't need a wife ... he has himself! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think what they should've done was say a care home or any NHS worker would not from now be employed unless vaccinated! They're already short staffed ... it's a worry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ðŸ˜± Nooooo!! Not tuna as well as chicken crisps!! Please not prawns next or I'll starve!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We're doing ok but in my position I need to feel safe! I don't find it such a big deal to wear a mask.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Admitting to wrongdoings does not absolve anyone else from punishment or at the very least the ruination of their reputation but I'm pretty sure Boris will get away with it! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Aye! Away and put your feet up grandad! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's face it ... it wouldn't take the police and an inquiry to find Joe Bloggs guilty of having a garden party during lockdown!! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dire Straits - Sultans of Swing lyrics #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Omg noooo T is too healthy for you!!! xxx Catch you later! :-) xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh there's always one! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think you're ok! I'll never eat 3 eggs. I've got trifle, sticky toffee pudding, custard and Cornettos! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thanks so much! It's not the best prognosis but I'm giving it my all! You never know what's round the corner! ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C'mon #HASHTAG# when are you going to reveal Meena for the murdering bitch she is? We're all getting fed up waiting!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah that girl is trouble says Tracey who's been in jail for murder! Takes one to know one! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As far as I'm concerned a tent has the same facilities and is a lot cheaper! It's pure snobbery! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you called them 'big' gems ... would big people be offended? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No it's not a private plane ... it belongs to the taxpayer! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh thank god Liam is ok! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've got 4lbs to put on to get me back to my normal weight! Then I can have some lovely salads! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I shouldn't be burdening you! Had a scadgie ... I'll be fine! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's always a picture of Jesus in these people's houses!! How warped and twisted? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great idea! ban 2nd jobs and perks etc and we'll soon find out who is really taking their political career seriously!! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What would be the point in that?  An opinion in a letter without appropriate content means nothing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My problem is the opposite ... I need to eat more carbs or actually anything! Folk think that's a great problem to have ... it's no fun!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He CAN manage on his millions! ... and I'm sure there are many more children to come! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally love Leo's suit! I want one! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol I know......I'm very tempted!!! That's what you get when you get a job and sign off though!!! xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good for you Brent! let the games begin! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right I've got a spare hour ... what's on now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My point exactly! They are doing something positive as opposed to blocking roads!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the #HASHTAG# could be much more interesting this year without Djokovic! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder why none of the couples don't just say piss off ... we're away to make our marriage work ... alone!! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I know how you get lost in the moment! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Russians have been coming to get us for years. I don't know why anyone hasn't seen that. They'll pick their moment!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm going I'm going!! lol See ya tomorrow bright and early! lol Night night Steve!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes I don't agree with horse racing either. That horse has to run whether it wants to or not! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You feel in her shadow Brett ... it's all ego!! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Putin particularly if he's losing will use every last bomb, bullet and life before he stops! He's a megalomaniac! It's what they do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh yeah! Like the Queen! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She said she tried to rouse him ... wake him up! Get it in context! 
The first thing you do if you think someone's unconscious is shake them to try to get a reaction!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're supposed to say I'll come with you and support you Nate! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Good! You've made me smile! Must be the only good thing to be infectious atm!! ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah 'cheer up, it might never happen' lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thanks Fiona! A bit weird but all for the greater good! ðŸ˜Š xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW!!!! This is Scotland bashing on a HUGE scale!!! Who the hell is she? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh c'mon #HASHTAG# When is Meena going to finally melt down?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right I'm bored now .... everyone is behaving like Russia needs a treat to stop doing bad things ... or maybe a seat on the naughty step! ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That photographer is top notch! You can't call them pics ... they are art! ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Haha! Noooo! I'll make them for you sometime! You'd think we lived on different continents! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think it's quite scary! BUT I think Boris will have to do a u turn on this one too!! He's good at that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol I think that might've been The Big Build! ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would say better the devil you know!! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trust me ... you never know what's round the corner!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choochooo is my catchphrase....piss off Michael!! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It's not like it used to be! My mum and dad had a party but then that was their night ... they didn't go out regularly. I can count on one hand the times I had a babysitter as a kid!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's not funny! She's going to starve me to death before the cancer gets me!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just got in before the rain came on! The gods are looking down on me after all! ðŸ˜‡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# THAT is one of my fav tunes ever!!!  I dance to that! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is everyone smiling on this prog even when talking about serious subjects? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I don't hate anyone! I disagree with being run from Westminster.  We are a completely different country and I have faith that we can do this. It takes courage!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think she's trying to be patriotic which makes a change! Have to admit I did comment to myself about it!! Not the best dress she's worn! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chicken soup on the hob! cause everyone knows .... it cures everything!! ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes but it's yet another thing we need to be highlighting as a case for independence! Too many thing are under Westminster control!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never done dating apps so I don't have a clue how they work! They sound a bit scary to me! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I had to get a 2 pin plug for my toothbrush! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hmmm there's a lot of darkness in that family! I don't really remember it but I've heard a lot about it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[pink floyd - another brick in the wall #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why aren't people able to take care of themselves ... they need the gov to guide their tiny little minds round Covid!! No wonder Boris is taking the piss!! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I keep going in to a room and forgetting why I went in!!! My brain is leaking through lack of hair! ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've had 4 rounds of chemo and that is hell. You can get skin problems with this but I just have to wait and see how it affects me. No option but to go with the flow anyway!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have whatever you want on Christmas day! Why is this a question? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think whoever invites the other person out should expect to pay! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Training dogs is not much different to training children! You want them to be liked so you discipline them appropriately! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aww my neighbour just gave me this!! It's a wee bit wilted but it's the sentiment that counts!! ðŸ™‚ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ah well that's a sacrifice I'll have to make! lol I've got 7lbs to put on! I don't care where it comes from! ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Isn't it a bit sad when you fancy someone ancient!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No that will only happen in a parallel universe. He needs his ass kicked there out of this universe!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was wondering when someone was going to suggest taking Putin out! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dianna ... the virus is something you breathe in .... it's a lot more easily transmittable than during surgery! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok I guess I should watch some news today!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well Prince George has to prepare for shooting Grouse and Deer in the future!!! #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>