<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol crying...its why gifting gift cards would be better folks just are bad gift givers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would tell other women how freeing it is to be single...men is too much headache at the end of the day i dont want a man in my face i choose peace instead #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We know ms t!na is a bird brain where do u think her daughter got it from]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just messaged my cousin to check in  if shes ok since shes an RN here in nyc...i can imagine how overwhelmed overworked she is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love normani so i get taking breaks after working nonstop with that racist mess of a group 5H but her mngmt did her dirty she needs to focus on the music...because showing up randomly in folks music videos,  ads its confusing random .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh and i love the British vogue cover the models loved it and the thinkpieces on it r pure misery. The photographer does these exaggeration so its not new...they look gorgeous and Charcoal Black ppl do exist yall would be mad if the models were yt or light bright so stfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He doesn't need to get money. That child was in a shelter...i dont know the story but if he didn't know where that child was either it was 4 a good reason or he just didn't care until he saw $$$
Maybe the grandparents could raise the child not him #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im sorry i really thought that euphoria girl had asian in her...i cant possibly b the only one who thought that yes i knew we come in different shades its just Hollywood's likes mixed looking actresses so i assumed she was lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sadly even in actual tribes they have lots of mixed and barely any Native Americans in their tribes the rules been sparse so no surprised a yt faked it lol #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol they actually do emt lawyers hospital staff its how they get info so quick #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He should have proposed at a restaurant he knew d#USER# well sweaty,  bad wigs and shes feeling embarrassed about everyone doing different dance moves it was a mess #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep i remember this because she started her career late in life and wants to be independent which i get but he is at a retired age life is too short]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# His career should have been bigger but he came up at the same time as bieber and mngmt did a terrible job promoting him smh lol 😆]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only???!!! I know shes yall fave but she has eugenics talking points anyone else gets drag for the same tweets. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep i was followed for 30 mins a few weeks ago didnt get notifications until i got home...but thank god i live in a private luxury building #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jamie lynn is ugly inside out did she show u her phone at all. She should have called out that pedo abuser producer from nickelodeon instead of trashing stealing from her successful sister #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wasnt it canceled on upn before it ever got on the CW like all the other Black comedies...The Game and one other Black comedy was left in the switch #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol oh my gawd same here...because yikes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The babies shoulder is what i think cause the tear because that was the only time i wanted to really d!3 ...idk how my mom did it 4 times grandmother 12 times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine the kind of air and chemicals they were breathing in and birth defects like how tf a chemical plant was built near residential area this would never happen in a white neighborhood...environmental racism is dangerous #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Im upset they canceled after a 3 year wait for season 2 just absurd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The answer is NO everytime they fought for civil rights it never included us Black women and girls (including trans and gay folks) . Patriarchy and misogynoir is really something #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On top of yt ppl not bathing they swim in sh!t water like they dont smell already #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay what about the thousands sitting in detention centers faced with sexual abuse, hunger, cold, trauma by staff #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank u love for reminding us.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol b!tch lied im crying...sxammer 🤣 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol crying sh!t great advertisement too because who wouldn't want a lawyer like this 🤣 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need yall to stop telling these men to go for custody like idc if its a joke...theres a reason why they dont have custody...

Its stressful time consuming on mothers too like please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember the blue check negroes that did this... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why negroes who sh!t on the bags brands are trash its odd Stella McCartney a yt woman uses pleather/faux fur but she never got vitriol for it.  Hes kind charitable and walks the walk #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Child birth(baby shoulders) ...my contractions werent bad ... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The harassment has gone criminal threatening r#USER# hyping incels in her mentions ...nnshe stuck by her opinion it is what it is folks need to just block leave her alone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BM are weak links they give traction to incels abusers misogynoir homophobia its sick its why i dont understand folks including spotify spreading that sh!t around #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These asian folks and yt folks cosplaying scare me...like for a second i thought maybe he was black asian because of his @ name #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone of those ppl with C*rn are sexual predators and rebranded as a "chef" but none of them cant cook and should be in jail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MLK day was yesterday yall was just tweeting about workers fighting for unions and higher wages the hypocrisy lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They are all war criminals next. Stop k!lling Palestinians men women children babies . Worst propaganda I'd ever seen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indigenous ppl in figi, new Zealand, Australia , or other places where natives are darkskin doesnt mean they are Black and they dont indentify themselves as Black even though racist yt folks call them slurs related to Black ppl because of their skin tone ....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ill discussed something tomorrow that im not liking...the bar has been moved but ill wait tomorrow to go further ive discussed it before]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol ok i c the tweet this is pertaining to nevermind 😆]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# After 30 years of controversy,  abuse, allegations,  harm they caused us Black folks and women and girls i cant believe still folks deal with the clintons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U can blame tribes for how easy yt folks join they get enamored with whitness but are extremely racist towards us Black folks u cant even date them without an issue lol their bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# U know what not anymore not one but i do love true crime lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its yt ppl mess i dont know how it got anywhere on our side of twitter lol #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course a c00n n!gga translated it...glad hes getting dragged stop translating things for cr#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Exactly nothing to defend i get it its your child but he took it too far. That was assault endangering etc ...plus defending a racist yt will never be my ministry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See a true professional and license i want folks to get services like this and let go of those ig ppl #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol father god i died in how this tweet progressed #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep u even hear from those biracial kids how racist the yt daddy is...idk where the myth that a yt partner is better all men r trash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Other Black folks withhold ur fvckin votes thats how u negotiate.  the projects, nycha, the Black community, prison system, laws wont change if ur nig nog a$$ is voting for these ppl. They know that...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weak links ...he looks like he eats Black ppl for breakfast and this c00n standing next to him. Its always BM doing this #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so weird why did u have to say Ludacris with braids we see that so random #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep my mom was a single mom but i saw the married folks in my family doing equal to more labor ...and i said no even though marriage was drilled into me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These sh!ts are ugly Dior agreed to this in the 1st place shameful ... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol crying i never watched either 😭 but i didn't tweet it #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Too much and not enough lol...over a few hundred dollars i think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do original ideas for movies not exist anymore #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U say a deadbeat or whatever he is has a good case against dhs and i make a point that that man doesnt deserve penny or custody whats not to get . He didn't know where his daughter was , he worked for NYCHA like plz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didnt realize that dimwit feminista jones was tweeting that...shes a weirdo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yall not gonna like this dont u wonder maybe the step mom when she first dated his dad gave off a nasty disrespectful energy like she doesnt consider his kids important enough to know or care about.  Its ok to agree with a guy when he isnt in the wrong js #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Estelle doing this everytime she tells a story cracked me up 😆]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 90s was something lol 😆 the early 00s long shirts passed the knees was a mess #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep rich folks dont get their kids taken away like the poor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When i tell yall the foster system is a cesspool of neglect abuse from the case workers to the homes those innocent children go to ...it needs to be abolished #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# White gays really need to stop tweeting like this since we know your history of racism of Black gay and brown folks and transphobia. Erasure of trans ppl who fought for the rights u all have and ur yt forefathers r responsible 4 those laws overseas so be quiet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The backhanded compliments smh and this man ugly thats who folks were thirsting over ... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She has horrible taste in men an upgrade but still]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It was embarrassing so many Black folks deserved that job and the excuses they made for that racist unqualified yt to get it was outrageous  . She didnt even apply she was given the job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly this!!! Schools have disproportionately been under funded in some communities for years, no equity in what Black and Brown children received compared to white peers, teachers underpaid, no nurses, healthcare #USER#, toxid food &amp;water #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now Black ppl with 2 Black parents are not Black it has to be cr#USER# at this point...i...unheard of  

zendaya is biracial Black...that storm girl is Black like please stop the madness because some u obvious looking negroes r not full Black either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Native Americans dont like us Black folks so i stay out of that ....discussion nnPlus they still never acknowledged the slaves they owned here in the US]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well today was fun lol...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No because they go in on tyler perry actresses with bad wigs they  pick and choose. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She sounds like a hater. Older women who look down on younger women because men are checking them out. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its why i tell other Black women stay home stop marching putting ur lives on the line for these men that wouldn't spit on us if we was on fire. If its not concerning BW including trans women and Black lgbtq its no concern to me #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mind your pvssy if u not helping mind your business #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did it make you feel good to go in on a dark skin Black woman who fell in love .  for a biracial and her ugly fiance that didn't even like her... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one:nnNot a soul:nnBlack africans proving to the whites they dont live in huts: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why are the women always older and the men broke young and from a different country very odd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow wow i wondered how that happened he should have not signed his rights over they both trash #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol i would not have known they were Gucci...they really fell off but yeah cute for kids who dont know any better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats how n!ggas in Black family get away with sh!t the men r coddled hes a bum and got what he deserved...its not just a car like the audacity #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is she a yt...that makes no sense ill take all her sh!t out #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why u insulted New Edition like that lol im crying u didnt say B2K which is more like it 😭 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jl is talking in circles girl u been at this for years dont know how to do interviews or talk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gene was suave but its funny the same ones thirsting over chris aka the swirlies are not with this casting lol #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God i would love to see critics and audiences faces when they watched this abomination lol #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL# lol scammers the gaines should be ashamed attaching their names to this couple]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The response was vulgar i was shocked ...im not condoning abuse from parents but that was extreme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sh!t we saw how that played out with a Black president this doesnt surprise me . Black folks get a certain income or power turn into c00ns unfortunately #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember callmedollar was the one questioning meg thee stallion being sh0t hes trash and a misogynistic loser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The thing is the US donates too many clothes because haiti, india, sri lanka etc look like this from organizations donating these clothes but its not needed because its too much ...they need to stop sending clothes are making too much or just incinerate here in the US]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remembered the court case unsurprisingly my own mother didn't believe the boys i was shocked nobody believed those boys y because the LA sheriff targeted MJ true but to say allegations were a lie is y victims dont speak up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From experience with bisexual men this is correct ...cis hetero men r uselessnnBi men even the dl are exceptional #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol we know how much did this study cost wasting money like that. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im avoiding ig today i dont need to see whitewashed waterdown MLK quotes from the whites and suburban/rich Black folks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol father god walmart is ghetto 😂 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol father god yall r too much and same even then i will never get on here to ask 😂 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im about to season these chicken thighs im starving lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh yes thank u i forgot the tw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well the temperature drop substantially i left the windows open felt like an ice box ...happy xmas eve everyone if u celebrate or happy holidays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol What kind of southerner...im from up north love Catfish and collard greens but grits no but paired with fish delicious 😋 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol father god  and yes having gone through pregnancy (all day morning sickness pre-eclampsia) childbirth and post partum its scary #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police r useless see this daily with my own eyes I literally had to tell them about homeless folks who were passed out like call the hospital something .... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol you're me because if u call yourself a misandrist and still lay up (date marry) with a man im judging]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes it was..its when i knew i hated joe and understood michaels arrested development . Its what caused all the problems leading to him grooming boys smh. That man was a tyrant abuser and took it out on all those kids and each of them had problems #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shes a racist b!tch but yeah its her body her choice #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We told yall they r the opps...what would Malcolm X would say ...naacp been a joke colorist anti Black #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I dont understand how they thought that was a good idea...it slowly started happening with bringing in more reality tv shows in the 00s and a couple of great scripted drama but then only reruns. mtv is a mess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think i met my dads 3rd wife once she was a b!tch how u marry a deadbeat ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Haitian ancestors burn sh!t down now imagine my a$$ paying to go on that same plantation same land for a tour i rather be struck by lightning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He should be jailed and charged what is there to investigate.  Imagine his wife and kids the abuse they endured #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol you're right spanish and yt guys its why BM are sh!t at it 🤣 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But shouldn't the conversations be had between whoever your partner is its not focusing on his needs but both. I mean how many cis hetero coupling where 1 or both r not satisfied #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its been so normalized in that household i remember watching that biopic as a kid broke my heart the abuse those kids went through . For some of them 2 think it was "love" trauma thats what it is #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im glad br33 n3wsome was dragged this past week for harassing her husbands rape victim on top of suing the woman and former organization that she worked at shes a trash hypocrite rap3 apologist and bully ... im shocked folks r still following]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She was a child why do u think she should be involved in adult business and mess. She was friends with kylie not her adult sisters . #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah i dont know how she has a career and shes not funny...weird girl wasnt she called out by a co star for something #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok i take it back lets leave White men alone...nnFrom a distance #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About time she said something miley spoke up first...why did she wait this long knowing Brit influenced her music career...literally did a lizzie eps dressed as her #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol yeah right. how many Black folks say this before they sell their souls to the devil aka politicians and corporations #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think because that family is abusers and stay having abusers around them its odd that the one with a mental breakdown is the one they have an issue with but yeah i agree he shouldn't b around them kids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daughter has super hero day had her wear her pony gymnastic one piece pony pants and cape shes super pony lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its hot out like early spring hot wtf we almost in January never felt like this in nyc....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously i don't recognize harlem its not the place i visited grew up or lived at in the 90s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hes trash and u dont need to be asian to have almond shaped eyes because they were technically the same. I see why asian women leave them for yt men...loser #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yall h8 us poor folks and i wish u guys say it with your chest. The OG made an ignorant comment just block the B....but then yall made it worse saying only poor ppl live in rural areas huh...and going in on low wages for what...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know women irl who can fight and they r not online being nasty rude or condescending unprovoked i promised those r the ones that dont have hands every time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's actually why white folks farmers or poor whites had so many kids throughout history free labor lol....but it's her vagina so I'm a mind my business ... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whew reminder us Black folks created invented music...periodt #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asian folks are very racists even to biracial Black children ...its why most asians date yt #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol these ppl have no shame and this was from other Black folks i guess they just couldn't fathom it 🤣 like im a whole negro plz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol true but still she abandoned them... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol i stopped too didnt want to take a chance #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# People are obsessed with her shes at home with the kids not bothering or talking to anyone and she comes up in every convo unprovoked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I was so mad i didn't even noticed i was tweeting another BW lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please tell them but they want to say lesser of two evils which was already laughable #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[!!! Yep its why folks dont fully disclosed .  we saw how it happened with Britney can u imagined a regular person yeah its what scared me about therapy i couldn't say what i wanted to say u had 2 b careful #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did society a favor Ukrainian rapper .... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because apparently they are "rich"...folks get nasty and anti poor very quick #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not a real Black account i checked his page its weird...probably a racist yt behind the account #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol why do white ppl do this like racism and white supremacy doesn't exist today. Us Black folks,  POC,  or jewish folks dont need color pics because we are still living this lol #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*whispers* i dont really like donuts, loved them as a kid but not my fave pastries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nope this man is Black thats why her hair was fine. The other one looked messed up with her yt beau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daughter is the most dramatic person ever ...mini shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# U r  *gly racist and looked like u was marching at the Capitol January 6...go to ur kkklan meeting and stop bullying a Black woman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol u get on my nerves ... and i said it in his voice reading this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like clockwork...they cant be saved and i hope gen z Black folks wont vote ...either nnWithholding the vote would have gotten sh!t done years ago since jfk at least #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Way too many ppl i follow following her yikes 😆 🤣 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Its embarrassing at this point im not surprised gen x like them(idk y)  but fellow millenials its a sickeness...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This world doesn't care about us Black women and girls our allies are only other Black women and girls its truly sad and scary out here with all the evil in the world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I...rob needs to pay more child support... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah idk why they didn't just leave it alone the og series only had Black folks as guest starts and they had to be light brown no need to add them now its try hard inauthentic #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol i...i didnt even know they knew MLK over there father god 🤣]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[!!! Looking at the Cl!ntons, b! den and others #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holly wrote the book and kendra tried to sh!t on her...because she said hef was abusive and trash smh #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we cancel Black history this month i just enough embarrassment...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curse twitter for giving negroes Blue checks...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's how the racist rich whites got the poor whites to join their cause #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[N!ggas online embarrassing our ancestors these are the negroes that wont get in touch with their African culture history spiritualism but online to prove to white supremacists that they too will grovel 4 them 2 b seen as humanbeings...embarrassing.  smh #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah these are the ugly Hermes that r sold in shop not the beautiful custom mades that royalties or European actresses have... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol right i live in a pet friendly building with a doggy daycare and that wasnt enough because i didnt have prior experience now i have a dog theres another issue ridiculous lol i have a hound mix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes shockingly the men were more understanding compassionate the older women were mean girls bully at their big age #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me put this d#USER# sparkling water in the fridge im too angry to drink this tuh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is true many lawyers starting off start as clerks then move up #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I...this sounds like the greatest horror film...what did he do that he had to stopped wow #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish the video wasnt cropped and most folks like myself stopped watching after she said racially ambiguous it would have helped having the full info. But yeah men on here are trash over that video #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[!!!!!! Im sick of BM not understanding this them being men has its advantage that is not afforded to us Black women . The power abuse influence they have on the Black community is substantial #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to know if any of those ugly hags r living #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*whispers* never ate crab legs before i dont get the hype theres barely any meat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welp what did we say stop hanging with them yt folks they befriend until its time to get rid of you. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh its about gifting men lord dont let the fake misandrists find those tweets the ones who lay up with bf or husbands at home telling us 2 not be kind to men u like lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its why shes an icon...see how men need us #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol asian women know d#USER# well these yt men are racist but they want the status, half yt child and not deal with an asian MIL .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im glad i never converted to catholicism i almost did i was going through so much in my early 20s . my advice get ur sh!t together b4 u think of joining any religion cult whatever lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol folks were defending this man and calling us all kinds of trash when we said he was a republican hes a racist pro cop war criminal rapist #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol but collectively African women across the board wear bad wigs but yes us Black Americans suffer the same fate too #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yall do not give these incels podcasters violent men ur time they do this for shock...nnDont tweet about them dont share videos or audios thats exactly what they want. nnIf anyone u follow does it block them bcuz y bring that on the tl 4 what]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please god i hope there was actually toys he was gifted. Since the beginning of times kids have never cared for clothing items as gifts . #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[D#USER# tgis is hard...living single because they seemed to all love each other but i do love Insecure minus tiffany...and Girlfriends minus Joan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charlize Theron is taking that place...in my opinion #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never understood those your grandmother must be 30 or whatever because baby if u go way back our ancestors had children very young...so to shade on other Black folks makes no sense lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This fat racist ugly pedo get her out my screen #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Exactly!!! Maybe their something wrong with my eyes the 3 women listed are dark skinned...dark brown . Adut akech is darker skin why folks afraid to say who's darkskin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want his sons to answer since hef isnt here and his ugly perv brother if hes still alive #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a grey matter. I understand what your saying but looking at us Black folks and through generation trauma and slavery and how we learned beatings from yt slaveowners which passed down through generations can u say that exclusively.  Its only recently we ... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep it will always be a privilege because if you're Black american, british or European...you will be treated better than local Black africans. Plus that money spent wont help any1 in the community...it wont even leave a dent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Featuring drake a groomer creep, chris a creep woman beater and future a deadbeat with multiple kids thats how they want to honor Aaliyah smh #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yall stop rt following Br33 Newsome how many times do we have to say shes a rap3 apologist fraud and sued her husbands rap3 victim and the company/organization  that she "worked" at. Like yall r blinded by large accounts and blue checks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remembered watching shaka zulu at 9 man i was traumatized had nightmares for days why my momma let us watch that lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Its embarrassing at this point a director should know who's in his film. Even if the casting director hired them did he not get snippets of who was who]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol this im tired or maybe jealous idk ...its too much on here #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cant believe i ruined a tory i dont deserve nice things...*whispers yes i do*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This!!! It wasn't a secret especially if you're old enough to know her and tom in the 90s...she even did interviews back then...so idk y anyone would watch and the actors and creators trash #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yall think someone born in a African country is Black is laughable might as well start calling Egyptians Black if thats the case. Only an idiot would think he had an ounce of Black in him. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like if we called her a former war criminal that fvcks yt peen we b wrong...miserable at home bully online]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But shes not Black shes mixed Black a huge difference. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sh!t not i ...i stayed home... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Considering she was considered a joke among those yts... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And as a victim of child sex abuse its horrifying that even recently folks still support MJ allegations i love his music contributions his social justice and speaking up about racism police brutality but i will never discredit his victims ever]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>