<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't afford Obamacare. If u don't qualify for subsidies it's totally unaffordable. Glad Biden is gonna cover non citizens. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These larger than ever hospitals, nursing homes and warehouse we build (and more coming in Build Back Better including big corporate pre schools) are really scary with  tornadoes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do trick plays vs an inferior team?  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only way Republicans f up 2022 is picking nut cases. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I also lived thru riots of late 1960's and early 1970's where things around me like KU Student Union and KCMO burned.  My grandparents in middle of latter.  

50K dying in Vietnam in my youth about 47K more than died in all wars since.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This clearly tells me he knows #USER# won't be back with #USER# next season. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder. A member of Obama Administration. Also, reminder my Congresswoman #USER# has voted for every single dollar printed and spent for 3 years. Also she voted for huge Build Back Better that failed in Dem controlled Senate. Now buying a car or house in 3rd District harder #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Poor #USER# looked miserable wearing his mask while doing his report.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KU getting all the calls in this Tech vs Baylor game too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think at times the Mahomes family deserves criticism for being attention whores.  But anyone discussing any split second look at a great college hoops game, is an idiot. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What bugs me is when a cause of a fire is reported it is never from 2 sticks rubbed together. I think investigators often overlook simple causes. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Rideshare driver with 19K rides.

When going west on 43rd, jog over to Westport Rd.  

I do it every time.   Easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Question for #USER# #USER#.

I know a weird offseason with lock out but usually at first of year we get announcement on #HASHTAG# ad campaign &amp; hashtag and an announcement broadcast crew returning. A new Veep in charge of some of these decisions.   Broadcast crew changes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mundo arriving at studio at 5:55am tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They aren't banned from youth sports.  Co-ed or sports with birth sex are 100% open. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back in the day when people bought classified ads the newspaper biz was right there too #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody writing better op-ed stuff than #USER# . #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mizzou was a good Big 8/12 hoops program. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until he returns to Super Bowl he probably isn't gonna be over it.  There was #HASHTAG# legends dying right now not over 71 Christmas Day double overtime playoff loss.  #HASHTAG#Kingdom #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steelers want a safety to make a tie less likely. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Esky....center field and leading off next yr. #HASHTAG# I hope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Pete would like it.  Really not woke.  Kansas/KC references galore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it is Hillary vs Trump, a Wang/Gabbard independent ticket would be interesting. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The stay at home and watch games on 70 inch screens is the way to do it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am sure it brings back memories of the muddy Mo in KC. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder. Dr. Bollier didn't know what is the very famous and often discussed Patriot Act was during the campaign. Incredible lack of knowledge. She would have been a rubber stamp for money printing for JoCo elites. Build Back Better for northeast JoCo bank accounts. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ya he has been very careful due to pre-existing conditions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then at 9am interview for open afternoon drive position. #HASHTAG# 😎 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Would love to read it but the app hasn't let me reset password for a week plus.   The link they email out isn't a live link.  

I see shortstop Witt at #HASHTAG#.  Too bad he probably isn't gonna be shortstop here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Now I didn't watch Super Bowl but it appears no Royals media campaign launched yesterday?  

I need a new hashtag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Mitchell is staying in KC for a while.  Back must be better.   Hmmmmm.   Right tackle not exactly settled for my favorite team #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trump screw it up thing is certainly a factor in Georgia, Arizona. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weeks before New Hampshire.   Now people will be announcing  right after 2022 midterms. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Waiting to finish contract with Bob Stoops. If Stoops backs out we might keep Miles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Florida better worry about just Florida. With Missouri coming to the SEC East, it is a big trouble for Florida.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sadly at times we gave back during the season too. #HASHTAG#  Good job by the team. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like I have said for 2 3/4 years, Marcus Garrett doesn't shoot enough. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my theme of life in USA in 2021. It's not trickle down. It's trickle up. Example if this free preschool passes every mom &amp; pop religious school will close &amp; huge elite preschool buildings will be built by the elites. See the new giant hospitals that came w/ Obamacare. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# probably applauded the gas down 7 cents from it's 7 year high.   Pay your fair share for gas? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facts.  Missouri was a Democrat State prior to 1980 when it became a swing state then a Pub leaning state in 90's.  True conservative state only last 10 years.  But still 8 years of Carnahan &amp; Nixon Governorships recently.  Mo last jn those stats for yrs &amp; yrs including Dem yrs. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broncos much like pre-Reid Chiefs.  Some really talented players. Badly need a QB and Coach. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does she know Orlando doesn't have a beach?  

But glad she is here in middle of USA at KU.  #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem isn't Mahomes.  The problem is drops and shitty Andy play calling after start of game scripted plays. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day after landing a spot on Board of Directors of a big solar company.  Traditionally people resign from Corporate Boards if they run for office. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# about to write a Melvin Ingram column.  The Ben Zobrist acquisition of the current Chiefs.  

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not to #USER# except at the area elite Country Clubs. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ogbaji free throw misses are so frustrating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When in-state schools like Indiana and Fort Wayne get together you throw the records out. Bitter rivals. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow up on previous tweets on subject of why our country is broke.  

I am a KC based guy. Medicaid paying me $400 to drive from Lenexa, Ks to Clarinda, Iowa, pick up a patient &amp; drive 30 minutes to Shenandoah, Iowa for dialysis, wait 4 hours  &amp; return. This happens 3x week. 💰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dole supported Trump twice.  I suspect Trump &amp; Biden might be together at a funeral soon. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So are all the people who couldn't get Royals last season gonna get them this season? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I remember that game.  Awful Chiefs team just kicked crap out of really good Raiders team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big game.  I expect a playoff mentality.  I can see Patrick scrambling  for 1st downs more on 3rd down than we have been seeing. Maybe Tyreek in backfield some.  #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# He may end up being released and you could just sign him to a new contract]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember the big news is we forced a tie in the Challenge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyclones on a 15 zip run vs Mizzou. 

It means more in #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing a 3am to 5am CST show.  Putting a suit on that early morning is a weird concept. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty amazing it took until 3pm in afternoon central time to speak.  Oh well.  Glad he said something. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# With 169 and 70 bridge work overlapping they might not have any customers to park.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super nice guy and my 2nd fav KU beat writer ever.  Prayers for #USER# . #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# and my Congresswoman #USER# wants to take away the very popular and very successful voter ID out of 3rd district elections. Why? The scanning of ID makes things go fast. Spelling hard names and looking at 1955 voter rolls is slow and STUPID. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unless you are a sprinter like Usain Bolt.  His motto is it's a sprint not a marathon. 

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny to watch #USER# about to cry about a Parents Bill of Rights in Ks schools &amp; next story is about a dead KCMO student age child who clearly died of some kind of system failure that closing schools &amp; masking his pained face didn't help the situation. Biz as usual #HASHTAG#. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My very educated guess from a rideshare ride who has give 20K rides past 6 yrs. There is 50K to 100K people more now in KC area that can't afford a car than when pandemic started. The days of buying a decent used car for cash with tax refund to get a family by is over. Disaster. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Only bright side is if Ryan gets traded not sure if anyone has a quarterback in that division.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So how is #USER# ever gonna pay off her bankrupt coffee shop debt? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dak has talent but just inaccurate QB in general. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lesson of the inning. You can give up an out on a sacrifice bunt and still have a big inning. Never forget it. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KU has played whole seasons without a defensive line. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor #USER# just sacrificing his holidays. The guy can spend the rest of his life anywhere he wants. To ask avg Joe just lucky to get 3 day weekends next 2 weeks to not see family isn't a comparison. Elites out of touch. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# will soon fix the problems. . Well maybe not but if he has his way you can vote without photo ID. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is Overland Park fire gonna ruin season premier of Dancing with the Stars? .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lost to WHB so 2nd in Johnson County. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Didn't they draft a decent QB prospect in 3rd round?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# of #USER# takes or finds best Twitter pics or vids #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's dangerous. See Reagan picking Sandra Day O'Connor who was never close to a great Justice or Sotomayor who as first Hispanic is proving to not be sharp. Pick the best qualified. My guess is the best black female isn't gonna be picked but the one to charm public in hearing. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It was a Big 12 tweet saying tickets available to tourney on 2/25]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing how all the white school districts got back to in person school but the black majority schools didn't. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A perfect touchdown drive here will let us all sleep better tonight. 

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# is a hall of famer and Orange Bowl champ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What could go wrong?  Jack County makes so many good decisions thru the years.  I think the FBI has a field office there. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder, Roeland Park Mayor Mike Kelly is a very serious candidate for Johnson County Chairman. 

Please vote for someone else with common sense who actually follows science. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gpnna be huge Democrat fight over lots of this stuff. Elites will be asking for poor Dems in places like Ruskin to pay for fun. Only state/fed roll will be interstate. Streetcar going over very long river bridges to KCK or NKC is dumb. Probably better ways to do people moving. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labor participation rate bad. Maybe this is good or bad but Government benefits so good a bunch of people not working who aren't even collecting unemployment. Maybe more Mom's staying home with kids is a good thing but millions of open jobs. Lack of used cars not helping either. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or reduce emminsions if cars aren't stopped in traffic jams. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brooke spending part of Christmas in KC. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Greatest nose tackle ever?  

He actually got better in Houston in a 3-4 defense. 

Great college wrestler.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barring a big play a time is coming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Esky is so unappreciated as a leadoff hitter and offensive weaon. Never doubt Ned. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God punishing Olathe School District on their first day of school for masking kids something Black Jesus didn't do during Swine Flu. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would love to know how old was Amazon building?  I have contented inflation of 70's and 80's led to cheap construction practices that led to collapses at KC icons Kemper &amp; Hyatt.  You start substituting non available parts on construction protects from original design good luck #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Big 12 impressive this bowl season. Vegas money might be pouring in soon against Sooner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The common denominator of this person being convicted after that unwarranted Police assault and Jackson County's history of wrongful convictions is the Public Defenders and Prosecutors office really is bad. So many Public Defenders and Prosecutors really suck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KU shoe partner.  And #USER# came after Snoop pole dancers. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really amazing the things that happen at Southern border which don't have to happen. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin has won the war with the west by just selling oil.  Boy he must love Biden policies. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ned should have seen Duffy in trouble after the first batter and went to pen. These 2 homers on Ned. 

#HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real January 6th.  One of the great Christian stories #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will #USER# ask him if Fairfax GM plant in KCK and neighbor supply biz's close with rush to electric cars?  Pretty legit question with new electric plants being built as we speak. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So all the favs gonna win &amp; cover except for America's Team?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I predict a #HASHTAG# breakout offensive game. One run on six hits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note, gas down some here locally from peak in KC area but still a good $1 a gallon higher than last December.   

My fear is how much once we start reloading oil reserves and spring demand and summer blends?  My guess gonna be in high $3 range come March in KC. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fox doubleheader week.  We just got noon CBS game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Her district incredibly reliant on gasoline but with the price of new and used cars maybe we will all just bike. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# 50 yrs ago today Bud Stallworth scored 50 to beat Missouri.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iowa State wearing Iowa colors may explain why their year kind of disappointed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much did the Biden family get from Ukraine giant energy company? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sorry Biden sucks.  Sadly we all have to live with it.  Keystone monster  mistake.   Enjoy riding the  bus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Short season shows all essential move too fast and get weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Look at the rule, you can if no part of ball is ever gonna be over the rim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a crappy list.  First two I read were KU and Alabama.  Both terribly wrong. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I noticed on a recent vacation all the already expensive spray sunscreens have gone from 6 oz to 5.5.

Real inflation waaaaaaaay more than 7%.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Old enough to remember 1970's inflation.   It literally lasted 9 years.

This current inflation isn't no thing that is gonna be over anytime soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100% supported by my Congresswoman #USER# . Oil up to $109 a barrel as we buy 600 million barrels a day from Russia to finance the war.  Oh but we got electric busses and a toll 69 highway.  You can't make this stuff up. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The 2 best baseball players to come out of KC are Albert Pujols and Victor Royas. Now together in Anaheim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# training for Chiefs beat writer after Sam replaces Sam. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing run the ball some and passing game opens up too.  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mask those kids forever.   Proper education no big deal   

Reminder, most of the rest of the world not masking school kids. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dan Quayle was the whitest guy ever and he is probably closest comparison to #USER# Harris. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting thought.   My guess purely a defense decision. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Score on first drive and sit key players and get ready for Thursday night football.   #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 71 Chiefs had a great shot at 2 Super Bowl wins in 3 years but lost an agonizing overtime game in KC.  

Not tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder you must mask in Prairie Village to shovel the driveway. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We still have to build a toll road on United States 69 highway.   Nice job. #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do you think the gun control folks understand their brand new favorite country Ukraine is probably the greatest case ever made for guns ownership by citizens?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Title IX eliminated all SEC men's luge programs.  We have sucked since.  #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# should call him.  I am sure plenty of Italian places in Columbia. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# commented on this on his Twitter timeline today.  Most likely wearing his Final 4 ring while tweeting. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sure bet if u have an overseas sportsbook. There is a prominent reality show on network TV having a pretaped final. A chef show. A local contestant wins. Can't say more. A little google should fill in blanks. 100%.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such bullshit.  We print money to pay our debts. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A secret. Leave Power &amp; Light by either foot or streetcar and catch a ride somewhere else. I would suggest by foot to Streetcar Tavern at 16th and Main. By Streetcar go to Union Station or River Market. Lots of construction in Power &amp; Light district right now. Get away from it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women's sports had a nice run of about 50 years 1973 to 2022.  RIP #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think we need to draft a running back at 17th pick in the first round. 

#HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanna hear the Brent Musberger call of kick on Raiders radio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can u imagine if we ran out of Covid tests in JoCo 22 months into pandemic if Trump, Brownback annd Yoder were in charge? 

Trump would be impeached and Brownback and Yoder recalled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, I will call this a Cry Wolf, snow.

The weather people have so consistently, in this town, missed on snow totals, nobody took this storm too seriously. 

Waaaaaaaay too many people tried to go to work today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait, Bill can't recuit with NCAA hanging around. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump running 5 to 10 points better in MO. Trump obviously dragging Blunt down #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bieniemy not in a position to turn this job down but this seems like an awful opportunity.   Big shadow from previous coach, no QB and a total rebuild. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Biden, Kelly and Davids ran out of testing.   They must have thought it was over too.  

LOL  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a weird ending of that half.  20 straight missed shots?  14 zip run?

All to a not very good team who can't hit 3's.  Impossible. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This soumds like a no brainer but with state jobs come benefits including a pension you really can't get in private sector.   If you work as a processor at Department of Labor doing easy office work $14 an hour in small town Missouri with benefits and pension isn't bad. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 inning game approaching 4 hours. I blame the DH.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In previous labor disputes I always knew where individual owners stood on things.  I have no clue in 2022.  Heck, I have zero clue where Mr. Sherman stands.  I always knew where Mr. K &amp; Mr. Glass stood. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I dunno.  Just know one teammate I drove there said big team gathering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the far left of late 70's Dem party destroyed him. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He may be right but Packers and Bucs play in awful divisions and I will happily take my shot vs Rams or Cards.  NFC flawed too. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# doesn't smile a lot but when he does it's a great big happy one like after his huge game winner tonight. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too bad we closed most nuclear power plants. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self is gonna work their ass off tomorrow in practice. 

At Iowa State and Baylor here this week.  

We may not win again until first round of NIT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder Mizzou slept on this guy in-state.

I get it, weird things happen, but he comes from a family with a prominent UT volleyball standout and prominent Mizzou alum bball player and NBA Scout went to same high school. 

It is so impossible for MU to sleep on him.  #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Problem with this approach is it probably won't lead to a long term deal and we might be doing this again next year.  Keep pressure on both sides for another week.   Long term deal needed. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing moderate #USER# #USER# not being targeted because she isn't a moderate despite what local media calls her. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You can get a ride but could be expensive.   From a guy who does lots of rideshare driving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kansas was pro abortion capital of the USA before Roe v Wade. Famous for late term abortion in Wichita. The elite Country Club Republicans and Country Club Dems that ran the state had a real Margaret Sanger attitude about abortion. Stop welfare before birth. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And none of those guys got arrested multiple times in their 20's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Classic sexual harassment. Rod should not be treated like a piece of meat. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bobby Witt Jr. for Royals. He can't even get on 40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think if we got predicted 3 inches instead of 1/2 inch.  🤔 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roeland Park  and Prairie Village still masking #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avg IQ of someone with Down Syndrome is 50.

Who is making decisions on things like breast implants?  

Guys getting off on someone modeling sexy underwear and with mind of a child is sick. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like Andy Reid in front row #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# So the keystone natural gas and oil pipeline wasn't stopped? Is the gas pipeline by St. Louis not considered next on list? Elimibation of natural gas fracking? This bullshit all effects market price of gas. Sharice supports it all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing how expensive are Westport QT and all midtown gas stations.  30 cents hire than most of metro KC. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ya but Gordo and Esky saved 15 runs in those 6 games so could have been 58 to 1.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Probably a mistake leaving Alexander in the game I know where Ned got his patience and his belief in players]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that would be nuts batting Whit leadoff. Esky has earned it. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One reason I deep down inside root for #USER# more than #USER# is the Royals actually talk to the fans. Even an open process well ahead of time on the downtown stadium. Chiefs have more secrets than the KGB. But I do enjoy #USER# bikini pics. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Denny Mathews loved to call him Chester.  Chester once for White Sox hit a homer deep into fountains back when that rarely happened #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Makes Bills getting 7 before half less likely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember to avoid poll lines, Trump and Johnson voters on 11/8 and Clinton and Stein on 11/9. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another day my Congresswoman #USER# favors all these policies  including amazingly favoring buying oil from Russia instead of Canada via Keystone Pipeline.

#USER# is a hack for the elites &amp; doesn't care about the working class in 3rd district. 

Elect #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pete, he's not wrong. Covid led to huge money printing thru $1400 checks which started with lower incomes but within a month or two it trickles up to all the equity holders in Mission Hills. Printing money is great for economy other than inflation with really doesn't hurt elites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# and even #USER# must be slacking on the job.😎🇺🇲 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This actually federal roadway wise fixes very little. As an Uber driver nearing 2OK rides, I could in 3rd district alone list 10 huge federal highway significant issues this isn't touching. Dangerous left hand exit &amp; on ramps in Wyandotte not getting touched. 69 toll road. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# is alive and well.   Survived another Jets season.  

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Ben finishes career in KC, please.

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Neocons all in place in the Dem party are laughing their asses off. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder, Covid testing kit shortages. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Super Bowl a week and 1/2 later than in recent years this year.  It almost hits start of pitchers reporting date now. It threw me off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surprised #HASHTAG# Quarterback Coach Mike Kafka isn't bring hired as an OC somewhere.  #HASHTAG#Kingdom #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pain pills story.  Wife slightly broke her wrist recently. Advent ER Doctor automatically wrote her pain pills RX. She refused the RX.  Went to orthopedic Doc next day. He offered her pain pills too. She again declined. Easily could have had two pain scripts when zero needed.  👎 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Just don't totally freak out candidates by mentioning the kid will have Missouri blood. Save that shocker for several months.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe has had #HASHTAG# or #HASHTAG# job 9 of last 13 years.  

He failed to save it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While one still shot got the most attention from social media which I think is a cheap shot vs Patrick &amp; his girl, my question is why was the Mahomes entourage the only people not participating in white out? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About the school shooting in Olathe East. Congrats to heroes. Sorry to those who had to experience. But when I hear our kids today have it so bad I say BS. My youth saw 3 incredible political assassinations plus near assassinations. We lived thru cold war &amp; 50K die in Vietnam.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I lived in far western Shawnee for 17 years on 7 acres of grass surrounded by nothing but grass.  Potential grass wildfires scared me bigly but never happened.   

In KC, I would be more worried about some hilly forester areas in the metro. Lake Quivira in north JoCo an example. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mizzou and K-State dragging down another list. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Are u &amp; #USER# covering MU &amp; KSU bowls? Good assignments &amp; dates.

To be serious, MU complained about Big 12 bowls screwing them over as a reason to leave. They got screwed yesterday by SEC bowls, IMO.

Why does Mizzou get no respect?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I personally don't mind proxy votes if you are in your district.   If you are in Napa Valley or Scottsdale with elites, nope. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden and Russia getting rich off of price of oil and aluminum. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And my Congresswoman #USER# 100% approves.  She wants all the commoners on electric busses. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# is the definition of moderation and common sense.  If you are ruling party you hate moderates but amazing how much left is hating on her type #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They paid the Big Guy millions and he still didn't stop the Russians. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't trying to get rid of #USER# on #USER# essentially book burning? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just saw the Mayor Pete motorcade in JoCo.  My tax dollars trying to Re-elect #USER# .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moose is racist. Should we remove his memories from the 2015 World Series? #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be interesting to watch.  The one on this list I might disagree with is Kelly at LSU. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a soccer hater.  Respect #USER# as an organization. 

Watched the 2nd half today.  Have watched parts of many big SKC matches.

Sorry, just so many more great moments watching Royals, Chiefs and Jayhawks in my sports fandom in big games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing on twitter that MU won something.   Can't be football and we know it's not men's hoops.  

Good for them whatever it is.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>