<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You would also quite likely experience heart failure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So, if one of the players has his character jump off a 10th story roof for role-play reasons, should the DM suspend gravity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Video Essay is arguably more a format or medium than a genre. Also, post boobies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It just goes to show, though we may be separated from one another by space, by oceans and mountains, by language, nationality, and religion, all men share a common humanity. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# All the missile defence does is prevent ILLEGITIMATE, ILLEGAL, TERRORIST attacks by Hamas.

Iron Dome can't attack ground targets. It just stops incoming terrorist rockets.

That's a GOOD THING. The number of people Hamas should be able to kill is ZERO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love how wholesome this looks... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are there no depths of evil to which the Land Of THe Dragon will not sink? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# ...that HAS to be impeachable, no?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Please, call me Cybersmith.

Also, SamoyedWave was wrong about that, the default clothes have debuffs. It is mechanically advantageous to not wear trousers during the first part of the game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Those two hours after Chang's death must have been awkward...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be fair, identity fraud is harder now, thanks to electronic record-keeping. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A: yes, #USER#, you should. Retweets can be disabled if you absolutely must.

B: please, call me Cybersmith.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It is an actual documented fact that the CIA is funded through drug sales.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Unfortunately, EMPs are non-discriminatory. They can't be aimed like a bullet, they just affect anything close to them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think my interview today went well! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Because medical professionals are, of course, inhuman. Immune to bias, ulterior motives, or corruption. #HASHTAG# you really think GPs never mislead/patients, please talk to mentally ill people, or fat people, or transgenderoids.nnI've been lucky with GPs myself, many haven't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Religion predates that by a fair bit, so #USER# is Fake News.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Mate, I have a Masters Degree in Engineering.

I am MORE THAN READY to cite sources. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why did they show the Super Battle droids as being so big? They were large, but not "tower over a fully-grown adult man" large.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Really? do you think these people are ready to co-exist?

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tired. Ready for sleep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No. This may be a difficult concept for a Frenchman to grasp, but two wrongs don't make a right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# THEY WERE DE-BUFFING THE ATTRIBUTES I WANTED TO USE.

I EVENTUALLY FOUND SOME WHICH BOOSTED AN ATTRIBUTE I LIKED, AND I WORE THOSE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I have learned that Samoyedcire likes to trick people into doing phrenology...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a bit like arresting someone for trying to hit a ball with a racket at wimbledon. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, they were at it. He had neither the right nor the responsibility to interfere.

The International Statute of Wizarding Secrecy exists FOR A REASON.

There are rules that cannot be broken, no matter the cost. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Cancer is hardly "insane circumstances".

Most people, if they live long enough, will develop some form of cancer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gee, why would we accuse Barack ð˜ð˜¶ð˜´ð˜´ð˜¦ð˜ªð˜¯ Obama of being a #HASHTAG# Terrorist?nnI mean, it's not as if he bombed civilians in the Middle East, or transferred lots of #HASHTAG# to a radical #HASHTAG# Regime, is it?nn#HASHTAG# the Kunduz survivors that he wasn't a #HASHTAG#! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Arm herself, and take Kabul back.

Watch some Liam Neeson films.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd say the main difference is that Harley Quinn is explicitly a villain. She's not a good person, and is only ever a protagonist when contrasted with much worse people (like Black Mask). #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If France goes to war with the USA, then the UK will be obliged to go to war with France.

I wonder how I should spend my winnings...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I'm still on tumblr, but so many people have blocked me that I miss some of the Discourse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On some level, I actually admire the audacity of him leaving this tweet up on his verified account. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So passes a worthy adversary. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Then we'll find/make a new Earth.

If that sounds impossible, remember that splitting the Atom and Walking on the Moon were "impossible" too. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I re-bloggerise images. Sometimes those images depict boobies. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, it was called that because it happened on 11/09/2001 AD, and Yankee dates are weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER#, you are (at least) woman-adjacent, what is your opinion?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hell. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I maintain that film had its moments.

Also, given the general trend in those films to portray evil as being essentially a loss of inhibitions, I think having peter act like a drunk moron under the symbiote's influence was an interesting choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Stochastic terrorism is a #HASHTAG# concept that attempts to infringe upon #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why doesn't the technician who regularly works on military-grade hardware dress like a fashion model and wear her hair long? Don't the makers of #HASHTAG# know that characters being sexy is literally the most important part of #HASHTAG#?nn#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[XD authoritarian "logic" brilliantly satirised. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is how history worked. Look at the house you're living in, the land you stand upon.

At some point, it belonged to someone else. Such is the way of human interactions, the endless cycle of conflict.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# IT is not the same thing as actually coding.

You didn't learn to code.

You learned how to make spreadsheets.

Software development is still a valuable skillset.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# All the faces you've thrown away... all the names you've cast into silence.

Do you even know who you are anymore?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mister Uyger, with the deepest respect, that is stupid and so are you.

Justin Trudeau is also white, and we Right-Wingers do not like him.

Please stop reducing everything to race.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I hope things turn out well!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why would you argue that it isn't elective?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, because the surest sign that an intellectual property is "dead"... is when a successful producer continues to work as a producer. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, that's clearly a ridiculous idea.nnWe should instead use assault rifles, which have such a good track record of working, which is why the USA campaigns in Afghanistan and Vietnam were so quickly resolved.n#HASHTAG# the blade, or be doomed to military stagnation. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If there is no roll that can succeed, then the player attempting to grapple the dragon will just fail.

Rolling doesn't change anything. That's not agency, it's the illusion of agency.

Again, the attempts to do something, and the player rolls to determine the outcome. If, how...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Some of Mark Wahlberg's films have been okay, and he never killed any of the victims of his racially motivated harassment.

I bet if he were one of those hardcore communists like Justin Trudeau, you'd be falling over yourself (metaphorically) to excuse his chequered past.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow! Even by your standards, this is really well-done!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You had your chance to avoid this.

In January, you were presented with an opportunity to retain your champion, Donald Trump. Alas, you chose to squander Him, and this is your reward.

Bask in the horror you have wrought.

Weep.

Tremble. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah yes, Planescape Torment, The Witcher Trilogy, and Fallout New Vegas.

A set of games known for celebrating violence as an unalloyed good, and never questioning if it made the world a better place, or positing that it could cause unintended suffering.

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# As long as he keeps the feature from PoE 2 where you can equip one weapon in multiple slots, so switching what's in your right-hand doesn't require you to drop what's in your left-hand.

(seriously, #USER#, I disagree with you about a lot, but THANK YOU for that)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sorry, I can't hear you over actually meaningful increases to my Strength score.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh. For a moment, I thought you meant the war in Afghanistan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 1. Freedom.
2. The jobs which would be lost in various industries.
3. When cars are outlawed, only outlaws will have cars. Are you willing to live in that world? A world of road warriors? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A: please, call me Cybersmith.

B: no, I haven't spoken to Thivus in years. Also, Thivus, please unblock me, it's just petty of you at this point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I forgot to post this last night, but I made Toad In The Hole!!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ah yes, #HASHTAG#, the eternal refrain of #HASHTAG#-ians.nnSo Maduro, Chavez, Castro, Stalin, Mao, Hitler and even Marx weren't real socialists. #HASHTAG#, Terminally-Online champagne-sippers who spent big $ on a gender-studies degree are the only REAL socialists. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He doesn't seem to realise that harvesting these potatoes will take time...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Until someone gets tired of their nonsense and introduces them to this amazing concept called "amphibious assault teams in full body armour".

Let's see how they like facing a platoon of Royal Marines decked out in Kevlar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I prefer "transfemininity enthusiast" to "chaser", actually.

Also, please, call me Cybersmith.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well, one of those characters is a child, so... no.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Let's defecate near our drinking water and use the death penalty for minor crimes.
-Also 12th century Germans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# &gt;the genre didn't feel like it was on life support

Compared to WHEN, exactly?

If the "genre" is on life support now, when was it doing well? When were more people enthused about Science Fiction stories?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Those posts were taken out of context.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't know what "Epicurious" is, but I know that it is run by #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Those italians are indirectly responsible for people beating their loved ones?

That's honestly sad. We shouldn't be hurting our own countrymen/countrywomen at this time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A hand-towel.
Dustpan + brush.
Spare Cutlery (you WILL misplace some).
A cheesegrater or cheese slice.
Chloroform (because sometimes people ask questions, and must be disappeared).
A heatproof mat + iron (the ironing board in halls might not always be available).
Notepads + pens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She is right. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh, sorry, I thought you were.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'd alert the proprietor that there was an underage person in their alcohol-serving establishment, ensuring that you were sent home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...red, I imagine?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Part of caring about something is accepting that you may one day lose it.

Insisting that you should be able to hold onto something forever, to stop it from changing, isn't love, or compassion, or care.

It's greed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# They literally are, though? That's the whole point of a desert.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Grogu is explicitly not a clone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Someone said it in a video, then it got quoted a lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How long will it be before the Woke people accuse Wallace of being a slave-trader, and demand that this statue be removed? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...are you arguing that the police should be LESS empathetic?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LION Ted! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, yes, but that's just what happens in the unpleasant heat. It's hotter there than it is in Cornwall, and Cornwall is REALLY hot. I went to Cornwall on holiday a few times, I nearly passed out from dehydration once. Far too hot!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm not joking.

Why is this so unthinkable?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ...I'm beginning to wish I had recorded that stream, to be honest.

It would be interesting to use it as a baseline, then compare it to other playthroughs made by other people, to see what the average reading speedium is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I dare you to eat three kilograms of sugar-free gummy bears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sustained by nobody wanting the Hutts to show back up (to secure tribute), or another syndicate to step in!!!

Nobody wanted to get rid of him because of precisely what is happening on the show now. The Mayor doesn't want Hutt assassins running around. The gangs don't want a war. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# &gt;"You're letting him kill an innocent. Find and save Martha"

That's even more words!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Objecting to medical abuse is hardly being a "Karen".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wait, he's severely mentally ill?

Doesn't that call all of his previous statements and publications into question?

In any case, I hope he gets the appropriate treatment, in or out of prison. I've dealt with mental health issues before, it's terrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did they actually state that they were chasing you for racial reasons?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ah, yes, there is absolutely no #HASHTAG#.nnNepal just has a chronic tinsel shortage. #HASHTAG#://t.co/auFo6kIgxann#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's because you came in late.

The early-adopters weren't rich, just clever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Of course it's necessary! How else are they going to tell who is on what side of the conflict? Without uniforms, they'd risk shooting one another.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The #HASHTAG# is trying to tear down our culture. This is not #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's not a good thing to do. Be the bigger person, he is merely a child. His brainium is not yet fully developed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He is a visionary. He is the Herald of Tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, they did sell drugs and profit from the misery of others.

The show isn't called "Breaking Good".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Which rather defeats the point of insurance, but SOMEONE decided to make paying for it mandatory... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Human nature demands hierarchy.

If they cannot have lords and barons, they will have social media influencers.

You Whigs are to blame for all of this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Doesn't Twitter have an option to hide the nsfw content?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No he isn't!!!! Don't be mean!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The NHS's funding has gone up every year the Conservatives have been in Number 10.

You are #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Please put this in a thread?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Probably not before His plans come to fruition, and it becomes a moot point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Samurai would never have surrendered without it.

They were indoctrinated, raised to despise those who laid down their arms in battle.

Only the power of the atom could bring them to submission.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Pence betrayed the light. He fell, so perhaps it is better that he die, that he might be remembered as the good man he was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't think I've ever seen this one before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I didn't delete my account, though.

It was the tumble Staff, and I remade.

Also, please, call me Cybersmith.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Gosh, if only someone had mentioned this before!nnSadly, nobody ever told you leftists that your rush to censor people would have consequences. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This really is a fantastic drawing in concept and execution!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't understand your objection, then.

The snow didn't feature them, or state that they didn't exist. The Spectres aren't the only rebels in the galaxy, as is made clear at the end of season 1.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good for Kyle Rittenhouse, though. He responded very well to adversity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Without a nuclear deterrent, what stops Iran, or Canada or something from invading you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# We don't cheer in the UK, but the collective gasp when the Raddus collided with the Supremacy was something I haven't experienced in any other cinema.

Film magic, that was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donner's take is no more 'definitive" than Snyder's.

They each had their own interpretation of a pre-existing concept. Superman predated them both, and stories about superman will be told after them both. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do you think they were bein disingenuous?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...trategy when facing an enemy caster is to try to steal spell component pouches or holy symbols. But if you treat all of them as flavour text, you are likely to unintentionally imbalance the party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is he wrong?

Someone who toils daily simply to put food on the table doesn't have time to focus on niche issues like that.

Someone trying to keep his or her children from malnutrition isn't going to waste precious hours contemplating abstract marxist concepts. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, the enemy is "not having enough energy".

Nuclear power produces more energy in less time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That is, in fact, a valid term for it.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# &gt;china's last eunuch died in 1996

So are you admitting that you were wrong about this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you like YOUR will to be public knowledge? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Then stop supporting the socialist policies that people like him use to stay in power!

Make California a hereditary feudal territory, like one of the member-states of the Holy Roman Empire.

Have a (Right-wing, Libertarian) Duke rule until his death, then appoint his eldest son.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No. It's not as if you are running around kidnapping other people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Blair's "constitutional reforms" have been an absolute disaster. They give too much power to the House Of Commons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So, when some chainsaw-wielding maniac in a bloodstained hockey mask bashes down your front door and tries to harvest your skin for his or her human skin collection, will you still disparage the police? Or will you call for them to come and save you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You might have to.

That is, legitimately, something that could happen to soldiers, sailors, marines, or airmen in the field.

By your logic, medics should never bother learning how to splint a limb, because the correct response is not to break any bones in the first place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It is a vector for the transmission of law, civilisation, and technology.

What was Britain before the Settler-Colonialism of the Romans? A miserable little archipelago at the end of the earth.

Settler Colonialism lifted us out of the mud, gave us roads and rules.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt;petty reasons

He literally smashed an unarmed suspect's ribcage in.

That's... that's murder.

"They beat him up" to recover the weapon that he used to commit said murder. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# This player did play a role in a story.

The role was "idiot who does something stupid and dies to demonstrate how serious the situation is".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was literally created by an act of parliament, it is funded in large part by direct contributions from the state budget, and the rest of its money comes from fees that "service providers" are mandated by our legislature to pay.

#HASHTAG# is ð™–ð™—ð™¨ð™¤ð™¡ð™ªð™©ð™šð™¡ð™® the government!!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# &gt;for good reason

No, the reasons are bad. I do not deserve any dunkings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Both of these are extremely valid. Also: putting your dog (RIP, Buster) in a fedora to make him look classy and cosmopolitan. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A: I've been here for a while.
B: please, call me Cybersmith.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah, yes, there is absolutely no #HASHTAG#.nnNepal just has a chronic tinsel shortage. #HASHTAG#://t.co/auFo6kIgxann#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hence my opinion that it would have been a poor choice for the final showdown of Season 2.

A Light cruiser is a serious threat to Mando, but not a totally insurmountable one.

Once he ejected the DTs, it looked as if he had a serious chance of victory.

An ISD removes that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You took that out of context.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Interviewer: please use only one word.

Nancy Pelosi, Mother of Lies, Whore of the Illuminati, Dark Mistress of Communism: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why, the understanding nature of strangers who absolutely will not use it as a cheap Ad Hominem when they disagree with us, of course! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Holy Goalpost Shifting, Batman!

First, you claim that Flash travelled back immediately. When I demonstrate that is false, you pivot to an issue with stakes, without acknowledging your error.

It seems that you are simply determined to hate great art. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Except the boycott would hurt the people you intend to help!

You can't just magically transform good intentions into good results.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And, most likely, card-carrying members of the same political party. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is a pretty strong example of why a one-state solution won't work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wise man does not celebrate the demise of another, even so misguided an enemy as Samoyedcore.

I shall remember my enemy, just as I remember all who have fallen along the way. Ultimately, must I stand in solitude?

Shall I be the last, alone in my glory? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think calling the evidence-based testimony of multiple medical specialists a "rumour" is a little dismissive.

Let children grow up, and if they elect to pursue your lifestyle as adults, by all means, allow them.

But spare the younglings from these Mengele-esque experiments!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not all Conservatives.

I hate how people ignore the fact that he was literally dragged back to Spain and tossed in jail for his crimes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Name one person the British Empire kidnapped and sold as a slave.

(remember, there is a distinction between states and their individual subjects. Joseph Fritzl locked his family in a cellar, but we don't blame the state of Austria-Hungary for that)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ð—–ð—¼ð˜‚ð—»ð˜ð—²ð—¿ð—½ð—¼ð—¶ð—»ð˜: whilst empowering a single, ambitious leader to enact his own grandiose will upon society has the potential to backfire, it also has the potential to be really, really fun to watch. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Okay, go through the most recent 20 posts. How many are abdl?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That means insurance costs go up, and it becomes too expensive for anyone who isn't already rich to own a business.

Essentially locking the poor out of ever moving up the economic ladder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chokey Bob, the Strangulation-Specialist Serial Slaughterer: crime victims are too "obsessed" with oxygen. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What?

A: no, he isn't.

B: please, call me Cybersmith.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# &gt;Is there an anti-capitslism legal system

There's China.

Venezuela.

A lot of the global population there.

&gt;nearly complete legal coverage

Unless you are motivated by retaining your (capitalist) profits, why should that matter to you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Hollywood's metrics are daft if they consider a film trilogy that made billions and billions of dollars to be underperforming. If those films underperformed, so did virtually all films ever made.

I like my tweets because I stand by what I say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# ...ever, there is no chance of success, then the roll hasn't served any purpose.

Player agency is maintained by you saying that they fail.

Rolling isn't a prerequisite of agency. If a player decides to, say, buy a drink in a tavern, they don't need to roll for it. They just do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I mean, the first one was, certainly, but it didn't want to force me down one specific path. I picked a high-strength, high-agility build, I tag unarmed, stealth, diplomacy... so I started with a stealth boy and brass knuckles.

Fallout 2 gives you a spear no matter what!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stories about the humour inherent in cross-cultural juxtaposition may not be your figurative cup of tea, but plenty of people do enjoy them. Stop being a killjoy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is trending.nnWow, it's so fantastic that the liberals got rid of Donald Trump and Dominic Cummings!!! Clearly, de-platforming Right-Wingers has made the world a nicer, more tolerant place. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One could load less-lethal rounds into an assault rifle.
There is no way to carry out a less-lethal abortion.

You have made a false equivalency. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# &gt;nobody on the left
&gt;democrats

What? Democrats are literal communist socialist freedom-haters. They are pretty far bloody left!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wow, you're so right!nnThen he should have done a matrix-style slo-mo flip over the criminal suspect, and punched his soul out of his body like the ancient one from Doctor Strange!nn#HASHTAG# are not superheroes. They are mortal men and women who volunteer for a hard task.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I understand that it shouldn't be, but it increasingly IS.

That's the reality that people are facing, and it's the reason for the backlash.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...esistance.

People just didn't want to admit that another war was inevitable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dang, that scar is gnarly. If you were a character in a Western, the 3rd act would reveal a shocking twist about how you got it. Presumably, you used to ride with desperados, acting as a femme fatale to facilitate their heists, but abandoned that life of crime to marry a Sheriff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He does make some interesting points...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sure, they got separatist military aid.nnSure, the Separatist HEAD OF STATE met with their leader.nnBut that doesn't invalidate the separatists at all... #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# &gt;You could say that about any technology ever

Bingo.

&gt;Every technologic breakthrough looks inevitable with hindsight.

And they all look impossible in foresight. At least, they do to miserable, pessimistic naysayers like you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes.
Because I stand by my words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The attack on the World Trade Centre occurred in 2001.

1990 &lt; 2001 &lt; 2007]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I am many things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Fallen order is just 5 years after ROTS, I think?

Judging by how old Luke looked in the trailer, I think this could easily be after Fallen Order.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stop being homophobic. If someone wants to share an intimate moment with a Drill Instructor, that's none of our business.

Also, why don't you ask the Ugandan soldiers who fought the LRA how harmless "brown kids" are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Eventually, it will get to a point where no more potent morphiate can exist because the molecule wouldn't be absorbed by human cells.

It will take time, but it's a solvable problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I never actually played street fighter. Is Ryu good?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# &gt;going out of their way not to promote my work

She really has a staggering sense of entitlement, doesn't she?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 2014 AD, Kotaku proclaimed: "Gamers are dead"!nnFive years later, Gamers still exist, and Kotaku is dying.nn#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Every addict thinks of himself as the exception.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Except that he provides evidence and citations to support it. Why do you believe that Rachel Maddow is infallible?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note the clearly defined calf muscles and boobies?

#USER# and #USER# are #HASHTAG#!!!!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What's the premise?

An ancient warrior-woman falls in battle, leaving behind an amulet imbued with her power, and this amulet is found by a man centuries later, who can call upon it to fight against injustice, taking on aspects of the champion who once bore it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Didn't one of them say that he felt sorry for slaves, but he found the institution too convenient to dispose of?

There was more nuance to the issue than OP implied.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Name even a single person (preferably a hereditary peer, but a life peer would suffice) who has been killed by Tory politics in the last ten years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much did you tune up the brightness in this screenshot to make your disingenuous rant?

This isn't what the actual show looked like. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good for you. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is the problem with not teaching classical philosophy in schools.

The Romans would know that a wise man simply chooses not to respond. Stoicism teaches us that we can only control our actions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why not?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This isn't "racist", paper made of bamboo is absolutely real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well? Was he?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I am many things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It was "homegrown". She defended one of our islands from a brutal South American dictatorship.

Thanks to Margaret Thatcher and her policies, those Falklanders were spared the gruesome fate which awaits people defeated in war by South American tyrants. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wrong.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What would you consider to be a "victimless" crime? Is attempted murder victimless?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Do you think he's just an invisible army of women?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One could load less-lethal rounds into an assault rifle.
There is no way to carry out a less-lethal abortion.

You have made a false equivalency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Freedom speaks for itself. What is right is right, however many people dictators may cow into silence. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I wonder why someone would call members of the "national SOCIALIST german worker's party" socialists. What a mystery. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You and #USER# are both wrong. You should watch the 2010 series of #HASHTAG#. Nothing is ever forgotten, not really. There is always some trace. #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>