<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Security by Design Enters Next Major Phase – PCR | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Local school districts get trained on new violence prevention strategy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | Wondering how to hide power cords? This $24 solution has 24,000 5-star ratings #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | Cold air’s back, let’s get serious about weekend snow #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Press Briefing by Press Secretary Jen Psaki, January 25, 2022 | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zim criminals go hi-tech – NewsDay Zimbabwe | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple ‘Hotel Key’ Demo | How Apple’s New Room Key Feature Works in iOS 15 | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#security #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Jersey Tightens Cybersecurity Rules for Water Systems | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | Dating apps to use when you’re bored of Tinder #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | VIDEO: State Rep. calls community safety meeting in Ferriday over gun violence concerns – Mississippi’s Best Community Newspaper #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DHS warns electrical infrastructure an ‘attractive target’ for domestic extremists | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Krunal Pandya’s Twitter Gets Hacked; Hackers Asks For Bitcoins From Krunal’s Followers On Cricketnmore | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Open Firefox Using Command Prompt on Windows 10 PC 2022 Tip | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global corruption report a damning indictment of Modi govt, which rode to power in wake of Jan Lokpal movement | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School investigation report details days surrounding Suffolk girl’s COVID-19 related death | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warzone Hacker Gets Tricked Into Showing Their Cheats on Stream | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Addressing the unprecedented behavioral-health challenges facing Generation Z #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Azure, Teams, Security Drive Record Quarter | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reddit users slam ‘Selfish’ wife slammed after she refuses to take husband’s ‘affair baby’ on family vacation | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Businessman creates dating app for men with small penises | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phone scam alert in Franklin County | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WVU leads global effort in steering the future of oral health through behavioral, social science lens | WVU Today | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | AFP launches seven days of online safety as students return to school #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple creates personal safety guide as AirTag concerns mount | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bored? Think twice before taking that Facebook quiz | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lilbits: What do you do when your phone stops receiving security updates? | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#security #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nazareth Area upends COVID safety plan at tense school board meeting. Masks now optional. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Releases iOS 15.3 With 10 Important iPhone Security Updates &amp; Fixes | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#security #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catfishing Cases and the Financial Losses That Come With Them Are Rising. The Public Wants Social Media Companies, Lawmakers to Crack Down on the Issue | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banking and financial services litigation: 2021 in review | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gwinnett Judge’s Indictment on Computer-Hacking Charges Hinges on What ‘Prosecution Knew’ | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delay in Creating New Cybersecurity Board Prompts Concern | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nassau County Executive Bruce Blakeman tells Governor Hochul to ‘stand down’ with appeal on mask mandate ruling | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Here’s how parents can help them stay safe on social media #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Complete takeover. Pushed into an old WindowsNT sandbox? Very Nasty. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even Johnson’s own fraud minister couldn’t bear the stink of this government | Simon Jenkins | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Special Needs Schools Stressed as Parents Neglect Responsibility :: Uganda Radionetwork | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL# Shuttered in Latest Spate of Global Takedowns | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the Marine Corps uses IT to defeat evolving threats &gt; United States Marine Corps Flagship &gt; News Display | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four more MCPS schools temporarily going virtual after COVID-19 review | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coronavirus cases in schools go down again | Coronavirus | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YouTube channels of crypto creators, Indian exchanges fall victim to scamming attempt | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New year, new resolutions from CES | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Letters: Answers for fighting crime? We already have plenty of those | Letters | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Brazos Valley task force created to combat child sex trafficking | Latest Headlines #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DHS Says US On ‘Heightened Alert’ For Russian Cyberattack | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | Jehovah’s Witnesses hope to help families with bullying #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling Civilian Casualties a ‘Failure,’ Democrats Urge Biden to Do Better | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Web Browsers Market – increasing demand with Industry Professionals: Google Chrome, Firefox, Safari (Apple) | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CoxHealth seeks help from college, high school students amid COVID-19 surge | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than 1,000 students were sexually abused at this university. An ex-NFL player wants their stories to be heard | Crime | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A WeatherFlow Tempest UDP Broadcast Receiver in Golang, Rust, Swift, and C++ | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#security #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Cleveland Rape Crisis Center receives $1.3 million grant, plans to work with LGBT youth, victims of sexual assault #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Fends Off 3.47 Tbps DDOS Attack on Azure Servers | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gun Control Advocates Hope for Progress, While Opposition Remains | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Premier of Tasmania – Strong Families Safe Kids reforms delivering positive outcomes, Tasmanians with Disability Supported #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ingram Micro acquires Keenondots to strengthen its cloud platform | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cequence Security collaborates with Tetrate to embed security into cloud native applications | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple issues watchOS 8.4 update with bug fixes, security updates | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents of Two Oxford High School Students Sue District Over Shooting | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | Governor Hochul Urges New Yorkers to Prepare for Dangerous Cold Temperatures Through Saturday Morning #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | Why Teen Mom’s Amber Portwood Walked Off the Reunion #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Urban Warfare Devastates 50 Million People Worldwide, Speakers Tell Security Council, Calling for Effective Tools to End Impunity, Improve Humanitarian Response – World | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money Laundering Picks Up Steam on DeFi Protocols: Chainalysis | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Five missing teenage girls found, 30 sex offenders arrested #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DOJ directs NBI to probe phishing schemes vs. teachers │ GMA News Online | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parent maces student after fight at Asheville High School | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Gun control advocates nervous as Supreme Court takes up first 2nd Amendment case in a decade #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Milwaukee musician’s Instagram hacked; victim of cyber scam | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man accused of shooting Sullivan Co. deputy hospitalized after being found unresponsive in jail – WJHL | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DeadBolt, the ransomware that attacks QNAP NAS: here’s how to protect your data | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salisbury council, staff discuss Parks and Recreation program investment to deter crime – Salisbury Post | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woodland Park school board approves memorandum of understanding with Merit Academy during special meeting | Pikes Peak Courier | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poland’s ruling party tries to block phone hack inquiry – POLITICO | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Sex workers, victims’ advocates at odds over Winnipeg’s bid to remove licences for sexual service agencies #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2022 Cybersecurity contest opens; Sheridan businesses lead past winners list | Local News | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hacker Finds Connected Cars’ Security Flaws | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Prince Andrew’s responses to Virginia Roberts’ catalogue of sex abuse allegations #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumer Reports: Why you should use an alternative email | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AT&amp;T (USA), Bitglass (USA) – The Oxford Spokesman | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Yonko wanted for multiple ‘wobbly wheel’ scams in Harris County, deputies say | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYT expose on India acquiring Pegasus spyware from Israel has left Modi govt without a fig leaf | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Skoda the latest brand to ditch safety tech amid semiconductor shortage #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life Clips Enhances Security Of BelfricsBT Blockchain With Disruptive XOR Transient Intelligent Cipher Process | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forbes India – Bitcoin: It’s Hard To Tell When The Crypto Bubble Will Burst, Or If There Is One | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff member injured, several students in custody after large fight at Meadowdale High School | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nvidia to arm Indonesian university students with AI skillsets | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | The Fifth Annual Black Lives Matter at School Week Set to Start Monday #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roadside bomb kills 4 police in restive southwest Pakistan | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 students charged after fight at Pahoa High &amp; Intermediate School on Hawaii island | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Indian Land school bus struck by two vehicles before crashing, injuring bus driver #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pomona Unified schools to start voluntary coronavirus testing for students – Daily Bulletin | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows 11 Build 22543 rolling out with UI improvements and more | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Mitigates 3.47Tbps DDoS Attack, a New Record | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woodland School District releases updated COVID guidance – Daily Democrat | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | CHILD TRAFFICKING EVENT WITH SPECIAL GUEST SENATOR TED ALEXANDER #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Join The NY Alumnae Chapter Of Delta Sigma Theta Sorority’s Human Trafficking Forum From Conversation To Commitment #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal Cyber Security Market 2022-2030, By Top Key Company Profiles – Cisco, Splunk, KnowBe4, Deloitte US, Microsoft, Sophos | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotify is reportedly taking down Neil Young’s music on Joe Rogan podcast objections | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Letter to the editor: Maine privacy amendment would recognize ‘right … to be let alone’ | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AT&amp;T CEO suggests Netflix’s price hike is great news for HBO Max | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# | Drop in #HASHTAG# pregnancy #HASHTAG# in #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# - Gaston County’s teenage pregnancy rate has fallen more than 60 percent over the last decade. The number of pregnant teenagers here has been progressively lower for... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian school guidelines detail dangerous COVID-19 conditions | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House attempts to strengthen federal cybersecurity after major hacks | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monitoring COVID Numbers a High Priority For Mascoutah School District – Herald Publications | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL# Closes $31 Million Series A to Automate Best Practices in Software Supply Chain Security for Cloud-Native Applications | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SB Technology to Offer iboss Zero Trust Cloud Security as a Managed Security Service | News | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couple steals 13 gold rings from 92-year-old during ‘test’ scam, deputies say | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gun Control Advocates Demand New Regulations After Michigan School Shooting | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rahul Gandhi kicks off Punjab election campaign after paying obeisance at religious shrines in Amritsar | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Arena Holding Will Present at the Emerging Growth Conference on February 2, 2022, as the Global Election Services Advisory Board is Formed | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | October is National Bullying Prevention Awareness Month, Jehovah’s Witnesses offer online resources #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | Nigel Girgrah, MD, PhD, on well-being and top stressors physicians are facing #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Teach Philosophy of Science in High School | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost half of organizations don’t use all of Microsoft 365’s features | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key steps for SMBs to stay safe from cyberattacks | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK companies told to bolster defenses against Russian cyberattacks | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greenwich Schools to Loosen Covid Mitigation Strategies; GHS Clubs to Resume In-Person Meetings | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Sex offender charged again with failing to abide by registry rules | Top Story #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | UScellular names sales manager | Mt. Airy News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whitmer says schools should return to in-person learning. Education advocates want state support to do it. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | City committee hears arguments for and against licensing sex workers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBB reports most common scams in Lincoln area | Community | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 10 Best Ethical Hacking Tools In India In 2022 | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#security #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bangor High School students continue to ‘mentor’ younger kids | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple wants to turn your iPhone into a contactless payment terminal | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#security #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Russia conducts false flag operations | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waterloo team competes in computer protection competition :: #URL# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frassati Catholic High School unveils plans for new sports complex | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hancock County Board of Education launching new website | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harrison County (West Virginia) Board of Education to meet Tuesday with multiple special recognitions | Harrison News | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trend Micro Charts Growth with Cloud Ecosystem Partners | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | People with anorexia and bulimia ‘bombarded with dangerous dieting adverts on Facebook’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Measuring success of a farm is more than just yields, prices | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher’s classroom intruder fight-off plan involves hockey pucks, as seen in viral TikTok | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education board weighing COVID pay bonus for Buffalo Public School employees, new hires | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher named in FIR urges students to call off protests | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | United Way presents: Empowering families with strength and healing while battling domestic violence – Orange Leader #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[University of Nevada, Reno partners with TalentSprint Inc. to offer TechWise program supported by Google that aims to increase diversity in technology education | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Security Gateways Market Size 2022 And Analysis By 2029 | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scammers on Social Media Stole $770 Million in 2021 According to the FTC Data / Digital Information World | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turkish businessman arrested in scheme with Utah polygamists | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Launch Your Career With a Cyber Security Degree | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FireFox Gold Drills More High-Grade Gold at the Mustajärvi Project, Including a Big Step Out to the Northeast | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Mexico’s governor signs up to be volunteer substitute teacher amid staffing shortage | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Millions of files being reviewed to identify victims of child sexual abuse #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dark Souls 3 exploit could let hackers take control of your entire computer | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HIV clinicians should ask gay men if they want to become fathers | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NDP MPs criticized for ‘terrible’ social media comments on Ukraine-Russia crisis – National | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting kids back to school without the COVID guilt | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | How Arthur Rock kick-started Silicon Valley | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.K. Warns Organizations of Cyber Attacks as Ukraine Tensions Rise | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vijayalakshmi’s post on parenting wins hearts | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAIC Emphasizing Digital Engineering for JADC2 | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gun control advocates express disappointment with Biden | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do Not Pay Any Online Purchases With A Credit Card in New York | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Roblox Safe for Kids? [Parents’ Safety Guide 2022] | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Predator Catchers sting leads Novi police to arrest man for allegedly arranging meetup with teen | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google is coming up with a new feature which is called “People Search Next” / Digital Information World | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[February is National Career and Technical Education Month | Community | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your 2022 Latinx Parenting Horoscopes and Power Words Are Here | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Chrome issues major update to all users over ‘critical’ security flaw | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#security #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | Terence Darrell Kelly pleads guilty to kidnapping four-year-old Cleo Smith #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nonprofits build house for licensed foster families | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | A secure future for children in Canada: X tips from experts #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wistar is awarded federal funds to boost biotech workforce | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPDATED: Stafford child abduction suspect arrested after standoff with deputies | Headlines | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Social Media Watchdog In The Works? – Media, Telecoms, IT, Entertainment | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Chrome issue with PDF showing as HTML files frustrating some | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Stop nagging!’: why China’s generation Z is resisting marriage and babies | China | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Govt’s anti-trolling bill should be scrapped: Law Council | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American-Islamic Relations Org. Calls for Federal Hate Crime Probe of ‘N***** Lover,’ Fire at Tenn. Interracial Couple’s Home | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | ‘Here We Go’: Fabrizio Romano and the Art of the Deal #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High school students gear up for firefighting careers | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College rejects voluntary recognition of Student Worker Collective at Dartmouth | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. appoints new Ambassador to S. Korea amid N. Korea’s multiple provocations : The DONG-A ILBO | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Karnataka e-portal hacking: Probe traces money to various accounts | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Is Lake Township, Ohio a hotspot for sex trafficking missing kids #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trial set in assault of Capitol Police Officer Brian Sicknick | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shawn Johnson and Andrew East to talk life, love, parenting in Columbus | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[Update: Jan. 27] Apple macOS 12 update tracker: Everything we know so far | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College Station man accused of selling drugs | Crime News | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft cloud revenues power Microsoft’s $51.7 billion second FY’22 quarter | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swedish village ‘Fucke’ wants to change its name, and you can see why, Sweden | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SCS Adolescent Parenting Program helps expecting and teen moms – FOX13 News Memphis | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran state TV shows dissidents’ images after apparent hack | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Midland Schools Not Putting Litter Boxes In Bathrooms For Furries, District Says | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pixel users experiencing touch screen issues after Android 12 update | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For moms, balancing pandemic parenting and work is like trying to solve an ‘explosive Rubik’s Cube’ | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Estate agency apologises for email hack and urges ‘caution’ if transferring funds – Property Industry Eye | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chromebook won’t print to an HP printer with Chrome OS 97? You’re not alone | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former employer accused Lincoln couple of embezzling $155K | Crime and Courts | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Best child lock | FOX 4 Kansas City WDAF-TV #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homer continues to rally in support of ‘walking miracle’ Tyson Garrett | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | Anti-Trafficking Ministries Now Fight QAnon Conspiracies T…… | News &amp; Reporting #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waterloo Schools seeking nearly $150,000 in state preschool funds due to COVID-19 impact | Education News | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DHEC, Greenville Co. Schools respond after district’s initial request for modified quarantine guidelines | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG#. | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# | NJ martial arts instructor accused of sexually assaulting 2 teens #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Enable HTTPS-Only Mode in Firefox Browser 2022 Tip | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why this will be just another eyewash and not make any reversal of policy direction | #HASHTAG# | #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>