<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sounds like being down on the farm............with no swimming pools...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If you're gonna wear his swim suit please don't post a pic of it......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of us have to to get up at 4 am, this is bullshit on a Sunday night.... #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Smells Like Mark Hamill....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did #HASHTAG# declare a fine state of affairs?....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One great thing about this #HASHTAG# deal is sports fans can expect everything to go up in price.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you put pop in your whiskey you're clearly insane.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You forgot the most important thing, LOVE!!, I'm just fuckin' with ya, I meant A&amp;W....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'd rather eat dirt....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The theme song to Welcome Back Kotter makes me sad....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a shit hockey player Crosby is, he hasn't done anything all season. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Sally didn't welcome you today... here she is.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember that time back in the 60's when it took forever to download an app and after it never worked, so you just said fuck it and started drinking booze.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Ugh........Italian, pasta!.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was told not to blame Gibbons, ok, he must be an awesome manager for someone to defend him, that's great. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make yourself a nice rhubarb and cheese #HASHTAG# and chill the fuck out.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Messa got tired reading all that...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're still too hot to let go.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Is that the version Stephen King didn't like?....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was the best hockey fight I've ever seen. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're hungry have yourself a nice cheese and pickle sandwich.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I like when sports channels air spelling and dog shows. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hazel Mae is the best sportscaster in the whole world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Might be a Tragically Hip fan....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently some guy named James Webb blasted off into #HASHTAG# .......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is this fanny pack on your Christmas wish list? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I took a knee and it hurt like fuck.......Messa needs pillows...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You should probably eat a sandwich right now.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah and he played great for Team Canada...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope this #HASHTAG# game doesn't overlap the #HASHTAG# .....wouldn't want to miss that awesome show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Fuck standing in line, I'd rather drink homemade beers with my aunt screaming in my head......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Can people actually differ sea salt from regular salt?.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah like nobody has heard that enough. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soft kittens are nice....dogs too but they bite....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Years ago working construction type job, as a crew we would go out to lunch and I'd always order a Julienne salad and this one fucker would say to me every time, rabbit food, I'd laugh and say ok man man.....He talked like Squiggy from Laverne &amp; Shirley so that was funny..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danica Patrick will win one of these days, LOL. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I just wanted to see Yo-Yo Ma perform.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When I lived in Newfoundland for one very long year, we ate rabbit and have to say that it was ok until the bones stated turning black right on the plate, after that my hunger went away...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm not a boozer, only drank one beer so far today.........(case)....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You talk too much". A phrase no man has ever heard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But putting 340 test in liquor stores is a good idea eh?.......Gonna be a long drive around Ontario and a trunk full of booze to find one.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'll go to the beer store tomorrow.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You might as well eat a #HASHTAG# I mean what the fuck else ya gonna do!?.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing about living in an apartment building is smelling other people's cooking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I was gonna try to make a #HASHTAG# tonight......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're aware that it's most likely done by groups who target and go to any protest just to disrupt it and who have no interest in the cause.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like having McDonalds, LOL just kidding, I don't eat horse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Toronto news and commentators mention Crosby yet today? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Only if you buy us some tim biebs....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I watch the #HASHTAG# game on #HASHTAG# or do I watch the #HASHTAG# on #HASHTAG# hummm tough choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Been there.........I mean yeah not good...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They are outsiders doing this for the sole purpose of pissing you off and media attention in a negative way...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when #HASHTAG# would bootleg booze across provinces, state lines and borders, those were good times..... #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hopefully you found some cool percussion.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the stale cigarette smell from my neighbours apartment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have one every morning but with cheddar.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You got a real bum's eye for clothes...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There's a lot of hair going on during that solo...... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I honestly never tried it.....and I'm Canadian...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Game should be starting by the time this song ends..... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Geez.......What do you get when you put a Blonde in the freezer?.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked science class an all but the only time I used a Bunsen burner was to heat up some knives....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I do, and use them, also vinyl and use them too......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maybe the Hurricanes are denied entry in Canada.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I deal with this whiskey thing all the time...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's actually a good episode and nice start....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My neighbour is a stupid cocksuckin' low life piece of shit and probably has brain damage from eating from the garbage bin at the back after the raccoons ate first and never took a bus to school because there wasn't one short enough.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What time does the Drive-In movie start?....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are soft sweet kittens a thing for #HASHTAG# ?......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah well who gives a fuck at this point......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best part in the new Superman movie is when we find out where he came from, coz we all didn't know that already. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fuckin' knew someone would miss read this......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Like when the Six Million Dollar Man uses his bionics?.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ritchie and the Fonz will make everything right....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That'll teach 'em, send a plastic toy...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah! Should be a wild and crazy time. #USER# I can't wait until the draft lottery. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly, who starts a hockey game at 8:00PM on a Sunday!!?......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Take care travelling on the tube....and elsewhere...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You're the best Twitter GM around of all pro sports.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully soccer becomes the number one sport in Canada.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm winning the #HASHTAG# tonight so you know the drill......don't fuck my mojo...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cool movie, the character was also played by Harrison Ford which is also worth watching and there's a show called Jack Ryan that is also very good......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably shoulda took a right at Albuquerque........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whaddya say, this might just call for a toast!!..... #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everybody is so tight assed these days yet Archie Bunker and The Jefferson's are still on TV, explain that to me...... I was gonna say you fucks but I held back...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somebody Get Me A Doctor, coz I'm too high...... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like tiny chocolate bars.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I get it why some don't like them, same as the Hip....not everyone is gonna like the same music or cheeseburger toppings, and it's fine....you gotta like dogs though, I mean c'mon...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Booze is my family and I'm rich with it.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I never DM's, not even from porn............messa sad...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Fuck Tim's bring on the Buds....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Think so, I'm on a Android box....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ya think there's enough college football games on today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah like all their draft picks really worked out for them. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new replay rule is awesome for baseball. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You might as well wear a jacket this weekend.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've watched fuck all of #HASHTAG# and I don't care...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I would wipe my face on it, oh fuck that's what happened....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who here makes the best Sheppard's Pie? My money is on #USER# ......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hope they find a good home for them....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I honestly don't recall this Sesame Street episode..... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He's stuck in the Tim's drive-thru coz of that fuckin' Biebs bullshit...........or he broke a fingernail....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The next time you decide to piss against the wind keep this in mind...... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just had some of my hot secret pasta sauce and now my mouth is on fire, cold beers should help....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If she caught a turkey I would freak right out....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She was clearly taken from her lunch break....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have yourself a nice bowl of garbanzo beans......and toast...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm told McDonald's coffee is better but what do I know, I prefer beers and whiskey..........and cheeseburgers ðŸ”...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My burger needs a little more bacon..... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I might be number 1 but you treat me like number 2......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really enjoy when a person has a conversation with a cashier and has no regard for the people behind them. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait to watch those after talking shows......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I have this album. His sound may have to do with working on Prism Armageddon album early on in his career...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nylander did his job, now he's going on a McDonald's run..... #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two rights make a wrong....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is like peas and carrots, you never know what you're gonna get.......wait that's not right....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Fuck off, you're not getting shit today............Have fun eating at the vending machines you sick fuck....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I`m gonna go lay down now...........fuckers...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bought a new can opener today and thank fuck it has instructions on the package.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Driving tomorrow morning is gonna be so fun...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Apocalypse Now and Full Metal Jacket?.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I second hand smoke at least a half pack a day. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You try to be nice and respectful but when you have cunts for neighbours you have to put your foot down and tell them face to face to fuck off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ooh, lovin' and a livin' and a treat me like a fool
(Didn't you? Didn't you)
I mean, you're doin' all you can to make me sad n' blue, yeah yeah
(Didn't you?) Uh.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It would be so much easier if they used Google maps..... #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if Huey Lewis watched #HASHTAG# ......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Is that a fact? I have no idea. The monetary situation is no comparison...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Probably thinks he's a Monkees.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Snortin' whiskey and drinkn cocaine......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Kevin Bacon penis run is better.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no wrong time to rock....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's #HASHTAG# go ahead and get shit faced....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Looks like a big boner....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He shoulda stuck to music with his brothers....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The new replay rule makes the long game even longer now, so awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I knew a guy that did that too, funny thing is he and his wife have good jobs, combined they are close to a hundred grand a year, yet they steal.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I knew it.............Messa rolling barrels now......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# still have a great chance to win this game. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# At least you don't play a shitty one like mine....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Honestly, who buys cheese that big?.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Give us a pic of the nutritional value, I bet it's high on all counts.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Simmons is the best writer of them all. #USER#: Fucking arrogance of media. #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You should probably eat a big fuckin' steak right now........with whiskey...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clean your wiper blades with WD40, you can thank me later.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If I get a cat in the new year you have to name it.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Somehow I knew you were into golden showers.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I can't say that name anytime fast...........or slow...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait for The Royal Wedding, I'm gonna record it and watch it everyday for life. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't had a Christmas tree in so many years but I will this year and show you all, not the Charlie Brown one though but a little better.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that was a heavy opening scene..... #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's clear of the food chain in that house...... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Tell two friends and they'll tell two friends and so on and so on and so on.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your conversation baby ain't got no end
Yakety-yakety-yakety-yak all the time,
You keep on talking baby drive me out of my mind
You talk too much..... #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# DOFO= Do Our Fuckers On.........I got it right eh?....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's something #USER# would wear....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Sidney Crosby back in the lineup tonight? I haven't heard anything in the papers or on sports channels. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't deny the fact that Ralph Furley knows what's going on..... #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I like when chicks call each other beautiful and lovely......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a good thing the #HASHTAG# owners locked up some players with huge contracts to this point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think they should play that #HASHTAG# commercial just a little more, it's not on enough. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I shouldn't drink so fast coz the next day all I do is complain how my throat is sore, maybe I'll just sip.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG#PA just keep sinking lower &amp; lower But hey, those hard working pencil pushers deserve a break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One hundred million dollars!!?.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This fucking show really went off the rails..... #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Domestic violence mainly happens because of cocksuckers like my neighbour.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I'll be able to sleep at night by knowing that. #USER#: There's a new Alvin and the chipmunks coming out -.-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fuck you asking us for, we're not watching.........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm gonna take all my clothes off and won't tell you why, also I put baby powder on my nuts....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never tasted a girl like you and her name is______]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Willis has another movie out now, I think it's his 20th this year....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Most people around me didn't understand and thought I was just crazy and foolish....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey! Did ya buy a giant TV today?......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A cup that turns blue when I pour a cold beer in it......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sweet feathery dish"!?.... LOL.... #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Coz the heat is off......Do I win a prize!!?........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Movie Alert!!......Bruce Willis has another film released today, movie fans are certainly on the edge of their seats for this one....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Guatemala a popular determination place this time of year?.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Would you like a delicious sandwich?....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crazy that some mutherfuckers thin Harlem Shak is cool or hip, or what the fucke ever, and yes I spelled skake wrong on purpose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Probably because they are cunts and can't speak English properly..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I just thought everyone was outside having a smoke......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think people that live in apartment buildings should slam their doors harder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be surprised if they call this a goal..... #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your ear hairs look wonderful today....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pricks #USER#: Wow, Toronto has the first PP of the game? Are you sure you made the right call, refs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At this point in my life do I really need laser eye deal?.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Never worked for my punk ass....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ah the youth of today, so inspiring....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I like I Love It Loud by them, that's about it....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The place where nothing cost a dollar.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You don't even know that Monday is pizza day.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes and created by Hugh Dillon, lead singer of Headstones.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This by far his best version and it is inline with this fucker...... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I hear Ottawa and Ukraine are nice this time of year, you have some nice choices...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Remember to never mix whiskey with pop, ice is ok but anything else is insane......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Wendy's dinner tonight!...........and whiskey...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Cool, I'll have a Teenburger with fries and rings........and a beer, no root........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should start wearing turtleneck sweaters..... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I should get a pet but always worried to leave it alone, maybe I'm just looking for excuses...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That one came outta left field....]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>