<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Out in the World: Global Black Pride announces 2022 in-person event and leadership team
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Swedish PM picks Mikael Damberg as finance minister
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC slammed for failing LGBT+ people – especially trans lives – in damning open letter

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Cruel’ bid to force trans people into wrong prisons condemned in House of Lordsn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trans Pride flag planted at Antarctica’s highest peak to celebrate “resilience” of community
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[60 female and non-binary artists from Northern Ireland to watchn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC doubles down on support for infamous anti-trans article in infuriating response to complaints
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some parliamentary stuff...nnComment and Features is a right mix. Suffice to say that in the season of goodwill to all, some outlets have very little goodwill for trans folks. Tread careful.nnLGBT+ rights and issues in sub-Saharan African#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jessica Alves puts on VERY busty display in cleavage enhancing top and corset as she flies to the UK after revealing she's considering voice feminisation surgery #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SNP lawyer accused of insulting MP in leaked email
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Sex Education’ Gets More Inclusive in Its Intimacy
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Presenter comes out live on-air as trans-masculine non-binaryn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Manchester set to get the UK’s first purpose-built LGBTQ+ Housing Development?
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loudoun County 'boy in a skirt' is spared prison after victim's family asked judge not to jail him
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AND JUST LIKE THAT'S QUEER MIRANDA STORYLINE IS A TV CAR CRASH'
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which Countries Recognize Third Gender Option on Passports?
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airline To Offer Non-Binary Ticket Option Following Gender ‘X’ Ticket Rown#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JK Rowling address tweet by trans activists won't face police action
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy Philipps says eldest child Birdie 'discussed' coming out as non-binary with her as she labels them 'the coolest' for embracing their true identity #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In part two of JULIE BURCHILL'S denunciation of woke and its celeb disciples, she asks: What would the Suffragettes make of M&amp;S selling hijabs for four-year-old girls - and throwing open female changing rooms for trans women? 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that a "before" and "after" picture?

Ada to Adam: True story of hen that became a cockerel shows only humans react to gender swaps
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Push to ban trans competitors from women’s sport
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents Take Legal Action Again UK Govt Over School Guidelines
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex Reassignment Surgery Market Size, Landscape, Industry Analysis, Business Outlook, Current and Future Growth By 2029 | Rumer Cosmetic Surgery, Transgender Surgery Institute, Mount Sinai Centre for Transgender Medicine and Surgery (CTMS), Phuket Interna
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting. We spoke with this journo to suggest most trans folks WEREN'T trying to "erase" her...but guess the wordcount was needed nnWhy the Harry Potter generation rejected JK Rowling n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beijing 2022 - Timothy LeDuc could make history and become the first nonbinary winter Olympian
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands Sign Petition in Solidarity With J.K. Rowling
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A right to speak over
#URL#
‘How insane does he sound?’ a BBC doctor was chastised for referring to men as “people with prostates.” 
#URL#
I can’t wait five years just to feel comfortable in my own body
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden administration denounces forced genital surgeries on Intersex Awareness Day
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK News: hairdressing and anti-trans schools policies seem to be to the fore!nnNot exactly. The ask was for passports that specify a non-binary gendernnNo obligation to provide UK passports that did not specify the holder’s gendern#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The UK Government has lost control of its woke civil service
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lorraine Kelly doubles down on trans allyship in wake of Kathleen Stock TV clash
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Awesome moment’: Dana Zzyym celebrates as first American with an ‘X’ gender passport
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nepal's third gender people are at greater risk of contracting HIV: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USA Swimming official quits in protest over transgender swimmer Lia Thomas
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘NFT’, ‘DOUBLE-VAXXED’ AND ‘CHEUGY’ AMONG COLLINS DICTONARY’S TOP 10 WORDS FOR 2021
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girlguides launch probe into trans Commissioner, 58, over saucy dominatrix-style picture 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis Of The Whole Life Order Imposed Upon Wayne Couzens – Umar Azmeh Writes For The Barrister
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the graphics on this article will have your eyes out!

Anonymity No More? Age Checks Come to the Web.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not all menstruators are women': Why trans and nonbinary folks want to talk about their periodsn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marxism, moral panic and the war on trans peoplen#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sam Berkeley: Enough with the trans moral panic 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not entirely sure this falls within our remit. But since one of our clippers clipped it, we’ll leave it if anyone is interested in reading. But tread cautiously!

WPUK submission: WESC Inquiry into GRA Reform
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Atheist Richard Dawkins signs controversial declaration opposing gender reassignment surgeries and puberty blockers for children
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using intersectionality to examine organizational justice can paint a fuller picture of the discrimination experienced by LGBTs in the Federal service.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming Out Chats: Jodie Harsh and L Devine in conversation
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What? Did activists turn up and forcibly remove his dressing gown?

Hugh Sheridan poses naked in a silk robe as he opens up about his mental health battle after being 'cancelled' by transgender activists for playing a genderqueer character in a musical
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why I’m celebrating the trans Drag Race contestants over the straight cisgender onen#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Piers Morgan mocked by Have I Got News For You panel after branding time on show 'awful'
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comment and Features is a right mix. Suffice to say that in the season of goodwill to all, some outlets have very little goodwill for trans folks. Tread careful.nnWhy am I being abused for trying to improve the gender recognition process?n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Peace exhibition at Gillian Jason Gallery: new Soho space celebrates art by black womenn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Father of UPenn swimmer slams NCAA 'cop-out' on trans athletes and urges USA Swimming to tighten the rules as he says his daughter has lost spots in races because of trans athlete Lia Thomas and teammates are 'really unhappy'
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 times Harry Styles made our queer little hearts go all aflutter
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quidditch leagues set to pick new name after JK Rowling trans row
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human rights law prof says inquiry signals “path towards reconciliation” | ABC News
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AJLT: Should We Still Define Our Sexuality So Rigidly When Gender Is A Fluid Construct?
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trans employee who spoke out against Netflix’s Dave Chappelle special resigns
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So keen, they wrote it twice!

Sporting advantage tips scales of complex trans athletes debate

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homophobic and transphobic acts in St Andrews branded ‘disgraceful’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radio presenter comes out as transmasc non-binary live on air in heart-warming videon#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the student survey responses shared by academics and you’ll see why Professor Hambling is justified in burning hers

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LGBT lives aren’t political, so stop treating us like they are
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Spectator. Nuff said...

Why did lawyers try to cancel me over trans rights? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why I'm more optimistic for Britain in 2022 than almost anywhere else in the world: Author NIALL FERGUSON on the vaccine triumph, the refusal to cave in to the woke mob and that stoical determination to keep calm and carry on 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JK Rowling opted not to appear in Harry Potter’s Return To Hogwarts reunion special
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEX AND THE CITY REBOOT NEEDS INTERSECTIONAL FEMINISM AND SELF-AWARENESS, UNIVERSITY PROFESSOR SAYS
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Universities union backs trans rights in row over anti-trans professor Kathleen Stock
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proposals to offer more places at special school to pupils with SEMH needs 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comment &amp; Features is a total mix…but a fair few positives!

Equal Play: Transgender Athletes Talk Fitness &amp; Fairness
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex Education continues to fly the flag for representation as it shakes up the TV landscape
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transgender man, 22, boasts that he can steal a girlfriend from ANY other guy because he 'knows how the vagina works' - and he uses first-hand knowledge of periods and make-up to win them over
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our teenage children went into hospital and didn't come home alive'
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serious misgendering in this piece...

Trans, whose name is Fufau, talks about financial difficulties and says she doesn’t have a job: “I won’t do prostitution myself.”
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nolan Investigates review — examining Stonewall, brick by brick
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPenn swimmers considered boycotting final meet over transgender teammate Lia Thomas
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK News with loads of Stock...

BBC row erupts as thousands hit out at corporation over controversial article
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ACLU’s rewriting of history shows just how dangerous the insidious march of trans ideology has become
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would a feminist Glasgow look like?
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police take no action over tweet that revealed JK Rowling’s home
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comment and Features broadly OK…but some spite nuggets

MY SECRET I’m transitioning male to female but my gran is the only person who doesn’t know #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hugo Weaving reveals why no gay actors were cast in the lead roles of his cult 1994 movie The Adventures of Priscilla, Queen of the Desert 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Renfrewshire residents urged to seek domestic abuse help over festive period
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delta Air Lines accused of discrimination after ‘refusing non-binary passenger’n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cis people get gender-affirming healthcare over the counter. Why can’t trans folk have the same?n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas’ reviled abortion ban temporarily blocked by judge: ‘The fight has only just begun’
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Northern Ireland art group Array Collective wins 2021 Turner prize
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In just a single day, three trans people were brutally murdered in Colombia 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trans teens sue school board over abhorrent bathroom ban: ‘It’s discrimination, plain and simple’
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain's first openly HIV-positive mayor quits as Labour councillor over series of racist and offensive tweets in which he used transphobic slurs and compared Muslim women to penguinsn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tory health minister Sajid Javid thinks trans-inclusive language ‘could literally kill people’
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Father is SUING woke Loudoun County after his 15-year-old daughter was 'raped' in 'gender-fluid' girls' bathroom by a 'skirt-wearing male student' - only for cops to arrest HIM after he complained at school board meeting
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over in International News things get better. Except in the USA, where the pace of anti-trans is hotting up again.

Republican senator rings in the new year with two cruel bills attacking trans kids
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Archbishop Desmond Tutu compares barbaric anti-LGBT+ laws to apartheid: ‘I can’t keep quiet’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keir Starmer leads his 'patriotic' party on the road to nowhere - LEO MCKINSTRY
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eddie Redmayne brands his Oscar-nominated role as transgender artist in The Danish Girl ‘a mistake’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice as an article about the difficulties of dating for men with small penises, including an intersex man #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Island bosses agree to accept non-binary applications ahead of 2022 seriesn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top TV comic Kiri stands up for LGBTQ+ youth clubs in Gwynedd
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British Airways to stop using 'ladies and gentlemen’ in announcements #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PSNI mulling over landmark judgement on recording non-criminal acts which people find offensive
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last but by no means least…

Model Talulah-Eve says 'fight still goes on' during Black History Month
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of West Side Story’s biggest changes is a powerful, poignant win for trans representation
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesters stage ‘die in’ outside NHS HQ in powerful demonstration against trans healthcare crisis
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brian May says Queen would be “forced” to have people of different races, sexes and a trans person if they started in 2021n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dave Chappelle addresses trans community directly and lashes out at Hannah Gadsby
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theatre for women and non-binary writers to open in north London
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It took almost 30 years for me to realise I’m trans – you don’t always ‘just know’ 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transphobic hate crimes rise in Lancashire while homophobic attacks remain in the hundreds
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We would suggest that that places it firmly into the realm of police, not press.

A bona fide journo should identify who they are, where they are from and why they want to tlk.

Someone refusing to do that is not on the level.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New generation of Asian influencers share the future of the metaverse
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Island 2022 accepting applications from non-binary contestants in push for diversityn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix stars to back staff walkout demanding support for trans people after Dave Chappelle special
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lecturers’ union has ‘effectively ended’ my career, says professor at centre of transgender row 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The nature and non-binary baby names every parent will be considering in 2022n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Bond boss suggests Idris Elba is in the running to replace Daniel Craig
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Humiliated but Determined’: Pro-Trans UK Doctor Suspended for ‘Insulting’ Tweets
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NHSE sanctions limit basic healthcare for young trans peoplen#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate crime rises 10 per cent in London in one year
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In International News, transphobia season is getting going in the US. Also, papers continue to froth over trans sportswomen

Biden nominee Holly Thomas confirmed as 9th Circuit federal judge
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Lewis issues lukewarm response to backlash over ‘playful’ new advert
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This could have been quite a good piece. It isn’t….

Finding love as a trans woman 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forest Hill school wins top award for LGBTQ+ inclusion work
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senegal rejects chilling bill that would have doubled punishment for gay sex and criminalised allies
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British media, ‘your bigotry is killing trans people’n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mum fuming after being unable to buy gender 'X' plane ticket for her non-binary childn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ooops...we left three stories in a single tweet.

The extra two are:

‘How insane does he sound?’ a BBC doctor was chastised for referring to men as “people with prostates.” 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comment and Features is the regular mix, but nuggets of spite every so often. Tread careful!nnMARY HARRINGTON: How could the Lords vote to let trans women into female prisons after this fiasco? nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fury as psychologists are encouraged to call their clients 'SLUTS' if requested
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lorraine Kelly Won’t Be Having Any of This TERF-y Nonsense, Thank You! 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So. This appears to be not true. But hey! It’s January!!!

Universities withdraw from Stonewall workplace league
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ceredigion gets behind Hate Crime Awareness Week
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Belvoir’s The Boomkak Panto is a joyous, subversive and Australian twist on the classic Christmas tradition
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still looking for someone to work on the next story. 

For something so significant – allegedly – it is getting very little coverage in the US press…being picked up mostly by far right outlets and the UK’s Daily Mail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Spirit Day? Why celebrities are going purple to support LGBTQ youth: 'We stand against bullying!'
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trans worker ‘bullied by manager’ at Zara
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Side Story banned in Saudi Arabia and parts of Middle East over trans character
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Department of Health pulls out of Stonewall scheme amid single-sex wards row #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hollyoaks star joins parade at Alsager Pride #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 Online Resources to Help LGBTQ Youth Find Support
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pilot program offers cervical cancer screening for transgender men, nonbinary individuals
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Mail has been writing a lot about trans folk lately...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What is disturbing is the way in which they keep repeating the canard that the only issue with Kathleen Stock is that she has said that "biological sex is real", when it is very clear that individuals have many more issues...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survey asking if “queers” should use “normal people” bathrooms goes around school
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tories should give non-binary people legal recognition by 2024, says equalities committeen#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same-sex marriage backed by Chile’s MPs
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Filmed in 2019’: Harry Potter fans react to way Return to Hogwarts distances itself from JK Rowling #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oxfam drops Wonder Women Bingo game celebrating 'inspiration woman' including JK Rowling after trans protests #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sister of federal officer killed by extremist sues Meta for promoting 'inflammatory' content
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big (and real) stories in UK News: gender neutral passports and voter id proposals. Froth: JK Rowling making waves again…

Supreme Court backs Government's decision not to allow gender-neutral passports
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Large majority of Scots think people should be ‘free to express their trans identity’
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JK Rowling accuses 3 people of sharing her address online
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frustration at Conversion Therapy ban proposal with 'worrying loophole'
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US figure skater becomes first non-binary athlete to qualify for Winter Olympicsn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Non-binary and nature names set to top the list of baby names in 2022n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONTENT QUEENS 1000-lb Sisters: How can I watch season three?
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Footy legend Dani Laidley wears 'D' earrings in a nod to new girlfriend Donna who joined her in a hero's return to the AFL club she once coached and won a premiership
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transgender professor pushes to normalise paedophilia, coins term 'minor-attracted persons'
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeopardy! champ Amy Schneider taught 83-year-old man to accept trans people #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britons value stopping hate speech over free speech new poll shows
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: LGBT+ veterans stripped of medals will have them returned by Remembrance Sunday
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmmm. Reading the article, this seems to be having a go at trans folks by proxy…nnSquatters force landlord to put Cardiff shop sale plans on holdn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QuidditchUK hopes to be renamed and 'distance' from JK Rowling after trans comments
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last but by no means least…

Jeremy Clarkson worried Diddly Squat farm cows are 'lesbians' and bull is 'trans' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suit settled over trans teen's suicide at detention center
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘The Transgender Issue’: it’s time for a reset in talking about trans rights
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contested Bosnian Holiday and Hungarian Election Trigger Online Violations
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 glaring red flags from the Tory government’s proposed so-called conversion therapy ban
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the law firm that acted for Forstater
Doyle Clayton
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Island 2022 could feature first non-binary Islandern#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shotgun Carousel's Christmas Extravaganza Announces Guest Stars
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than 200 women and transgender inmates to be transferred from Rikers into state custody
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And finally, Arts, Entertainment &amp; Culture

Child of evil murder doll Chucky confirmed as canonically genderfluid in new series
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M&amp;S praised for new feature on staff badges
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out' on the force: Transgender law enforcement officers say they fear backlash from both their coworkers and the LGBTQ community
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lloyd Webber criticises film version of Cats as ‘off-the-scale all wrong’
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College student mocked for complaining about 'cisgender men' who installed radiators in his roomn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The BBC visits a retirement home for third gender people in Pakistan: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hogwarts Legacy could be in trouble and delayed until 2023
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Horrific TERFs’ won’t stop Little Mix icon Jade Thirlwall from being an unwavering trans ally
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of Wonder Sets Bar for LGBTQ Media Production
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Dakota becomes first state to advance ‘shameful’ anti-trans bill in 2022
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The parents have spoken! Furious moms and dads confront Loudoun County school board and reveal they've filed petitions to have chair and three board members removed after boy-in-a-skirt rape 'cover-up'
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: University that is being sued by law student for dragging her through disciplinary after she said 'women have vaginas' during transgender seminar plans to fight the legal action
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queer Wales and the anniversary of Section 28 repeal
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And last but by no means least…

Eddie Izzard, 59, opts for an eye-catching fuchsia pink coat and stiletto boots as she heads out for a stroll in Chinatown
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jessica Alves goes BRALESS in a steamy photoshoot after losing 5.5 stone
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gender diversity in nursing: time to think again
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This, amongst many other reasons, is why we mostly have given up on complaining about the BBC nowadays... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy Philipps: I received messages from other moms after talking about my kid's gender identity
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US issues first gender 'X' passport that's not male or female to Navy veteran
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leading group of girls' schools says it 'will not accept transgender pupils over fears admissions policies based on gender' will 'jeopardise status as single-sex institutions' - as union calls on Government for new guidance #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transgender UPenn swimmer Lia Thomas wins the 100m AND 200m freestyle races against Harvard days after USA Swimming said it would release new policy on whether 'elite trans athletes' will still be able to compete against biological women #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Straight White Men writer Young Jean Lee: ‘Diversity is not some moral imperative like vegetable eating’n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trans Joy: 23 trans and non-binary people share what’s making them feel hopeful for 2022n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[International News includes a lot of David Chapelle. Also a disturbing allegation from a school in Loudoun County

Feds OK Colorado plan to cover gender-affirming care
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Island and the boring, right-wing obsession with LGBTQ inclusionn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trailblazing non-binary Green Party activist Tom Pashby wants to make history yet againn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eight-year-old trans girl says transphobic Texas lawmakers ‘are just scared of us’
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Piers Morgan sparks outrage by calling British Airways’ gender neutral greeting ‘virtue-signalling nonsense’
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Just Like That... fails Che Diaz with a clichéd take on non-binary representationn#URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>