<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# hear that loud n clear. i love animals, but since they suffer &amp; die as well, everything's tainted here. &amp; ppl ruin things so badly, it sort of eclipses how great animals are. not animals fault at all of course, just how shitty ppl are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's not a fam tree. fams destroy trees (toilet paper, food packaging, wood to make homes, etc)
it's a chain. chained in pain, suffering, &amp; misery
my part of the chain dies w/me: childfree for life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ALL lives matter

as long as yr among the richest 1% in the world

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why ask why?njust be cruel n selfish #HASHTAG# ppl are meat-eating, leather-wearing, procreating cruel n selfish machinesn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ppl, i know our world is ending, but be calm &amp; carry on, keep going to work, so the fat cats at the top, their $ can continue to make $ at a rate that is satisfactory for themnthank you 4 yr cooperationn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[watching a doc last night, almost changed the channel, bc 2 ppl were having a loud, nasty argument in a small apt, &amp; the poor dog was like, "stop fighting please!"
all the abuse animals, pets have taken from ppl, but also having to witness all these horrible rows #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i've gotten "yr lucky" incl my mom. thanks, mom!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is NOT right. i don't need her reminding me i only had 1 parent: a crazy 1 (also a reluctant 1, selfish, lazy, uncaring, incompetent)
i wake to a brutal instant mind rape: another fuckin day. then there r plenty more mind rapes to endure
her showin me how crazy she is: FUCK!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yr shrinking soul,
But there won't be a single thing
That you can do
He's a god, he's a man,
He's a ghost, he's a guru
They're whispering his name
Through this disappearing land
But hidden in his coat
Is a red right hand
You don't have no money?
He'll get you some
You don't have]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i have very sensitive sores on 1 side of my mouth. i have sensitive teeth on the other side. so when i was eating #HASHTAG# ice cream yesterday, i let it melt on 1 side, then switched it over to the other side when all was left was the chocolate-covered nutsnLIFE IS GOOD! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["justice" would be no more meat, animal products. they can have whatever meat, etc that exists now, but absolutely no more legal violence against animals
those who have profited from animals' misery are Nazis. take their $ (they don't deserve it), &amp; use it for animal sanctuaries #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how all animals should be treated: well
they cert shouldn't be treated like enemies, criminals, or worse, which is how defenseless animals are treated on factory farms #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[once again, they're cooking steak on 1 of PBS's cooking shows: negating their own climate change programming &amp; promoting unnecessary animal cruelty to boot #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's always been a world of countless horrorsnbut just keep calm &amp; carry onnkeep adding to sufferingn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i like bein reminded how tiny &amp; insignificant i am. i don't even amount to lint in the universe's belly button #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i wake encased in filthy bedding, bc i'd rather not exist than do laundry. it would require less effort, &amp; be much, much more fulfilling, to pass into nonexistence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[got another letter from my mom. she's still obsessed w/my grandma's 100th b-day, which was last year. the news is Biden still hasn't sent her a card. i might have to email her. i really feel it's abusive for her to keep reminding me i only got 1 parent: who's crazy &amp; useless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this woman in the supermarket parking lot was yelling at 1 of her kids while she &amp; her other kid were in the middle of the lot: instead of on the side, closer to the cars, so they wouldn't be in the way. a driver was very patient waiting behind her. i prob would've honked, but]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[whilst i slumber, existence removes my soul, has its way w/it, then returns it b4 i wake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[once again, how do you get on the news? by being cruel &amp; stupid. (from memory) "yes, i'd like a vaccine for my (7-mo old)," a mom
for the baby you forced into the world knowing damn well there was a pandemic raging?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[saw a squirrel where i put the whole, unsalted peanuts today, &amp; figured that's what she was there for, then realized she was stuffing her mouth w/grass
i dk: maybe making a nice, soft bed for a baby? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all these ppl in constant pain comin into contact w/1 another: &amp; all the poor, defenseless animals
recipe for disaster, cruelty, violence, &amp; suffering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["everything in moderation"
def incl existence. my body, mind, soul always tellin me i've had too much of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["cave-ripened cheese?! yeah, right! i'll believe it when i see the cheese cave! SHOW ME THE CHEESE CAVE!" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the internet has prob been horrible for pets: takin attn away from them. i think of Berkeley literally standing between my ex friend's face &amp; his phone
if you have pets, please make sure they get the attn they deserve. petting, cuddling is good for you &amp; them #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what about the state of the union for factory farm animals? or the chronically, desperately miserable who need help leaving this world (ppl were allowed to force em into), but they can't get it?
won't matter to the masses as usual i reckon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[poor squirrel out there lookin for peanuts where i usually put them
"peanuts gotta fall from the sky everyday! wtf?!"
sorry, didn't go out today. more to come, tho #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ripping, tearing trap of existence. tears the soul &amp; flesh into tatters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i was a burden baby
result of teen sex, i was not wanted nor loved. i was a burden. "all i did was have a lil sex! this is unfair! this is bullshit! this lil shit is ruining my life!"
my mom blamed me 4 being born when i was a kid "i could do this, that if not 4 u!"
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["there's a smile when the pain comes. the pain's gonna make everything alright"
-Black Crowes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the life of diarrhea
blast, squirt, trickle, drip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[there is nowhere 2 go

there is nothing 2 do

there is nothing 2 ingest

2 quell an existential crisis

2 satisfy a soul that wants 2 die but is afraid 2 take the necessary steps

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yay! the #HASHTAG# (no hashtag intended) in my bank account are bigger! what could be more important? #HASHTAG#arcasmn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#y #HASHTAG#elfish #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[listening 2 a song

reminds me of my hypocrite breeder

(shit. they all are)

"friend" he's a perv. but once he had a daughter,

WORLD, U BETTER CLEAN UP YR ACT!

&amp; not be vulgar anymore

that's how breeders do it

force em into the world

then complain about it

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[calm clam (anagram) yeah, they seem pretty fuckin calm to me
don't need/want to eat y'all. y'all can just chill far as i'm concerned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[crowded subway car. man standing behind woman. he's close to her, but not touching her. he involuntarily becomes erect &amp;, w/o moving any other part of his body, his penis is now touching her. if he goes backward, he puts his ass in woman's crotch, so he doesn't move
is crime?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i â¤ï¸ squirrels! they're nuts about nuts. i used to have an outdoor pet squirrel: Nutsie. i only fed her pure, unsalted nuts. seeing a squirrel hop after you: priceless #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wow! it's been a long time since i was inside a fast-food restaurant. what i miss most about them are the ambiance, the decor, &amp; mixing/mingling w/the creme de la creme of society #HASHTAG##HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how you treat him is how his life goes
-Yellowstone
yep.&amp; with 2 parents who never wanted/loved me, it's been a shitty 1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[unless 1 is lucky, pain &amp; fear is the cost of admission 2 an early reentry 2 nonexistence 
but pain &amp; fear, i know. i know them intimately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[blocked an mf for bein overrated. mf's getting beaucoup likes for posting shit i, &amp; others, have already posted. not accusing the mf of rippin anyone off, but A LOT of ppl have had the same fuckin thoughts. diff is i got a paltry amount of likes, if any, &amp; this mf is overrated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[breeders know it's a fucked up world, but then they have a kid, look around, see the world's still fucked up &amp; say, "wait a second, world. i know you were fucked up, but now i've had a kid, i'm special, so my kid is special, &amp; it's time for you to clean up yr act immediately!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dead soul ghosts of sue asides haunting those who deserve it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my mom broke her silence by sending me a postcard saying my grandma is 99 + 7 mos old. yesterday, an email saying she's 99 + 8 mos. no offers to help in any way. so lucky to have such a useful, crazy ass mom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wtf are you braggin about: 31 flavors? mental illness, counting the animals too, bc of what ppl, the world, other animals, existence have done to them, has ZILLIONS of flavors #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[watching "Incitement," &amp; this actress inspired the above comment. clearly beautiful, but always dressed conservatively, classy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if i hear yr son playin his loud fuckin music again, i'm gonna crack some nuts in my nutcracker #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[she was so fucking stupid. the bathroom at the bookstore was filthy bc no 1 cleaned it, &amp; the sink was always pretty clogged. u had 2 wash yr hands fast, bc it filled up quickly. the water had 2 be shut off 1 day bc plumbers were working. she went down 2 see if the water was back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[could be wrong, but i don't think squirrels get an emoji here. chipmunks do, &amp; they're great, but they ain't squirrels
why do ppl love birds but hate squirrels?
bc they're stupid #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[to go out all those times, unsmiling, into the world of unsmiling ppl, i know there are smiles out there, mostly fake i assume, but, at work, shopping, for ex, not a lot of smiles, &amp; have kids anyway
wtf?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[they're both helping each other get thru it, &amp; that's the beauty of animals &amp; those who love them #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[almost played goat in scrabble, but gout instead for more points. won't post a pic of gout tho. true story: a coworker had gout &amp; took off her shoe &amp; sock to show it to me in the breakroom. i didn't mind; i fancied her. nothing ever happened between us tho: wasn't gout's fault #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[soul, body, mind: all in turmoil 
free fallin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# no chance. she wants me to clean her mess: no way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the realer you are, the less popular you are
Ryan Seacrest is a bitch. he's a fakeass smilin, laughin (when there's nothin to smile or laugh about), lyin, fake complimentin motherfucker #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[always trying to fill insatiable holes. the hole in the soul, &amp;, not joking, but the piss &amp; shit holes too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the obsessive, repetitive, invasive thoughts that never leave 1 alone for too long
the glimmer of hope that attempts to betray the brick wall of despair that's been built solidly over the decades w/pain, misery, madness, fear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is that it? are ya still pissed that Jews supposedly killed that fictional character jesus all those centuries ago? yeah, that makes a lot of sense #HASHTAG# n#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i would've majored in Hari Kari if possible &amp; if i'd known how shitty things would get]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# well, he's dead now. we've gotta let go of guilt when it comes to the dead; they're fine. i don't even really feel guilt. my ex wanted me outta there; it was NYC; i couldn't afford to live there at all, so i had to move to another city 
circumstance pushes us around]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sex is the devil
it's why i've suffered (as have countless) for decades w/prob decades more of "natural" life 2 go

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[they were talking about the child tax credit on PBS Newshour, &amp; everyone loves it. yes, reward cruelty. David Brooks said, "no one's gonna have kids to get it" $100s/mo? really? gonna hafta disagree w/ya there. ppl will chain their kids to the radiator &amp; spend the $ on drugs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[such a backward society
all these ppl that need organs &amp; want 2 live
1 could offer 2 donate 1's entire body in exchange 4 a "good" death &amp; 1 would surely be turned away

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the mind's gonna ask what if? what if you did this/that?
well, there's still the chronic pains worsening w/time, chronic exhaustion, having to deal w/shit ppl, having to clean or live in filth, having to do laundry or wear filthy clothes
then there's all the other shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[goddamn, at least no one can accuse me of tryin to get laid here. i'm disgustingly real. tho w/our filthy asses, we all are really: except those who use colostomy bags!
"&amp; i say to myself, what a wonderful world"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["don't treat pregnancy like it's some special achievement. crack whores have babies. all u have 2 do is spread yr legs &amp; invite some1 2 jizz in u"
-Trash Fire (movie)

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[suffering mind, soul, body trapped in decades-long horror story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i was talking to a woman on Plenty of Fish yrs ago &amp; she said we literally have nothing in common, when of course we literally have MANY things in common, so i made a comment like, yeah, except for a brain: no profanity or anything. she got me kicked off the site!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you don't need to eat any fruits or vegetables. just pray to god to remove that undigested meat that's clogging up yr tubes &amp; has you completely constipated #HASHTAG##HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[for all the times i've felt like a loser &amp; a coward simply for continuing to exist, in addition to all the other shit (a shitload), forgiving my parents for fuckin me into this massively fucked-up world, &amp; all the other subsequent ways they failed me (many), is an impossibility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the Menend*z bros were convicted of the murder of their bio parents
shouldn't be a crime. bio parents unnecessarily cause immeasurable suffering #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's incredibly unfair that ppl who really want 2 die, but are 2 inept, exhausted, afraid, etc 2 kill themselves can't get help w/it

all they want is a bottle of pills that already exist

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[human existence is a bad (horrible) deal. i dk how ppl can't c this. it's painfully obvi to me. pain, misery, boredom, fear, danger, mean, nasty, violent ppl, losing looks, weakening due 2 aging, having 2 clean, do laundry, work a hated job, commute 2 it, pay bills, etc
it's shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this dream from 2 days ago still remains in my memory. an ex friend &amp; i were in a Wu Tang Clan vid. it was a long, boring shoot that involved being uncomfy on row boats. my ex friend asked about payment at the end, &amp; the reply was, "are you hungry? we're about to go eat"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["hunters against PETA?" it would be horrible if u all went on a cruise &amp; were hit by 1 of Kim Jong Un's missiles #HASHTAG##HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#AndBeHealthy #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[we've gotten to 7.8 billion, bc so many ppl are monsters. like animals, we're hardwired to want sex, but it's highly likely animals don't realize the sex will result in babies. however, we do (or def SHOULD), so ppl who reproduce premeditatedly cause the suffering of their babies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[something's going on over at Snak Faves, which is my choice of pretzel brand. the pretzels have changed, &amp; the salted 1s used 2 say "fat free" on the bag, now they say "low fat," which is what the unsalted 1s always said, which didn't make sense 2 me
scandalous! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Parents spared jail after driving through flood that killed 3 children"
they drove thru it intentionally thinkin it would be fun. they still had some kids left to say, "pls don't put mommy &amp; daddy in jail" guess that's the key. you can spare some if there are enough left 4 that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[get all yr food at the dollar storendollar store foodnyum yum gimmee sumnn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my farts make more sense than yr posts. they say, i'm gassy
i dk wtf yrs are sayin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[do you think images of ppl fleeing the attack on Ukraine w/their (young) children will stop ppl from procreating?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i use words like pain, misery, dread, despair to describe what my life is like, but it's all pretty insufficient. my life is truly intolerable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["good" memories tainted by a horrendous past (going back well over a decade), present, &amp;, surely, future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[def looks like a keeper to me â¤ï¸â¤ï¸â¤ï¸
"i'm on dog butt! me rule dog butt!" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I, turn up the collar on
My favorite winter coat
This wind is blowing my mind
I see the kids in the streets
With not enough to eat
Who am I to be blind?
Pretending not to see their needs
A summer disregard, a broken bottle top
And a one man soul
They follow each other on the #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i've alienated ppl, but, in my defense, i was/am totally miserable w/chronic pain, depression, OCD, etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yeah, it's the refusal to blame the real culprits for their misery: their bio parents. they "love" em bc they're supposed to, so they take that suppressed/denied rage out on others]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all these things bother me, but so do i! all these thoughts: u should clean, u should exercise
so i bother myself
existence!

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my mom's crazy. she's a hoarder. my dad i dk. she passed mental illness on to me. i don't fuckin appreciate it
childfree: the (crazy) buck stops here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yeah, i'm so disgusted by it, i had my will made over a decade ago (when suisidal), &amp; i said i don't want 1. give my body to science. med students can ridicule me on the slab. i won't gaf. fuckin used to it anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["should i fly to Los Angeles: find my asshole brother?"
-Bush]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's so exciting 2 be single &amp; avail! there's a seemingly endless amount of women out there 2 reject &amp; ignore me!n#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[goddamn, hearing that loser POS new neighbor's voice, bc he's outside smokin another cig (he clearly smokes a lot), talkin on his phone
ppl are such shit. they can easily make a life that's already horrendous much worse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["we can't let evil win! no matter how many mass shootings, terrorist attacks, ppl killed by cops, cops killed by ppl, etc, we must go forward w/our plans to have 23 kids: the ultimate tribute to Michael Jordan!" #HASHTAG# n#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's so easy to see all the pain, drama, violence, suffering, etc is a result of existence. i'm always watching the news or docs &amp; thinking, well, if ya hadn't pushed em into the world, not a goddamn thing woulda happened to em
they can't see what's right in front of their face]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm free
i can be desperately miserable here
i can be desperately miserable there
i can be desperately miserable on the way
i'm free]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my mom's still emailing me about my grandma's 100th b-day, which was last year. she sent the entry she got put into a newspaper. she forwarded it, so i could see the person who replied to her was annoyed w/her (shocker!). "she has 2 daughters &amp; 4 grandchildren" 
guess that's the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's going down, &amp; it's going down slow &amp; hard (no, not talking bout sex, u disgusting pervs: the viscous 1-2 punch of #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG#), but keep taking selfies &amp; pumping out more human puppies to suffan#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# took a sick mind to chain a scantily clad Leah to him ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in a hell of bio parents' making
i hate all of them: esp mine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["as you can see, i ain't lyin when i say i'm JACKED" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ppl are programmed over &amp; over again to be selfish. they're forced to go to school, which countless have hated, bc it prepares em to go to jobs they hate. "work hard:" that's the main programming, bc it makes $ 4 their masters, &amp; they also profit when they hafta pay 4 everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my parents are criminals 4 forcing me into this world w/o my consent
time will punish them
but it punishes me 2
&amp; they've got a head start on death, which seems quite unfair 2 me

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[suffering soul trapped in 
suffering flesh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[postponed jury duty. didn't read the summons thoroughly enough to realize i could do that. that's what i mean. all the pain in the ass bullshit that comes yr way ya gotta deal with, &amp; pay proper attn to, when yr miserable, suffering, &amp; fulla despair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hesitate to defend the weakest &amp; raise their voice 4 them
81 is action &amp; even struggle, it destroys as much as it builds. So, u are not afraid to break established conventions to create fairer 1s, u take risks &amp; do not hesitate to go into battle, to face trials head on"
-Angel #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the light shines on a precious few

as the masses struggle in the dark

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i hope all nests stay where they're supposed to be on this very windy day. tho i find squirrel nests tend to be quite wind resistant #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nothing like millionaire reporters &amp; multimillionaire anchors reporting on ppl getting $1,400 checks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nobody but me knows what i've done to myself, so when someone here said, "if they haven't done it, i guess they don't really want to," i blocked their ass. that's ignorant. who the fuck are you to make such comments when you obvi haven't committed suiside yourself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# thanks, man. if i had to do it over again, it'd be diff. but i'd already walked quite a bit in the heat &amp; carrying weight, which wears me out at my age: incl mentally. i know the world's full of assholes, but i was caught off guard by that 1. never again tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[smooth, unbroken skin will be cut intentionally by its owners, bc their parents felt the need to procreate, even tho it makes no good sense, unless 1 wants to see their progeny suffer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[names that are too similar: stupid. my asshole ex friend's ex is named Caroline. i called her Carolyn once, &amp; he angrily corrected me (bc he's an asshole)
it's 1 thing if someone keeps making the mistake, but those 2 names are RIDICULOUSLY similar. whoever came up w/the name of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ask yr local optimists what they think about pain, aging, stress, anxiety, danger, etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i know what they're getting at, but i still hate when they call trump "dangerous," like he's a bad ass. he prob loves it. but he's a pussy. he didn't invade the Capitol. he doesn't have the balls 2. he's a coward

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all the $ wasted on ppl trying 2 get 2 the part of ppl where the piss comes out

would've been better if u gave it 2 charity, u filthy fucks

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[bio parents: "we dgaf how many times ppl express their extreme misery/pain/fear/dread/despair, not to mention all the tragedy on the news &amp; throughout history, we didn't do nuthin wrong, &amp; we might reproduce again!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yr soul rises out of yr body?
no, it dies w/u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yeah, i laugh at ppl who kill me in the like dept. they're getting all these notifications for putting out crap, bc they like the crap of others. it's a network of chumps. meaningless numbers: as they often are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i want young womenni'll study the bible &amp; start a cultnn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["behind my impassive face, my soul curled up into a ball, waiting until the unpleasantness was over"
-Jeffrey Eugenides
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[mission impossible: forgiving my parents for what they've done, &amp; haven't done, to/for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am just as fucked as you
Please don't take pity on me
My life has been a nightmare
My soul is fractured to the bone
If I must be lonely
I think I'd rather be alone
You cannot save me
You can't even save yourself
-Stabbing Westward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all animals are friends: not food, pests, clothing, &amp;/or OK to experiment on, hurt, or kill 
"The pandemic's unlikely pet: Chickens - CNN" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[daddy's lil girl is all grown up. she's a truck stop hooker. fucking filthy truckers 2 get by

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[never needed to:
worry
obsess
agonize
feel pain
frustration
intimidation
dissatisfaction
humiliation
indecision
confusion
torment
despair
disgust
anxiety
misery
regret
doubt
rage
fear

exist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[conformity makes the decisions for u! convenience!n#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[soul exhaustion: every goddamn bit of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[don't make the monsters uncomfy!neat meat w/them! have some human puppies so u have shit in common to yak about!nconform!nconform!nconform!nconform!nconform!nconform!nconform!nconform!n#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[anger boilin over in a miserable soul, but he don't express it effectively, so it does physical damage to him the way stress surely does]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i dk why Ted Dans*n is in everything like he's so incredible. sick of seeing him. why not share the wealth w/other actors? he memorizes lines other ppl wrote &amp; repeats them: big fuckin deal. i don't think he's funnier/more talented than the average person. i think it's true when]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reach out and take for me, fruit of the poison
Tree,
Give me your body and your soul.
My youth is fading fast, years melt into the past,
This mortal life will take it's toll.
I'm sick and tired of losing, you find this so
Amusing,
It's all I have to keep myself in this state I'm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# they are but they're also eclipsed by all the asshole ppl, bc that's how shitty they are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[interest when she found out i wasn't a homeowner. at my age, that's a loser alert. she declined to say yes &amp; ended up marrying another coworker. think i saw her the other day in the library parking lot. didn't say anything to her. no reason to. she chose someone else to put his]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the more you avoid social situations, the more honest you can be. someone makes a joke, you don't think it's funny, but you offer a little pity laugh anyway to avoid awkwardness
yeah, shit like that sucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i don't need to go to ancestry . com to know my ancestors are/were dickheads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[now playing
Eddie was amazing, but what good does it do him now? he's gone #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in the future, they'll make boybots for pedophilesn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so used to pain &amp; exhaustion. when i'm dying, will i even realize it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you can't age, become more pain-ridden, uglier, weaker, slower, mo hated as a result for free: no! you have to pay for the privilege!
pay till death, motherfucker! it's the biggest, most blatant legal scam ever, &amp; bio parents can't wait to sign their babies up for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i def prefer the nothingness of nonexistence to the "too much" of existence
since i'm a minimalist, it fits quite well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[animals make great friends: many of them are "species blind" (copyright old, bald, ugly loser 2021) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[let's all be PC &amp; shit out babies while we're stuffing our faces w/meat, bc if it's PC, it's all goodn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[society did not make things better; it made them worse
capitalism is a way for the haves to capitalize on the have nots
everyone knows there's a huge disparity of wealth 
it's not right. it's not fair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WORSHIP DEFECATION
Soul evisceration
Death hallucination
Malignant humiliation
Ritualistic suffocation
-Bloodbath #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[women
more likely to be:
vegans
parents than dads
victims of abuse than perps
said it b4. my dad left when i was 2. i was raised by a woman: no siblings. therefore, i have a somewhat-very female soul #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I lack the constitution for svicide"
-Rust Cohle
fictional characters have the luxury of accepting such fates. real ppl, not so much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[work hard, work hard for respect
it's a lie. i've been disrespected, &amp; badly, plenty of times, bc i was determined to be a loser for doing what i was at my age. go to my blog if you like (link) &amp; there's a story titled "cowards" i believe about such a time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[any adult going round acting like life in this world is okey doke is a liar, insane, very stupid, or very lucky

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[keep reproducing!nthe world needs more wasters, addicts, mean, violent ppl, terrorists, mass shooters, homeless, breeders who can't even take care of themselves, pedophiles, rapists, spouse abusers, child abusers, ppl who clean up other ppl's shit, etcn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["dogvane: a small vane carried on the weather rail aboard ship to indicate the direction of the wind."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my life is pain/misery/dread/fear/anxiety/despair management]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[of course god had to be invented to keep stupid, miserable, harmful, destructive human existence going, but not everyone can believe such obvious bullshit ðŸ™‹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just heard:
the soul i took from you was not even missed: yeah!
-Black Sabbath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i assume ppl are worth less than butt plugs until proven otherwise #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yeah. i've communicated w/ppl here, not knowing their gender, not asking, tho wondering, sometimes guessing incorrectly if it's revealed. doesn't matter. i'm male, but was raised by pretty much only women, so i feel my soul is quite fem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ignore, deny the truth #HASHTAG# n#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i can't post about sue aside, but of course ppl can say "we're pregnant!" which is a heinous threat that will deliver much pain, misery, &amp; suffering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Parking Wars"
a Detroit parking enforcement employee, "it hurts me when ppl talk badly about Detroit"
what if someone says, "i love bacon" or "i have 4 kids?" would that bother you? ppl's priorities can be so stupid. Detroit isn't a sentient being that can feel pain &amp; suffer #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[every new day is an invasion: another relentless attack on my soul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[no optimist can convert me: no fuckin way. what i've been thru &amp; knowing it will only get worse w/the increased pain, weakness, ugliness of aging &amp; how those younger will hate me more &amp; more bc of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ignore the pain &amp; suffering &amp; do what everyone else is doing n#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[stay
No money no babysitter, she couldn't keep a job
She tried to sell crack, but end up getting robbed
So now what's next, there ain't nothing left to sell
So she sees sex as a way of leaving hell
It's paying the rent, so she really can't complain
Prostitute, found slain, and]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if yr not very tuff

very stupid

or very lucky

(i'm none of these)

this world will beat u into submission long b4 u die

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[they don't think it will happen
they don't think it will
but it still happens
it happens still #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[once again,
"laugh: make the spontaneous SOUNDS and movements of the face and body that are the instinctive expressions of lively amusement and sometimes also of contempt or derision"
this is why i never write/say "lol," bc it's redundant &amp; stupid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[death is the end of shame, regret, indecision, guilt, envy, doubt, pain, misery, despair, pettiness, suffering, waste, fear, anxiety, depression, obligation, needs, wants, desires, unrequited yearning, frustration, humiliation, intimidation, exhaustion, deterioration, disgust, +]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Rep. Lauren Boebert posted a message on Twitter saying "The Speaker has been removed from the chambers" as a pro-Trump mob breached the U.S. Capitol"
&amp; she pushed past officers &amp; the metal detector afterward at the Capitol. big gun nut #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[don't want 2. penis ugly 2. that's my theory. evolution made em ugly on purpose, so ppl wouldn't want 2 put their mouths on em, they do anyway of course, the dirty doggies, but would have intercourse instead: making more ppl w/butt-ugly gentials #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[fear of committment
not just relationships, but signing leases, paying for 6 mos of car insurance, car registration, etc
bc the future is a shitstorm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[against the law to violate/brutalize someone's body, but not their sanity, feelings, soul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a world where everything breaks. animals, ppl get sick, injured, disabled, feel pain, suffer, age, die. things break. why intentionally bring animals/ppl into such a hopelessly broken world?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i've been betrayed by ppl so many times. even a small, tiny betrayal nicks the soul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[solution
is a Violent Revolution
Violent Revolution, Violent Revolution
Reason 4 the people to destroy
I do not need a cause 4 my rage
I just despise the nature of the human race
When all I see is repulsion &amp; hate
Violence becomes my only friend, my saving grace
When love is lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a slave mentality is hard to break! i catch myself worrying about getting in trouble at work, when, in my heart &amp; soul, i'd love to be liberated from that miserable shithole
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[really seems like there haven't been any mass shootings since the pandemic began
guess they think it'd be in bad taste &amp; are waiting for "herd immunity" to start up again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i used to encounter that at work. i'd literally retreat, &amp; they'd often pursue. it was absurd. gotta have yr personal space, &amp; w/my OCD, esp. it's disgusting. germs are flying out of their mouths]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[blood around, I'll see you ride
Your face is scarred with steel, wounds deep and neat
Like a double dozen before you, smell so sweet
My soul is longing for, await my heir
Sent to avenge my mother, sweep myself
My face is long forgotten, my face not my own
Sweet and timely whore,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yeah, there are plenty of drs who recommend a whole foods plant based diet. meat eaters will say all sorts of stupid shit from what about protein to what about the shape of our teeth? well, they're not like a shark's or gator's, so wtf?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hopelessly tainted soul in a hopelessly tainted world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dear everyone who thinks yr sons/daughters are/will be special,
you're wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[soul
I'll turn you into me
I'll turn you into me
cause I'm a liar, a liar
a liar, a liar
I'll hide behind a smile
and understanding eyes
and I'll tell you things that you already know
so you can say
I really identify with you, so much
and all the time that you're needing me
is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[they reproduce to have "a reason to live" it's only natural to want yr progeny to succeed, but they see successes like the Williams sisters &amp; the Manning bros, &amp; think, i'll encourage em to play sports, &amp; maybe they (we, me) will hit the jackpot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[losers must be treated as suchnit doesn't matter how they got therenthey just need to be punishedn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#nessIsNotNormal #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[waking to this hopelessly fucked-up, violent, dangerous, miserable, doomed world again makes even the very worst ways to die seem not so bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[many ppl are quiet storms. storms are freq raging inside them. sometimes the storms get out, &amp; things get messy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4got to punch out, which i obsessed over
my ex friend was waiting to give me a ride. i came out &amp; said, things are a bit cramped there, &amp; he replied, no shit
a guy didn't like the music i was playing: In Flames. so he asked to c the jewel case, took the CD out, &amp; tossed in into]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How 2 be famous: have as many as kids as u can &amp; when something horrible happens 2 1 or more of them (bullied into suicide, victim of a mass shooting, terrorist attack, murderer, etc.), go on TV &amp; cry &amp; bitch &amp; moan #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When people run in circles it's a very, very
Mad world, mad world
-Tears for Fears #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the world is unfair, but ppl have made it exponentially more so #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in the ocean
none of that. this is a successful person. let's keep things light &amp; forget about the destruction humans are wreaking while promoting this person even further, &amp; send the message loud &amp; clear that animals, the environment, &amp; the future don't matter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[they hate me 4 consistently looking like the way they feel, 4 letting my miserable mug be a window to my miserable soul, 4 not having neither the energy, nor the inclination, to act as though i'm enjoying this shit existence, 4 not playing their bullshit game
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[don't give yr likes 2 #HASHTAG# who challenge u 2 #HASHTAG#, give them 2 #HASHTAG# ppl who say, "being childfree is the ultimate in kindness" (which i NEVER like, BTW)nnjust keep patting yourselves on the back 4 being childfree while u support #HASHTAG# nn#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[pure truth (with some insanity mixed in, bc it can't be helped)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 many lies
2 much bullshit
existence is absolutely unfair torture 4 the #HASHTAG# person who was forced into this fucked-up world

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just wondering how many bio parents procreated to be badasses/get off on the badass aspect of what they've done
handed down such pain, misery, fear, dread, despair, etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[society sacrifices the many for the sake of the filthy rich few
&amp; it's been going on for a long time now
doesn't seem like it's gonna change anytime soon #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the main prob w/the world is far too many ppl lack empathy
all of our bio parents lack empathy, or else we wouldn't be here
nonvegans lack empathy
&amp; these ppl are causing massive amounts of suffering, fueling climate change, etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 of the worst things about suiside is 1 won't be able to see the reactions to it (if any, &amp; 1 could easily be disappointed, bc ppl tend to = shit), but that's the case w/any death, obviously. tho suiside is diff of course]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know your life is empty
&amp; you hate to face this world alone
So you're searching for an angel
Someone who can make you whole
I cannot save you
I can't even save myself
So just save yourself
I know that you've been damaged
Your soul has suffered such abuse
But I am not yr savior]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>