<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Can Dave Meltzer teach Kevin Kross something about wrestling you can't?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Neither. Get that dough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You adults letting your annoying ass kids squirm and jump around in restaurants solidify my position on not having kids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These right wing assholes consider any opposing parties as either deep state actors  or crisis actors. Just murk yourselves already.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They have a chance with Darby Alin, but they're blowing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# With NIL and being starting, does it matter where kids go? If they shine, they shine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Both cut good promos as champion. I will say Big E should have dropped all comedy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I told you the virus could mutate... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carolyn... you can see the manipulation...

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# AEW needs to convert the casuals to grow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I didn't say they were. But mocking a group of people can dehumanize them. I haven't seen Dave's special, so I don't have an opinion on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Damn dumb liberals... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# WWE has more viewers, tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't have any. Just drink lost of water. It seemed to help me. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# This is his tweet. I take him at his word. He's on Fox news and you don't watch Fox news, so you don't know what he said either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck that dead bitch. Not like THAT, #USER#... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He's small. No wonder your fans love him...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Khloe had an out of wedlock kid with an NBA player, but she's the victim...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's about the holocaust, not hardcore sex. If you think teens don't have access to nudity and cursing on their phones,  you're nuts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cancel culture is in our courts now #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm sure your gay friends would be fine with you using their struggle as sarcasm...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He's trying to change the core argument. Typical right wing maneuver. 

"Forcing people to wear masks is tyranny."

"The Florida gov pressured kids to take off their maks. That's not tyranny?"

"So what, they looked stupid."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Made my own birthday cake last year. I was all alone #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All these people aren't racist. 

The white people DEFINITELY are.

When will white people stop using light haired white girls to stop garnering sympathy for shit? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TV is only supposed to make black people look inferiorn#HASHTAG# #USER#: West Virginia senator demands MTV cancel "Buckwild"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If all his son can do is play ball, LeBron is a failure. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Replaced the birds with cats and this will be some of you women in 10 years😂 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# tell them your credentials and let them know you're an expert. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you have to check a non white woman when she uses the word "chinky" to describe eyes. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I'm no WWE Stan. They suck, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[there were no black people on those graphics....nn#HASHTAG##USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like Nazi war criminals. You're so smart!! 

Let me guess... Jan 6th was ok because Trump really won the election, right? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-#USER# #USER# I agree!nWhite guys not getting beat up in movies doesn't look right eithernn#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At times when it comes to paying money, you just gotta say "fuck it".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Jackie Kennedy. Don't know if brits know her, but don't you want to wear a pink Chanel suit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White women are smart not to look us in the eyes while walking by. It makes us go into attack mode. Not robbery or rape just attack #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What he says resonates to a lot of people for a reason...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# what a louse #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm sure that's as hard as year after year of daily physical training and diet as new challengers give you their best shot...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a cigarette in his mouth. 

Meanwhile, we can't get people to wear a Corona mask. 🇺🇸 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No, he should learn from Meltzer, because Meltzer has studied be business for 40 years. Never wrestled, but you know, he has talked to people who have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# am I crazy or were you in one of these movies? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She doesn't add any value. Why is she special? She has a hard job, so she's gonna have hard questions. Being a woman and half black is going to make a lot of people vote against her. With all that, she needs to do more than just add dumb black voters who would let Trump win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At this point, I'm willing to marry any women under a size 8 who doesn't have ANY tattoos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah!! Let white people act like entitled assholes if this is true. Anyway, libs are a major threat to the safety of America with all their guns and anti government leanings. They they elections are phony!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Is that the white guy who uses 5he n word?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# How long till dumb trump fucks are getting snake bites on purpose? 😂😂😂😂 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# y'all girl Brandi out here wilding...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But Brian said Dynamite beat RAW...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did he keep wrestling around your knocked out body?

The fact no one cares that stupid #USER# let the match continue while you were out cold, after sustaining a head injury or who knows what, at that time is fucking ridiculous. They treated a human like a bag of laundry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black women who grew up in working class homes with a dad, get a college  degree, then complain how black men with college degrees who aren't company VPs are beneath them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found white. I mean not guilty. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I was really drinking water when I read it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Uh... I'm no lawyer or CSI guy... But specimen? It doesn't sound like they are talking about blood...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# this company needs Brandi(Chief brand officer) to do her job... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Tell us why it's ok for Critical Race Theory to be banned from schools]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't criticize a cop, because it means you hate all cops...n#HASHTAG# nn#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Things I don't give a fuck about:

The Met Gala
Taylor Swift
Megan the Stallion
Brittney Spears court cases
Ronaldo
Ed Sheeran songs
Harry and Megan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can an overweight woman tell me I'm wrong to be attracted to fit women? I really need someone what to think for their own personal benefit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There's a Jimmy John's opening in Saskatoon tonight...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "Come on, guys!! He just made a mistake. People get confused. Ignore the fact he was a 30 year old grown man. He's just a white man who had a bad day. The world is hard sometimes."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Money does change you, it reveals who you are." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.#USER# changing is name is basically a cheating girlfriend getting new boobs.

The issue isn't your boobs. 

We can't trust you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The show still couldn't keep a million. And the ratings dropped after the match. Ask #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do all the women who decide they want chest tattoos, gather together and compete to see who can get the worst one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It needs another living object to provide biological assistance. Without that assistance, it does. You can't say that about anything else living. Human or animal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Will dare to? Angry Black Lady and all her "strength" has already blocked me for something. LOL. "For what? I don't know."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# So he wouldn't want to talk to a top talent coming into his company? He wouldn't want to talk to a man with a solid career who can add to other talents? A 5 min convo, with a man who carried ROH would be too hard? Ok.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't forget ladies, black men are dangerous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me with this update... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget, #HASHTAG# is a terrorist group...nn#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No disrespect, but dude should have 14 armed bailiffs around him... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Typical right wing projection, on display, from start to finish. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's wrong of the court, because that's Tucker Carlson's job #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I would have given you at least $300 and a Popeyes chicken sandwich.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tony when he sees Swerve is black... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.#USER# is gonna berate him from crying like a kid, right? Oops, he's not a black athlete #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I thought we were talking about people not wanting to get vaccinated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Not the fat one...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But the demo...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# this kid is gonna own #USER# in 2 years. LOL..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Like a third of repubs think Trump won the election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Racism isn't real. Us black people like to make it up... #HASHTAG# #USER#: BlackManUSA - unbelievable that man is still alive...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He's black. Cuban mom. 1 drop rule.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then explain why Kyle looks 20lbs overweight #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dog, help him find a new wife that's as good as yours. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why men don't want to get married part 17,311 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Says the "man" who won't answer a direct question...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who sleep on their backs are serial killers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The coke in Vegas must be amazing...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is disgusting in quotes? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FAT BOY KYLE NOW HAS A SHOW ON #USER# REPLACING THIS GUY #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fox News has all the racists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lots of truck people are stupid. Sorry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# are you gonna eat poontang on Thanksgiving?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[45 year old woman put "must have money" in her wants in her dating profile. She wasn't exactly a model or slender.

Good luck to her...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# the people you defend #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tucker Carlson asked why we don't like Putin. Putin never accused him of being a racist.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sorry, I forgot. Hope you're in good health.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did you wake up in a new Bugatti ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But the demo!! And AEW has Adam Cole and Bryan Danielson... Yeah most people don't know who they are, but they're huge!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I should also have a separate anti NRA group just for black people...nn#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Listen to experts, not your feelings.

Have a good day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# He was 52 and from the looks of it not fat. According to you, he had nothing to worry about. So you don't  know what you're talking about. He and Rogan are probably around the same age. Why did Rogan live? What cured him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The right says the vaccine is mind control. Or something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# is Donnie gonna cry when Cody shows up at Wrestlemania?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Don't worry about it. You don't like being called out. Just keep whining about the libs, Mr. Apolitical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He does. It's from his dad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# totally normal #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck. Britney Renner is crazy as fuck. I don't care if there's gold in that pussy.

RUUUUUUUNNNNNNN!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# stand your ground doesn't apply to black people. Just white people armed with gunsnn#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: 49 million Americans are food insecure, meaning they do not get adequate access to food."nnAll black people, I'm surenn#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT'S

FOR

HOR

SES #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White men are an oppressed classnn#HASHTAG# #USER#: Not so lucky: Tom Hanks loses at the 2013 #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish someone would tell me I should like "thick" women... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kevin Samuels needs to set you straight... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 2 years later, and you're still right..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To remind women, white men are the best?nn#HASHTAG# nnRT #USER#: Why there are so many shirtless dudes in ads now...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# So you got the vaccine, but you're too scared to get the booster... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is the dumb bitch who dumps a guy because the relationship is boring.

RELATIONSHIPS ARE SUPPOSED TO BE BORING!!! YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO LIVE IN DRAMA! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hear me out...

It's not that when you get older you can't drink a lot, it's that you're not in drinking shape. I used to drink like 4 days a week. When people have shit to do, you can't do that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Larry Elder is trying to out coon Ben Carson.

Pack a lunch, Larry...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# People love the word "toxic". I'm serious, when people use the word "toxic" is a yellow flag..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real cancel culture, but cunt face Tucker won't talk about this on his show... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Can't stand AEW. I don't even listen to the review show now. Maybe again when the product gets less goofy...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There should be a special place in hell for people who have their phone volumes up high in public.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If he's a bad person, they causes danger, than he should be kicked off like Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Is that some wacky Eastern PA slang?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Liv is gonna win. You can see it on her face]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Disco is a Republican, or a guy who can't criticize anything they do, which is pretty much the same thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I believe #USER# and #USER# would like to volunteer #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharon's boobs have been on fleek lately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Me: Was Donald Trump partially responsible for Jan 6th?

Disco: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hannah Neise has a giant ass. Sheesh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Jeez. Has he missed any shows? If he had covid or symptoms, that's the only acceptable explanation for this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every Liam Neeson movie looks like a Trump voters wet dream. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "...pains Eddie to do this. He's doing the right thing." JR really knows how to call this company out. 😆]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No AEW fan even pretends to go the gym... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So you know for a fact he won't have long covid and his gf won't? Ok, Meltzer...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# YEAH!! 

And after Obama became President, racism ended in America!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It makes a bunch of right wingers look stupid, so Disco doesn't want to believe it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Your local food bank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If he didn't talk to you before you got hired, things don't work well where you work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He only wants to talk about topics where he can bash the libs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-#USER# #USER# its ok. Sometimes I worry white people will try to lynch me and rape black womennn#HASHTAG#  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Kelly Giddish is kinda slept on... I have eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# His need jerk reaction is to agree with the right and try to trigger the left.

Remember, he's an independent thinker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# did BG take a line of coke before reading that letter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The WWE's long term plan of not building stars has worked. Daniel Bryan is only a star to hardcore wrestling fans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm going to appropriate this word from you people... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man: "I don't want a girlfriend, just an FB."

Women: "You're terrible.

-------------------------------------------

Woman: "I'm a strong woman because I'm aggressive."

Man: "Not really my thing. I'm not attracted to those kind of women."

Woman: "YOU HATE STRONG WOMEN!!!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Are the Republicans who serve with Lauren telling her to resign? She was putting out hate speech.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHERE'S MATT GAETZ?!?!?! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# With all the people getting hurt and the top guys not bringing  in larger ratings numbers consistently over 1 million, it's hard to believe that...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember when they were the party of "family values" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate her more than Prince Andrew hates puberty #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Really?! 

McNulty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Didn't find any numbers related to corona vaccine deaths.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You stink at being a corona expert. You've wrong all the time. Corona is the flu. It's going away. It only kills old people. Vaccines don't work. Blah, blah blah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# good thing no one violated his rights. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not just the men. These women are just as bad... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# if those people started working out during the start of covid, they all would have lived. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: Steven Spielberg loves "Modern Family" "nnHe has more black people in his family than the show does...n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can always trick idiots into using technology to screw them later #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# True. 

Dude is either gay himself or 12. There's no other explanation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#....nnRT #USER#: #USER# im not racist.. If anyone is racist it would be those nigger judges]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# unknown black wrestler beat MJF less than a week after Tony looks terrible addressing race... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calah looks like a less trashy Britney Spears

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He made his organs tougher with drugs. See Keith Richards... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That poor guy in the background doing wrist curls... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Betty White is the female Billy Murray.

People randomly decided at one she was cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red2 nnbecause old white people deserve to be in movies before black womennn#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's news. Can't believe idiots think it's a credible win...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck him. 

Fuck his family.

Fuck the #USER#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Worst Booked match(ex: Pockets VS Hobbs)

Most overrated wrestler(male female)

Dumbest Meltzer statement regarding matchwrestlerangle

Worst promo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any concerns about the morons who attacked the Capitol on Jan 6th? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The media told me to think Ukrainians being attacked is a bad thing. I know better... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They shut him down after he called out bad cops... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# told you about this two years ago... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The Billi Bhati segment is always a banger. BOOM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grew up in the northeast.

No. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite possible. Idiots who say America is full of snowflakes don't want to wear masks #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# the right is the party of the emotionally triggered... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# please use your genius to explain this... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: Legal weed causing sky-high travel demand to Denver #URL#"nnAll black people, I'm sure...nn#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're the same person who says let the KKK and white supremacists half a public platform, because people aren't dumb enough to fall for their rhetoric.

Hilarious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If they paid him, I would respect the anger.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you can Sean Ross Sapp reaction gifs on Twitter. 

You're welcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I hope you're little sister Toni ends up in a good place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# THAT'S IT!!! 

PEOPLE SHOULD STOP GETTING COVID!!! YOU'RE A GENIUS!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I saw a picture of this random woman, I understood why this was a national story... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Your move....
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# are most women trying to do things to be a wife? I don't mean marriage, I mean the role of being a wife.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Let's get the whole story first...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# More people know Lethal than Brody King. That's a fact...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Wrestling fans usually don't play sports. Or go to the gym.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah!! How else will pharmaceutical companies make money without corona virus?! 

LOL. Idiot. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Corona sent my chubby ass to the hospital, and I didn't learn shit." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# So if Tony didn't talk to Flair before signing Flair, that would make sense to you?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>