<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Kamala Harris Could Become First Black Female Supreme Court Justice #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Activists: Women’s Colleges Hurt Non-Binary, Transgender Students #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Profits of Doom: Globalist Elites Doubled Their Wealth During Coronavirus Pandemic #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennessee police officer shot in standoff with armed suspect #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lee Zeldin Raises Record $8.4 Million in New York Governor‘s Race #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Karl Rove: Biden gave his critics 'lots of ammunition' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arnold Schwarzenegger Involved in 4 Car Crash in Los Angeles #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another Democrat Drops Out Rather than Face the 2022 Red Wave #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Live: Abortion Industry’s Latest Strategy to Target Black Women #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brother of Texas Synagogue Terrorist Reveals he had a Criminal Record #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VIDEO - CBS Host Stunned NOT ONE Participant In Focus Group Believes America Is Better Under Biden #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats face painful reality as priorities stumble #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hannity: 'Incompetent' Biden is universally disliked #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep. Pfluger on border crisis: Biden administration 'inviting' illegal immigrants in 'record numbers' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate Alarmists: The Sixth Mass Extinction ‘Really Has Begun’ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mary Katharine Ham OWNS NBC harpy flipping OUT over Glenn Youngkin empowering parent CHOICE with student masking in kick-a*s thread #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video exposes secret government migrant flights #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gun control advocates express disappointment with Biden #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Biden Claims He ‘Outperformed‘ in First Year of Office During Meandering 112 Minute Press Conference #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police not supported in Democrat-led cities: Marine combat veteran #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mandatory Mao Zedong Classes on UK-Chinese Collab University Course #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The UN Is Funding The Invasion Of The U.S. Southern Border, In Line With Globalists' Goals #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Francisco DA Chesa Boudin accused of withholding evidence in officer misconduct case #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden can be cranky as long as he holds press conferences: RealClearPolitics reporter #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2021: The year Biden's approval ratings sank slowly underwater #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Final Exam’ returns with Perino and Watters #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Red-Handed’: How the Bush Family Cashed In on Friendship with Chinese Official Involved in the Tiananmen Square Massacre #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch: Joe Manchin Stands Up to Democrats in Epic Floor Speech Shaming Them for Trying to Nuke Filibuster #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Rise in violent rhetoric’: Lawmakers in both parties report spike in death threats #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[INDOCRINATION - 1.7 Million Union Teachers Getting License To Censor (Rate) Websites For Students #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FX/Hulu Series ‘Y: The Last Man’ Imagines ‘A World Without Cisgender Men’ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boxing Champion Manny Pacquiao Opposes Vaccine Mandates as Philippine Presidential Candidate #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Florida Lt. Gov. Nunez: Hispanics 'flocking' to Republican Party for 'freedom,' 'opportunities' #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Outnumbered' on Biden casting doubt on 2022 midterm election legitimacy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prominent Jesuit Priest: Good Catholics Can Be Pro-Choice #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California Bill Would Let Children Get COVID-19 Jab Without Parental Approval #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH NOW: Pennsylvania parents stress involvement in children's schooling: "important role in the education system' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pentagon: 2 'High-Profile' ISIS Members Killed from Drone Strike #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virginia school districts sue Youngkin over order giving parents choice on COVID-19 masks in class #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden's connection to China: Peter Schweizer  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Prioritizing Antiviral Pills for ‘Non-White‘ People #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. Mark Shrime, a Mercy Ships volunteer, urges a new understanding of 'purpose' in life #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Cleans Up Again After Joe Biden Questions 2022 Election #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH: Standing Ovation as Widow of Slain NYPD Officer Calls Out Soros-aligned DA Alvin Bragg in Tearful Eulogy #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Concha on rampant inflation amid crime surge: 'That combination is not good for the party in power' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CDC's Natural Immunity 'Bombshell' Catches CNN Completely Off-Guard, Sends It Scrambling for Answers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outrage after DC Mayor Bowser's new COVID vaccine order: 'Will kill businesses not viruses' #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYC councilman: New Yorkers largely 'support' Mayor Eric Adams amid unveiling of anti-crime plan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen on why he's petitioning the NFL to move Super Bowl to Saturday #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive — Mike Cernovich: Attempts to ‘Hoax the Country into War‘ Are Failing, ‘Nobody Cares‘ About Ukraine #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohio company hires stay-at-home moms, high school students amid worker shortage #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI Raids on Outspoken Public Figures; Biden Says That Without Voting Bill, Midterms Could Be ‘Illegitimate’ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2022 Pennsylvania Democrats Skip Joe Biden Event in Pittsburgh #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Defiance Of Youngkin, Fairfax Public School Demands High Schoolers Participate In ‘Privilege Bingo’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York says it will prioritize non-White people in distributing low supply of COVID-19 treatments #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro-life advocates rip Kamala Harris' prediction that 'women will die' if Roe v. Wade is overturned #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How This Mom Took Back Her Kids’ Education From A Far-Left School Board #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Dems beg members not to quit in the face of fierce GOP midterm challenge - #URL# - #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH: Foreign Journalist Asks Psaki About Biden‘s Foreign Policy Failures: ‘Is This What "America Is Back" Means?‘ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. forward Weah to miss Canada game due to vaccine issue - #URL# - #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PolitiFact Is Again Doing Damage Control for a Biden Blunder #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Biden’s Second Press Conference Ever Was Another Total Embarassment #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National security expert: Putin is 'obsessed with NATO' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden administration is projecting 'weakness': Rep. Tenney #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maher: COVID Measures Look Like Every Never-Ending Government Program, ‘Can‘t Be More Invested‘ in Someone‘s Health than They Are  #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poll: Donald Trump Sees 40-Point Lead in Hypothetical GOP Primary #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snapchat Claims It Is Making It Harder for Drug Dealers to Find Your Kids #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With apparently not much else going on, NBC News and other media introduce America to Biden’s new cat #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psaki declines to reveal when Biden learned of Breyer retirement #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK Accuses Putin of Trying to Install a Puppet Regime in Kiev #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-NFL Player Nate Burleson Claims Volcano, Tsunami a Result of Climate Change #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tucker Carlson, Clint Ehrlich Blast Attempts to Push the US and Russia to War over Ukraine #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayorkas can no longer lead DHS: Former acting DHS secretary  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sears: We‘re ‘Challenging‘ Politicians Who Deny Poor Kids School Choice and Send Their Kids to Private School #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SHOCKING POLL - Nearly Half Of Dems Support Fines, Segregated Camps And Prison Terms For Those Who Disagree With Them On COVID #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public health expert predicts omicron surge will 'get much worse' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indiana bill would ban transgender women from scholastic sports; public hearing planned #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nancy Pelosi Just Announced She is Running for Re-Election in Creepy Election Video #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Biden administration is lying to us about the border crisis: Astorino #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contrary to what abortion advocates would have you believe, 71% of Americans support legal limits on abortion, according to a new poll commissioned by #USER# and conducted by Marist Poll. via #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disney Shares Plunge After Analyst Downgrade Warning of Slower Theme Park Recovery #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden admin withdraws COVID-19 vaccine and testing rules struck down by Supreme Court #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alec Baldwin sued for $25M by family of Marine killed in Afghanistan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minneapolis Restaurants File Suit Against Democrat Mayor‘s Vax Mandate #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBC News president says his network does not do 'advocacy journalism' #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[33 Migrants Arrested by Texas Troopers on Ranch near Border #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[March for Life taking place as Roe faces potential end nearly 50 years after landmark decision #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Los Angeles police ID Shawn Laval Smith as suspected killer of Brianna Kupfer #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[German ambassador to US vows commitment to ‘Ukrainian sovereignty’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN's Jim Acosta: I still have 'marks on my back' from standing up to Trump #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden Is Not Alone. Democrats Have Been Delegitimizing Elections for Years #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYPD officer Jason Rivera forever remembered a hero #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neil Young &amp; Even the Surgeon General Want to Censor Joe Rogan — But Spotify Just Gave Them Bad News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freak Out: Covid Dictators Left Scrambling As Major Western Nation Suddenly DROPS Vaccine Mandates &amp; Restrictions #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13 Happenings In 2021 That I Never Would Have Believed 5 Years Ago #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tucker: Biden has ‘enabled’ an ongoing assault on our national sovereignty #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch: Navy Seals Running for Congress Unite to Defeat Nancy Pelosi #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30 Migrants Found in Truck, 20 More in Texas Motel near Border #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taliban Leaders Touch Down in Oslo to Woo Humanitarian Donors #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelly takes under-the-radar approach in Arizona Senate race #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The TSA Is Letting Illegals Use Their Arrest Warrants as ID Papers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This California City Might Let Illegal Immigrants Vote #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gutfeld: COVID chaos hits Canadian truck drivers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH: Elephant Topples Family‘s Car at Wetland Park #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S Aircraft Carrier Strike Group Heads for Mediterranean amid Russia Threats #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['These are Criminal Companies!' Watch RFK Jr's Brilliant Takedown of Big Pharma That Ignited a Media Firestorm #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: Chicago Schools Train Teachers that Sex Is ‘Not Rooted in Biology‘ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nolte: New York Times Debases Itself with Puff Piece on ‘Willow, the White House Cat‘ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Blames Canada, Not Raging Domestic Outbreak, for Omicron Threat to Olympics #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia Confirms It Granted Novak Djokovic a Valid Visa, Blames Computer #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joni Mitchell joins Protest over Joe Rogan Spotify Podcast: ‘I Stand in Solidarity with Neil Young‘ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hawley says he would have opposed resolution to honor Capitol workers on Jan. 6 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man Welcomes Joe Biden with ‘Let‘s Go, Brandon!‘ Chants During Pittsburgh Visit #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liverpool Bomber Had his Asylum Rejected SIX YEARS Before Attack #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NCAA facilitator resigns over organization's updated transgender participation policy #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sinema reignites 2024 primary chatter amid filibuster fight  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rooftop Revelations: Pastor Brooks shares the lesson he learned from Thomas Sowell on school choice #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. Tom Cotton on Russia-Ukraine conflict: Biden's weakness has 'emboldened' US adversaries #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zelensky Prioritizes Ukraine‘s ‘Financial Stability‘ in Biden Call as Russia Panic Threatens Economy #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 Men Arrested After Committing 70 Crimes Targeting Asian Women #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[University Of Pittsburgh Report Tries To Explain Away Barbaric Experiments With Aborted Babies #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fallen NYPD Officer Saves Five People Thanks to Organ Donation #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nolte: NPR Stands Behind Debunked Fable About SCOTUS Mask Controversy #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arizona Lawmakers Introduce Bill to Fight Forced Labor in China #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYPD widow blasts NYC's pro-crime policies #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scarborough: Putin, Xi ‘See Joe Biden as Weak‘ over Russia Statement #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My College Mandated Boosters And Can’t Give A Good Reason Why #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ESPN: Brady retiring at age 44, winner of 7 Super Bowls - #URL# - #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID therapeutics becoming important tool in combating the virus #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neil Young threatens to pull songs off Spotify over Joe Rogan: report #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Clueless' star Alicia Silverstone flips off body shamers in TikTok video: 'I think I look good' #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be Honest, You Don’t Really Care About the Uyghurs Either  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DOJ: Illegal Alien Stole Disabled U.S. Veteran‘s Identity to Get Welfare #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rams' Odell Beckham Jr hit with surprise drug test after wild-card win #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘None of this adds up’: Blue-checked poli sci prof’s evidence that Glenn Youngkin just sentenced Virginians to COVID only proves she’s an idiot #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch: Tucker, Freedom Convoy Spokesman Explain how Canadian Truckers are Fighting for Freedom #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CULTURAL INSANITY - MI School Providing Litter Boxes In Bathroom For Students Who Identify As Cats (Furries) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWKWARD - Biden Tells Kamala At DNC Event, 'I Love You, You Always Have My Back'. Harris Replies 'I Do' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British Police Force‘s LGBT+ Network Unveils Creepy Cow Mascot #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chicago Mayor Lori Lightfoot Mocked After Offering ‘Stack‘ of Money to Get Vaccinated #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AOC scolds both Sinema, Biden in call for 'brass tacks' approach to progressive agenda #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's time to impeach DHS Chief Mayorkas #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UChicago targets unvaxxed student athlete #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rising crime puts focus on mental health crisis, homelessness in cities #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive — Rep. Greg Murphy: GOP Doctors Caucus Is ‘Infuriated‘ that Fauci‘s Policy ‘Has All Been About Vaccination‘ and Not Therapeutics #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fridays mean ‘Notable Quotables’ on ‘Special Report’: Here are this week’s best bits #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carlson: If You‘re Not ‘Terrified‘ About a Russian Invasion of Ukraine, Media Say You‘re on ‘Putin‘s Side‘ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crenshaw: Border Officials Preparing for Numbers Well Above What Obama‘s DHS Head Considered a ‘Crisis‘ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tucker Carlson: Democrats Now Value Border Security, Just Not Along the US Border #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breitbart News Daily Podcast Ep. 61: Joe Rogan vs. WHO/White House/Woke Celebs, Ukraine Fake News Exposed, Guests: Emily Jashinsky on Culture, Mike Cernovich on Jan. 6th #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video Shows Pennsylvania Official Admitting Election Laws Were Broken In 2020 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DOJ Arrests Texas Man for Allegedly Threatening to Kill Georgia Election Officials #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homebuilder Confidence Slips as Foot Traffic Declines, Materials Prices Soar, and Supply Chains Issues Rattle #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep. Turner: Anything Putin says about Ukraine is false #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beijing Locks Down More Neighborhoods as Genocide Olympics Staff Arrives #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas Judge Temporarily Blocks Biden’s Vaccine Mandate for Federal Employees #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eric Shawn: Crime fighting... or surrender? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kilmeade: Momentum is on Republicans' side ahead of 2022 midterms #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nolte: CNN Ratings Plummet -78% to Below 500,000 Viewers #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fed signals key interest rate hikes to fight inflation  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[438,110 Dead: NYT Admits Biden Failed on Shutting Down the Virus #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington Post Joins New York Times In Portraying America As Racist Based On Long-Ago Deeds #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Francisco DA Chesa Boudin sued for turning back on Asian attack victim as anti-AAPI hate crimes soar 567% #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge Reverses Decision to Place Loudoun County Schoolboy Guilty of ‘Forcible Sodomy‘ on Sex Offender List #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The UN Just Gave the Taliban $32 Million, Has Pledged to Give them $20 Million Each Week #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mandatory Olympic Athlete App Gives China Data Goldmine #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TSA confirms it lets illegal immigrants use arrest warrants as ID in airports #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disney Heiress Makes Documentary Criticizing Pay Gap of Disney Employees #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawsuit: 99.7 Percent Of Kids Banned From School Under Covid Rules Were Healthy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The CIA Is Training Ukrainian Paramilitaries to "Kill Russians" As the Globalists Push for War with Russia #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans not hungering for Biden-Trump 2024 presidential election rematch: poll #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gas prices soar, national average price jumps as Americans grapple with rampant inflation #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hostages taken at Texas synagogue as crisis negotiators continue to work to secure victims' release #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden‘s DHS Chief Admits Illegal Immigration Is ‘Worse Now than ... Ever‘ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diversity is code for 'not White': Matt Walsh #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Propaganda‘: Art Showing DC‘s Vax Mandate as Communist Appears #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poll: 72 Percent Say 2022 Economy Will Hurt or Plateau Family Finances #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gingrich: Putin and Xi Sense Weakness in Brandon #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing Number of European Countries Rolling Back COVID-19 Restrictions #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US believes Russia may soon launch cyberattacks against critical American infrastructure: source #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Flash‘ Star Ezra Miller Posts Video Warning to KKK Members in North Carolina: I Suggest Just Killing Yourselves‘ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ferguson: Democrats to Push ‘Slimmed-Down‘ Build Back Better Bill #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia continues military buildup around Ukraine #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive — Kari Lake Plans to Circumvent Feds on Border Policy #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[REVEALED: Sen. Dianne Feinstein’s Husband Partly Owned a Chinese Company That Sold Spyware to U.S. Military #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Veterans react to Russia's purported plan to install pro-Kremlin leadership in Ukraine #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifth Time's the Charm? Israeli Trial Shows 4th Shot of Covid Vaccine Doesn't Stop Omicron #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enes Kanter Freedom Posts List of NBA Players Sponsored by Chinese Companies with Ties to Slave Labor #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sears: Criminals Don‘t End up in Nice Neighborhoods of ‘Woke People‘ Who Let Them Out, Woke Should Help Those They ‘Claim to Help‘ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Economic Forum Hears Call for Global Wealth Redistribution #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swimming World Publishes Oped for Limiting Women’s Sports to Females #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fauci on Fox's Jesse Watters: He 'should be fired on the spot' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats' abortion bill called 'radical' by pro-life advocates  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vaccine Passport Protests in Europe Draw Thousands of People #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox News' Peter Doocy says Biden 'cleared the air' with him following the 'SOB' insult #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure deal slips, GOP pans $1.7T White House offer #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Domestic Terrorists BLM DC Chapter, Complains About Shot Police Officer Treated As 'Heroes' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[J.D. Vance Criticizes Opponent Matt Dolan for Indians Name Change, Rails Against ‘Weak Republicans‘ #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mama June gets cozy on a hike with new boyfriend Justin Stroud #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans Battle for Control of Missouri’s Redistricting Map #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>