<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Many Russian troop lives will be saved with this stall, more if they return to Russia.

Impossible to believe that many from Russia want to bomb civilian targets. THAT is the mission--do all the troops know?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Guessing you include in the Digital Bill of Rights the “Truth Social” platform and thus challenge their operational Terms of Service, which are hardly open and free: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Are any of the faithful appalled at her self pairing with Jesus Christ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sure, he sounds ready to be the face of America with the international community!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# “Amend his answer”? How does THAT work? Someone coached him about what to say to get away with this crime?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Because he was wearing it around others and didn't take it off yet. And he's about to be in close quarters with others and cares.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Good call! The rational and reasonable thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Is he preparing remarks to commend the FBI for their work in MI and extend words of thoughts and prayers for the well being of Gov Whitmer? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They got THEIR news from the Twitter followers of Trump/Tucker loyalists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Now, convince others. Voters have rights…to access and to voting and ensuring their votes be counted and count.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's a lot of time and money spent not on constituents #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wonder how many thank you notes from other members and staff they’ve received in light of this announcement?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sick. Incorrect. Wrong. And he keeps saying stuff and the very misinformed run with it. Fox Entertainment has got to just stop. They are hurting people with their rhetoric.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why not wait for Truth Social? Why take up with Parler instead?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So, only SOME of America with a rigid and limiting litmus test.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Actually, the silence of so many in response to his anti-Semitic and racist remarks show us just how ordinary he is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Have the Truth Social investors weighed in yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ugh. And Oy! And, is this now a campaign ad for any and all opponents?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Has an elected leader ever before denigrated and talked down the country like this, ever? The doom and gloom, calling the country a laughing stock, describing it as destroyed…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I still cannot believe this was not stopped in 4 years, not reported in 4 years, not a much bigger deal — constantly and continually breaking the Records Act with deceitful, irreverent, illegal and childlike behavior.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That’s not what this is about. Many people of all ages and races benefit with easier access, ballot drop boxes. Work and family get in the way of requesting the absentee ballot and DeJoy and post office delays interfere with ALL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How many peacefully assembled were forcibly removed for those events? Guessing her take since hundreds or thousands were removed for this president and zero for the others the high numbers count in his "winning" column?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I’m an educator, vaxxed and boosted. I know a number of people, also vaxxed and boosted who got COVID, thankfully mild. But I have a husband with late stage heart failure who WON’T get a mild case of I bring it home. 

Wear a mask for others. It’s not tyranny, it’s compassion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# His donors matter more than his constituents. Time for him to step down from Senate and grift more, oops, make more in the private sector as a lobbyist. Please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That’s where he heard “the world is laughing at us” from which he is now creating domestic policy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So, NOT Manchin; let's talk to Senators Romney, Murakowski, Collins, let's keep the list going of those coming to understand that our democratic republic form of governance is at stake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Let’s take a look at the arrest records, as I’m thinking the arrests are NOT simply for protesting or being “dissidents”. Residents are impeded unlawfully, businesses cannot be accessed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Floridians should also push back against their GOP members and Senators who voted down funding for FL infrastructure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well doesn’t everyone get invited onto the private planes of people they don’t really know, again, and again and again and again…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Bless you and thank you for your activism. Straight talk calling out bad behavior DOES help..got me from passive supporter to active voice—calling legislators, writing letters!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Read today that 3 banned substances identified. Grandfather taking all 3?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Many of their calls, texts, emails are already captured because they've exchanged messages with Mark Meadows and others who HAVE provided evidence to the committee. That's how communication works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It’s as though we people haven’t connected that case rates, hospitalizations and deaths have been dropping WITH masks and vaccination. Sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I missed the part where she said, “Excuse me, May I pass?” thank you for posting. Thank you lovely young woman in black for not escalating. Thank you for posting so we know who to watch out for: angry older white woman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Same for independent K-12 faculty and staff and public schools. Most decisions have been made in the past 24-30 hours!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is anti-decency, anti-humane, dishonest, shows lack of judgement, lack of character and lack of integrity. And he continues to be taxpayer paid in a position of authority.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# What you MEANT to say is that you appreciate the consideration for your constituents that the Democrat Senators gave in voting for the Infrastructure bill. You give them your thanks on behalf of your constituents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A real man will do that. President Biden, I was ok with your comment and have deep respect for the follow up call to apologize.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Santa surely hasn't found them to be nice and deserving of more vacation nor recess!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# WHAT Christian values? What threat is he defending? There is no threat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# How did this administration allow so many unqualified people to remain in their positions ( )? Taylor wasn’t fired first cause, he resigned. It is unconscionable to malign ones professional reputation simply for calling out the president. That is allowed in our country!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# One million KNOWN cases as we are unable to account for at home testing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It bothers me that their concern was Trump’s legacy and reputation while lives and safety were in danger and ultimately harmed and lost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This gave me a headache and heartache. One goes to a library by CHOICE. One selects a book to borrow and take home to read by CHOICE. Do not restrict my freedom to CHOOSE that which to read. Leave on the shelf for ME any book that does not meet with your approval. That is all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Of course SCIENCE can, should and has been questioned. Guidelines have been revised. YOU all dismissing and discounting not questioning. Big, HUGE difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# intended to add to end of my tweet --I expect nothing in terms of integrity from this bunch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# This meeting won’t help the defeated former president because he will concede/admit to nothing. He will know what is happening causing him, in all likelihood, to malign many and possibly declare candidacy thinking it makes him Teflon like and able to declare “witch hunt!”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She does get points for not simply getting the cat…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You KNOW that’s not what really happened, yes? Fear not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# As a parent, grandparent, educator and decent human being, my response is shame on you for promoting this level of selfishness and self involvement. Wishing for those in your community to care more about others than the lot of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Biden’s first stated qualifiers were of expectation of highly qualified candidates. Ignoring these remarks doesn’t make them go away. I’d be happy to talk qualifications for members of Congress. Senate with you #USER# ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And tells us the country won’t even be here in 50 years if Biden wins and that our guns will be taken away and police departments demolished. Thank goodness he is speaking of calm things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Had same reaction to this ridiculous and grossly inaccurate declaration. I’ve never loved Christmas, always celebrate Hanukkah, appreciate the thoughtful intent when wished Merry Christmas, but, no, never “love Christmas”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# but but but their boss said not to fear and not to let it dominate . . .they trust him, yes? . Please tell me they have a choice to work remotely?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That cannot be as he is the “law and order President”, he would not break the law? He would not vote illegally? Nor have staff illegally use gov’t property on behalf of his campaign?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Straight to jail, “Do Not Pass Go”..so no indictment, charges, due process or even a “request to appear” before a committee?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Very sad that Floridians are paying the salary and under the influence of someone doing #USER# ill informed bidding and missing out on the services sorely needed during this pandemic. Floridians are still dying and hospitalized due to COVID every day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Had same conversation with the in laws. It’s likely that my husband and his sister will not see each other again before he succumbs to his heart disease. And there will be no in person memorial. We shall all be sequestered in our grief. For not a good reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Or more time off than that and less frequently working and they work in DC offices Tuesdays-Thursdays!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When my then toddler was starting to talk and I caught my toes (sticking out of the walking cast) on the crib rail and cried out “Oh, damn” the kid repeated. A week later passed the gas station and w/same inflection cried “Oh, Jeannette!” And kid repeated, “Oh damn”. Sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Biden threw him a bone and he built a herd of cattle with it. HE created he vaccines and HE “saved tens of millions of lives” and his loyalists will tout that, giving him credit, even among those staunchly unvaccinated. The disconnect is…vast and incomprehensible,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So very sorry you are going through this. Still hoping for a diplomatic result Jon before more lives are lost. 
Signed USAF mom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I am so sorry for how challenging and stressful is this for her and appreciate her work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And, no, some Americans hated segregation because they were racist and worried that if someone else "got" something, it would be at their personal expense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What happens in those states when a teacher or aide with a same sex spouse mentions that “my wife” or “my husband” and I also have a pet, went on a vacation, went to the Grand Canyon, recycle, etc?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It must be very taxing to have to make stuff up every night, remember the fabrications and find people to blame that others want to diminish. Much harder than reading and learning facts. And being kind and decent. #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And to have a good day and to take care of daddy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Wow. This is very unsettling and disturbing. And bad for children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You too! No mentions of FBI, antics…You KNEW then president Trump could and should take action! To save lives and save democracy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If the border is blocked that means no more Russian soldiers into Ukraine, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And if you selectively discuss on FNC and various radio programs what you've refused to discuss in front of a Congressional Committee, should we not consider privilege waived?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because these people show up in Meadows’ texts and emails?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# WHY are you declaring war on duly elected officials? They, like you, represent constituents. As a statewide elected official, you have an obligation to ALL in KY not only those that voted you into office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I read this and a few other similar tweets and was wondering what M&amp;Ms are, because it can’t be the candy getting all his airtime considering the Jan 6 documents, grand jury in GA, depositions in NYC and Russia/Ukraine…but #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fox would be nothing without propaganda and misinformation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I personally think the reason he doesn’t go to church more often is because there it is not all about him, rather about Him so not a fan of Jeffress for making it about Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In the middle of the day?? of his 3 day work week?? The gall!! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# MANY students understand that the masks are for the health and protection of others and are willing to wear them for others. For these students, others include: family at home, their teachers, school personnel, teachers and everyone's families. The know. They care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Will SCOTUS gift the American people with our records?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It would be sweet to convene on January 6 and pass a voters’ rights bill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Thank you for the article. Problematic: 1) "and producing research to support it"-- what the CB did a few years ago w/"research" to show predictable success based on SAT scores, absent significant control factors 2) more School Day SAT dates with SCHOOLS paying staff/proctors!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is tragic. Many cite the relatively low % of children who get COVID , have symptoms, are very ill, die. But % are numbers and numbers ARE CHILDREN. The actual numbers are too many. WEAR A MASK, GET THE VACCINE! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There is SO much evidence that he would wreak havoc and abuse power of ever given reign again. Another go round will be much worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# “Smuggled”?I know many teachers BUY classroom supplies with their OWN money and carry them into classrooms. In CA the curriculum is online on the state dept of ed website and textbooks must be on public display before purchase. Not a secret. Also, do HW w/your kid and you know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My mother's current signature, as an elderly person, would probably not pass muster. However, she is the same person, registered still, and still wants to and expects to vote!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Have had parents very upset when maternity leave is announced for a teacher or counselor and we get, "What about my son/daughter and their class, college applications, etc" We are announcing a highly qualified substitute/interim. And the concern is very self focused.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Add to the list of places to avoid, and for the week afterward, people who attended.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You may not have all the facts: 1) have you told dog “no glasses”? 2) perhaps dog felt they needed to be tested before you used them again? 3) “I didn’t see them on the couch before I lay down (on the couch I’m not supposed to be on, but that’s not the point right now! Focus!)”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Please. I dare say they knew nothing about the 1960 election when they signed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hearing more re about young children testing positive, some asymptomatic, some with symptoms. Any new numbers by age?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# is epic. Think it must be THE vernacular on air and in print going forward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# All of this is NOT the residential behavior. Shouldn’t more people among his loyalists see this as disqualifying?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The answer ought to have been remedy; she was either eligible to vote or not to, not voting is the remedy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How is google totalitarian if YOU initiated the ban? Also, THANK YOU for removing the podcast!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Didn’t he meet with leader MCConnell? Who talks to the GOP Senators?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I always read the bio before choosing to follow someone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# “Just remember” that the restrictions and mandates were dependent upon participation and the refusal to vaccinate, the gatherings unmasked, the blatant disregard for most mitigation thwarted the efforts to defeat the virus. Human error. Reckless disregard for others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The target for this needs to be your colleague #USER# before he further praises Russia/Putin as a champion and throws Ukraine and its people to the curb!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Did they acknowledge on air his death due to COVID?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So, a teacher in a heterosexual marriage shall not reference, "When my husband/wife and I went on vacation to the Grand Canyon" because that is a reference to their sex life? And because you don't want a teacher in a same sex marriage to also reference said husband/wife?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Husband very ill and will not help get affairs in order. Only said to cremate him and not tell anyone he’s dead. Need more! NOTHING in writing!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep. It’s not someone’s right to be more likely to transmit the virus to others. Often these others have compromised folks at home. Too much unknown and more coming out about long COVID leaving many more with compromised health. NOT OK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The more officials attempt to censure and diminish voices, the more amplification the voices are given. Censure is NOT the answer.
Students KNOW what they need, and right now, that is to be heard and to be safe. These are reasonable asks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Let me fix this: against Donald Trump and Ivanka Trump and Donald Trump Jr—they are NOT children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Phew! Good to know Herman Cain is only in the hospital because he’s been COVID tested. Until you tweeted this, I thought he might be sick! Relieved your campaign staff and valiant Secret Service team are positive because they tested, won’t get sick or make others ill!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I missed it too! Maybe he and Trump were in the Oval today preparing a joint statement?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not so much since 2020 WAS a secure election, much evidence to support, w/o voter ID.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Still wondering about the exemption offered in the community of Mar-a-Lago as a for profit and a residence, something denied to every other in the community. It was only requested by the defeated former president for tax relief uprises, so cheating the people of FL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not hardly; remember this “father-of-the-year” has a daughter who jacked up insulin prices, wants to judge the parenting of others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That’s 100s-1,000s of National Guard troops reporting for duty, away from their families at Christmas. The choice made to not vaccinate does not affect only YOU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Let me amend slightly: Mitch McConnell has changed the rules and will do so again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Important to think of Jan 6 and the conversations, plans and events of Nov 2020-Jan 6 as a playbook for the 2024 election. These along with the legislative elections actions underway and already enacted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And NONE of the GOP electeds calling out Trump for denigrating the country, constantly, driving us into the ground…hardly patriotic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Gaetz and several others consistently and often use the word “power”. This is deranged and frightening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just curious: Do you support those found guilty of injuring police officers at the bidding of DJT? Those who desecrated the Capitol on his behalf? Those who sought out the VP to hang him, in support of the mission of DJT? Of the former President violating the Records Act?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So Spotify itself and not Neil Young nor other music artists are canceling Joe Rogan? The hand that feeds is canceling Joe Rogan? Do Federalist Society members and Trump loyalists know who is really canceling Joe Rogan??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Also, tests are very hard to access in some towns, many at home tests are not reported and test results are being released much later (by days) than previously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah. Travel good. Expose staff good. And it appears the “mission” statement is that 2.5-3million American lives were not lost so Yay us and Yay “the President”...still doing my drinking game: shot every time VP says “the President”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ummm, the “mission “ began while he was POTUS, about his practices as a private citizen so alleging political agenda against a private citizen is cloudy and alleging she sees HIM as a political opponent is untrue (and laughable) “who she views as a political opponent,”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Was Eric upset that big brother’s fiancée was getting all the sexy photos attention?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Work as “staff” at a K-12 school so many kids are vaccinated; my work is mostly with MS/HS and keeping them masked properly indoors is a constant and daily battle. But the unmasked to speak administrators are appalling. Who do I report to about them? Days til we resume: 5. Sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It is NOT an unforced error, rather intentional. This IS who "they" are, the Trump loyalists, fragile snowflakes who define others by their narrow view of who is RIGHT. It is clearly a discriminatory and limiting litmus test of who is a real "american" everyone else be damned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Way to preside and focus on what matters! By all means do not address the number hospitalized during to COVID , the exhausted health care workers and shuttered businesses on your watch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You will work to shut down Twitter? You are announcing your intent to shut down Twitter—on Twitter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He lied to the people he exposed. He traveled prior to his arrival in Australia in violation of their travel rules. He blamed others for these violations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Concerned for students who may not feel safe, for those with family members who identify as LGBTQ, concerned for faculty and staff who mention partners or spouses, appropriately in context but then parents accuse of curricula violations . .hot mess, wrong, disrespectful, harmful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Commemorate the day by doing THE most appropriate thing and passing voters’ rights legislation. THAT is the right/best to do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No presidential misinformation about COVID, no threats of buying other countries, no insults of world leaders or domestic electeds, no lies, gosh missing the defeated former president]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Someone tell him he just said all that without fear of arrest and will not be arrested for saying what he did. And he can safely say it again. Had he said same in Russia . . . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fortunately, ALL the people around the BP and the Gov have antibodies for COVID including at the self serve beverage bar so the unmasked and close proximity are non issues!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Read that he’s started work to fight against human trafficking…his choice left those he hoped to help without his help, his family mourning and grieving. COVID is awful, deadly, lingering. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Political rally at church, during a church service, maligning many with political differences, heck maligning many. Really, what church is for? Really, why people go to church?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Because he came in as a strong second and raised a lot of money. After all, that’s what most look for in a president, yes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#   #USER# 
THIS is what your glee and support for the very small minority of anti vaccine truckers in Canada has wrought. Call for this to stop!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Have heard that the College Board plans to offer more weekend AND School Day SAT dates with the digital SAT---hard enough to have School Day with loss of instructional time, but WILL NOT and CANNOT if the College Board doesn't pay proctors on School Day--they do not do so now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Testifying as in talking to them and answering questions or exerting her fifth amendment right against self incrimination?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Thrilled this is being taken care of while I cannot get tested pending helping my elderly mother who has Alzheimer’s and hypertension]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Frustrated by what exactly and annoyed with whom? She KNEW what she was doing was wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "has questioned" means Trump asked Putin, "did you do anything with our elections?" and Putin said "no" and questioning over. Bold Mr President.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Comes with a bonus of Ginnie as a chief advisor?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# THIS and more these past few months cements the reality that “Trumpism” is code for open racism, open anti-semitism, open LGBTQ/gender identity/trans bias and IS the problem and is present nationwide. He made it “OK” to be openly hateful and hurtful. Pass VOTERS’ RIGHTS, VOTE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This week has felt as though 10 days long.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Actually, I’m ok with him being someone else’s problem…not that I can think of a country or group of people who I’d want this problem to affect…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pretty much yes, though. And unlike Boebert, Santa cares about kids so he’s probably wearing his vax card, with booster notes, on a cord around his neck. The missing piece for her and her cronies is the care-about-others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But they are calling on Ukraine to help resolve the crisis..by doing what? They are DEFENDING themselves. What should they do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right language, right intent, but now need a test case to see if the College Board has the mettle and if a state legislature understands teaching and learning…and consequence #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Thank goodness they can still play football! and that they are giving students and families time to recover in cases of positive COVID results (AND the experience of their teachers dying!). No mention of masking nor encouraging vaccination. sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How many 25yo make $100K/year?????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The style of the community, culture and infrastructure of the village, may not be affordable. Just saying…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What part of Trump’s “Fight like hell!” comment was intended to be peaceful? Why did you and Laura and Don Jr and Kilmeade and many GOP lawmakers have TIME to plead with Trump to send HIS people home before he finally addressed them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sending positive vibes to her, you and the health care team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Parenting is always challenging and the gifts of smiles, loving words, accomplishments are fewer than the challenges, but far more bountiful. I carry a lot of my kids’ transitions. Best to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The job isn’t meant to be “power”. You applied for, ran for a job to govern. Still waiting for governance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well we knew that because President Trump talks about him regularly, expressing concern and offering to send his cure. Right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I’m sure they will all be flooded with donor opportunity emails.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That the only concern is the call MAY have been recorded illegally is a significant problem. I don't think the defeated former president always lies, sometimes he believes his lies so he's befuddled at the outcry. He believes, as POTUS, he could not be accused of wrongdoing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Easy: here are the rules of what “users may not” do and I suggest testing #HASHTAG#:
“Users may not disparage, tarnish, or otherwise harm, in our opinion, us and/or the Site.”

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So of course #USER# has disclosed this on air, yes? Haha and guessing NOT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When did he get his booster shot? Did he pay for his booster shot? Has he listened to a physician about the booster shot? Also, shall we finally stop amplifying his lies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And when the topics are complex or disturbing, we discuss! Discussions that start in school can continue at home (many of which could have, should have started at home!).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They are also suggesting teachers are more afraid of lawsuits than the Department of Education—the entity overseeing their PROFESSIONAL WORK. They WANT teachers to know parents MAY sue over WHAT they teach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The ballot requests sent BY the Lt. Gov campaign had printed as the return address, the wrong address? SERIOUSLY?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Rep. Jim Banks, also known as Tucker Carlson’s son’s boss? That Jim Banks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Aww shucks! And "a portion of the proceeds" were due to go to the foster care system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Except for the dozens pleading in court that there were there for Trump and that Trump sent them there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Love the library and librarians. My aunt Helen was my favorite librarian ❤️ Thank you for doing that!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Incredibly incomplete &amp; inaccurate report of their coverage the night of January 6th and since. They blamed everyone EXCEPT Trump supporters on air while clearly believing Trump had ability and responsibility for HIS supporters at the Capitol that day. Expected better #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This language is problematic and potentially criminal in intent: launching a "direct and collateral attack" on election results and now I am very curious as to what "options for January 6" might be and what language is used. Insurrectionists took direction from these memos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That doesn’t make him innocent or not liable. It makes them as guilty and wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I’ve believed for months that my unvaxxed in-laws won’t tell us if they do get COVID and reading this now makes me think I’ll not likely tell them if my family or I as vaxxed and boosted get COVID. Sigh. More likely my cardiomyopathy stricken husband won’t see his sister again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# and except for the President and VP? and the force field is operational when at their desks so no others stopping by will be subject to transmission and no one touches another's desk or leaves papers so breathing in at one's desk and touching ones maskless face is safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How much more evidence of wrongdoing is needed? With all of this bad faith acting for a free and fair election let’s bring up legislation in GA to return to more equitable and fair access to early voting and accessible in place and number drop boxes. Also, arrests for harassment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There have been no attacks on Judge Child’s, from the left or otherwise. President Biden had many highly qualified candidates from which to choose. YOU voted for Judge Jackson before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Faculty and staff home sick because MO officials and some parents CHOSE TO NOT MITIGATE, NOT MASK, NOT VACCINATE. This is the consequence of poor choices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Do faculty and staff have additional KN95 or multilayer cloth masks provided to them? Upgraded filtration for the cold winter months when doors and windows sit remain closed? You do know if they, their families are sick, not enough staff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Well, at least they are learning and taking it seriously now if only to protect others, their staffs and their families.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Our tracing policy isn’t public but based on anecdotal evidence, I don’t believe anyone vaccinated has been considered a “close contact” of a COVID positive person even if they’ve been in close contact, for the purpose of notification. If I ever test positive, I’ll self notify.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wishing them well, brief of any symptoms and full recovery!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# THIS. This is how the GOP is politicizing the insurrection of January 6, 2021. People were killed that day. Our democratic republic was threatened. Members of Congress, their staffs, the VP and his family, journalists, all threatened. The GOP doesn’t care about people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Please do. You are in a very difficult situation, day after day, and it’s been a profoundly long time. Prioritize YOU—it’s the right and necessary thing to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Protecting the suburban housewives? Sending in federal troops to take care of the Dem run cities in half hour? “They are going to take your guns away”? No scare tactics here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# These people are making me wish for the revival of Sunday morning evangelical mega church on tv services. Sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well I’m sure the DOJ heard about this from WH officials or Trump as soon as they were approached?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No, they thought, we thought, think, the piece of cloth will contribute to the fix, as will the COVID vaccines and only being with people who mitigate similarly. Whole protocol for reasonable thinking people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# What you can DO about Trump’s speech is call for a floor vote of Voters’ Rights to show that you stand with the people of this country. January 6 would be a good day to hold the vote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He also called out the Supreme Court, McConnell and much of the GOP, and effectively most Americans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Do you have resources to help the family of this hero HCW?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Do you know who is more tired "of COVID" than "people"? Health care workers: tired of treating COVID, tired of those denying effects of COVID, tired of COVID deaths, tired of hostile family members and patients. If we all mitigate, we don't need mandates. We still need humanity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He Manchin is courting the GOP, which when the offer is right, will hand the Senate back to Mitch McConnell. Be wary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Barely before. Unvaccinated according to her declaration. Which is why there are vaccine and mask requirements at many places.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, that’s always been the purpose and goal when selecting a Speaker of the House, 3rd in succession to be POTUS. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Very sorry children and school personnel were put through this! Hope there is photographic and video evidence to prosecute the trauma they imposed—trespassing, terrorizing, threatening, harassment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# So you DO want to "come up here and SERVE"(???) because of the perks including insider information available . . got it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And DeSantis, Youngkin want parents able to approve/disapprove, legislators making choices, not educators. In most states, public school curriculum is viewable online, textbooks are publicly viewable and children live with their parents who can talk to children and view HW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Channeling his daddy with his word choice and personal attack. Cute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wait. The son of a president used his name and his father’s connections to get special favor for himself? Someone.tell #USER# because he seems upset when that happens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That’s why she had notes and plans drafted to streamline the process well before her daughter’s rejection! Wait, what? She didn’t? There are no notes and no plan? I’m shocked, I tell you! . #USER# Try again, first words are “I’m sorry” followed by “I made a mistake.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# helped with a compilation of VP certification script statements and #USER# version showing knowledge of the false alternate slates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I have a visceral reaction to these events, the flags, the hate speech.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What exactly is “fundraising solicitations” supposed to do to help them in court?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>