<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we be honest about some? Okay no? Fine imma go first!!!nnI used to argue with white men because I used to value their opinion subconsciously. Winning an argument with them meant approval. This is obviously the structure of White Supremacy + Patriarchy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hold AWNNNN alicia keyes and jay z inna room lmfao?!?!?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# U have me thinking! If Cancer is the mind, they really only get influence from themselves. The chanelling that happens is in them &amp; thru them. Virgo gets a lot of chatter outside of them tho (Pisces opp) so I wonder if it's easier to get stoic in the face of multiple waves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone wants to ignore the fact that Aquarius stay being misunderstood cause 

A) in sidereal they're coming from being a trop Pisces

B) in trop they're ruled by Uranus who is an out cast 

You're not gonna magically theory us into normal social behaviours ~]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wayment IM SCREAMING!!! She asked no *demanded* for free readings &amp; then tried to use Saturn as - ol gurl needs to run ðŸ˜­ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days I think its over and I'm ready to move on and its like she knows and she picks up on it and the next thing I know she is all that's on my mind. I dont even know if she knows shes calling on my soul. But i cant free myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Sounds like a personal problem den.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As they're ruled by the divine twin physicians (deity rulership). Nakshatra ruler is Ketu (south node)  and has an element of spiritualism attached to it. So for sidereal Aries in this case it's more spiritual, disciplined, &amp; potentially obsessed with occultism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[str8 women who allow themselves to be intimate with other women - i see how yall talk abt your wax appointments - but then turn around and call lesbians predatory - WHY?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&amp; sure you can be jealous n angry at me all you want but really you need to forgive yourself for not knowing better. cause that jealousy n anger WILL hurt your kids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transmisogyny rebranded loool.

You can be treated similar to women (not females) as a non woman bc patriarchy just oppresses anything that isn't a man (cis or not) in a similar grouping. You're better off discussing that than w/e tf this is. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# LISTEN LMFAOOOO my 3H Hasta Rahu saw that &amp; said oh its a WRAP skskkss cause thats hot asl &amp; probably isnt gonna help ðŸ˜­â™¥ï¸ but at least you can be the villian in his anthology series if it goes left &amp; sue him for all his writing $$$ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[some blck men dont deserve rights and idc cause they be moving in ways thats always harmful to Black women &amp; Black nonbinary folks. nnyour existence be causing the rest of us suffering, pls go figure out how to dissappear off the planet ASAP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and ngl she reminded me of my ex bestie for a moment cause they have the same big 3 (just sun n moon switched) w/ 8H synastry but its chill. they're v different in personality but they do share some aesthetics --- what can I say I have a type ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜‚â™¥ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cap sun x moon conj ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥

Libra be giving me a headache lmfaooo but at least I know this is an accountable friendship!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uttara Ashada moons STAND UP ITS TIME WE HAVE A CRY SESSION (BY MOSTLY FORCE)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't disagree. I'm very aware of the history of Christianity. However it's an insult to African Christianity to compare it to what is being practiced. Historically, the second Christianity reached Rome, WS was embedded. The Romans literally refused to read abt Jewish folks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found black Muslim tok n they lit lit fr Masha'allah â™¥ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# which a lot of cis men are already told to ascribe for under patriarchy so of course cis cap men are gonna be awful but its mostly because theyre men ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmao yall doing too much. Gemini = jack of all trades, sidereal or not. 

You're gonna have to give me more on how Hermes connects to any of the nakshatras sitting in sidereal gem &amp; their deities. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But if you wanted to check them yourself looks for any aspects happening between Mars &amp; planets in Virgo rn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[naur i shouldnt say none but like yeah - when nonbinary folks are everywhere &amp; are being "accepted" by corporations lmfao &amp; yet gender affirming surgeries for nonbinary folks isnt discussed, offered or covered???  nnmm deff performative, folks be lying somewhere #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it be confusing ppl when i say im not a woman n then go on to call myself a Black Woman but really ion see whats so confusing abt it ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜‚ 

its 2021 catch up !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... tbh ive read a cheating situation only once in a tarot reading. its not even a common occurrence omfg stop giving people anxiety ðŸ˜­ Also leave the Queen of Swords alone that's my baby ðŸ˜‚ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's two fold - recognizing unhealed vs healed Cancers. Unhealed cancers can &amp; do weaponize their emotions because that is their talent, &amp; imo its noble because we live in a society where weaponized emotions are extremely looked down upon (partially related 2 misogyny).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You're arguing semantics over shell companies ðŸ˜­ It's a merger, technically neither owns. But the point stands that FCA is not recognized as Fiat but rather Chrysler pointing to some form of ownership over Fiat in its operations in the states. Take it up with corporations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must he go through Hell (Taurus) &amp; figure out his values (Gemini) but alas so few have done so for the desire of Taurus burns n burns n burns with no reflection back towards God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me growin a likkle stache rn for 16 year old me ðŸ˜­ðŸ¥° #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[im in my stake era (stud fake)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yall rlly wanna feed malnutrition n poverty bodies to ppl by trynna associate stretch marks with nutrient deficiencies ~ nnjust say u hate fat folks n keep it pushing uggo #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[some bout Libra szn puttin me on my fuckboi mode #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saturn, my abusive father who I haven't decided yet if he's more or less abusive than my actual father ðŸ˜“ðŸ’€ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah I see! The fragility and implications of/for men comes once again before the liberation of Women ðŸ¥´ 

I think if yall want to create dialogie n space for cishet men (racialized specifically) u gotta engage them in being anti misogynoir for starters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[id pay big bucks to watch Megan twerk fuh me in person ðŸ¥º #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BRO IM HEATED ASF UNVAXXED BAE IS HOT ASL N POSTED THIRST TRAPS ON INSTA OMFG

i need a dyke to tap in &amp; help me write the messy reality tv show script that is my life cause the ppl need to see this A S A P ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sun, Mars &amp; Ketu nakshatras. nnI wanna befriend or marry all these naks ðŸ¥° The women &amp; nonbinary folks it be producing is just *chefs kiss* ðŸ˜˜ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read up on Vampires to get a better understanding tbh. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Absolutely! Your judgement goes beyond mine in this case.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They cant solve it globally but they can do a lot with that money locally. Distributing wealth should include the distribution of disposable income. They can afford to eat take out 7 days a week &amp; also donate to mutual aid funds. 

It's people with a 3rd of their income doing so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooo they have 4H, 8H, &amp; 12H synastry they must ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insha'allah ameen the good lord moves me back to or in proximity to the hood, i miss my ppl ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jan 4th, 2021 I put in a diary entry labeled "The truth is" ... 

&amp; just right now Jan 5th, 2022 I put in a diary entry labeled "Truth!!!" 

That's so fucking cool how the Universe is always in sync!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[rlly, i just want love for everyone! 

&amp; if we all want love for everyone, love that is defined as self actualization, freedom &amp; choice

then we WILL get love for everyone who wants it â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please b ooooooooooo st â™¥ï¸â™¥ï¸â™¥ï¸ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think a more positive so3in is to consider that if anklets are grounding &amp; provide protection (as per some cultures), then the thing you loose could be to your benefit. 

I wear a silver anklet w/ evil eye charm &amp; those days I never miss my bus. I'm losing my time being wasted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[its styll work hours but imma masturbate n take a nap skskks byeee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wasn't being shady at all with this tweet ðŸ˜­ it just REALLY clicked things for me!!! The way synastry be real af.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just knew in my mind that 1 of my talents would include an inclination towards semi constant inertia.

5th highest is *Libra* sun. Sigh. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if u are unwilling to do that for another because you recognize the foolishness of it, then why would u expect another to do the same for u? what u really want is someone who prioritizes emotional wellness &amp; regulation. someone whose favorite questions towards u are -]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Venus Mourning Star comin thru more than anybody else. Esp since I have a night chart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[im rlly preaching today oh my days holy spirit come thru! another reminder: when someone continues to flirt with you after rejecting you, you're not making it up in your head I PROMISE!

they're insecure &amp; like the attention you're giving them while they give you dust.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish nonbinary folks had more options available when it comes to transitioning. nnFeeling like you gotta go the traditional methods of transitioning for binary folks is stressful cause typically what you need is not covered under transitioning health care costs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oufff I am still trying to figure out how to better help my stomach because even with all my shadow work chileee the tummy STYLL UPSET ðŸ˜­ðŸ¤£â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I love it when uneducated people pretend like they know what's going a w n ðŸ˜­ðŸ¤£nnWhat even is leftism? Can you define it in a sentence?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i love seeing Black nonbinary femmes w/ top surgery ðŸ¥ºðŸ¥° 

lowkey goals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And thats all thats important! u finished it and now it can serve as an opportunity for reflection ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[n obvi when u compare to how binary trans folks are both not accepted &amp; come across similar barriers, it's v clear that transphpbia was not defeated via the "radical" identity of nonbinary folks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the jokes abt Drake being gay prolly not funny but this the same man calling himself a lesbian &amp; targeting teen gurls .... 

hes also not gonna be a good example of male heterosexuality ðŸ˜­ even in an alt ~ way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thinking about how fat women aren't allowed to post headshots like the skinny folks because it means we're hiding our bawdies like ... maybe my makeup was popping but im still wearing pajamas what do u want from ME?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pls pass along funds if you can spare some!!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i am at peace with Islam, i no longer live with it in fear. Somalis used to worship a sky God by the name of Waaq who can be understood to be Allah before Allah was known as such.

That already tells you a link exists between "polytheism" &amp; monotheism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Death can be beneficial if it's making way for a more grown version of you. However Death takes its toll when it takes the self away without permission, &amp; something tells me we don't actually want to be putting others before ourselves. So dont.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[clearly feeling a likkle unstable but idec its LIBERATING!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe analysis might help. I have a 3H Virgo Venus. We're using my tropical placidus chart here. 

I *value* (Venus) communication (3H) in relationships (V). I am of the school you can talk through anything ~ 

However my Venus is also incredibly service oriented (Virgo/6H).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @ my trans folks on hrt - has a covid diagnosis got in the way of your meds? Is it gonna cause complications to take my T this week despite being sick with some?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my managers making me go into work with covid symptoms ðŸ‘€ðŸ¤« #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[its actually rlly easy to cum solo dolooooo but k #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you hate me? Do you wanna see me lose it? Hurt myself? Just free me. Stop thinking about me, about us. It never happened. Bury me asap!!! I dont understand anything that happened between us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My bloodline did not survive colonization &amp; all its horrors only to be taken out by exhaustion overseas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So maybe it's a sign you need to talk about yourself more.

It looks like bragging but sometimes people are just proud of themselves &amp; their accomplishments despite the daily struggles they go through. 

We should all give ourselves permission to talk ourselves up more! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lotta cis men have body envy n just be mad they cant serve bimbo realness when truthfully they could if they wanted ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're gonna be arguin with yo self all day lmaooo, I said what I said in the first place. 

Ps, didnt realize "doesnt date trans people" was a sexuality but I learn some new every day about you brain - nignogs. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[im sorry but yall will never make me wanna bully a Black Trans Woman thats "scamming" with gofundmes

yall really mad at the root of the problem!! i dont have time to be outraged over that when Capitalism is right there ðŸ˜« like ok u got scammed?? take the L &amp; keep it movin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: crying bc im trans

You: acts like ppl willingly want to be trans

idk fam u might be wrong here #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[its the way yall keep saying nonbinary isnt a 3rd gender &amp; then just dissolve it within the binary ... nnwhile we on the topic of men getting pregnant - nonbinary folks too. its getting uncomfortable out here w/ the way gendered language is utilized.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i geuss its fair to say i still miss her but my life woulda been so stagnant had she still been in it 

so many things have changed in just 5 months - so much more than the year &amp; a half i knew her 

when things be revoked, its ALWAYS to your benefit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the nbys been asking since the early 2010s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the danger in rebelling against patriarchial norms by taking on the opposing norms is that you miss out on an opportunity for interrogation about what genuine roles you play &amp; want to play. 

look at me now, i cant cook despite a desire to want to at least know the basics ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the idea that someone outside of u is going to come in &amp; save u is rooted in the myth of the caretaking mom. u grew up only knowing help when it was intrusive &amp; anticipating. to require that same kind of aid is to require another human being to put their entire self aside for u.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[im not in community with trans men &amp; nonbinary folks who don't know how to act right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lmaooo sun moon + potential moon moon omfg ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜­!! Imma look at both their charts closer rn since I'm watching the show!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is it weird that ion trust the yt aquintances I know from France because I don't trust yt folks from Quebec? ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it woulda been sexier if she just sat there sucking her loli n said none!!! sometimes silence be sexier than this weird whisper stuff fake doms do ðŸ˜­â™¥ï¸ but styll love her #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dont want to be around people who make me feel like a monster/abuser/etc for making mistakes

The kind of people who wanna punish you &amp; see you humiliated n small 

Cause EYE do not wanna be that person. I'm choosing to believe -]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm realizing that this entire time I wasn't looking for someone to complete me, or make me whole or do anything that requires me *needing* them. I simply want to be seen &amp; accepted for who I am, because *eye* see myself &amp; who I am &amp; what I can be. That's all I ask from a partner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me &amp; having an affinity to always dying my hair red. Wonder which one of my ancestors be coming thru. Gonna have to ask around about Ancestors ðŸ¥° #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Venus day hoes, Aphrodite said ION PLAY ABOUT MY BLACK GWORLS!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# that my blackness &amp; femmeness will always be a signal of war to others &amp; that there's nothing wrong with standing in honour of your identity. She's given me the gift of building a genuine base for my self esteem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[we can definitely agree that its usually more nuanced and relies on the building of class structures supplementing other factors like ethnicity &amp; religion for where "race" cant exist

but its all predicated on whiteness existing at the top of a hierarchy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# oh my the way i been stressed &amp; its the yt folks at my workplace thinking its all a game ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the summer was actually traumatizing. i was being surveilled by pigs for activist work i was doing, fighting all the "organizers" ie community members i thought had our safety as priority, being in private meetings w/spies etc on top of mourning the death of friend #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's definitely your DK cause I feel the same way abt Martians ðŸ¤¢ðŸ›‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should include nonbinary genders within it. Even nonbinary genders that have nothing to do with womanhood. This then forces the field for man to actually narrow as cis + het instead of woman. This would however have to include a concentrated effort from nonbinary folks exempt -]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i owe it to the people around me to seriously ask them how i can help facilitate them falling in love with life &amp; themselves again. i blame nobody when i say what im about to. i spent the last 5 years wanting to die &amp; i wasnt silent about it at all. i deeply internalized death.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i actually dont like a lot of yall ðŸ˜­ its gonna be an unfollowing spree soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I know im not part of this convo so please someone tell me to exist if necessary! 

I have a sidereal Cancer rising &amp; it took me a long time to get along with Cancers &amp; I still struggle. For me it's my 12H Cancer in tropical. We gotta interrogate our 12H of the subconscious too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Mars dk showing out real loud i hate it here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[not to be a hater but im so tired of seeing Black/White interracial couples on my TL ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ nnI want better for Black Women I'm sorry you can't convince me you experience more intimacy with a cracker then literally anyone else ðŸ¤§ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last paragraph or two is what did it in for me. Un fucking hinged. FULLY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[but yes im a libra sun in both trop &amp; sidereal &amp; it makes me feel [redacted]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[imma be real - the only teacher who saw my writing skills is a Chinese teacher I had in the 3rd grade. She was the ONLY racialized teacher at my elementary school. It's because of her positive words that allow me to keep writing despite all the yt women who said I can't. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In loving myself will I find my mirror &amp; together we will pray to the Gods.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[psychiatrist youtube lady just told me that much research isnt done on bipolar + shrooms so u prolly shouldnt do it lmfao

ok bipolar here ðŸ‘‹ðŸ¾ i dont suggest it unless u rlly ready to be triggered to hell n back. and lsd is a NO ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ™…ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[not twin flames just meaning someone with the same desires n goals as you in achieving communal love ~  

im a firm believer if u are coming into contact with an unhealed twin they not gon be yours this life time OR they not your twin.

throw tomatoes at me ion care!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&amp; unfortunately a lot of beautiful women are groomed into accepting less, waaaay less. Beautiful women being with you is not a marker of your worth. It's a marker of her now proclaimed inferiority. She *belongs* to a lesser man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# &amp; now everyone around me doesn't believe I had a cousin ðŸ˜± the vaccine made that nigha DISSAPPEAR!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[being attracted to genitals is weird idc nnI like women, &amp; I like nonbinary folks who dont I'D as men, but their genitals? Dgaf. Theres so many ways to have sex like chileee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i LOVE THIS! In Islam a call to the end of times is exactly like in Kali Yuga - role reversals. Its almost affirming that actually things are meant to be like this. we cannot destroy kingdoms if our Kings are in them!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My UBP Ketu being the reason for my obsession w/ snakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't want ANY kind of pressure to be perfect, I just want to be! So I'm making peace with the fact that people may come back &amp; I will make mistakes again. The fun is trying. Also, sometimes person from the past = you. Dont forget that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby we gon be leaning on each other HEAVYYY cause ðŸ¤¢ i know who all coming back #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have much love for Cancers n Geminis. I MUST! They be all up n in and out my life ðŸ¤£ðŸ¥°â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this thread isnt saying gay folks are complicit in their own oppression cause lets be clear these ppl being violent don't see themselves as gay.nnbut its showing how queer identities are socially restricted/repressed &amp; can become tools of violence with the support of patriarchy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me, not wanting to get outta bed for work sksksk. imma sleep in a bit. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Okay imma see if i can find software to check my d10 with pushya!!! Right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hmm we do both share Jupiter ruling the pada wrt Sag &amp; Pisces! 
That's interesting, I try to hold my tongue but can't ðŸ™ˆ

So there's deff some self indulgence. Sitting around too long makes me itchy tho &amp; I'm sure other placements can explain - ie my Ashwini 10H AL as 1. Thank u!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lmfao i gave my number n insta out to security bae

man the way im stressed 2 see if she hmu ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean whatever it was it was dark n heavy n mans actually doesn't care for his fans :/ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You start by interrogating your feelings. How do you genuinely feel about people who move that way? Give yourself time to accept them &amp; you'll find yourself accepting that behavior in yourself. If others don't like that standard, that's okay, they can simply keep it pushing âœŒðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[no we're forever mourning the true love we're constantly denied #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[its wishful thinking but we're abt to enter some rlly dark times ... 

might end up with a federal conservative gov &amp; provincial conservative gov #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i guess thats the beauty in being an artist &amp; writer. i can rewrite our story a million times but it will be in anticipation for another life time. maybe today i can pen the story in where we get it right next time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what kind of garbage?? 

the entire point is you dont #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think there's truth to it but like cis ppl saying that are really just parroting what they hear cause wtf they know abt gender variant folks?!

Honestly the give away for me is them identifying as females instead of women. They see their sex as some they contend with -]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[exactly like "delusion" is just u exercising your imagination i cant believe ppl be trynna police dreams n imaginations n shit smsksksk 

i want others to want better for themselves!!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aries &amp; then Cancer being next in the cardinal signs makes a lot of sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# just close your eyes! i see red strings pulling us all, tethered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SCREAMING!!! ðŸ¤£ðŸ˜‚â™¥ï¸ As you should!!! Its an extreme sport trying not to make even eye contact with them!!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Ok and? What do u plan to do about it? Its easier after a point to just let go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&amp; really it all boils down to what ive been saying but have been too ashamed to say LOUDLY!!! it always comes down to love. the reason for caring, living &amp; activism. all our motivations should always come down to love &amp; self love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dont call me a non man loving non man EVER ðŸ¤¢ 

lesbian is ok 2 say]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing to life aside from the ability to experience joy of the self &amp; of others. We all deserve to experience that joy regardless of our qualifications. To live life, to deserve to be alive has nothing to do with material conditions. It has to do with feeding the soul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[its so funny when ppl say this to nonbinary folks cause clearly ive figured it out!nnnaur anyway, the gender affirmation when transphobes try to transphobe ðŸ˜ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[deff used in homophobic ways rather than a critique on how frustrating heteronormativity can be but a whole word! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I want to make clear is the inclusion of some nonbinary folks under the same oppression women face points to woman being a useless identifier if it just stands for cis read *BINAR* woman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes yes yes! it is my responsibility to hold my emotions &amp; check myself &amp; move accordingly after the fact â¤

&amp; while i may be in my feelings for a minute or so bc that's the human brain, I will get over it in the name of giving myself &amp; others love. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All kinds of nonbinary people who are perceived as women, as feminine, as submissive or lesser than in their supposed masculinity like a soft butch nb individual. I'm trynna find more literature on this. Obviously this doesn't include all nonbinary folks under woman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly, Ancestors always provide for me even if it's not optimal, &amp; because of that I feel so much better doing readings for people &amp; having them donate things instead!!! 

Maybe in the future I can have an option for both but after coming out my 12H profection year -]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plus ruling every day matters &amp; communication it makes sense to attribute even the convo thats always reoccuring to merc retrograding lool revisiting the same old ðŸ˜­ Mercury that biiih!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# In that situation you treat them like any other human &amp; enforce your boundaries &amp; create distance. If they ever want your insight on how they can do better, you can give it but the main priority is distance. For healed Cancers, imo its the discomfort in how open they are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Came across a thread talkin abt your rising sign &amp; childhood experience &amp; leo rising came up for those who experienced physical abuse. Kinda shook lmao cause yeah &amp; then I realized it's the Scorpio 4H in WSH.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all this to say i am v content being single &amp; am just gonna devote myself to the Gods ameen ðŸ™ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Translation: big bad PPC leader doing spider man meme with the big bad Liberal leader]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is genuinely a lovely read. It resonated, all of it! for me as a Pushya rising! 

The only advice I have for us Cancer risings is courage. Yes our power will be tested, but we cannot fail. In our most vulnerable, there will be those lurking in the shadows ready to defend us. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Your cancer rising holding a lotta weight against that Taurus sun merc venus combo w/ aqua moon ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ 

Is this trop or sidereal? we share a moon if tropical! Also the gods said make this one attractive when they came up with you!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also my thread is in no ways saying all Black folks have access to AAVE, but that as a Black person you have access to your own form of language to communicate w/ the ACB folks around you. &amp; that when discussing AAE (African American English) &amp; ACE (African Carribean English) - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[anyway i woke up today realizing everything that is to be taken away from me will because its written as such &amp; that i cant keep fighting that energy. 

like the Universe isn't constantly taking opportunities away from me ~ its actually constantly giving me better opportunities]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sometimes blue lights come for you simply because they want to, not because you've done shit.

avoiding them isn't about internalizing guilt for shit u aint did, its about staying safe.

some battles you will n do lose. its gonna be okay â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes actually. libra is love of the self based off derivative astrology. 

therefor love of the self can include masturbation &amp;/or sharing masturbation with someone ie sex #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Virgo wants to always be perfect (constructed) because they see all the moving parts that creates the structure &amp; it's so overwhelming. They feel like they have to know how to navigate something instead of just navigating it. With time tho does it get easier to float.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I forgot to reframe the 9H being the 12H from a reframed viewpoint. Since you are no longer required to extinguish your desires for the good of others, what do you think happens? From the 10H, you understand that when you remove fear from the equation, your desires stumble -]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[also do your part &amp; stop asking ppl who dont volunteer info up why they're using a cane lmfaoooo 

that shit awkward &amp; insensitive af.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ive been productive today - working on music &amp; writing &amp; im so scared this trend wont continue but im also tired that i pulled my tarot cards out for permission 2 rest ðŸ˜­ 

then they made fun of me for pulling cards to ask for permission to rest IM SCREAMING ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤£ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# its genuinly devious the way Somalis are pitted against other Black folks, esp when it comes to Black funding ðŸ˜¬

I hope February brings a partnership that fully sees you in your authentic light!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I believe in you fr fr!!! You are just as amazing n magical as the ppl in your life. If you need an extra push just think of all the ppl in ur life &amp; their wonderful qualities n know that they're qualities existing in you too â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tbh when I dated men it was the feminine men I fucked withnnW/ women n all nonbinary folks I give em a bigger space to work with to be fluid nnBut men without any femininity present not only turns me off but I also lose respect for them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... so you dont own the means you just own a fraction of it which you then also hoard leaving even less money to "trickle" down to people under the poverty line ... not capitalistic at all tho #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saw someone trynna make fun of nonbinary folks by saying we have multiple gendered ppl in our heads n honestly issa mood fuh me not even a drag nnits not just me in this vessel. my Ancestors of all genders shine thru me ameen ðŸ™ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love astrology so much. Any problems I have I go to consult the sky! 

Helloooo ~ Air sign things ðŸ¤ªðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmao I don't apologize cause ion fuck up in the 1st place - UA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pleasee we need to talk soon ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ man I rlly pissed someone off past lives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do not want to live in anxiety &amp; fear this year. I will be trying my hardest to let go of what ifs &amp; worries &amp; doubts, especially if they belong to others. 

I do not speak the language of what ifs, worries &amp; doubts, esp those I CANNOT CONTROL! Imma let it goooooo! Imma just DO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wasn't there so I can't speak to your context specifically if I'm being truthful.

You can only trust those who shut down certain conversations to have done so with a good enough reason for *them*. If the reason isn't good enough for you or others, please create a new space ðŸ™ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen y'all, please! If all someone talks about is negative astrology or dark astro with no regards in how everything exists in duality, just leave them alone. 

It really hurts when I see the way ppl abuse such a spiritual gift &amp; tool for negative ðŸ˜‘ #USER# is amazing â¤ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜‚ then i become the villain for spraying the house down in lysol cause im poisong em!!! But lets gooooo ðŸ˜‚

black folks crack me up akdkfjc #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[to create race is to then further classify people. If women are objects &amp; racialized people are capital, then racialized women become objects of capital. &amp; so on!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What am I missing? She didnt touch the sea lion. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Neoliberal" ahh you mean a (socially) progressive capitalist? ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmao other Diaspora African folks stinky as hell. Go back home then if y'all don't wanna give African Americans peace smfh?!?!?!? Make it make sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delete it but I got the screenshots styll lmfaoooo #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you want power - go to men
if you want love - go to women 

even tho power &amp; love belong to men, women &amp; nonbinary folks, this is the construction that exists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[??? How are they Indigenous to Israel if Israel is a recent existence ðŸ˜­nnUnless you meant Jerusalem, which was the Indigenous home of Arab Christians, Jewish folks, &amp; Muslims.  Collectively*** #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I refuse to answer to anyone who wants my demise, who wants me oppressed &amp; under their control. No.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm gonna try and download it on my sisters computer this weekend and keep you posted because I'm mostly curious at this point!! 

Also thank you! Personally consulting for someone else's business sounds awful. Not enough freedom in speech! Hence Merc x Saturn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[theres some abt fire signs not wanting to commit to you but being too possessive to let you go and be sabotaging every attempt at romance you make with others lmfaooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# oh fr? that's why i must love her !!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scorpio is where Justice lands underground. 

The purveyor of souls. It is He who aids the Gods in the judgement of characters. 

Scorpios cannot be lied to because they will always see through you. As Angels of Dark &amp; Light (literally), lets put some respect on their name â™¥ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Please I was just thinking that!!! ðŸ˜­ I hope her nails are okay ðŸ¥²]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# wish it was acceptable to spit on ppl like dis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[damn its a good thing aint nobody touching me n my moon ðŸ™ðŸ¾ Visvedevas come thru w/ them yogas too!!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Quran clearly states that hellfire is kept going by men &amp; stones!!! Humans and the stones we cast in wickedness!!! To reject love for another is to reject the Divine, is to reject faith, &amp; in hell you live. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think teaching small classes would maybe okay? Or not cause it's Virgo which rules small things ðŸ¤£ 

Idk the more I think about it tho teaching/consulting sounds nice ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[trynna watch a pick a pile about my current crush and ofc demon from the past comes thru ðŸ¤¢ 

i regret ever letting her know shes v capable of conjuring smfh skxjxjjx you 8Hsr' got me fcked up!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LMFAOOOO fr its a toss if imma get licked but dont care cause imma still talk my shit and throw my punches #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[atp I see an Ecuadorian flag &amp; any mention of communist in their bio &amp; block cause they rlly about to be on some anti black &amp; highkey fascist politiques]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[we are living through an opioid crisis + a housing crisis + climate change + a *pan*demic ... things are not ok right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rest in power bell hooks. i cant even ... lmao imma write some poems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Universe really got blessings on the way for you Masha'allah ðŸ™ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bantu isn't a culture??? Erhmmm racist. It's a language group. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# on your chart is a little excessive, and atp I'd look into working on your control issues wrt Libra n Virgo placements ðŸ˜œ but yeah just a natural method of remediation is to simply live your life and focus on changing the things you don't like with therapy or introspection - 2/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head to toe coordination LETS GO LIBRAAAAAA !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somali* lmfao can yall stop playing with our name!!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the vers urge to equally reciprocate this act between each other #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I really think you have the ability to pick up on peoples energy &amp; emotions too, it just takes time to get grounded enough to tap into it. 

21 &amp; after seems to be a time people tap back into that energy, &amp; 24 gives people a solid understanding of what their abilities be!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Africa as a whole is healing. My dad said, "people will come to stop caring back home about the ways you exist" &amp; it paralleled convos I been having with friends all month.

Africa WILL see a day without colonialism, and it's gonna see it sooner than later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if ur a capitalist still in 2022 omfg how EMBARRASSING ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[some abt certain gay women expecting their partner to be vulnerable in certain ways, be degrading them &amp; then denying their partner that experience.... cause they know its abuse, mmmm smells like misogyny 

u gay or just hate yourself &amp; be punishing women???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I regret pulling tarot cards. Last night I pulled the 2 of swords &amp; fool reversed. I had a feeling of what the decision would be but I didn't think it would be weighing on me this heavy ðŸ˜¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEVER!!! I am always moving forward in looking for connection(s). #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I AM SCREAMING AKDJFJFJCJCJCJ!!! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ 

I am my biggest nonbinary goals fr ðŸ˜ #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>