<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ Without the position of power and PhD or certification as a therapist or doctor etc it's nonsensical and pretty crazy at times. Don't tell me they don't see it and even laugh about it. There's just no way. They're laughing all the way to the bank but when they encounter truly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've shared a book from Google Play Books
Do As I Say (Not As I Do), Peter Schweizer.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. media release graphic photos of American soldiers abusing Iraqi prisoners at Abu Ghraib | HISTORY
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch "I'm giving a police department an armory" on YouTube
#URL#

Help him raise money!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dunno if this has happened yet but this ebook/book is about the USA focusing on profit for war, not national security. So basically, we're just pirates. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: America's education system is in need of dramatic reform - CNN
#URL#

The education system hasn't changed in 150 years while everything else has drastically changed. I was listening to an audiobook, Abundance: the future is better than you think, hence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though who knows how that video was edited. I'm not sure which way the blame goes but you'd think just cooperating would be the thing to do but I can see being scared to get out of the car.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope I'm not contributing too much to negativity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antifa and nerds can be racist though so kinda the same difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These people weren't cops but it's that general attitude that bugs me and I don't think people are that conscious of it sometimes. It just is and it's so mainstream it's like questioning breathing and eating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm thinking it's the Kingston clan or there's other polygamists in the neighborhood or the sects are simply satellites. Testing the waters and scouting ahead and networking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ Wow, scum white trash are still starting stuff in Smith's. Even saying stuff about my mom in aggression and that I should stay away from their women. It's because my haircut looks nice and I like spiritual white music. Teens too not just older long haired men that belong in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ken Wilber's Call to Grow Up, Clean Up, Wake Up, and Show Up | Psychology Today
#URL#

Great idea!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Platforms like Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, live journal, Reddit etc make you wanna get in people's faces and make statements that WILL trigger someone out there. Kinda odd we still use them like we still eat McDonald's even though it kills.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghanistan: U.S. Worried Iran Sending Chinese Weapons To Taliban
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.#USER#, #USER#, #USER# This pandemic won’t end until we get people around the world vaccinated. Direct Congress to invest in the global vaccination effort this year. Let’s get this done. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've encountered several nice people but I'm surprised at how many mean people I've run into.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LGBTQIA can be racist too and even discriminate amongst each other. It's not like they're all innocent and there's high rates of domestic abuse and rape among them compared to other groups and more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ I'm deferring to God. I don't make the rules. I prefer rescuing everyone but if it's to be it's up to he.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cranky geeks, Natalie DelConte, Miss Download, Diggnation etc i forgot the others i binge watched.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ Ohh that reminds me of the BBS people lol they were nerd bullies. All they could think of was debate at first but then they calmed down. Growing pains and one told me it was cuz they went through a lot. I hope they and theirs don't have to go through crap again. I know what #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ recognized because he says the left gives them a free pass, which only increases that crime and it makes things unsafe for the Black community overall not just white people. He didn't say that all in so many words but that's what I gather from his videos. It is the same for us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ dusting at mass and pokin the altar boys in the shoulder with my pointing finger to annoy them with "pester pester child molester" cuz, get it? Like Webelos has don't molest the cows and it means the same in Spanish lol and then i made jokes about the polygamists thinking it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utah is full of creepy people I'll add. Freaking polygamists or whatever. Just so many creepy people and not just the weird Kingston creeps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes the pedos. And then Winslow is full of shit that he's investigating polygamists. Dude, he works for them lol and at Deseret news as well before Faux 13]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google can be a good service but too much cyber or simulation, fake, is emptiness. The abyss. The darkness instead of the light. Google is nicer than Facebook that's for sure. I'm buying a Pixel again next chance i get but I'm #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch "Prosecutor who opposed COVID vaccine mandates dies after contracting virus" on YouTube
#URL#

That's sad. That's someone's family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ My motto still is "mean people suck" and I was gonna get a t-shirt and bumper sticker as well. I'm thinking this is over that. I talked about it a lot. And i tweeted that the song Mean I'd play from Mexico City about the racist gringos when i immigrated there. These people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ but no warning from the state department to not go there. Lame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moses 7nn#URL# verse 22. Mormons think Africans came from Cain but there's a footnote that leads to 2 Nephi 26:33. That's brilliant actually cuz it says yeah, like the fall of Adam means we are mortal but we only answer for what we ourselves do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch "Make It Happen" on YouTube
#URL#

Maybe these vices and sins are merely regression or never leaving a childlike state. Ever see how children are with little self control and discipline? Plus there's mental illness and TBI.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ there in believing you cease to exist after this life? And they're doing science rather than focusing on charity? Dude! What's that say about atheism? Sure there's atheists that give a lot to charity but it didn't really start that way. It was nullifier time against religion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I suppose they can invade by proxy. Political parties, activists etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ Remember avian bird flu/SARS in China? They stopped that. Sucks that this time it got away from them but also from Trump. He claimed it was a hoax and refused to do anything for a long time and then suddenly he's all saying he knew all along it was real and was the first to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I made a big donation, comparatively, to this. Climate change. Everything else is in motion and this is the most neglected so I'll try to pay attention to it the most. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like i call Hitler Dumkauf Shitler. Lol and nutzis instead of Nazis. And Nazi mormons and Nazi blondes. Lol and krautzis here in the USA. Funny how Romney and his polygamists in Mexico are fighting the cartels for their right to dingle teens. Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not all Mormons are like that. There's a fair amount that are but many are decent too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abuse is a cycle and they were probably abused themselves. Maybe the kids made comments and pissed them off?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Verge: Facebook runs the coward’s playbook to smear the whistleblower
The Verge: Facebook runs the coward’s playbook to smear the whistleblower.
#URL#

Figures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They seemed like nerds though in Walmart. Hmmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ Richard Dawkins is wrong about the idea of God being a delusion and the Bible being false. It's too structured, complex and sensitively sensical to be a delusion. No offense to him he's trying to be good but he's just wrong. He's right though in that some use religion to do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ somewhere but how long are we just going to keep starting and pray for different results? It's not just Spain or a few countries. We're all pretty much like that except I think the Nordic countries are doing a lot of things right. I haven't kept up but what I saw surprised me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ I'm trying to be good meaning I'm good and sticking to my guns, and here I've got haters. I'm not some public figure or even an author, scientist, teacher. I'm unemployed because of a TBI and Latinos in this country have mostly been creeps and assholes. That's the raw truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ brotherhood and sisterhood, new rich experiences that enchant and enhance your heart and spirit and make you happy. I think racism stems from misery and when travel makes you happy around other people, happiness makes you kind, and kindness makes you happy. It becomes the good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch "Pixel 6 Review: the only smartphone you should buy" on YouTube
#URL#

I kinda want one. My Samsung is acting up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ I think the BBS types were partly responsible for my losing my spiritual connection, which ironically kept me friends with them and apart from concussions changing my personality and views, that's why I turned on them. And then also turned my back on family and church. Look]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Browse the Lists of Intangible Cultural Heritage and the Register of good safeguarding practices - intangible heritage - Culture Sector - UNESCO
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People in jail with brain injuries when they all should be in the hospital with the mentally ill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch "Valeria Gastaldi - Mover Tu Cama" on YouTube
#URL#

Woah! She went bi or lesbian! Kinky and hot. Lol one of my favorite singers. I remember her song Inventario and also beautiful day. I bought the whole album.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's why certain latinos in the area i live in targeted me. It's a type of chess move so to speak. An investment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seen this online. I'm not sure if true but wouldn't surprise me. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ but definitely not the other guy speaking to his kid unless he's being a funny man going into a Mexican restaurant and seeing how long it takes me to catch on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# North Ogden pass has some good sunsets too. Utah in general is sunset heaven. Thanks for sharing. This is one i took with a Samsung phone some time back. I think it was my S10. when i had a Pixel 4a 5g it also took great sunset photos and video. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope there's a peaceful solution but I'm not holding my breath.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch "Linda Ronstadt - La Charreada 1989 live performance" on YouTube
#URL#

She does it well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Accused of Laying Off a Terror Group for the Iran Deal
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The BBS people were offering me sanctuary too. Maybe it's still a thing covertly. The knights templar against the Catholics still.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ I think I know why there's a disproportionate amount of Black people and interracial couples in commercials etc and in the media including movies and TV. It's the opposite of the broken window effect. It's actually not a bad idea but it does feel odd at first but if you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It could be symbolic, a warning to Asians I've been friends with or to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ Don't criminals sometimes return to the scene of the crime? The serial ones. That's why Bill Mangus tried adding me on Facebook. And it reminds me of the youth gone wild song by skid row he liked so much. That also reminds me of my experiences in Utah with some people. Pretty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… La Raza by Kid Frostn#URL#'m realizing... Utah and Idaho have issues with people from California as if your inbreeding, sheep molesting, child molesting, marital rape states full of Nazis, KKK and teen raping polygamists are better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ And the Kingston thing. That freaks me out. I might have done 2 things. Fallen for a lie by now or be married it not for the bbs types "warning" me about polygamists so yeah, seems that LGBTQ are hunting, gays and bisexuals actually. A few transgender have messed with me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ that's like. I think I partly won them over because I'd been through a lot and didn't let it get to me. Until it did and then I lost them but that's TBI and mental illness that results from it. They're hard to distinguish I mean there's no bubble over my head that let's me or]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even in Mexico there are commies including their current president. He's friends with other communists as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ If I can remember, the Marxists took over civil rights and Latinos are among them . Latin alliance and their album rapping that this land is stolen and that they're fighting for their land again and they're a Hispanic causing panic and the fact that Mexican communists are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL# per Deseret News Mormons support him most and Winslow is from there. Either undercover or not. Cuz that group was mean. But it seems they knew about polygamists before i did. Not that it had anything to do with me. Dunno why they brought him in later]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ It's not just the YouTube algorithm. The news mostly shows black and Latinos committing crime. Or immigrants and refugees. Then you get people going Nazi and KKK on ethnic people. It's almost like tech and news is used to herd hate towards all of us, even the innocent. Or they]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know, negative people turned me into negative news. I'm as bad as the journalists I criticized now. Hmm I wonder if that was the intention of some. There's gang stalking etc but probably just as mischief in my case though they make threats so it's bullying too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Atlantic: Why Health-Care Workers Are Quitting in Droves
The Atlantic: Why Health-Care Workers Are Quitting in Droves.
#URL#

That's terrible for our healthcare workers. I feel for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3/ It's also medical doctors at times. That's why people avoid the doctor cuz you're gonna just get worse sometimes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox News: Cruz blasts CNN analyst over ‘Let’s Go Brandon’ post
Fox News: Cruz blasts CNN analyst over ‘Let’s Go Brandon’ post.
#URL#

That's true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Won't that article on how we can get our two parties to trust and not fight work for us and Russia and China and eventually North Korea? If we explain our intentions and how it's not meant to bring down the other side then it's better for all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch "“Spot Me Up” | The Rolling Stones &amp; Boston Dynamics" on YouTube
#URL#

Great coordination]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Granted it could be white racists or hired by or just the fact that criminals just by chance that targeted me are of color. But it's upsetting when I'm a minority to be targeted by minorities in a sense but it would be as bad as being targeted by white people which i have been.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ other minorities and killed many. Marx was a bit brain too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ minutes away? I'll take the taxi. I have nothing against taxis. They've been beneficial for decades. I think they can just bring more to the table and be relevant to customers again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ Africans aren't descendents of Cain. That's racist bunk and I've heard some Mormons in Oroville say Africans came from Cain but when i moved from Oroville i heard the mark isn't that. It's something else. Oroville is small town mentality. They had in 2010 about 12k people. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ sword. Seriously. Look what we've come to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ I'm just pointing this out and certainly not condoning it but could it be that people dislike or hate Jews because white people, the West, Christians that do so much bad or did, keep pushing the notion that they're the chosen people? That's basically discrimination by]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. A couple guys were racist to me when I went to Papa Murphy's to get my pizza. It wasn't staff but customers and one went into the Mexican restaurant next door ironically saying something about Mexicans in general being a menace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There would be a violent uprising though if you made it mandatory like seatbelts. Dunno why but people are crazy. Well, Darwin awards. That's the truth of life. I hate to say it but they did it to themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ How Native Americans adopted slavery from white settlers | Conflict | Al Jazeera #URL# They're so woke. Al Jazeera is lame. Even in the movie Dances with Wolves it shows raiding parties being used to take slaves. Africa had slaves and the middle east and]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost like we're watching, you're surrounded. Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohh the CIA is tied you cartels, Mormon polygamists to Mexico, and the Anarchists blow up AI and Nanotechnology there and veterans think AI and nano is creepy. Yup. I agree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Deeth/Starr Valley, Nv #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ Watch "Bronagh Gangs In Utah State Prison" on YouTube #URL# I'm appreciative of the ones that were kinda and peaceful but what changed? Seems the fat chicks and Mormons and others. No joke. And Anarchists. Hackers too. Likely the pedos etc. Polygamists etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ Mexicans" etc they'd be mean to me and go out of their way to make it uncomfortable for me and since i have PTSD and past traumatic experience with that sort of thing, I naturally assume people are after me and they think they're after the people that offended them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has a treatment for Alzheimer's been sitting on pharmacy shelves for decades? Scientists have two possible candidates
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ I'm pretty sure the far right and left partnered. The old version of a cartoon. One for me, one for you, one for me etc.. religious terrorism. Like in ain't no fun by Snoop Dogg and Michael Swift and Mormon polygamists which it's not always willing women. Though some women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to try to take it easy from thinking. It's too much for me. Over thinking that is. I need a rest. I've had neurologists tell me to take it easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ maybe they're just being funny but I'm sure there's people that are serious. Aren't there gay communist cowboys? I've shared the links before. They're probably not happy i did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vets should be getting fewer disability benefits, more help in post-military life says former SECVA
#URL#

Read a little bit. I guess that's true. It's like not healing a broken bone and giving you money instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ later in the years in 2010 I was afraid I had another Mangus incident because I didn't remember making up or them apologizing to be my friends. And they're hackers. Hackers and other tech people have hazing which i wasn't aware of until years after I got mad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ I have other friends though so it's ok. It's obvious it wasn't meant to be as we're not on the same wavelength and they don't understand me. It's in the past and bygones etc. It's not like they're stalking me at least not anymore. Lol if that was them since one moved near me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Occam's razor. That's the simplest answer in Utah so the most likely to be true cuz even the gangs were trying to marry me off, some of them. I think that's a message from up above. If you look you'll see that sort of thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ I've shared a book from Google Play Books The New Jim Crow, Michelle Alexander. #URL# She worked in Northern California to fight racial profiling. Seeing the racism against Mexicans even in Mormonism there I'm thinking i owe her one. Though cops are more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3/ you'll teach them to fish and then some. And honestly we should do the same for poor whites. Why stop at tan skin? And yes mental health treatment is needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ in tough times when married. It's not supposed to be all fun and games. Marriage and relationships are tough yet at any hint of that everyone scatters. It's not like I'm perfect and an expert but I'm a product of my environment, as in the media but I have Mormonism to counter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ Anarchism and Gays | Revolution by the Book #URL# You can't tell me Ben Carson is crazy. Or do you have problems with literacy? I'm not saying they all come out gay. Plenty of celibate people are not gay or rapie. Duh. How about those women or guys that say]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ We have multiple full county jails and prisons too. And warrants out for people and crimes unknown and being investigated etc. And then there's mentally ill. The druggie type mentally ill. I remember one guy would harass me at the bus stop years ago who was crazy. I could]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ and calls himself to the scene whenever they feel offended they're of white territory. They get called in by asshole civilians. And what do the cops know? They're there to save people regardless of color.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Per vaccine mandates... The questionnaires ask if you're allergic to vaccines, eggs, latex etc so it's not like it's a Nazi prison camp. And other vaccines are required unless you think the measles is a good idea or other childhood diseases. Oroville is dumb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those go perfectly well together lol but I'm not joining though the latter one is likely a joke group. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ Watch Geri Halliwell - It's Raining Men on YouTube Music #URL# Now you only hear about the negative about men and it's sad to see our species go downhill because men get our X Chromosomes from the women. We're a product of our mothers and mostly good and it's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch "Mexican teen develops app to help deaf sister" on YouTube
#URL#

This is the real Mexico.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3/ just stop and drop the sword and say I'm doing a cosplay it's not real I'm gonna cooperate. It's that easy but you run and lunge and even just if he ran then that's suspect. Running without a sword is suspect. That thing is still a deadly weapon. You can run someone through]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe it's criminals trying to punish me for not going bad. And for pointing out when they do bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch "Samsung OneUI 4.0 - Everything Explained!" on YouTube
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TikTok Witches Are Hexing the Election This Halloween | WIRED
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tried making excuses for Mormonism but that's not wise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually didn't want to know. I don't like that song.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Safety first. After my past experiences I'm not big on illegals or Latin immigrants. Trust is earned, not demanded. This has been going on since California actually.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch "Samsung S21 Ultra One UI 4.0 - Android 12 Update - Now Available" on YouTube
#URL#

I think I got mine early. It was so early I thought it was just a security update but i thought, damn, that's almost 3 gigabytes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Police NY Gubernatorial Hopeful Has NYPD Security Detail, Lives On Military Base - The Police Tribune
#URL#

So much for trusting the streets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ where they say "Ren said let's start some shit" and i don't remember the rest but it involves knocking the teeth out of people or causing trouble at a mall or something until they're thrown out by security.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL#

That's so nice of him! I've had dreams where i was naked or without shoes. It's probably from reading the Bible as there's a reference to clothing the naked and feeding the poor. I think because of my TBI I feel i can't fend for myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was a short long haired guy with a dog.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ hate Mexicans in particular. I've run into that all my life. And the frustrating thing is that shrinks at McKay Dee, Weber human and Ogden regional adamantly deny there's any racism that happened on my life. That means THEY'RE racist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Obama let Hezbollah’s cocaine empire thrive ‘to save Iran nuclear deal’
#URL#

Newsweek and others say it's so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch "Call of Duty Mobile Frontline MVP" on YouTube
#URL#

I did ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ up. So, these Nazi LGBTQ and Mormons and KKK and polygamists and yeah the system, are rapie and racist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ Watch "An Anti-Homo PSA 1950s era" on YouTube #URL# This stuff actually happened but it's not that all gays are this way. I think social justice warriors are crying foul just cuz they're bitches. Straight people also take advantage of youth, the perverts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ many voices, how can I know better? Yup. I concur.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For a while I was getting hardcopies of the SPLC publication. So how does 3 times a truck with "in Odin we trust" get in front of me for me to see in different parts of ogden? And then the other stuff? And attacks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stanford Prison Experiment | History &amp; Facts | Britannica
#URL#

Maybe this is why people are keyboard warriors online. All the power, no consequences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Saigon to Kabul: Biden?s response to Vietnam echoes in his views of Afghanistan withdrawal - The Washington Post
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohh the actual evil polygamists are LGBTQ that are bad. Promiscuity and gangs and Scrubs and white trash.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ North Ogden, Utah #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ at times that creates procedures that never change. That pride of not showing weakness is the pride of not caring what happens to our families and fellow human beings and future relationships/families. No one sees a Russian or Chinese person and thinks "that's spouse material.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ Ohh I think all sides swear allegiance out of fear like they say oh my God, which isn't something you're supposed to say either. And one of the Mormons that didn't like me playing with a Casio keyboard in Montgomery Ward punched me in the head hard and repeatedly and I was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now i see why people think it's genetic. It probably is honestly. Science says we're genetically predispositioned to act certain ways. Free will isn't 100%.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch "Eritrean &amp; Sudanese refugees speak about Bedouin Rape Camps" on YouTube #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ me. I only think it's unfair how I'm treated. Kinda disappointed people don't wanna be friends/friendly. I like social interaction. I'm starting to figure out people and it's awkward. I'm trying to think more advanced than i used to and I feel lost sometimes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# the dog is Laika and the cat is Shikari. Sometimes the dog shares the bed with the other cat Dido. And Orlando the main coon cat likes the bed to himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ etc in this area. There's Aryans end antifa and not just homies here and there's Kingston clan and yeah polygamists have their own cops, historically, but it's difficult to say. Could go either way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ marching in pride with nambla. When they still sing praises to Harvey Milk and talk about Stonewall like it's not their fault, a lie because they're repeatedly busted for two things, child molestation/association with nambla there and association with the mafia that ran the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mormons can even be considered infiltrators or traitors if they stray too far and start hating. Hate is against church rules and why some try to disguise it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ can text while driving in an emergency by voice? I don't want to be a spot on the road or miss out and then there's wearables. There's articles saying soon they'll know more about your health that way than your doctor and you'll share info from your wearables with them more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch "Let's Go All the Way" on YouTube
#URL#

One of my favorite songs as a teen. This could pass for a modern song. The instruments sound modern still.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indian food is good but spicy. I wanna try it again sometime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The war on drugs is fucked up. I'm watching PBS talk about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3/ years ago, very open to Christianity but history happens. And our supreme court admits to Native Americans they were robbed but does nothing for them still. How are we different? And as a minority I've been a target and others like me but also white people have and I for my]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ here. That's enough for me. Even though Native Americans were "here first" they did immigrate and start hunting innocent animals. Did they eat meat sparingly? No. They're not farmers. They didn't make bread. And they were psycho like the Comanche, well, by today's standards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ Ramirez v. Collier: Does religious liberty apply in the execution chamber? #URL# I don't think he's faking it. Sounds like he's worried about his salvation. He's worried about burning. The system just hates murderers. You know there's murdering Romans etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ They're creeps and they also might try to get me cancelled in one form or another. Or beat up again. No gifted person that has normal psyche does what they do. They're dumb and antisocial. They're abnormal and upset about being outcasts. One seemed homeless maybe. They could]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easy targets? Sex Trafficking in the Prison System – A Contrario ICL
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before your child is injected, watch Dr. Robert Malone’s statement on child COVID vaccinations - Global Covid Summit
#URL#

Is this real?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ There's an innocence, a naivety to people who are homophobic as well. We're not born knowing everything. There's a lot of imperfection in the LGBTQIA community and i think they're equally naive and innocent in that aspect, and both sides deserve their civil rights. It's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ Compared to Ogden and salt lake city that's tiny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3/ similar incidents with frequency. My sibling worked with someone that encountered a nude male with a video camera years back in the lady's room on campus. Dunno why Weber human thinks there's zero dangerous people out there. That's crazy right there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not as bad but seems cuz they both banged little girls that made me and my family a target cuz Winslow said he hunts polygamists and infiltrates them to bring them to justice. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SciTechDaily: Industrial Chemicals – Linked to a Long List of Serious Health Problems – Detected in US Fast Foods
SciTechDaily: Industrial Chemicals – Linked to a Long List of Serious Health Problems – Detected in US Fast Foods.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate migration... People are moving because of weather. And not just illegals as they're termed. People in the USA want to escape heat for example. Or flooding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've donated to all the causes now! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#army #HASHTAG#goals #HASHTAG#s21 #HASHTAG# @ North Ogden, Utah #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ It's pretty mean actually. Abusive even.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ they did this to me, making me chunky and overly medicated and he was relishing in it. And i think of my first experiences in the BBS scene, and it seems there's gangs there too unless they're messing with me these nerds. I keep getting negative comments from Latinos mainly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ Watch "Never Surrender" on YouTube #URL# Rather than approaching life like a fight or struggle, approach it with love because we're social creatures. Fighting drains you. Love invigorates you. It's not taking the easy way out either. Love gives us life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll poke fun at Biden and Trump but I respect them as human beings. I'm not fanatical in hating them. They have quirks or health issues but they have feelings. I wish people realized that because both sides have people like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People tend to pick the lesser of the two evils at worst. Perhaps their perspectives change if even worse than that. They might think "I see what they mean now. They're right."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ Like my cousin took one bite from several pizza slices one after the other in order to get them all for himself, and gangs and others, polygamists and yes, LGBTQ do that cuz who the hell wants spoiled, rotten, diseased milk. In the other animal kingdom, STDs are also a way to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technically, if you're not abiding by LDS loving standards, you're working for the devil so they're not "the other Mormons" but sinners like anyone else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ I don't mean to call them out or shame them but it just sucks being minus some friends even if they're a handful sometimes but the positive emotions were there 99% of the time. I know I've complained about them before and i was just upset and yeah they're a "bad influence" per]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At WinCo and got negative comments from some homies. One was wearing baggy shorts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3/ FBI racial profiling and so on. It's called panic and extreme times require extreme measures. Want someone to blame for government being a pain? Look to the extremists and realize they're why.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ And people getting offended i think God might like beer etc.... Ok so he speaks and texts you as well? Like the Warren Jeff's guy in polygamists gangster rap? Or you think you can decide for God what he's into and then push it on me, like ordering food for a woman without]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ I'm realizing even though they may cause a bit of trouble, in my experience and by statistics, minorities and ethnic people cause much more chaos and damage. I guess I let my curiosity get the best of me and i shouldn't. I think it's maybe just a way to troll someone and]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They might be breaking laws but now i gotta wonder what the entire story is. I'll be honest, the cops can be good but still not do a perfect job because the system is fubar to begin with. Look at our origins. Duh. They didn't allow Latinos, Jews and Blacks and Asians to (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ potentially an Ice Cube, or a Crip or Blood etc if denied the right enforcement and environment. Don't they say there's no such thing as a bad dog, just a bad owner? It's the same with these kids perhaps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch "Michelle Jenneke Women's 100m Hurdles sexy dance Barcelona 2012 complete race" on YouTube
#URL#

Lol i can't help it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something Really Wants our Attention. One Object Released 1,652 Fast Radio Bursts in 47 Days | Universe Today
#URL#

It's hungry aliens lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I couldn't help being curious and him being my friend he showed me. If i became paralyzed I'd be thankful that we least it's in this epoch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ Watch "Elton John - Nikita" on YouTube #URL# Kinda appropriate. We only see boundaries and chess moves not potential relationships and that's the USA too and maybe we're the main problem sometimes. It could be a damned if you do, damned if you don't issue too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ superiority and others backed him up from the group. I'm gonna have to learn to forgive but it takes effort and time. Wells etc weren't kidding but dunno about the BBS types. Maybe. Maybe not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch "Why Latino Dads Don't Say "I Love You" | ON PAPER EP. 1 - mitu" on YouTube
#URL#

Actually very touching]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ se but aren't we supposed to do missionary work among the sinner and not be judgemental and love without condition? I can't say oh I'll only like the righteous. Nope, that's a sin right there. You have to love the sinners equally just like Jesus did and it's why he said he who]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch "Hollywood's greatest betrayal: How sexual predators operate in plain sight" on YouTube
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ mom's tacos and tostada's etc. We get conned into burning bridges for someone's agenda. It's usually contempt for someone that offended them. Other times they want what they have. You know how everyone says Jews love money? Well look at what happened to them. Nazis are nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ of Israel I'm told. They're the ones, the racist Mormons, going against church doctrine. I could drink coffee and repent at church every Sunday and still get into heaven easier i imagine. God is about love not perfection. We get in by his grace and love not because we're that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch "Cosmic Encounters: A Journey into the Fascinating World of Space Exploration | Free Documentary" on YouTube
#URL#

This channel has so many]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Washington Post: Opinion | 3 retired generals: The military must prepare now for a 2024 insurrection
The Washington Post: Opinion | 3 retired generals: The military must prepare now for a 2024 insurrection.
#URL#

Figures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch "NAC--(N-Acetylcysteine) Potent Antioxidant and Anti-Inflammatory" on YouTube
#URL#

Good info]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm getting spammed by escort services in Google chat even for the wrong sex. Lol I got signed up by an asshole when I turned him in for fraud when he tried to rip me off in a work from home scam. Well, I'm assuming it's a guy that was scamming me. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ogden city officials hiking their pay? Well I realized I got a cost of living increase from social security. Maybe it's just cost of living.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN: Avlon: Trump really doesn't want you to see these documents
CNN: Avlon: Trump really doesn't want you to see these documents.
#URL#

Doesn't bad news wire us to divide and fight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People most have ate pot brownies in Oroville because people would use our utility room bathroom and the shit smelled like it. I dunno if it's bikers or who but they've knocked on my door as a child before wanting to use the bathroom and came into my room. Those guys are evil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ profession or models. That's how you know Hollywood is fake and meant to milk you for your money. They also marry their own. We're not good enough or outside their agenda, a third wheel. It's ok but be honest..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ best. All people on the street really and not just the system in figuring out how to help them. They need help not punishment. They were born into a punishing environment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Metaverse Hype Is Like Communist Propaganda: Soviet-Born Tech Founder
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on one lol Friday jerks have me in a bad mood. I'd rather be indoors and away from public spaces on Fridays. Saturday isn't great either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3/ with fear of how communism spread in Latin America. And the CIA dealt drugs in Latin America and might be behind cartels according to some. Yeah they have to improvise. That's according to Al Jazeera and other journalists and some "whistleblowers" on YouTube but who knows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slate: Border Agent Who Posted Doctored AOC Sex Photo Got Away With It
Slate: Border Agent Who Posted Doctored AOC Sex Photo Got Away With It.
#URL#

They sound like assholes to me, these border agents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fundraiser by Sarah Hoyt : Help with moving for my health.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The old guard of Mormons, a couple at Smith's, just admitted they plotted against younger people like me to keep me from getting their daughters to sin. That's code for not marrying a Mexican in my experience. I'm not out seducing and never intended to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5/ hospital. They don't tell me to shut up. Looking back they probably really have a story to tell about the crazy conversation I had with them but still, they had patience and compassion. I dunno why I'm having dreams with doubts that would turn most bitter. I think it's because]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ These people tend to be a spiritual threat as well. All good things come from God and all bad from the devil. Hey..... That YouTube video about satanism in/from Mexicans. That might be it. Might be similar in the Taliban unless they're genetically daft. How can they think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I only stand a chance of being a photographer. I can't be a scientist with this much brain damage. Science does some good even though it's not perfect per se, it's perfect enough it seems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And no one warned me to watch out for hate crimes in Utah. I thought it's full of Mormons so it's safe. And i didn't think it would be full of gangs either. This place is dangerous. And it's full of hackers and not just the good ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mother joined Nazi polygamists or the south american Nazi pedo cult has fans here or they networked into Utah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple’s Huge iPhone Mistake—Bad News For 1 Billion Users
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planet 9 may be closer and easier to find than thought—if it exists
#URL#
via Natgeo App
#URL#

Way cool]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>