<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Go to Dubai on holiday and see what an X will get you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No wonder that you would avoid a battle of wits when you are so obviously unarmed .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# These "cis women" sound absolutely terrifying. No one would be safe sharing spaces with them. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# What you think doesn't matter. Sex is male and female.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That whole thread is full of horrible terms for people who merely have a different opinion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Only trans people are real people. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They night not all be fascists. Some might be there for the ambience. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Waiting to pull out onto the dual carriageway today, a passing car hit a pool of water from a burst water main and a tsunami came through the open window of my car. For water that had been standing on a hot road, it was surprisingly cold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Were there a lot of married gay couples holidaying there? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There's also the Dolly Parton Moderna.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That would be a good one too. So many suitable choices for proper statues of women.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You have obviously never seen Thomas and the Magic Railroad, making Pokémon the Movie seem like Citizen Kane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The sports class for their sex.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's only from the perspective of a non Jewish Australian woman can you get the full understanding of the complexities of the Middle East. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not as good as the original "nutcracker" chopper bike.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I didn't know that either. It is the most fragile form, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "wanting intimacy with women more than intimacy with men."

So that includes men and all men and women who are sometimes intimate with men. Basically everyone except gay men. 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm on a rather different scale with my smaller deliveries sometimes getting as exciting as going into Essex.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If I were in the market for a sensible new electric car, the MG5 would be top of the list.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Or possibly support to allow India to increase their own production.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A thought just struck me. When we do the first manned trip to Mars, and it will be a couple of years round trip, will they take a dentist with them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, why can't #USER# be more respectful and sympathetic to women. Like #USER# is. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Well done. That's putting those uppity women in their place. #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Little do you know your debt to Les Dawson and Roy Barraclough in the 1970s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The 2010 Equality Act allows for sex based protections to remain. Even then, reality is that a woman is an adult human female.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The previous poster, who has me blocked is an idiot (in no small part the reason for the block). No one can change sex, although the TRAs flip to and fro claiming that they can or cannot as suits them at the time. This is because these fools have no understanding of what sex is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The vinegar was merely a ploy to put them under the control of Isaac Newton's calculus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# On a lot of topics it is very hard to tell which is parody and which is not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Humane might be housing transgender identifying males in their own prison unit that is not in the female estate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He's not making an effort with his hair, is he? Like a misogynistic boiled egg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Their act was heavily based upon Norman Evans, who starting doing such characters in the 1930s. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Us poor chaps. Matching socks and women think we are asking for it. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You demonstrate a total ignorance of what "intersex" actually means in a way that is offensive to people with differences in sexual development.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AliExpress are at it again. A search for RC plane reveals... In true Sesame Street fashion, one of these things is not like the other. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He was a hero before that. His tank and others were key to the storming of a Pacific island during the war.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is it an immensely heavy book on the very edge of the top shelf?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've never liked phone calls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Have you not seen Comerford's take on things today? I will at some point get bored with mocking his outrageous statement, but not yet. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh it's the Jews again. It's always the Jews. Even when it looks like it couldn't possibly be them, it is. #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's pure transphobia, pointing out cis privilege. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's uncommon for rats to join a sinking ship like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In the past, we have found putting seed trays on the draining board when the dishwasher is running brought on seeds quite well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Very true. Reinforced by repeating in every episode, of course]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They will have to give students warning of some actual educational content.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Shortage of sperm donors. "There's a lack of men coming forwards"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I hadn't thought of that and both myself and Child 4 have the number of the beast in our mobile numbers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Their son, the photo journalist, which meant he traveled around finding vital new French vocab for us like windmills.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Medical condition that affect men and women. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The tubby cycling cheat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wasn't even a fence sitter. It was a world that I wasn't aware of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Does WEP stand for Worship Every Penis?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was it... the Jews? #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Morris Marinas all had new sills within a few years. I bought one at 17 years old on the original sills. The first owner had sprayed with Waxoyl when he first got it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When I did the car boot sales a few years ago, I went to Denham which is basically West London's car boot sale. Some guys had bought some old sewing machines at auction and within minutes had sold them all to African buyers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Surely to properly honour what he stands for, we should all go out and catch the clap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You know how it is, one she regards as a dangerous extremist group that no one should have any dealings with and the other is the Taliban. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# On a par with Mussolini making the trains run on time.

Spoiler: He didn't. The punishments for late trains was so harsh that timetables allowed for huge time allowances.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You've probably snapped your cock off by now over this. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# With Stonewall running all those courses for the police? I don't think so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But transwomen have women in the  name and clownfish and intersex and stuff. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# JKR needs to announce that men shouldn't slam car doors onto their cocks and we would see who is willing to "put her in her place" over it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That assumes that the speed of light is a surmountable restriction. It may well be not and so the distances involved make the whole enterprise irrelevant. If so then all spaceships, new or old will be travelling at roughly the same velocity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Will he want access to female only safe spaces?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There's a garden centre in our town, run mostly by volunteers, that takes dying supermarket plants, gets them to recover and sells them on.  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I assume that you got the call as Joe's carer. Has he had his yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If immigrants aren't willing to join in with this, how can they expect to be welcomed here? #HASHTAG# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She's been dead 53 years. I'm not sure how holding to account works here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Turn left onto Poles Lane"

I'd rather not. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The Jews made him do it. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How could mere women understand biology more than an actual doctor (of American studies)? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've been delivering to a family of sculptors. They live really out in the back of beyond in Hertfordshire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We have had our $28 million worth of penis jokes out of Bezos and his adventure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The special unit that turned Boyle around seemed to be one that targeted those who the mainstream system could not reach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I've discovered. He's ex army.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Again you are wrong. Most children desist and therapy rather than medical treatment provides better outcomes that medicalisation for those that do not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's the people who won't be vaccinated but will still demand access to places where you should be vaccinated. If the condition for going down the pub is vaccination then you won't be going down the pub.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Polish eat carp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "And so brothers, it is written by the great Magdalen that men cannot be lesbians" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The fact that we are made up of atoms formed inside a long dead star.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Surely you mean the recently closed Museum of women's History? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The easy answer to that is that the risk to women from males is the same whether they are transgender or they are not. Where one ought not to be the so ought not the other .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That's not even algae doing that. It's actually an effect of dolphin urine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Most likely one police officer far more than the others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She could just give a couple of million to her lawyers and just tell them to go hunting with it. So many woke blokes think that they are untouchable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And another one with a block on me. I seem to have become King Feminist. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It was of course the Jewish Zionist lobby that made Jared O'Mara a complete arse. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# He also admitted that he missed the start of the Stonewall riot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# All those spiders packed together. Soon they will get hungry and there will be fewer and fewer spiders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Just not you women. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# When the judge comes in and someone says "All rise, the court is now in session".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's the thing. What she wrote in the books isn't even remotely antisemitic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Was it Lehrer that said that Von Braun was a man willing to count from ten to one in any language?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Lesbians at a gay pride event. How awful. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not so sure about the part where someone called Samuel gets horribly murdered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So it's September and I appeared to be suffering from hay fever. From what? Child 3 (that one) has come down with a stinking cold after her unmasked music festival. Thanks for that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Everyone is either male or female.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You have selectively singled out a very few people who agree with JKR. The reality is that the beliefs and dogma of your cult hold little sway in the real world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# To be fair, my Xiaomi phone uses one of those symbols when charging. Rather more concerning is that it puts another one next to the first when fast charging.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Meaning is a bigoted cis sexist concept. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# From a whole album that is quite good, available via YouTube.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The football statistic I know for Scotland is that the suicide rate drops whilst Scotland are still in a competition. I think that even when knocked out, there is  not a peak just a return to average levels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Trump set a date for the end of US involvement. Once the Taliban had that, all they needed to do was sit it out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Far, a long long way for him to reach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Even then, that's only two of your five a day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the Jews control chocolate. With that they control the world. #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why don't they fund DV shelters for transgender people if they are so flush with cash?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Who knew that so many women would be rapists? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I didn't say that it was theft. Appropriation, certainly. Don't forget that following their Kiwi Farms thread, it is well known just what sort of person we are dealing with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There's a guy on our allotment who has the worst bindweed imaginable. At last he has gone after it. All his beds and paths disassembled plus he has lifted all his raspberry canes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The are ones reading your tweets thinking "Are there people out here...washing...bed sheets?! "]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The next step is to book a track day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A man goes to the doctor's because he is embarrassed that he has three testicles. The doctor tells him that rather than being embarrassed, he should be proud. 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Those "cis women" sound absolutely awful. I wouldn't want to share a space with them #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Straight bananas and Polish Muslims coming over here, taking our jobs and not doing any work. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Very poor male athletes will lose to women athletes. That is no surprise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the Jews. I knew it was, even when it was the Blairites, I knew it was the Jews. #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jewish money financing a campaign that gets every fascist out from under their rock. Obvious, really. #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I have delivered to an elderly lady who was bedridden. I had the number for her key thing on the wall to let me in, then frozen to the freezer, chilled to the fridge and the rest to the worktop. I don't do that many of those but I do some.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lenses, notably older ones, add a characteristic tint. Modern sensors and electronics add their own character (Canon gives "cool" images, slightly bluer). What you can do is use pure white in the shot and colour balance from that or take a shot at that location of a colour card.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's true. Thick bastards don't have a vaccination card.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# His tweet was got out past the nurses by a visitor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's not gay people again, is it? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A man arrives before St Peter at the Pearly Gates.
"I'm sorry but I can't let you in as you have done nothing of note in your life"
"But I have walked into the Kremlin and denounced Stalin to his face'
"I have no record of that. When did you do it?"
"About five minutes ago"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The worst from the vaccine is still better than the best from the virus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You want to put men in with women in rape refuges and have them run by men. You are in no position to take any sort of moral high ground.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Double Bassoon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And how do YOU, Mr Baddiel, intend to solve all the problems of the Middle East?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The "Looking Up An Old Friend"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Actually, the Lee Hurst jokes here on Twitter are pretty funny. Which is more than can be said for Lee Hurst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Poor George couldn't. His strings were pre tuned in advance and all he had to do was strum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This tweet hasn't aged well. The guy is a convicted sex offender.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "and while I'm here buying cosmetics in the hardware store, I'll have that concealer too" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'll tell you what, it is absolutely definitely not secret Jewish lobby money this time. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Only a man can truly understand what it is to be a feminist. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think that I can cancel the ambulance to hospital because of my ribs broken due to laughter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They are getting confused with a Bridget Bardough, whoever she might be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No.
I've put slug pellets around my slug traps to multiply the deadly effect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 1990s? That's almost like being at Stonewall.

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Of what? That a female motorist is more at risk than a male if she breaks down?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As an unpaid carer, I could bump myself near the top of the list but I don't think that I will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's going to be a fraught day getting it all done. Some TRVs need replacing (all of them really) but that will have to wait. Hive thermostat arriving too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think that Paul Hogan has dated. Of his time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Or "the scrum" as she imagines it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# In fairness, I have been on. I needed a suggestion as to how to get a sock out that is stuck in a vacuum cleaner pipe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I guess that it's him as Pickles the evil cat isn't a celebrity outside of our cul de sac. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What you must always bear in mind is that the story of a secret agent imprisoned and interrogated on an island is not the story of a secret agent imprisoned and interrogated on an island.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# There appears to be a Judge Knott in the USA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Women are no longer women. They are cis women. Only transwomen are proper women because they have to work harder at it. Cis women are icky and probably have cooties. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Variant D+, flu, norovirus. It would be madness not to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Someone in this thread has already mentioned #USER# . Using cardboard to suppress weeds without doing any digging can be very effective.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The cat is probably dreaming of playing rugby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny how Jewish people can be about Fascism, isn't it? #HASHTAG#  #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Those phones calls were merely transactivists trying to persuade her that they were indeed women just like her and that they should be welcomed into women's safe spaces. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Outside of textbooks, probably the most expensive book that I ever bought was the  Codex Wallenstein but even then I got a good price on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Threatening you? You are the one that seems very keen to suppress wrongthink.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Isn't that a one man band?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have seen the technique used as a combined hugelkultur raised bed hybrid. The bottom layer is basically fly tipping. There seems to be no other sensible way to compost logs and rotten scaffold boards or even sweetcorn stalks in the next layer above.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Intersex conditions (differences in sexual development) are a group of sex specific medical conditions that affect men or women. Their diagnosis is dependent upon the sex binary. How is that related to anything transgender?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My late father was a civil engineering student in the 1950s. Whatever one did with a slide rule, he knew how to do it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fascists lying? They'll ruin their reputation. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Will that be the 5 minute argument or the full half hour?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh so guilt trip me about wanting a tank, won't you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You have been given the facts. Ministry of Justice figures. As to yourself, you are running on empty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You must not call her crazy because you will confuse the very small number of people indeed who are even more crazy than she is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Tom was at the Battle of Ramree Island in a tank. That was also quite something. A battle notable for the crocodiles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I doubt very much that the attackers were part of any gender critical group.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's someone who appears to be in danger of becoming their own grandmother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# David Mitchell wanker, I believe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Whilst the scientific research is important, you just need to use your eyes. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That was a very wicked thing to say and obviously I wasn't thinking the exact same thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She also said that an Apple employee told her that vaccines can allow you to time travel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Who had the first penis? How much of a shock was it to his wife?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In my defence, I have never been tempted to purchase such an item.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Her songs have bisexual overtones but Joe Strummer sang "My father was a bank robber". In actuality he worked for the Foreign Office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# They understand that these transgender people are males not females and are biologically boys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Transactivism inflates the statistics to further the cause. It's hard to claim to be the most oppressed minority when you are one of the safest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I qualified by virtue of being a carer to someone vulnerable and I got a letter  I went down to the surgery and queried the fact that my son had nothing. They phoned back later that day with an appointment. If you genuinely think you might be missed, you need to ask.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I have some pictures taken whilst out delivering in the van. Up to Nasty. The thing about Nasty people is that for the most part, they are not. I also had to use a river ford then later a flooded road that was deeper than the ford. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Does this work for Gentlemen's sausages too? In that case The Very Important Person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My choice of electric three wheeler car is not the Aptera but the Sondors. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The legal advice to Stonewall Diversity Champions from Stonewall has been lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When it's something that it is obvious that Israel has done it, it is the fault of the Jews.nWhen it doesn't seem that Israel did it, it is the Jews being sneaky.n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There's a photo of a man with it and a Palestinian flag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Why should women have anything of their own at all? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We pay politicians, civil servants and assorted boffins a lot of money to come up with a clever idea, but all we seem to get is Baldrick's cunning plan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I did some proper swimming. I even swam underwater but then realised that I had swum out of my depth and decided that it was best to err on caution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# She paid black men to work for her. How awful that they should make money. Employing black people must be the worst form of racism that there is. #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# They are very similar to the Cybermen but my thoughts on the matter was that the Daleks were organisms controlling machines and the Cybermen were machines controlling organisms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When the reality is the this most oppressed of all minorities ever have some serious US based money backing them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Noticed on Twitter yesterday that Hyundai have given the Chelsea Women's team brand new electric cars each.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They have found a dozen or so gaffes in thousands of interactions with the public. That's a pretty good ratio beating Johnson, Corbyn, Trump and a great many others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Very good choice. Also WC Field's "Never Give A Sucker An Even Break" (1941) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It seems the opposite of school PE where if you forgot your shorts, you had to play in your pants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So it's quite a cultural phenomenon. That's interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The mother comes in and asks how much. The barber points to the price list. Indignantly she says, "But I had done half of the job for you already". 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If you believe that males can be lesbians and think that anyone who refuses to accept this abomination is a "monster" then you are a homophobe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Women and Spitfires and top of the list is Beatrice "Tilly" Shilling, inventor of "Miss Shilling's orifice" that remedied a problem with the early Spitfire engines. Keen motorcycle racer. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# In the US, mastectomies. 12 years+. If you want to include puberty blockers then pre puberty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well of course you can't tell if there's a cock in the way obscuring the bones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pah! These Jewish people who think they know about anti-Semitism. #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>