<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do to Central or Mongkok on the weekends and you will see the same problems. Only way to stop this is for employers to tell helpers the consequence if they bring the virus home: instant termination of service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am not surprised. The reason is that the variant has a longer incubation time and detection may occur more than 14 days after. Retesting appears to be the only way to detect community spread amongst the helpers. That said, anyone who appears at risk should be tested as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But they have the freedom to vote. And breathe free air.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Think you got the wrong person. #USER# has always been a Sinophobic ass. You are thinking about #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Except US can't defaul on UST anymore (ending Brettons Woods is a default). So default on the USD (debasement) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't really care what these Sinophobic countries think. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# As I aaid, you do not get antibody response to other strands of protein from the virus. That is basic science. And having antibody response to a protein that has changed doesn't work at all. Again basic science. You want to deny science that is up to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Agreed. And the science has already proven it to be dangerous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scoop? The "princeling" divested before his father became the finance tsar. He in no longer related the firm. And this is done in accordance with regulations and laws. So what is the point of this article? That the powerful in China has to toe the line? Or that anti-corruption #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Let them test China then....1.4b people will fuck them over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cross the red line and see what China will do. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Their interests? So are they saying Taiwan is their vassal? Guess they want to have a smaller Navy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# How about a degree in gender studies so you can decide how many genders you want between male and female? Or German Polka history? Looks like you have a horse's ass for brains.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Noah Smith is obviously a liar. Anyone who can read Chinese can go on Weibo to see how "restrictive" things are in #HASHTAG#. Oh we also have a famous trans-sexual as a tv presenter and now Dior representative in China.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US guys seem to think inflation doesn't matter. Or will not be sustained. Honestly, its like they do not know inflation is a monetary phenomenon. $1.4trn printed a year. It has to go somewhere. Velocity for goods and services has plummeted since QE started in 2009]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nope. EU was the party pushing for the CAI. They had a leg into China ahead of America, and America forced them to pull it back out. EU is a waste of time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to make a prediction. #HASHTAG# vaccines will protect China against Covid variants by limiting deaths and hospitalisations, while #HASHTAG# dependent countries will find renewed and more virulent outbreaks in the near future that will incapacitate their medical systems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You can't read Chinese right? Otherwise you would be eating those words. Fucking brainless moron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What exactly was the context? Was the comment meant to be sarcasm?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. This person is blind and deaf amd she can tweet! Impressive #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Actually those formerly infected are better protected against the virus than those vaccinated. Plenty of science out there proving this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You just exposed your moronic brain. Efficacy against what? Infection or death? What is the use of a vaccine that works against infection against an original strain of a virus but doesn't protect against death vs a mutation? The data speaks for itself. So fuck off moron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But how are you going to inflate your debt away? #HASHTAG# should really stop lying. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Errre China is dumping the USD as fast as they can ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No no. That is not inflation. The stuff is noe hedonically better. Organic eggs and milk are better. Diapers hold more pee. Detergent works on bigger load! You actually have deflation!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# discussions on China-US relationship and what Asia can do wrt to talking to America. #URL# While what he says makes sense, he doesn't realise that American political climate doesn't allow it to listen to Asia, or any other outside party for that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wut? But yes some people can't read. Otherwise their minds would explode. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well they are shooting themselves. South Korea will see themselves cut out of China markets. Which is fine by me. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why don't you read what #HASHTAG# looks like in every thread on Chinese aid to the country. That is all I have to say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tested. In other words, no one has any idea of the consequences on the human immunity system from this new genetic approach. If you want to be a guinea pig, go ahead. I'll rather stick with a vaccine methodology that has been tried and tested for decades.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Regurgitating coldwar debunked propaganda lies juat shows how brainwaahed you are. Even declassified US embassy cables said there was no massacre in Tiananmen. This just proves you are a sinophobic troll. Fuck off and good bye asshole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin will fuck Biden over US human rights record #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh look! The rat is complaining about Nigeria but doesn't complain when India does it (literally closed down internet in Kashmir) or when US blocked Tiktok. Go back to the sewer assholr #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What teen? He announced he was the police. And the lawyer STILL attacked him. Did you even watch the video?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Apologies.! Every sarcastic tweet should always be followed by .. sarcasm really doesn't translate well into text]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Which antibodies? People do not seem to understand how inactivated virus vaccines work. If you are testing for the antigen against the S protein, you will probably be right. But if you are testing for ALL antibodies created (ie to fight against symptoms) then you will wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I am not spreading anything. If you actually read what I wrote. I am pointing out the science. You can choose to pick what you want. I am supporting viral vector vaccines as well. Just not mRNA. Because of the SCIENCE. You can choose to believe what you want. Its up to you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What? Where is the oppression?! Where is the lack of freedom! Chinese people are brainwashed right?! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran already received China vaccines. ðŸ™„ðŸ™„ðŸ™„ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this is how you treat your best friend...... Germany should say goodbye to you. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The net has too many holes. The #HASHTAG# is going every where]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And do what? As long as US has vetp power, and Israel owns US Govt, what can UNSC do? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The West ia doing the opposite. They need to keep inflation high to reduce the debt they have built up over the last 50yrs from living beyond their means. So don't ahow off your ignorance moron.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No one said developed. Mote like willing to spend on science. What is #HASHTAG# looking at recemtly? 
#HASHTAG#Moron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fuck-up. There will be a new variant coming out soon. The #HASHTAG# variant. Which greek alphabet should we use? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh. #USER# has been supressing voices like mine for ages. And others as well. That is what you call "freedom of speech" American style. Guess it is your kind of "freedom"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not yet. As I said, it really depends on how the rest of the countries control the pandemic. As long as countries like India, Brazil exists more mutations will come. I am sure I will not be able to go north without quarantine for a while #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah #HASHTAG# just appeared. They don't appear often in my timeline. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Looks like brake failure to me actually.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Of course a brainwashed moron would believe the government data on inflation, and not the reality reflected by the social breakdown of Western society. But keep living in delusion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually agree with the testing. But it should be for everyone. Why? Because based on anecdotal evidence, the variant has a longer incubation and detection may only occur after 21 days. That is a scary prospect. I will be getting my family and helpers tested. Together. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. Frog in a well. Ever read about China? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one appears to be eating the crap that Western media is putting out about the China lab leak theory, as there is more evidence out there that #HASHTAG# has been in the West way before Wuhan. Other than morons of course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think the question is what antibodies are they measuring. And whether these antibodies actually work against mutations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. And you can believe that China will start clamping down on them. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This fucking journalist thinks running a vehicle into people is not terrorism. 
#URL#

#URL#

#URL#
So this is what #USER# #USER# journalist thinks? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sigh. I did look at the data. I downloaded the data. Watch the data a little longer. Because Delta just started spiking. But what the data show is scary. Why? For &gt; 50yrs old,46pct of dead are of fully vaccinated (2 doses). Over 65% have at least one dose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fyi, medical personnel vaxxed by Sinovac in Indonesia had zero serious symptoms. These are the people exposed to Covid day in day out. In Thailand, over 660k medical personnel were vaccinated. 0.1% were infected. Only 1 died. These are real stats. Now you can seriously f-off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# A Uyghur, Arken Imirbaki, is a vice chaiman of China's National People's Congress. That is so racist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the.... Don't let these people come to HK. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh look! Another fucking #HASHTAG# in my timeline. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No. Vassal state implies former independence. Australia is dog state of America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really? That you have misgivings about #HASHTAG# and #HASHTAG# vaccines show that how little you know? Did you know you can't sue these firms if the vaccines fuck you up? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This bitch is still spreading lies on #USER#. Is anyone surprised? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually you are buying your lunch from China. Economically. Because you decided you do not want to cook lunch anymore #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Higher GDP per capita. Less aged to support. Human deaths are irrelevant. The numbers will improve a few hundred thousand dead irrelevant when GBP rises vs EUR. ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# tacitly admitted this a couple of days back when they said a regular "booster" is needed. Whu? Because they need to "update" the spike protein immunity due to the mutations. The problem is that it will always be a game of catch-up because the virus is mutating fast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And now Pfizer is saying people need more shots on regular basis (6mth or a year) implying that the mRNA vaccine has failed against the new strains.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And 85pct of &gt; 50yrs old in UK are vaccinated. What does that tell you about the efficacy of vaccinations? Now look at hospitalisations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Australia is not worth a bomb. Strength can be demonstrated in different ways. China's way is not the Western way. It is much better. Let them crash themselves against the mountain that is China. Unless Australia is stupid enough to fire the first shot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# themselves unprotected without more and more doses, each of which will create even more unintended consequences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# still doesn't get it. Infrastructure and logistics key to tech manufacturing, and a whole supply chain. The #HASHTAG# on this thread do not realise this. Why every tech company will continue to flock to China. And being the biggest market for tech also helps #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US will see one of their ships destroyed if they continue this reckless path. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So if you cannot fucking understand the science behind the vaccines I seriously suggest you do not allow your stupidity be exposed like this. But what else can you expect from an #HASHTAG# like you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well your phone is made in China. You should not trust it. Throw it away.
#HASHTAG# truly have no brains. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fed has chosen: inflation is not their concern. Or rather high inflation is what they want, to inflate US debt away. #HASHTAG#? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice pics but too many #HASHTAG# in the thread. Looks like #HASHTAG# renewed the funding of these morons. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Of course not! But it takes me only 25min by West rail to Central. Its faster than me driving. And cost of living is lower. And I have room to order meats wholesale. ðŸ˜ I have a freezer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really? How many #HASHTAG# voices from #HASHTAG# have you suspended? How many Chinese people's accounts have you cancelled? You are a bit of a hypocrite aren't you? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really. No one. Go read the evidence moron. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dollar is onLy "king" to fools like yoi. Global reserve holders have stopped buying the dollars dumped on the world since 2014. But hey, keep believing the dream right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Inflation. They can't increase rates. They can only print]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You fled for freedom? How were you "free" to flee? Stay in New Zealand. We Chinese in China are happy with what we have. You don't speak for us. You speak for yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Unfortunate brainwashed people will search this out. Just got into a fight with someone close. Basically telling me Guangzhou outbreak bad and people under quarantine have no food for 2 days. And China is evil. Guess who published that? #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And collapsing USD not unlike Weimar. China and Russia both have made the decision to move away from the USD based system and this is unacceptable to US but America cannot win a war against nuclear powers. This shift has accelerated due to the pandemic. We are approaching]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not too sure about that. Lwill never know I guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like the Delta variant has spread or we have a new greek letter coming. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# HK people have been brainwashed for many years. To undo the damage will take many years. People in SG are also "me first". Their social conscience is sometimes worst that HKers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They will not open. And they are right. Because this is just the beginning of the pandemic driven collapse in the West. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Interesting move but priced in. Near term default risk low though. They can still sell assets. Won't want to be equity holder though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrong photo and apparently #USER# doesn't realise Dong JingWei gave a speech in BeiJing last week. #HASHTAG# evwrywhere #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is sarcasm. But doesn't translate well on Twitter. Always remember to put]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Jealous? Hardly. I have been to the West. Never want to go back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# He was not imprisoned. He was fined (rightly so) for spreading wrong info and went straight back to work. That is suppression?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah #HASHTAG# never fail to show how moronic they are #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hmmmmm not really. Covid19 traces was found a lot earlier in some places like Spain, Brazil.. etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeap. Best time to buy dollars! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Again, I am asking you if you support those who set fire to shops and train stations, vandalised the Legco, killed a cleaner and light up another? Do you support those who destroy train tracks and traffic lights in front of school children? Well? Want to be in my face right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ah sunday numbers are always lower.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese people woke up. Why? china dropped the Great Chinese Firewall so the people can see what Western journalists write about China #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Tested first. But don't trust RTHK on vaccination. Sorry but that network has been caught lying too many times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[with a ineffectual mRNA vaccine and gets infected with a variant, they are as good as being UNPROTECTED. Inactivated virus vaccines are created using the WHOLE virus. It forces the body to create antibodies for every part of the virus, including those that are related to symptoms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna keep repeating this: #HASHTAG# is the happiest nation in the world. Human rights suppression and genocide makes people happy! If you still think Chinese people are suffering under a dictatorship, I suggest you check yourself into a psyche ward. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Former French colony with one of the highest poverty levels. Hmmm and now developing because of...China. you have to wonder what the French did to the country. And using devt trap? That has been debunked over and over again. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They migrated to #HASHTAG# because firms were hiring mainlanders. Why? Because #ä¹ååŽ were a bunch of entitled nacissistic moronic generation of useless roaches. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh look! Another moron just appeared in my timeline. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really? So as facts emerge, statements can't change? Really? How stupid are you? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it "thousands"in Brazil but "millions" in Hong Kong. The crowd looks the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only a fucking #HASHTAG# would think space exploration is space domination. These morons love eating sour grapes. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why sell to India? They want a war right? Cut off their pharma raw materials. #HASHTAG# think they can push #HASHTAG#'s buttons without consequence. Lets given them some consequence #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It has been a very bad week on #HASHTAG# for me: #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# 
Hard to work when the overriding risk to any analysis is the pandemic and war.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# China gets 500b dollars a year. They don't want it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China minorities cheering genocide! . #HASHTAG# cannot be hidden forever. All citizens of China support China. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# From the thread it is clear you are recycling cold war propaganda that has been debunked, antiChina images, and well, all the BS Sinophobes have been putting out to suppress China's development. As I said, sound like a moron and you will get mobbed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, half of the world's mobiles will be on harmony OS. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China will warn US warships next time. Aim all their missiles them, and let them know that they are all aimed at them. Fire one over their heads and tell them the next one goes right at the bridge. Fuck the American navy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tea pots. ðŸ˜. Drink some tea. Might improve your sanity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# And THAT is BS. But hey what do you expect from Western publications?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# should shut up about fake #HASHTAG#, and look and explain their own genocidal behaviour #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If they publiah the data. The UK has and it doesn't look good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# rocket falls into ocean killing some #HASHTAG# fish. It is a crime against humanity! CCP is evil! Attack China! Democracy!! 
- what #HASHTAG#Morons and #HASHTAG# would say]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# would disrespect Grandpa Yuan. For that alone, let them die. Fuck them. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That is hilarious! The FX is from China's current account surplus. It is hiddel FX reserves. But #USER# will never admit that. Why he has been wrong for so long.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your lies have already been debunked. Why don't you try something else. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rinsr and repeat for tomorrow. Any idea on positivity rate? #HASHTAG# doesn't dare announce #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just stop supplying to Apple. And stop buying Apple stuff. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And pray tell, when was that? I have been to China for the last 16yrs (different parts) and never have I ever been threatened or assaulted even when I am out on the streets late at night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An #HASHTAG# thinks he can teach me. They really don't know the limits of their stupidity do they? #HASHTAG# 
No time to waste on fools #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When #HASHTAG# pushes #HASHTAG# policies as his own, he is basically concurring with Trump. Why Trump support is high #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You assume his brain will still be there in the 4th year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# antibodies to fight the disease when a person is infected. A big population with people vaccinated by mRNA, which allows a mutated virus to infect speeds up the mutation rate imho. I may be wrong on this but only data would prove how this develops. At the same time, in EM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait for libs and Western #HASHTAG# to call this "racist" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish all those roaches in Hong Kong will join their brethren in the #HASHTAG#. Then Hong Kong will have peace. Instead we have to exterminate them here #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch this in its entirety! #USER# #USER# what are you going to do about this crime against humanity!?
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But it isn't real. Why? Well hundreds of ISLAMIC diplomats and scholars have been to Xinjiang. You would believe a Nazi anti-Semitic German paid propagandist who have not been to Xinjiang and terrorists over these representatives of nations? #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Errr not really. mRNA vaccines tell your body to manufacture the S-protein to elicit an antibody response. The initial thought was that the spike protein was only used for infection. Now they have found out it directly impacts the cardio vascular system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chocolate is more important than slavery. Fuck America #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Why should they? They are making sure no one, including the regional nations, can create instability in the region. They are basically the elephant in the room that keeps the wolves at bay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# China has pretty much eliminated the spread of the virus domestically. Thru sacrifice and perseverance. And the borders are tighter than a vacuum seal. They can reap the rewards for their hard work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# apparently doesn't do virus math. Sinovac and Sinopharm are almost 100pct efficacious against severe symptoms and deaths. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese people must be masochists. They love their dictatoship so much! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It is a function of debt. First time they had a debt problem, US defaulted by removing convertibility to gols (under Bretton Woods). The dollar collapsed and inflation shot up. Then Volcker put the house in order while sucking up global savings to fund US deficits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great. LEAVE! If they think foreign education is so great. Of course, they are completely blind to the morons the Western syst has churned out. Actually better for these morons to leave. They won't be happy in HK. Just don't ever come back #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Do you actually understand how thr human body creates antibodies? Can the immune system create defence against something they have not been exposed to? mRNA vaccines target the S-protein to to create immunity via T-cell and antibody creation. And ONLY to that protein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well I am a Chinese citizen. Don't really care what you think to be honest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember that mRNA vaccines tells your body to create S-proteins which are responsible for cardiovascular effects, like heart inflammation. Likely? No. Definite! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When people ask why Chinese people support the CPC, this is why. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for #HASHTAG# to say this is a violation of human rights! Teachers from West can teach what they want in China! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be made on China, is that they did not take a firmer stance earlier. But I understand to some extent why. Unlike you, I have no delusions. It doesn't matter who is in the WH. The outcome of today's Thucydides Trap is already happening. You will soon dicover what that meansf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Actually death rate for vaccinated is near zero, like severe symptoms. You think the vaccines stop infections? No. They prevent death. But what would an #HASHTAG# like you know?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yah. I now know why China chose the inactivated virus vaccine route. They saw the speed of Covid mutation and how the rest of the world is ignoring their findings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't read Chinese? Too hard for your brain? Chinese is the most economic language I know. Conveys layers of meaning in 4 words, that will take a paragraph in English to explain. Don't blame the language for your own ineptitude. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So far, predictions have been fairly accurate. I hope it doesn't persist. I do not want to be right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# today. You sure you want to be like the US? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The primary strat gy of mRNA vaccines is to PREVENT infections and symptoms related to the spike protein. Think of it as a gate that blocks a virus with a certain look. When that virus changes its look enough, the door will open. Other vaccines may have a weaker door,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Really? So explain how has China bullied, oppressed and subjugated?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Peaceful!? Have you seen the violence conducted by these protestors?! I have seen them. In front of me. And people running in fear from them!? Peaceful!? FUCK OFF!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Given that you tweet under the Chinese Ambassador's comments, like the rest of "grateful" responses, you seem to be inferring China is to blame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Think you need to reinstall the whole OS. Wait for them. I am checking to see mate30pro is in the list. If it isn't i am getting a new one. Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# US politics and #HASHTAG#. Even the sane have to follow the narrative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Really? Its cheaper here in HK. I have a grill in my garden and I buy my meats wholesale. ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No. No one died because unlike you morons, Chinese people are smart enough to prepare for the worst. #HASHTAG# must think the world is as stupid as they are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Really? Tell me which protein does the mRNA vaccine target! s-protein. Does it create antibodies or initiate T-cells that attack other parts of the virus that cause symptoms? No. What happens when the S-protein mutates to the point cellular immunity efficacy collapses ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Mr Magnus. China knows thar diplomacy has run its course. If the West wants to play hard ball with China, China will play hard ball with them. We will no longer be charitable to those who seeks to put China down. Deal with it #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ðŸ˜ many cars stop there. And many get fined too. Lol. About average cost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What concentration camps and destruction of Tibetan culture? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Ah. Well, name a free app that doesn't do that? The user chose to share their data when they decided to use the app. That is the "price" for the app.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good!. Hopefully with prison time. No White Privilege #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly. Given how the world is fucking up on Covid19, that is the only thing they can do. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious. The one that is facing financial collapse in America and the UK #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Over 50pct of HK economy is directly related to the mainland. Taiwan exports 15pct of its GDP to China. Xinjiang, Tibet have higher GDP per capita than India. Only morons would think these regions are like Palestine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But if you actually think all vaccines are the same, you would be severely mistaken. I am here to point out what each type of vaccine does, how they create "immunity". You don't want to listen, that is fine. But others should do their own research. I am telling people to do that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nope. More...will...die...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No. It never hurt US consumers. It suppressed prices so #HASHTAG# can spend more, corporates can earn more, at the expense of jobs. It was all America. So please bugger off Yellen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quoting Fa Lun Gong. Like a true #HASHTAG#. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Errrr someone has to fund that right ie the discretionary budget. Since tax revenues can't even cover mandatory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Perhaps it is because mRNA is an unproven method and if you actually understand the science you wouldn't want to take it too. Why? Because it is a subunit vaccine that doesn't create wide spectrum antibodies. And likely fail against highly mutating virus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And ignores all the #HASHTAG# politician posts on #USER#. Which is much worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Moronic thought. Since 98pct of Chinese people approve of their government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Easy. US govt deficit. Capital gains tax as main revenue. And well, reserve holder boycott of UST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Whataboutism? How is it whataboutism when all avenues are investigated? Or is it that you fear to find the real truth?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No. It is because even with the vaccines the virus will still be dangerous. Why? Because Covid19 has a ridiculously fast mutation rate. And countries like #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# and majority of #HASHTAG# do not use inactivated virus vaccines. Maintaining tight border control is the only way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why? Just mute the roach. Or maybe start a gofundme for the assh#HASHTAG#'s immigration fee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Hmmm lets see what happens in the next 3 months first eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes. But it also looked like nothing was done to maintain or upgrade the s.tation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At some point, reversal becomes impossible for America. I believe from a political perspective in the US, we have already passed the point of diplomacy, from a bipartisan perspective. The level of Mccarthyism in the US wrt China is already at fever pitched level, and grown into]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So mRNA vaccines have shown decreased efficacy in preventing infections, ie reduced cell immunity, which is what I predicted. Now tell me how effective is it against severe symptoms? It is dropping based on data from Israel and Singapore. And it is early days. Now Pfizer is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how Sinovac vaccines work. It prevents severe symptoms and death even when the virus infection mechanism mutates. The mRNA vaccines seeks to prevent infection but leaves you unprotected when they fail. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally! The traitorous asshole will finally pay his dues #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What kind of bitch laughs at a kid who nearly gets his face ripped off in an accident?! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There is enough good companies for investors to pile money into. Dividend payment doesn't make sense when your economy is growing. Investment does. Unlike G7, China's interest rates are not plumbing the depths of the Mariana Trench. And rolling back profits into productive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# :) i was being half truthful and half sarcastic. Regardless there is truth in what I wrote. Call it vaccine math.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh in case they forget, you cannot sue #HASHTAG# if things go wrong with your vaccination.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I am quoting news findings. Tell them they are wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[to work with China on how to move your economy past its poor state. Relying on transfer income from your labour exports can't help you in the longer term. Try to see how you can make your country better to attract investors. Or tie yourself to America. Your choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Rights of others to do what? Beat up the police? Or anyone that disagrees with you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$300m can buy a lot of lying human rights activists and witnesses #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, think of it as rare free alone time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# resorting to outright lies now. I love in Hong Kong. Literally none of this is happening. It feels like 2018 here. Peaceful and happy. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Current a/c surplus of &gt;$300b in 1Q21 and capital inflows of almost as much. Can't see where CNY / CNH can go except up.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>