<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I demand that Barr indict everyone who testified in the impeachment committees hearings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The patron of my employer just announced that his foundation is paying the 4-5 years of tuition for all incoming students for the 2019 class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This would be a great conference if I knew Chinese. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #USER# I feel ripped off.  I was expecting rampaging mobs homeless vets on streets...#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# with all protest short of outright disobedience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now they cut off the live feed of the game in favor of a show to discuss the Chinese Basketball Association.  And it is mostly commercials.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I asked for the bill and two bartenders brought me a bill.  Yes I tipped.  I am an American dammit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Post a pic YOU took with no description and bring some Zen to the timeline. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Katie Porter and a white board=death.  Before you watch, you know what is going to happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US pig farmers, asked to be 'good patriots,' brace for new round of pork tariffs from China, Mexico.  So much winning in this easy trade war to win.  #HASHTAG#  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty much any Bond movie with Roger Moore has to be taken as a joke.  Theme songs from Sir Paul and Carly Simon are outstanding.  (And Duran Duran does not embarrass themselves--an accomplishment for them.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That left tackle deliver two horrible non-blocks for Buffalo--ending their season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So we are agreed that this only Democrats are racist is a product of fallacious thinking?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Would have been nice if all of you saying this would have looked #USER# more closely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Energy dominance.  How did that work out for you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Community is painful.  The Dean refuses to follow evidence because it goes against his politics. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lamar Jackson  you say?  MVP.  Yes.  Super Bowl winner yes.  John Harbaugh made great and ballsy decision to build entire team around Jackson and his elite running game and competent passing.  Most NFL teams would not do this.  Simply because running QBs get hurt more often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# free #HASHTAG# RT welcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We now know the answer to the question for a lot of people: What would you have done if a Fascist attempts to seize power?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Little India, Singapore.  More for the sign .  :-) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cue the "he was nice a boy who had a bad day" stories, and RT the Onion post that explains that nothing can be done in the only country in which this happens on a regular basis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course, our campus now requires everyone to pay to use the campus wifi.  And of course, the sign up day is the 15th of the month, and if you miss it for a silly reason like a quarantine, you have to sign up next month.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why lots of French is spoken in this neighborhood #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Of course Trump has most of his campaign leadership in jail.  Not Shady right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does administration make us use different assessment forms every year out of ignorance?  Or, is it a clever plot to make sure that there can be no comparisons from year to year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The S Word, the F Word and the Election #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things are getting back to normal.  Academics are posting more bad tings about Biden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fruits of good government: TP being stocked in Taipei. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The name was my fourth choice for this trip.  The first three were vetoed because they translated into something offensive in Chinese.  That was kind of the point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The biggest liquor store that I have ever seen is near a party building in Chengdu.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And everyone should know that his opponent #USER# will actually show up to do the job.  She will defend American and human values.  You can donate to her campaign here:  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I now know that a gekko was hiding on the back of a pan that I used to cook dumplings.  This is what explains the burning smell in my apartment.  Not eating the dumplings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wearing a toga to a tropical Halloween Party is surprisingly seasonal appropriate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We know this is the Democrats being nasty and mean and driving this country apart. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If she were white, newspapers would talk about the couple exercising their constitutional rights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cruelty is the point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Trump dies (and he eventually will), the same people saying that Floyd is not a martyr will be explaining how Trump is a martyr to liberal tyranny.  And, yes, screenshot this tweet and tell them to go fuck themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Let me know when you can sign my Kindle Edition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I honestly do want Hong Kong Police Academy graduates be presented with a compact yellow umbrella upon as a symbol of their devotion to the people.  An umbrella and its holster should be part of their dress uniform.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #USER#, thanks for letting my nieces and nephews know that Mexican immigrants to the #HASHTAG# are rapists.  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Treat yourself.  Get the Willie Dixon box set.  Muddy Waters (illegal in Georgia), Howlin' Wolf, Koko Taylor, Little Walter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw a Chinese commercial featuring a female police sniper, and then it shows as a little girl learning archery and becoming an Olympic Champion.  #USER# is really going to have a tough time with this ad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World War II Museum l, Gdansk, Poland.  Should have let scholars control content. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are talking about what George Carlin would be doing right now.  Honestly, he would be celebrating the deaths of everyone who has died from COVID.  See his final routines.  (I did not find it funny.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always love how all of the prime GQP meat trending tweets always coincide with prime Russian working hours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Holmgren trained a good number of successful NFL QB.  Mike McCarthy not so much.  Aaron Rodgers is just that good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you really want me to judge you on the content of your character, GQP?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most institutions have someone detailed to help you navigate the local medical care and grocery shopping and any other thing that occurs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Other than get special "top secret briefings" on Capitol Hill, members toured defense contractors and went to parties at their headquarters. 2/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is the timing interesting?  Trump attended Jewish meeting last week?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simple rule of drafting: measurables should confirm what you see on tape not substitute for tape.  Losing confidence in current Packers regime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Which candidates would benefit most from a $25 donation?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crypto collapse erases more than $1 trillion in wealth, forcing a reckoning for everyday investors  Crypto supposedly exists to circumvent government control yet investors crying to federal government about losing money. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just a reminder that I am a signatory to this document.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is not the percentage of debt relatively small though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe one of my alma maters can go: full Dan Snyder and rename itself:Dubuque Catholic College.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Something will have to change in how they manage old age.  The related issue is their inherent social Darwinism.  They want educated women to have children but these are precisely the women who do not want to get married and have children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Night of the Living Karens and Kevin’s? It would be fun to watch the Kevins accidentally kill themselves.  Of course, Idiocracy could be made.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One of the problems of Bernie (long term naysayer 1st time posting about this gun supporter) is that you are rolling the dice on his VP choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are right, #USER#, there is no difference between the Republicans and Democrats.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The cost of housing has increased because that Hong Kong real estate is the perfect way to money launder for corrupt CPC members.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# btw, graphic did not work Is this the work some radical Muslim?  #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Toward the Foreign Ministry, 2018. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toll booth  Xian.  Today I am going to do something that i have wanted to do since age 10. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My main beef with people bitching about capitalism is that they never have an honest replacement.  I want to expand the welfare state too and limit corporate power, but I understand the rule of business in society.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Undoubtedly this can be easily done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, I traded J.P. Losman for Aaron Rodgers in a dynasty and QB focused fantasy league.  Really proud of myself for that one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Barney Stinson and PLEASE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Willie Dixon Chess Box Set is one of the jewels of American Civilization.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone who illegally blocks people on Twitter has no business complaining about discrimination on social media.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Slow Train Coming has Knopfler, some political commentary, and a couple of good songs.  When He Returns is a nice ending]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seatac is deserted #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my guilty pleasures is to turn on Bengals games and watch AJ Green play football.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money Talks. Will the G.O.P. Listen? #URL# . He is just a George Soros trained crisis actor functioning as a conduit to undermine #USER#.  Always has been. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Here they are at their secret base in Ju Ming’s studio. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ok, I have to tell you that if want to take my United States history class, I am going to charge you.  You can read my online lecture/text notes if you like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But again, you have to take me seriously because impeachment is going--and I am holding Pelosi accountable.  I guess that the Democrats are the party of personal responsibility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It would cool if somehow the ending of the Good Place could be reshot to include Gardner Minshew in full disco regalia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Blackadder Goes Fourth ending was real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mnuchin Cites Principles in Clawing Back Fed Money. Democrats See Politics. #URL# Anytime a Trump Administration figure cites principles, you know that it is baloney.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am getting all sorts of Nigerian events trending on my timeline.  I am liking random events just to mess with Twitter's advertisers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jefferson Airplane Volunteers (Live At Woodstock 1969) #URL# via #USER# . Millennials just do not know anything.  Look at them think that they can dance into a revolution.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schaedenfreude: taking pleasure in someone’s pain; or, #USER# listening to someone bitch about any aspect of the University of Wisconsin System.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I purchased this postcard in Kinmen or Quemoy.  ⁦#USER#⁩ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since it was such a crappy day, I am going to start posting figures of one of my favourite photography subjects: European imperialist architecture!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #USER#, putting accused sex offender Robert Kraft on camera is not good optics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Did not happen.  Bloomberg would forfeit NY electoral votes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other words, this work as I revisit it is consistent with the ideas of Critical Race Theory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw this walking down Nathan Road.  An Anaheim jumped out in the middle of the street, jumped up and down, and gave them a thumbs down sign. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is lived in the alleys on Taipei #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok, people with money, if you followed a conservative investment strategy like investing in an S&amp;P 500 index fund, your return was over 24% year to date.  So why are you bitching about Biden being bad for business?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You constantly accuse people of wrong doing.  But you do not take action.  Demand that action take place.  I support impeachment because wrong doing took place.  I opposed and oppose Pelosi because she did not stand up for America.  You just see it as a political game.  Patriot?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I miss the era when our campus loudspeakers used to blast AC/DC between classes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I met Athan Theoharis after I was accepted.  He suggested my dissertation topic on our first meeting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Best I can do.  :-) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# my article on JBS and Wallace Campaign in Milwaukee.  Working on JBS and local politics during civil rights era.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You idiots who will not wear a mask or social distance are ruining my life.  You have destroyed the value of my most prized possession: my USA passport.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chick something has a commercial about how they brag about paying their employees so little that one won a car in a lottery and gave it to her friend who could not afford anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I honestly think that we should make "So What" to be the national anthem.  America is too cool for words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, I know what a subtweet is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I can tell you that if this program was enacted, Sheldon Adelson would have gotten a massive handout that would not have been shared with his employees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will say the same thing to #USER# that I said to the Democrats in 1998.  Take your censure motion to the president and ask him to sign it.  If not, I could care less what you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People have correctly pointed out that Trump forced out his navy secretary in order to defend war criminals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taiwan's indigenous peoples would like to remind the world that they have never given up their sovereignty over Taiwan and they never will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Closer than you think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Or why #USER# is the great comedian of our time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doug Flutie played with 9 NFL players and one Jesuit novice his senior year.  I hope that those guys got at least a watch.  Don't get me started on Tebow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok, I think that we are past the point that this was a "slip of the tongue" by Trump and that he received poor legal advice from his aides.  (Get to the: It is not impeachable defense please.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Low Altitude Earth Orbit Tour HAS BEGUN! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to your annual "let's watch university administrator's make millions off exploited basketball players" season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think that this would violate some safety rules. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #USER# got great service from #USER# Residences Chengdu City Center.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re MS corruption: don’t they have a corrupt group of Democrats running that state?  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Restore Bolivian Democracy and Break Its History of Coups #URL# . Constitutions are a nice thing to have.  Following them prevents crap like this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Anti-ZZ Top.  You should see the models in their MTV video!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# SobTrump did not flip flop on abortion?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got jabbed today.  Flash program for foreigners.  First in line.  Barely felt it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously why do die hard Sanders supporters deny agency to black people?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# for Empress--of the universe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t want to get vaccinated?  Really?  Don’t travel internationally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next door sounds like a party.  Not a good idea in a quarantine hotel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PS. As a head of state, Putin is immune to Magnitsky Act.  Side benefit of becoming dictator for life is that he retains that immunity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am always amazed at how people can spend every Sunday in church and then complain about refugees in their community.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# De Tocqueville said that the chief cause of American prosperity and the growing power of the nation was "the superiority of their women."  I suspect that heads would explode likewise as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why in God's Green Earth do students think that they can blow off the final presentation and think that somehow that I will be ok with it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Got some of this today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am seeing Maine wondering where the tourists are.  Really you can blame #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I honestly thought that all of the Claudia Conway stuff was something created by a Sarah Cooper style comedian.  What a weird planet this is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the way, I taught at a community college, and I quite frequently got home schooled kids.  They could not get into other schools.  On the general rule, they were quite good.  Funny, two that I recall off the top of my head went on to work in university administration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This Catholic asks you and the entire #USER# to resign for failure to do your pastoral duty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you choose not to decide
You still have made a choice."

Rush, "Freewill," Permanent Waves, (Mercury, 1980), track 2.

You have to be pretty lame Donald Trump to have me quote Rush in explaining why you have responsibility for the virus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regular thank you to #USER#.  Thanks for showing me greatness!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #USER#, you are #HASHTAG#.  So #USER# would tell you that the #HASHTAG# does #HASHTAG# have #HASHTAG#.  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trade war refugee camp requires sacrifice #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are talking about defund the police like it is a bad thing.  How about my motto: “NWA speaks for me.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[via #USER#.  In my case it is my paycheque and benefits.  Other than that, I could give a.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# On a scale of 10, I usually gave students 2 points for a great essay, 2 points for grades, and 1 point for every point on ACT over 24 (capped at 6).  I subtracted points if students did not take math or science courses.  4/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# They also sprayed Congress with bullets wounding members in the process.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School is FUCKING OUT ALL SUMMER!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the last week, you 500 times more likely to get COVID in the Dakotas than Hong Kong.  In absolute terms, you were 90 times more likely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn COVID. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thank you for your support in this matter.  Please note #USER# and #USER# this is how you respond to this matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please join me in supporting #USER#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And of course, Scott Walker is from Waukesha County.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While I do not want Mitt Romney to represent me, if I had kids, I would like for someone like him to raise them if I died.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I am skeptical of this story because it is about a restroom in China stocked with toilet paper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Hell yes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Primaries are mostly over and #USER# senators are starting to see polling data.  The cracks will come in the next week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turkish cafe next to the Macanese restaurant.  1 block from hotel.  Gotta love Hong Kong #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Croatia and Montenegro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And he has a really cool spy name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My niece and I are going uncommitted to Iowa caucuses.  My strategy is to make people talk to her for her vote.  I will follow her lead unless she wants to vote for Bernie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dude, the president has the privilege.  You do not.  If he chooses to waive the privilege, he gets to do so.  Furthermore, US v. Nixon ruled that there is executive privilege, but you omit that executive privilege is not absolute.  It is not a shield for criminal behavior.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not today... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So why do I watch all of these commercials from this mediocre Baker Mayfield and Lamar Jackson took his team to the playoffs as a rookie?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# and #USER#, your response please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Mighty Wind is Blowin' - New Main Street Singers, The Folksmen and Mit... #URL# via #USER#   Wha' Happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Do nothing Democrats. #HASHTAG#?  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL#  KPOP fans may have saved my life.  Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oyster, green pepper, and extra garlic.  If oysters are not available, go with anchovies.  Yes, I delivered pizzas for five years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hey it is never too late.  I was an aspiring historian, and after 30 years of teaching college, I still feel like an aspiring historian.  Nothing stopping you from being the historian of the Trump Administration.  (Sorry too depressing of a topic for me.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But if we are talking about reality, Superstore is by far the best when it comes to talking about most people's workplace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chick Fil A PR commercials never talk about the company doing any good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How much are they in the USA?  Free at hospitals in China.  170 USD at Hong Kong hospitals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Thank you America. That’s our show. Not a lot of people watched it but the joke’s on you, because we got paid anyway.” (Tracy Jordan on TJS, not 30 Rock)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Job #HASHTAG# and pack the courts immediately if the Roberts touches it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Line at neighbourhood beef noodle restaurant #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would like to tell all of those adjuncts that you should keep plugging away, but hey, I have never gotten a permanent job.  Take care of number one.  :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BRUISING YEAR MY ASS #USER#  #URL#  one of best years of my life financially.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your 22 year old son can take out a 2nd mortgage on your home without your consent, you got a much bigger problem than your ownership of Game Stop shares.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stopping Iran and Russia from interfering in our elections is a good thing, #USER#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only in Macau do you get an Azores themed fast food restaurant—except perhaps in Azores. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am sure glad that I was asked for my remarks, which the administration is changing the wording.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #USER# here is an easy one: stand up for Constitution.  It makes you look American.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, there are good movies geared toward women.  Just because one is made does not mean that I have to like it.  Bridget Jones Diary was wonderful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# When you hold Trump and #USER# to same standard.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER#, how does one prepare to watch a Scotland International Football match?  Since my wife and I will watch it together although we are in lockdown in two separate places.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my work, the bigotry generally comes from owners of property or capital.  I am familiar with one blue collar worker, but he was retired.  And a native of Louisiana.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christchurch, New Zealand. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Name and shame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, please remember Trump supporters.  You voted for this.  And I do mean this.  You voted to "blow up Washington."  Enjoy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Welcome to Taiwan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Before the GQP will ever change, they will have to have a couple of 1964 style defeats--at the minimum.  And there is no guarantee that they will change for the better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the weaknesses of the 25th Amendment is that it is his supporters who can be fired at will.  Conceivably the mere rumor of a 25th Amendment meeting would lead to terminations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hey, look if you want to pick a fight, go ahead.  Just do not misstate my point.  I heard few #USER# complaining about Johnson's comments.   Do not think that I do not check the numbers every day in every potential country that I have to relocate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If voting by mail is good enough for Trump, it is good enough for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so glad that I have been overseas for most of the pandemic.  I do not know how people in America are holding it together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Believe it or not, Chinese universities are much more compassionate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Let’s reject the history of American music while we are at it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bought shirt months ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Local Museum showed 1930 film shot by British diplomat in our Chinese city.  Half of it is of his dogs and cat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Someone apparently did not read about the role of French foreign aid and the French navy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# let's cut their military aid. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What #USER# headline writers write when a deadline approaches and they got nothing. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a dream that all nations have a website that explains who can go where.  Most nations are hiding all of their information.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Be nice to my nephew who is just starting.  :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Will there be a kindle version for us overseas types?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[via #USER#. Trump lied....  #HASHTAG#  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will now start blocking advertising on my #USER# #USER#Support until you rectify your policies re: Trump libel.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>