<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# no doubt about it: the joooos. muslims wd never kill muslims. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Ken Roth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# no idiot. it's not okay. but when they're trying to kill mine, and hide behind theirs, there's not much choice.
"it's okay for me to accuse israel of killing pn kids, but not hamas who not only assures they will be killed, but... kills them straight up."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# maybe what it's aimed to do. why does "our" country want to let in such corrupting immigrants?
/s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I don’t think you know what that word means. This is most definitely about culture. And you’re on my thread.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin Amis famously asked a crowd of London glitterati if they felt morally superior to the Taliban. ⅔ said no. he forgot to ask if they felt morally superior to Israel. 100% wd have said yes.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i wd never criticize another culture!
why? 
bc to compare them to the west by progressive standards wd utterly humiliate them and take all the wind out of my urgent reformist (millenarian) sails.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# When any pushback is unacceptable, even an invitation to debate is harassment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[terrifying
Facebook Puts Soros, Muslim Brotherhood, Activists in Charge of Censorship #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me guess. Because if Hamas is a terrorist organization, so are they.

Why does the PA/PLO reject the designation of Hamas as a terror organization? | PMW Analysis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# &amp; if UN had had the balls, they wd have suspended Arab participatn until they recognized Israel, created on the basis of a democratic vote of the members. Instead, they let them stay &amp; today the UN is a majority of dictatorships who systematically betray its founding principles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# impressive humanitarian racism
what choice do they have (ie they have no moral agency, on desperate and vicious reactions to injuries you inflict).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's okay. Habash just killed Jews. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# What’s not?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# light dawns slowly over the partisan mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# pot. kettle. black. w all the nazi/apartheid accusations against israel. 
but i agree. racism is an overused accusatn. more like humanitarian prejudice...
but if u cd just answer w/out returng the accusatn, don't you think yr v low expectatns of arabs reflects a certn prejudice?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# if human rights advocates ignore the #USER#'s obsession with israel, it's rank dishonesty both in indicting Israel and exculpating the Pns, then they, like Ken Roth, will be open to accusations of hypocrisy and practising a double standard in the Middle East.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# fighting racism with racism: it's sort of like cleaning up with paint.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It helped that the Romans killed over 1 million in the 135 rebellion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what's next? our journalists will make sure your eyes are covered. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i was referring to Halimi's killer
sorry, forgot my /s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Identification with the pretender]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# got 1000 BCE wrong.
more like 10,000 BCE (pre-agriculture), and once you got past childhood alive, you had a good chance of even making 60. esp if, as a woman, you survived childbirth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# policies tailored to suit an agenda.
question is, what agenda and how loopy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# or bending the knee to the zeitgeist. 
Seth apparently doesn't know that one reason israel was created was so Jews cd walk upright (kommemiyut l'artzenu).
which is why some of the folk already there found their presence so unbearable.
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# there's comfort in numbers
#HASHTAG# is easier than solitary integrity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# oops. i'm talking to the wrong person. sorry to disturb your vitriolic narrative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# bit juvenile, no? surely a man of your wit cd have come up with something better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive – Project Wiki – how Wikipedia is breeding armies of antisemites #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# started in oct 6, 2000 w cries of "death to jews" at a rally about #USER#. the "anti-racist" groups (MRAPP) present either joined in or said nothing. 
journalists did not report it.
by 2014, anti-Israel rallies featured hours of the same chant, followed by attacks on synagogues #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# that's not how it sounds. if it's a list of worthy names, it's valuable, altho not as valuable as it wd be if we knew how the list was compiled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# dupes of #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and the media/HRNGOs/"progressive" activists not only can't tell the difference, they invert them.

#USER#, There Is Jewish and There Is Arab Violence #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ouch.
Jesus will return when Christian ecumenical organizations condemn violence against Christians with the same force with which they lament the necessity of Jewish self-defense.
#USER#, Not any time soon...
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# need audio copy. they won't read it.
Buber, after coming to Israel, was asked how his hebrew was.
"good," he replied, "just not enuf to be obscure in."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i also give my thanks and gratitude to the western media for reporting our cooked statistics and then blaming israel for the deaths in gaza. it has made our sacrifice of them worthwhile. if we had been blamed, it might have backfired. all praise useful infidels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# it looks like they used google translate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# but i, as a gay, defend your right to do that to my fellow gays. look how open i am! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 2/2
in addition to the fundamental folly of his thinking Israel built and maintained those camps rather than the arabs (best enemy, worst friends),
there are many today who think this is still a good "description" of those camps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# and my old institution has given this guy Eli Wiesel's chair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# now do it, and get someone to interrupt you and say to the students: do you hear what he's saying? how can you think that's okay?
i shudder to think what they'd say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Believe All Women” is dead... collapsd undr its own rottn contradictns. Along the way, it did more to silence genuine victims of sexual assault &amp; poison relatns btw sexes than any supposd sin of patriarchy.
Joe Biden brought #HASHTAG# movt &amp; is collapsg w it #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Anything to piss off israel no matter how degrading]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# an attitude possibly admirable, also possibly encouraging of the victim industry.
is skepticism about some claims ruled out a priori?
al chet that i ever doubted any victim claim!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# you know you're in for a but when the good rabbi's sentence begins reasonably...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# like the guy added to the bus in color.
sort of a salvador dali kind of thing, i guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# if you're offended by a few crowds shouting that (as am I), are you not offended by Pn media - religious and secular - shouting "death to Jews everywhere" from the pulpit, on TV, at official rallies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# cd you be specific on what you're thinking of. i'm willing to bet that 98% of it is not accurate? who do you get your info from?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ah the ironies of #HASHTAG#-PoCo: no Truth gives birth to new Truth:
"They do not believe that truth is something that we can find together, but rather that it is something they possess &amp; can impose on others"

Stanley Fish and the Argument Against Free Speech #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# point is that Arabs were among most ferocious (&amp; successful) imperialists in history. They r not indigenes, they r imperial, &amp; much of Arab Islam’s triumphalist religiosity (wh eg can’t tolerate independent infidels (jews!) in dar al islam is a direct expressn of that imperialism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A white racist made up this meme.
/s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Conditions? Change in culture change in leadership. Nothing less]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# in my opinion, no. Hen, what say you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And nothing on how the “not riots” of summer 2000 are openly referred to as riots by this “spokesman”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just uploaded “CNN 190521 1808 B Anderson interviews S Haskel.mp4” to #HASHTAG#: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# don't start trying to correct rhetorical inflation... you can never swallow that ocean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# great blindspot of #HASHTAG# - think Israel's the problm &amp; were it to a) disappear or b) create +1 muslim majority state w terror infrastructure, that wd bring peace.
don't understand that hostility to Israel part of larger problem of arab belligerence
oops, I #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# who turned al aqsa into a riot center?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clearly, if govt wd just nationalize egg industry run by bureaucrats instead of filthy capitalists, we’d all have plenty of eggs to eat at way cheaper prices.

AGs from 3 states going after farmers &amp; market forces kept staples on shelves amid pandemic
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[falsely believe that Trump called neo-Nazis and white supremacists “good people” when in fact he clearly condemned them (see #URL# for the entire transcript: #URL#).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i can understand "far more understandable..."
the "far less reprehensible" is far less understandable...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# can u blame him? Jews r just so annoying. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# because his hatred is a projection onto israel of what arabs do to arabs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# ooooh noooo! what will the "social justice warriors" say about the end of Israeli democracy? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol. It's probably cause the script was written by Jews. #HASHTAG#  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If only bc the Jews have the nerve to boycott baseball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Is that new item per casualty, so Israel has 146 items per casualty?
Nice update of Virgil Hawkins, Stealth Conflicts:
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# you shd read Hillel Cohen, Army of Shadows. there were many arabs in palestine who much appreciated the improvements the zionists brought (huge arab immigration in those yrs). most of their leaders (eg the Nashashibi) were assassinated by the Husseinis (to wh clan Arafat belongd)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# yeah, but in the case of the soviets it took ¾ of a century]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because they have an office... wdnt want it attacked. Wd we?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# it's complicated. your green map is of muslim majority nations and we all know islam is highly variegated. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# stop whining. don't you know? it's just legitimate criticism of Israel.nsigh... you Jews. sooooo sensitive. why can't you be more like the Palestinians, who take criticism in stride?n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# here's a cloying post-truth journalist from France24 interviewing the film-maker and slobbering over her "higher truth"
#URL#

#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# discrimination, in context, is actually a positive act. but then... it gets into such things as merit, and we all know that's a synonym for privilege.
/s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# i look forward to their rebukes (not yours, who gets it).
i thought of putting a /s, but then thought, elder will get it, which he did.
than come the sarcasm police...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# can the whole world (and many jews) be wrong and a few (right-wing) israelis be right. don't be silly, you're delusional. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ah, the cascade of unintended unforeseen consequences...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# so what happened to the stuff about CAIR and Sarsour?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# gotcha. if you have articles to recommend on the topic, do post their urls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Like a fear of being replaced]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# as-a-jew, i cannot sign something denouncing my people's dedicated (and deranged) enemies. 

it just wdn't look seemly. too tribal.

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# explain how you know it’s fake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# nothing more impt than this.
// to Nero fiddling (klezmer) while EU burns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I know. Let's give Arafat a foothold in disputed territories. If he turns it into a terror state Israel will be in a better position to...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# also? in other words, your foolish obsessions, which are why you're still w/out state, trump (pun intended) your concern for the lives of your people. 
good work, Saeb, history will remember you fondly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# you can't subject children to genocidal hate all their lives without some of them cracking.
#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# yes i am. do you really think that if the idf targeted pn children they'd kill so few?
you know how many children have been killed in 10 years of war in Syria, vs. 70 years of war btw Israel and her neighbors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Leave it up to #USER# to take Barak Ravid seriously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# my bet is democrats wd rather take this than trump's snakeoil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# whatever the source, the reaction is pure envy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# why did, suddenly, gunfire ring out?
(love that intransitive verb)
the #HASHTAG# was the catastrophe brought on Arabs in Palestine by Arab leaders who, thinking they'd easily win, declared a war of extermination... &amp; lost.
hey #USER#, how about craving dignity rather than revenge?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# not Muslims, you #HASHTAG#, "central asians." #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Glad you know how ppl you hate feel about themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ummm, not sure on the first two, but the third? definitely not. everyone knows those jews are liars. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# sorry shd have added #HASHTAG#. meant that some, fearful of muslims, wd attack this graphic for angering them. not i.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# precisely. how dare they.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[astonishingly bad partisan journalism

all about trump's many vulnerabilities, biden only mentioned on offensive
not a word of his problematic behavior.
#HASHTAG# w #USER# as either patsy or player.
either way it's not journalism
#HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# toilet paper normally doesn't come with a warning to consumer: consumption may be hazardous to one's cognitive health.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7:40 "But that will probably never happen because Democrats don't go anywhere these days where they're not being pre-adored."

New Rule: Bill Maher the Messaging Czar | Real Time (HBO) #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Glad to know you know what I care about, I’m sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I like the math: a dozen evictions = ethnic cleansing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# we inadvertently hunt for them.
you'd think they'd show some gratitude... but no, try dropping dead in front of them and see what they do...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent, somewhat predictable thread by #USER# on Thread Reader App #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# u'v got my stuff right.
as to H, he's clearly in rhetorical overdrive, but he seems to have drivn u 2 off cliff. tone it down &amp; sound more convincg.
there is a problem w #HASHTAG#, that science can't handle. we don't know future (or w #HASHTAG#, present); anythg we say is conjecture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# the latter being a gift to oneself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL#
altho i agree with the analysis, i do think the either or of temper tantrum and (frustrated) triumphalist Muslims is mistaken. /2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s 6 months since #USER# published my article on the Oslo "Peace" Process Disaster and Shame-Honor Culture #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# an astonishing example of how tone-deaf the Israeli left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# it's not meant to be taken literally (in that sense, like gender), it's refers allegorically to everybody in the privilege business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# priorities man. we're saving democracy here. /s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# wow. that's impressive. not particularly austere, but definitely deplorable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Sounds like it’s the only reason you liked him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geller: “Steel yourself for the ‘fear of reprisal’ propaganda &amp; ‘islamophobia’ lies.”
Spencer: "establishment media will use it to hector Americans abt ‘Islamophobia.’”

not everyday that an article cites as deplorable passages that predict the article.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don’t forget America-hating. In other words the full package of vicious insecurity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# iow: "i remain hopeful that despite my disgusting remarks which revealed my sheer contempt for history and jews, that i can continue to slander israel in slightly less obvious ways." hopefully, earnestly, completely cluelessly yours, PO'B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# so far, our guy's son. but only time will tell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# my mistake. that's a more recent talk i gave at ISGAP.
for the text behind my earlier talk that you did ask about, here's the link to the article by that name;
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# of course when you declare someone else a mortal enemy, lose repeatedly in efforts to destroy that enemy, &amp; then the enemy doesn't treat you like a best friend (or better a conquerer), &amp; you call *that* dehumanization, it really illuminates little but your megalomanic self-pity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# good insight into how the anti-zionist bubble creates a shameless culture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# an old story, part of their cannibalistic strategy that only works if the western media cooperates.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bassem, one of the few people to criticize Palestinian rulers, nails it. The woke crowd screams "uncle tom" to hide its own cowardice and denial. 
#USER#  Hamas, not Israel, is to blame for the latest bloodshed #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# as a Palestinian friend put it: the Palestinians have the worst friends and the best enemies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# aletheiaphobia (fear of the truth)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Muslims imperialist? what is Karsh, an #HASHTAG#? #HASHTAG# what abt the anti-imperialist alliance of the #HASHTAG# and #HASHTAG#?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# in other words fulfilling the conditions of #HASHTAG# even as they dismiss it as a silly conspiracy theory...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# oh, i see. the arabs who tried to destroy the state in its infancy, aspiring openly to finish hitler's job... the israelis  somehow "considers them to be 'endangering' the state." how utterly ridiculous of them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# disproportionné. but you wdn't be suggestg that the french have responded excessively to the protests. after all, it is their citizens. israel's sin is to fight enemies... come to think of it, muslim enemies. that's the no-no. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# no y'r not. y'r coverg for a leadership that wants not freedom but dominion (ie takg away others' freedom), &amp; y'r tryg to convince the West that y'r the victim bc so far u haven't succeeded in gettg what u want. if Pns really wanted freedom &amp; dignity, they'd have had it long ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[impt thread on #USER#'s dishonest hit piece
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# is there anything here on how press lack of credibility undermine democracy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# damn jews making it sooo hard to hate them!
/s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# hoping for a more receptive audience for his suicidal advice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wrenchingly caught btw their progressive principles (save innocent lives) and the insanely anti-israel dogmas of their leftist bedfellows. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stephen Shoemaker is one of the best scholars on early Islam. Here's a review by #USER# on his latest: A Prophet Has Appeared #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# and how do suicide bombers feel when they *kill* kids?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# but she's misunderstood, man. have you no pity for the poor girl... just cause she misunderstands, doesn't mean you have to pick on her.
/s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# "experts" in misreading the conflict over the land btw the river and the sea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# i'm sorry. anyone who supports the pn cause is supportg people who TARGET children. the very idea that you can accuse Israel of not caring abt children when Pns so want to kill Israeli children they don't care if they kill their own, is staggering hypocrisy. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG! you mean those evil settler colonialist zionists pioneered in malaria eradication, a model for today's Africa?
damn. that doesn't fit the narrative, now does it?
Draining the Swamps #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# they're into shaming people, not patient explanation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# actually need to take it back to 2000 when the left (which had previously shown limited interest - 0 at Seattle 1999), suddenly adopted the Pns as thr leadg cause. Buruma in 2003: support for Pns (at the height of suicide terror campaign) is a litmus text of liberal credentials.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# guilty as charged.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# jews, they just can't take the heat. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# can't afford to see; they're stoking the flames.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[your sneering smug ridicule identifies you as an islamophobe. saudis are true muslims, hence, peaceful #HASHTAG#. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# of course woke is a term for all those who get outraged at the things they don't like...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i'm sure it's because they support the two-state solution like the jewish members of BDS. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# leadership seems helpless to resist. déboussolés (uncompassed), morally adrift
they mistake as honesty (look at self-critical me), when they are contributing to the growg incitement against their own.
it matches, in a passive way, pn leaders' willingness to sacrifice their people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No matter how well intentioned, will Biden be Phaeton driving the chariot of the sun?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This isn’t a partisan issue. “The percentage of Democrats who are worried about speaking their mind is just about identical to the percentage of Republicans who self-censor: 39 and 40%, respectively,” Gibson and Sutherland report.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# looking forward.
so they're on the path from '89, involved in the wind-up to Durban in the '90s, and then flourish in the aughts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# manomanoman. the rhetoric's something of a giveaway. serious scientists making serious points, don't talk about baloney.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# alas, Israel stands by while Pn preachers spout the most disgusting stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because only white supremacists kill people of color. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They are the Chosen Victims. How dare the Ukrainians steal the limelight? And make them look bad in the process? Unbearable. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What I like is he doesn’t even care that in the case - Allah forbid - that it happens, no one will be able to stop the slaughter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# and you really think this is the way to end jew-hatred?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone knows the Muslims are the victims. What's ur prob man? #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# no precisely. the perfect storm of lethal journalism whipping up jihadi anger, NGOs whipping up "progressive" indignation. this started with the Sharon visit in 2000.  hence, i call it:
#HASHTAG# - when jihadis attack a democracy, blame the democracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# failure to appear will result in being stuck in the present.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# he's a schoolyard bully. not going to change. it wins him points with his gang.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# sure she does. she went to BU. (NB: i taught at BU and don't know what they mean.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# and it burns the hell out of them that Israel liberates you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# only by the definition of people who abuse the term in order to silence legitimate critics of judaism.
donchaknow?
/s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 1) massive diff btw what Israeli govt/IDF do and what news reports. lethal journalism mainstreams jihadi propaganda.
2) whereas ppl refuse to make any connectn btw muslims &amp; jihadi behavior, they readily make connectn btw diaspora jews and [what media report as] israeli behavior.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# pt taken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# most? probably. all? alas not at all.
it's hard to suppress the gag reflex, tho.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# invitation to aggression
fake bravado is a provocation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[but it's different. jews in diaspora helpless. we have sympathy for their plight. israelis, they can defend themselves. we find that offensive in the extreme. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Are you suggesting that jewish students who support Israel don’t deserve this? What about all the #HASHTAG# that Palestinians circulate about Israel? Doesn’t that count for  something? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Just visit #USER# and see what Palestinian leaders have to say about the sons of apes and pigs, and the Hadith of the rocks and trees.
also #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Excaliber. at the end when he throws the sword and the lady of the lake catches it, if it had sliced off her hand, it wd have saved the entire movie. 
(too much monty python, i guess)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[not sure where the "unexpected" comes from. this has been a long time coming... and will be a long time gone...
Antisemitism from unexpected source - the African American Community #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# that's incitement against Muslims! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# santa? what are you going to do with the resurrection?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# is this part of the peace-studies paradigm. humans as naturally peaceful. war mostly from american imperialism?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# reread 1984. only there it's imposed by a tyrant on unwilling subjects. here it's imposed by the self (wannabe tyrant) on an eager self.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# We have examples in USA where the term is closer to the totalitarian camp. Accusations of bad faith can be debilitating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# judge not by the organization but by the quality of the research. who's double checking and who's regurgitating?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# as for what constitutes antisemitic antizionism for me:
accusing israel of behaving like nazis
of committing genocide
of apartheid
of targeting pn children
all in fact projections of what pn "freedom fighters" do or want to do. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# nothing like burning down the house of intl law and human rights just to get at your obsession. 
reminds me of the joke about the guy with crabs who shaved half his crotch, lit the other half on fire, and stabbed the little critters with an ice pick as they tried to escape.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What a remake of a pieta.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The owl cautions against apocalyptic enthusiasm. It’s not dawn. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# use accusation of #HASHTAG# to trigger #HASHTAG# among journalists who respond with deeds of #HASHTAG# 

Media Attack Investigative Reporter for Investigating and Reporting on CAIR #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# if saudis can show positive images of israelis during ramadan, and UAE can land a plane at Natbag, and the EU can investigate terror ties in Pn NGOs... well who knows, maybe the world can just save itself from a malignant case of Pnism.
next ICC replaces its current head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# link to text please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[on the madness of transgender PC

Did J.K. Rowling Just Get Red-Pilled? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you mean before Mussolini?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# not so side]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# sauce for your goose is not sauce for my gander. (esp in gender fluid times)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and "progressives" despise it? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And what percent of responsibility wd was you assign to belligerent Arabs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# isn't that the basic message of the Leila Khaled is just "resisting"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# and #USER# actually got the lowest vote total among Democratic candidates. her presence depressed voting in her bailiwick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Times has a fitful relationship to self-examination..."

check out Renata Adler's, Canaries in the Mineshaft (2002), Introduction on the decline of standards and lack of self-correction at the #USER# 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# that's "misinforming." they clearly are so self-deluded they don't know it's lying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# i didn't know they owned the sinai? who is "they"? you counting ottoman turks as arabs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The occupation of academia by thugs #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# so no need to bring it up now?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>