<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I don't get this: Cuomo is criticizing Cynthia for not supporting Jewish people...  I could swear that NY was in the US and not in Israel...  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# if you can't trust the White Supremacists working in the White House, who can you trust ...  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Unless Bolton's book is only 1/2 page Trump hasn't read the book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# is amazing to see Republicans 
more worry about Antifa and not as much worry about the FA in Antifa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nice video Ahmed :)
greetings from Montreal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Andrew... try watching TV shows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# explaining to a student that white people enslave black people 200 hundreds years ago is not placing blame on current White people. on the other side, maybe you don't want the issue at schools because you are ashamed of your ancestors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# AOC, you have 2 years to find the 28% that didn't vote for you, and ask them "how come?"  :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# hilarious!
the amazing thing Stephen's show has is that he is as good doing comedy as when he does serious stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Is tax payer's money... 
The Bill has programs that are standard in many other countries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm glad you are ok.

ps: those are a fantastic pair of lips :)
ps: eyebrows too :)  :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so it was true... the Taliban manage to come to the US and are passing bills #HASHTAG# RT #USER#: YUCK #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# no need to set a reminder.
I record every show :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# so, Mitch didn't convict Trump when he was still President... so... lets impeach Mitch...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# are all Republican Senators ok with this? 
do they still support Trump when he is doing things like this?
How incompetent they can be?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# if the Senate and the DOJ were serious about this scandal somebody will be arrested in the next week and put in jail while waiting for the trial. 

otherwise this is just a talking exercise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I'm sure there is 100 times money to be made from tourism than from the toilet paper this tree will become]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# of course... you are right.
but Trump doesn't understand logic or caring for others. He was told over and over to wear a mask to avoid spreading the virus. All the people around him were supposed to wear it too to avoid spreading the virus to him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# but if God sent the scientist that created the vaccine so we could all be safe... a religious exception will be going against God.... weird...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# lets ask Trump where are the HQ of Antifa and the names of their leaders...   #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# there is a typo... is supposed to say:

   FREELOADING]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I was expecting a Jan 6th event months before it happened. Saying that Facebook caused it is silly. Helped it maybe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# where are the members of Congress that were all for $12/hr?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# just watched the whole Season 1.  Pearl and Bayo are doing an amazing job. In general, all the characters are strong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cenk, have you noticed the headlines in CNN bashing Biden?
"America's messy retreat from Afghanistan raises questions about Biden's leadership"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# voter Bloc: Putin
how?... Putin will do its best to hack the voting system and change the results... having Trump on the WH destroying the US as we know it must be super cheap for Putin... no need of rockets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Clarification: Belarus is allowing Russia to invade Ukraine... Belarus has also declared war to Ukraine... they should get all the sanctions possible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# for Trump, 4 years ago, with Obama in charge, the Democrats were destroying America... then he became President... and still the Democrats are trying to destroy America... when is his apocalyptic message convince the Democrats to switch parties?nn#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trayvon's case is about self-defense: White people defending themselves from scary-looking black people #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# regulations are bad?
what about seat belts?
what about smoking in a room with other people?
what about preparing food in a clean environment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# you are comparing a treatment that is being abuse (glyphosate, which probably is unregulated thanks to Republicans)  with a vaccine process that is being carefully delivered. Nobody has said "get 10 doses"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# did you watch Nicolle with Chris  Christie? was a massacre. He could have reported her to the police after the beating... Joy is very animated but Nicolle has decades of experience...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# you are scare of Communists (my guess is you meant to say Socialists)?

so you think Capitalism has been doing great till now? wow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Great speech by Stephen for his friend Chris. He was tearing up and me too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# is known that if you don't support US military you are kind of unpatriotic... how is not mentioned this when talking about Billionaires not paying their taxes?  Taxes are use for the Military !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# maybe is time to present your thesis as a "Black Paper"  :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stephen has been doing an amazing job every night. Evelyn should get a piece of the award if Stephen wins since she has been providing the only laughter :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He is an idiot so the lost will me minimal for the country... most probably a plus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you are a monster... many people don't like you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 99 followers vs 325,000 followers

Kevin, I think you are the irrelevant one

also..... is "you're"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# how to avoid that Trump ends pardoning himself?.... just take out from the White House anybody that can type and put together the document Trump has to sign...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm confused...nhow can she get sick from a hoax orchestrated by the Democrats... nn#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# the human race might survive if we start trying to make real contact with alliens visiting Earth... I'm sure they could help with Covid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# what about doing Catholic ceremonies for young kids that kill themselves after being sexually abuse by Priests? is that ok? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In Peru I remember reading about a similar thing. If you stole something you went to jail for a number of years. If you were on a position of authority, the sentence was double... very simple.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# translation:
cleaning table = Stephen is really piss off and will like to swear on air for the next segment...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Cenk... that is President Manchin to you... he is in total control.  He is letting Republicans to get away with opposing everything. Now is Democrats not capable of doing anything. Republicans in WV will vote for Manchin in 2024 because they are grateful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# is Engel is placing AOC on a pedestal? he is assuming she has a power that she doesn't have, but he is sure she has it. "one person from high"... "she can anoint" ? so now you can't like one person over another?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pluto was discovered in 1930. If it was an older civilization they didn’t left that much about themselves... it was aliens 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wonder how many White Supremacists are on all the police departments across the US, sharing methods on how to "punish" people. chock-holds, knees on the neck, applying weight on someone's back, ... they all give me the same feeling. No violence on the body...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# sure, Trump respect Human Rights... is not like if transgenders were humans anyway... no right to enlist in the Military and defend their country   #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Emma... beauty and brains...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If the Supreme Court confirms a 2nd Judge that has abuse women, one day the SC is going to have all 9 with the same past... maybe they can join forces with the Priests who have corner the market for children being abuse... #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trump "best supply chain"? of what? lies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm guessing the casinos will be receiving a tax credit because their electricity bills were too high... 

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# and apparently they planned all this since 2012, when she seek professional help with her husband.... is amazing how Democrats can predict the future ... #HASHTAG#  everybody is an actor to people like you, right? who is paying you to attack this person?  Paul Ryan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tucker: named the whistleblower

Trump always said to any News Network that if they couldn't name the source of information about Trump they were "FAKE NEWS".... Are you "fake news" Tucker?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# if would be nice if the Provinces acted as if they were part of the same Country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# DEMs voted to impeach a guy that confessed grabbing women by their private parts... I'm shocked!    #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'll buy the clothes only if I can be assure that there were no child molesters in the production... #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# how many in the Senate have sympathies with White Supremacists groups?   I haven't seen every single one of them in camera condemning them.  Reporters should go and ask each one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# most politicians have no party.
they just give people a different flavor to make them believe they are "different" than the others. Is all a mirage. Progressives are the only ones fighting the Status Quo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# nobody has commented about how sad Matt's story is.  He is a "powerful" politician and could be impressing women in many places but instead he has to go and pay for sex...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# that policeman wouldn't back down from a progressive escalation.
all for a wide right turn?
wow!
check him for racists tattoos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# To me looks like a lot of money. The fines are not included. The objective is Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "little reason" is the name of his "friend" during zoom meetings :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# the goal is to put Black people in jail so they can't vote ever again...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# DEMs need their people winning in Texas but they allowed a bunch of candidates that barely reach 3rd place and they won't go into the run off. Why not select the 2 with the biggest chances? why not go into a small Primary first to reduce the candidates?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tweeter didn't want people wishing for Trump to die but on his last Tweet, Trump couldn't care less for millions of Americans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# sure Jared... is Jared suggesting the Palestinians get sniper rifles and start shooting over the wall to peaceful Jewish people? you now.. show come "commitment to peace" like Israel does?  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# yes, lets drill for oil on every single National Park. that will teach the democrats that Trump is serious... #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# women should choose to have a c-section after 6 months and give the baby to Amy Barrett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# the problem is not being a weirdo.
his problem is that he hasn't find other "weirdos" like him. 
tell him that he will eventually finding and all will be great. takes time but he will be ok at the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# something that I heard once or twice, was that the owner of the WTC buildings had a double insurance on them.  Never again was this mention. 
Was "double insurance" normal? how many more buildings in NYC had this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# clarification: 
Trump doesn't take a knee because he wouldn't be able to stand by himself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# separating you from your family when you are 7 or 10 years old is not torture?

Across Canada, there are mass graves discovered recently. No records. 

I saw a grown man explaining how he got stab with a pencil on his hand because he spoke using his language (he showed the scar)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# anybody watched angry AOC against Pelosi yesterday on "Our Cartoon President"?  was awesome :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Biden's problem is that he looks weak. Between Manchin and Sinema they are making him super weak. Trump never did nothing for the people but at least nobody said NO to him because of feat. Sadly, Republicans like that kind of strength.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# what is the fascination with a party on being 30% of the votes and trying to win by cheating so they can control the other 70%?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# more like 
"law and order... order... order... der... der"
that's the sound on a bunker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# When you talk for an hour to say the exact same thing you could say in 3 minutes you have a problem.
Something was off with Jimmy that day. He usually went into rants but a rant about "I was right" is really weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# there is also a possibility that if the minimum wage is kept in the reconciliation, nobody will vote against the Bill if they are planning to run again...ever...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# whatever Biden did with his son, Trump has done 100 times worse with his entire family... so... this "report" should change nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# most of the other causes of dead can't be prevented.
but if you get rid of guns, everybody will be safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# fascinating interview.
Mila is adorable. Very smart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trump is not good for the heart.
Weed makes you forget he is in charge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# those Democrats blocking BBB had months to make their request that they needed a full analysis for the cost.  They waited till the day of the vote to make their request.  This is highly suspicious. Is everything being coordinated by Pelosi or Biden or both?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# in my case I can't say no....

to buying more ice cream every time I'm shopping :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If solutions for Green Energy are not implemented right now, the headlines in 2035 are going to look like:
"the Government declares burning fossil fuels illegal as a radical measure trying to save Planet's Agriculture"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# every question Chuck Todd asks a person is as if Chuck just came from Mars and has no idea of what is going on in the US.  and God forbid he listens to the answer and insists on getting an answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So the guy that has sexually assaulted countless women and sold real estate mostly using cash has been charged... I'm shocked    #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I'm with #USER# ... Outlaw it !!!

sounds completely fishy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# is like if Drug makers were giving money to certain Politicians to say non sense stuff about marijuana... #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# so Republicans were fighting the South States to liberate the slaves? does Georgia and Alabama know this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# somebody should ask Trump:
"if your brother Fred didn't like you and he had to dumped mashed potatoes in your head to stop you from keep torturing him merciless, how do you expect that anyone else will like you?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think those military vehicles are in private property #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER#Live #USER# is not in favor of passing the Voting Bill because he doesn't want to get rid of "dark money". He loves that money. That's why he is in TX right now with some donors. That's why millions of votes might not be cast... just be cause of some money Joe wants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# some rules as weird.
you can't say  "s#&amp;t" or "f#&amp;k" on TV but you can say  "Ivermectin is just fine".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I bet he increased his medication so he could handle..... a glass of water... wowwwww!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Democrats did their part... they managed to get all the information, addresses, for all the dreamers, that now can be use by ICE to get them and deport them...  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Madison... you might be a horrible human being... just saying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# how can anybody talk to Rand Paul without saying "excuse me but you are a moron"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# that's a given.
Trump's superpower is to get somebody else to do the illegal activity and take the fall for him. Is unbelievable. Hopefully SCOTUS will authorize the release of Trump's tax returns next week. Everything people needs to know is there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# so... no obstruction needed from the Democrats for these people? funny how this works  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Condy is pretty smart but if Biden chooses her Biden will become a Republican... officially... all his talking about working with the other side when the other side wants nothing to do with your side is very suspicious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trump has the BLM movement so probably won't go international.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# mmmm... shrimps....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Probably Trump is giving instructions to the White Supremacists that were protesting yesterday... they are fine people...               #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# there is this Delta variant going around, the vaccines are not 100%... they are 95% safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# and after doing nothing the title of Progressive remains... without the receipts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# wouldn't it be cheaper for the Police across the US to try to find the bad elements and fire them before all this happens?  give a bonus to people that rattle the bad apples...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# you think a mask that I use for 30 minutes while shopping is the same as a whole cover?  maybe you are not using your mask right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# good lord!
is the first time I see this and it was perfection all over...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# reopening the economy without a plan is stupid. Every expert is talking about the need for more testing and tracing. It was supposed to be done at a Federal level. Is not being done. The message from the WH is that masks are optional. All this will end killing people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Conservatives are incompatible
with human life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# what system do you want in case 2 bad guys are breaking inside your house?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# this is going to be the new normal since Republicans are going to be a minority party for years to come. The only way to reach power is through lying and violence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# is he blowing into the bagpipe 
or 
the bagpipe is blowing inside Barr and that's the reason he looks... big?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Biden should setup a Forensic team to uncover every single illegal or questionable action Trump has done for 4 years.  Findings should then be made public and very loud so Trump's supporters understand how vile he was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# love your comments, love your voice, love you face... is beautiful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# on the Anne Frank website I'm reading that Hitler blamed the Jews for losing WWI. So he put a target on all the Jews because Germany lost but it was not because he just hated Jews because of who they were.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# a higher % of Black people are dying due to the virus. I'm sure WH Stephen Miller (the confessed White Supremacist) is not telling Trump that all those people were going to vote for Biden in Nov...   #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maybe SCOTUS heard that Ted Cruz was going to present the case and they all thought "pass!" and stopped the process.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[maybe Gaddafi's prisoners were guilty too #HASHTAG# RT #USER#: #HASHTAG#'s heartfelt statement pleading to let him live life a free]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# if you are in the news business, if you are quoting a racist that didn't say "n-word" but the word itself, it should be ok with everybody to report it as it was. I only have a problem with that word when you are putting down somebody. Reporting is just reporting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# did Nikki complain when Trump and Mnuchin took control of 500 billions... no reporting on who took the money?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# can politicians that are not doctors and are implementing laws about health treatments be sue by Doctors?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# that sounds about right (nothing surprises me anymore). I bet the people in charge are Christians and Patriots #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wonder what would happen if Swami Prabodhanand dies first... complete peace?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Emma says it wasn't true.

*Fernando bows to Julia and her powers of deduction and backs up out of the room*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm sure FoxNews will play his apology, right after they show all his comments

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER#  black people look 4 yrs older than they really are... that 4 yrs old kid on the train seemed to be 8yrs #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# so arrest the guy...
how is this different than robbing a store? he broke the law.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# disagree...
President's behavior is predictable.
He will screw everything he has in front of him so he can fix it later on and take the credit... you don't give "military" anything to Trump or to small children]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# when is happy White Supremacists day?  I don't want to miss sending Stephen Miller a tweet that day #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maybe the US is concern about Muslims being jail so fast and great numbers while the US is doing it so slow... in this case US is #HASHTAG#... that can't be... US needs more ICE people, without feelings for others, to jail Muslims faster . . .   #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# all campaign contributions should instead go to a bank account and use it to pay Politicians.... #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wish the speeches will address Republicans a lot more.  Talking to Democrats is good but they already know who they are voting for. Republican voters need to feel they will be better with Biden and stop the craziness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I would agree with you in a general basis but the timing is suspicious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# HE COULD BE LYING.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# US is #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# has Spain identified the bad Spanish people that should be blame for the terrorist attack? Trump thinks is 50%-50%, right?   #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There is no time to analyze this. A comedian did bad jokes last night against some rich people  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Chauvin kept writing during closing arguments just to avoid making eye contact with the jury.   His lawyer is not taking any notes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Ratings on those systems is relative. The Orville got 18% from the "experts" in Rotten Tomatoes and 92% from the fans. 
I saw a comment in IMDB and the person was bother by the lesbians and trans and other non-sense. It had lots of "helpful review"... very suspicious to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There were a few Republican Politicians that were traitors on Jan 6th. I wonder what Trump promised them... I hope the judges issue decisions in 24 hrs to move this investigation forward and fast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# if Russians can ram US army cars in Syria and Trump says nothing, why not fire a missile? I'm sure Putin and NK are friendly and exchange ideas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# is a monstrosity.
you have to be an animal... correction... animals are very nice... a sick animal to drop phosphorus on any one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# and if the virus comes back because the antibodies seem to be wearing off, the deaths will happen every year... over and over again...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm really bother by that 1 that voted against... is it legal or not to release the papers?  someone apparently disagrees]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I guess those women in Military Bases being rape are drinking while shooting their rifles #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Democrats love looking weak.
Trump supporters love the brute force Trump had on every speech. 
Biden should stop with that whispering-into-the-mic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Jim is going to be surprise when he opens his first bank account... or orders something online... or tries to travel across a border...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# that's incredible. the progress is going to be incredible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This defense questioning is trying to link Floyd's dead to his drug use.

Many people live for many years abusing drugs. 

100% of the people with knees on their necks will die in around 10 minutes or less.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hitler did the same thing if I remember well.  They did operations without anesthesia too. Trump had Hitler's speeches on his night table.... all start making sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Isn't Israel a failed State?
they can't survive without billions of dollars from the US while the US crumbles for lack of infrastructure update.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if people think gays can handle themselves when showering with guys, shouldn't they be force to shower with women? :) #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# nice to see all these White Supremacists sticking together    #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# the President is so brave... making phone calls to areas where the military is...            #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# garbage...throwing paint on the floor is not painting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# is sad that only a 200 years old man can be put in charge of something so important.  There is nobody else?  This guy is old and looks fragile. Come on!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# this guy has some serious mental issues. Whatever his objectives are have nothing to do with helping anybody. I feel everything is a game to him and he was to win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# more and more countries hate the US, so maybe it makes sense to increase their Military :)  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# this coming from the man that confessed grabbing women's private parts is really rich.

a reporter should ask him:
"do you think Kamala will let you grab her?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# translation:
Trump: "I hate seeing BLACK LIVES MATTER painted on the street in front of one of my NY buildings"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# while the MSM talks about Kanye, they don't talk about Biden or what is wrong with Trump.

This Kanye thing might be a Trump idea to distract everybody.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# and while the MSM discusses trivial stuff, the entire Democratic System is being destroyed by Mitch McConnell 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# maybe 1890 like in this picture:n#URL# me 20 seconds to find a lot of pictures:n#URL# you having problems using Google?   (#HASHTAG#)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# years ago I read that Putin probably had around 300 billion dollars.
he might have by now close to 1 Trillion.
No wonder why Russia's economy is weak. He is extracting all the cash for himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# jeopardize what and why?
I doubt Trump did anything lawfully in general. Those calls might show Trump's possible accomplices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# in 2024, after all the Democrats in the country become angry with their party and don't vote, Republicans will regain power in 49 States... except Joe Manchin's State which will remain Blue...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# you both missed the song... awwwee :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Flynn was setup? how? as in"Flynn: Judge... I did it"... twice...
how many friends do you know that talk to Russians? Because Trump knows a lot of them. They were talking to Australian diplomats (which started everything).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# everybody knows that you can't put any mark on your ballot to identify which ballot belongs to a specific person, but Texas wants to allow people making a video of the people voting and for whom they vote.... really? 

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "people" is the same one telling a bunch of things to Trump... "people" has to be stop...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# and in what conditions are when they "survive"?
their lungs are compromised.
What's the difference between not being able to vote because you are dead or because you get too tired just by getting out of bed and you can't go to vote?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Rubio: "the Military spending is not the cause of our National debt"... is not? who is paying Military bills? Mexico? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Trump just gave permission to ruff detainees ... that's great... I can't see any consequence that will be bad for policemen  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Trump and Giuliani are old people.
I don't want to see posthumous trials.
what's going on with the Tax Returns investigation? when are charges going to be filed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trump's goal was for Blue States to do poorly in their response to Covid so he could then go and blame the Democrats. That's why he never implemented any measure to produce PPE and testing. And he has been doing that: blaming Democratic Governors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Evie's laughter is all I need from this show :) and I got it again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think Trump should walk around of an ICU with Covid patients to show all those Democrats how immune he is to the virus... nn#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# get out of here... rich people doing that?... that can't be...   #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# To me the first sign of force is when Palestinians are kick out from their own homes. Israel is doing that to provoke. Then they go inside their Mosque and use force. If Palestinians do nothing they will keep doing something to provoke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# why is #USER# is giving comments on TV about the far-left?  she lost her election because she ran as a wanna-be-conservative. Why is a Red State going to vote for somebody with a D if they have the choice of a real Republican?  Progressive ideas have appeal from Ds and Rs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that's crazy talking :) #HASHTAG# RT #USER#: CAN a Woman like #HASHTAG#, talk #HASHTAG# AND be a #HASHTAG#? #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Helene was making wrong statements. Covid is not spreading ONLY because of the unvaccinated. Vaccinated people can get the virus and spread it to others too. EVERYBODY should be wearing masks. I'm even questioning if the people around the table discussing the virus were too close]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# hey Mitch: you are White and some States want to eliminate voting on Sundays on Black churches... you are racist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# the company that goes up for 4 minutes and comes back should be fine for wasteful...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Apparently she is a tough woman... and tried to stop an industrial fan using her bare hands... lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think the dysfunction is Trump's plan. He can always go back and blame every single Democrat in charge of those States.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wonder why the long convoy hasn't been attack yet.  If you attack the first vehicles it will freeze the whole thing. Just do it when they go by a near part of the road.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Biden should be asking for 3 additional debates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# is this picture right? I don't see Ivanka  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Can't wait to see #USER# attacking those self-absorb Middle of America farmers.   #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Facebook probably caused thousands of people that helped breaking into Congress.  But I have serious suspicions that Politicians, militia groups and questionable friends that Trump has were involved and I doubt they have Facebook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER#

Trump enjoyed watching the Insurrection.
He probably will enjoy seeing Ukrainian soldiers executed by Russian troops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# there is a complain against Kulvinder for spreading misinformation. 
There are thousands of doctors. You can't trust one.  You have to listen to the entire group... Health Canada.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "ignorant clods" sounds like Trump to me :)   

I thought you misunderstood my "so clear tweet" :P]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>