<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You really think a business can fire a striking union worker? It's hard to fire a union wordier if they aren't striking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# No om is mad a black women is on the court. You can't understand people are pointing out Biden's racism by using a black woman for political gain.  Do you not know that a republican appointed Thomas and support him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Then don;t believe it. I told you, that is your problem, not mine. I wonder why democrats refuse to believe the virus is airborne.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is often laughable, but rarely funny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thee is very little justice in America? You must live in a democrat run city to think that. I hear the DA there are pretty crooked. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Heh. Topics like this are hard. I can often understand how things are seen from different POVs. Have a g0od night. I get time differences. I talk a lot with someone on a different continent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats think a COVID death is more important than a cancer death.  Die of cancer and you are forced to cremate becasue it's cheap. Die of COVID and you get a fancy funeral. Democrats have no idea what equality means. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Democrat "experts" said it was impossible to have a vaccine by this month. Yet Warp Speed managed to do that. You have a severe case of TDS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# NYC police are probably trained to run like they do in Florida when a school shooter drops in. nnGuns are evil. you can't have cops carrying them around children. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controlling Political Language 
#URL#

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm attacked by greenies when I say we need to lower CO2 emissions, but point out that wind and solar can't do the job. And the attacks get really aggressive when I say the world isn't ending in 10,50, or 100 years. 

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's not me who says that, there are elected leaders who say they want their party to be the only one.Odd to think that my talking about what some leaders say is totalitarian thinking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Who got fame and fortune?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep, just like she showed up at the cabbie hunger strike and then pretended not to eat. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I was against Trump spending so much.Trump alsao signed a bill that sent money to people for not working.

Those tax breaks actually increased revenues,. Businesses shouldn't be taxed becasue the consumer pays those taxes at the end of the day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats passed  Religious Freedom Act in 93 that gave weight to Hobby Lobby ruling. LOL #HASHTAG##HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is there a union , were you treating employees badly and underpaying them?Or maybe you just wanted to feed money to your union donors. This sounds like a scam. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man on a basking show said he liked Mexican chocolate because he was half Mexican.I am half Dutch ,hate windmills, and have no idea what Dutch people eat. Why do so many feel the need to announce their race or heritage?Does it make them feel special?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching the opening ceremony of the Olympics, something stood out. There are a lot of racist countries that had only one race on the team. Oh wait, it's only racist if something is all white. No white nations are allowed by the left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One was  a Russian scientist. But there have been others. A  theory is the solar system entrees a cosmic cloud every few thousand years that causes the cooling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You said you wear only kn95, those are Chinese.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love when democrats eat their own. The movie/play Washington Heights celebrates Hispanics. Democrats want it banned becasue there was no black Hispanics. It probably should be banned since anything celebrating a single race is racist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who thinks #HASHTAG# aren't the  same racist of the 40's, look at product packaging. They have gotten rid of all people of color  on packages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those evil capitalist rich people. #HASHTAG#. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes most are  waste of time. I watch that one yesterday and nothing was learned. All I ev4r see is two parties playing politics.  Neither one cares about the truth. especially democrats. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've used space heaters my entire life. so I don't see that as an issue. All people living in space don't agree on temperature so often a heater is needed. I think the space heater thing was just used for political gain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The housing bubble was created  under Clinton. You can't give mortgages to people who can barely make payments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I still don't understand why me and other poor people have to pay off AOC's debt when she is a millionaire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You sounds like a typical democrat who wants to put people in prison becasue you don;t like their speech. Thank you for proving all my points about democrats. 

I bet you still think cloth and paper masks work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# So yoy hand them an excuse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually she didn't address inflation, all she talked about was price increases. She was right about finding the root cause, and that is democrat policies driving up energy prices.  Her social spending would cause more inflation. She is right about not increasing interest rates. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER#  writers are why the series ended. They did not know that super heroes have secret identities to protect friends and families. At the end you made Supergirl look selfish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ruling that the Babit shooting was justified, sets precedent.  Police can now shoot anyone for almost any reason. All the officer has to be is scared and protecting something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Hitler was 80 years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Also he bill says that you can only drive so far to a polling place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My only issue with any weapon is the noise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must not have watched the video where it is clear that he was defending himself from rioters attacking him. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Obviously they are getting around that. Just the knowledge that a bill will pass can be worth millions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does #USER# allow Juan William to tell lies. Trump did say on #HASHTAG# he took the vaccine and urged others to also take it.

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# LOL look in the mirror.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You are a scientist but has no idea what an airborne virus is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think wearing  a full bodysuit will stop men from looking, you don't know much about men. Those are skin tight and actually show more of your body, the body parts that men like looking at. Days ago 
#USER# was happy Billie Elish showed her body.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does this mean she is going to eliminate property taxes and otehr things that makes it cost so much to live in NYC? I bet she raises taxes that makes it more expensive. Anytime you see someone use the word "equity", run, becasue no one can guarantee equal outcome. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Maybe his mistake was letting governors run their own states and that's why so many people died in NYC nursing homes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I said the #HASHTAG#  ruling demanding vaccinations at medical facilities that accept medicare would prevent people form getting medical treatment. It is already happening. A doctor refuses to force his staff to be vaxxed. His elderly patients have to look elsewhere for treatment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I thought that wors  was banned by democrats?

Hmmm, so you think taxes and regulations don't drive up prices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# To clarify this a bit, it was an exhibition at the Olympics, not part of the games. I've seen this done in later years somewhere, maybe the 50's or 50's. Could it have been part of some international competition?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dem,autocrats especially following that path. They are demonizing white people so when the t9me comes to round us up most people will accept it, even large groups of whites. They teach hate of the US so they can end it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right, he wasn't on trial for doing something stupid. If stupidity was a crime everyone on th streets that night would be in prison.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Polling places are set up by districts, not cities. Every district has a polling place. I just got a notice mine is being moved from a mile away to 5 miles away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That is definitely interference. The more dollars they print the less value it holds. You can also look at the dollar as being a commodity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# please try following the science. Science tells us that people who had the virus have more protection than the vaccine provides.  Some people have natural protection. And people who have been vaccinated can  infect others. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More innocent Muslims just stressed out. #HASHTAG##HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Then what are they AI robots that run themselves?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Give me the exact wording and the formula.  I really doubt counties with more than 1 million people are all democrats. I doubt that all counties with more than 1 million people all vote democrat. If the language is about counties, that includes rural voters who likely vote GOP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats are the height of #HASHTAG#
They say vigilantism is wrong and then they say #HASHTAG#  is guilty becasue the last 2 shot were vigilantes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because democrats are in bed with the drug cartels, fentyinal crossing the border has doubled under Biden. This drug is basically poison. It's hard to know how many people have died becasue of our open border.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Have you ever heard of inflation and why it's a bad thing? Do you realize there is a world economy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That has nothing to do with your comment. You said capitalism is violent. I told you about another fire at a government owned building.  Government buildings tend to be in worse shape. Don;t blame freedom for democrat city problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've never listened to Rogan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# None of these laws contain poll taxes or literary tests. Who told you this nonsense?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sure, I have biases. I have biases against government and politicians off all parties. I question everything. I accept nothing as fact until I view it through difference sources and see what actually makes sense. Once you admit you have biases, then you can see the truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOLOL love the #HASHTAG#  roast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes that is part of the problem. But the elected people complaining about the rule have not introduced a bill to legalize the drug. It is against federal law to possess or consume pot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right, Muslims never did anything wrong, it's all a US govt conspiracy #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No assault rifles were used in those crimes, yet democrats use them to try and ban guns they wrongly label assault rifles. They also used these crimes to create hate against white people even though only one crime was done by a white person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I said mostly spot on. Let's use COVID as an example. FNC hand on people represent both sides. The ones who said most masks are useless were correct, but the professionals saying that were not allowed on CNN and banned form speaking publicly. Now the CDC confirms what they said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nope, they migrated here from other parts of the world. They have only been he3r about 35k years. There is some new evidence there were people here before them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You seem to be saying here that rules  only discriminate against democrats. I'm sorry, but that just seems impossible.  In fact, during the lat election it seemed to be the opposite, that since most polls are controlled by democrats, republicans were discriminated against.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# SNAP is food stamps for children. That is a separate program.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That is typical for all big pharma to do. They don't go to jail becasue it's not illegal. The ones who should go to jail are the doctors who are corrupt.Doctors take an oath to do no harm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ROTFL, you fell for that lie. So sad you believe anything they tell you. You honestly believe that antifa and BLM committed no violence. I shouldn't laugh becasue that is beyond sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Says the woman who complained for years the election was stole from her. Election fraud only exists when it hurts democrats. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats are feeding our enemies things to use against us. Because of what democrats say, the US can never question any country's stand on human rights. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes hey do have equipment to detect leaks. What might unknowingly leak is far below what leaks naturally into the atmosphere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet it doesn't apply to non-Americans who cross the border illegally. That is pure insanity. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hear doctors anonymously say they are afraid to ask questions for fear of losing their license. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yea, lets put druggies in prison and let dirty politicians and bankers go free #HASHTAG##USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That;s exactly what I said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm probably talking to one. I know exactly what racism is. I grew up in democrat created Jim Crow era.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I;'m sure Russia disagrees with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There can't be sexual harassment in the California state Capitol because we know all democrats respect women and minorities. LOLOL #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# called one of his black advisors, "boy". Can you imagine the chaos if Trump had done  the same thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BLM activist honored by Obama foundation tried to assassinate Louisville  mayoral candidate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is all about fear and control.  Fear to control and they ell grasp for anything that makes them look like they are doing something to help.  We  know the lockdowns didn't work, they might have made things worse. They wanted to be able to say their actions saved lives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AOC does have mental issues, but it has nothing to do with Trump. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I just hope you have bought your ticket to Ukraine to help them fight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You can get a landline or a cheap cell. You can go to the library to use the intent or go to the unemployment office to see what jobs are available.  Walk around and you will see help wanted signs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Those places wanted independence from Ukraine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# So basically, do as you are told or shut up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insane democrats keep telling us there cannot be limits on immigration. I bet they change their mind when the US has a billion people, most starving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quit importing cheap labor and wages will go up. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm just wondering why its not being used on the convoy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# SCOTUS is a p0litical organization.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New democrat rule, only white people can loot. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So you want socialism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Where do you live that people are like that? Where I live poor people are helped to get an ID to vote. They are even driven to the polls. Helping people is how you solve the problem, you don't do it by saying people don't need an ID for anything bc a few poor people can;t get one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So you think Israel should be wiped off the map. Aren't you a nice person. Seems odd you are a Hitler supporter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ys I said 35k years, that is thousands. There were people before them as science is learning. Natives did not originate here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Heh the curse might open them up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Study history, it has been changing for millions of years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are absoluely 100% wrong on this. The vaccine doesn't prevent people from getting and passing the virus. It actual helps create stronger mutations. Natural immunity is far better at slowing and possibly stopping e virus. Science 101 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just when you think democrats can't get more insane, we learn they think tax cuts create recessions. They actually believe letting people keep their money wrecks the economy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yea, this is going to make cops less jittery when dealing with blacks.n#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stupid republican on TV wanting to send troops to Ukraine. And apparently we already have 200 California national guard there. The plague isn't enough, we need a world war so democrats can hold power forever.

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rand Paul, Tim Scott to name two.. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ok so Bo was just a bought slave. Now tell me what hate Trump spread and when did he make fun of less fortunate people? Almost all of his listeners were lower middle class. You clearly never listened to his show. Again, he was not a very religious person for most of his life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# has ruined the One More Thing segment by turning it into a self promotion segment. 

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# f you look at the statistics, a major factor is singe parent families. In cities you see a lot of black children say they joined the gang because they wanted a family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No according to th3 reports I have heard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those who don't realize he mistake, the last CO2 should be hydrogen.  or H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The how come you have no idea what airborne viruses are?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrat:" Black people are put in prison for doing nothing."

Next day.

Black repeat offender who is out on bail for two separate crimes drives through parade, killing and injuring many people.

Why was this violent man still on the street?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# LOL I've ye to see a debate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh I know. They are just doing this to try and get voters. A true propaganda show just like the 2 impeachments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I simply tweeted it. Do you always read tweets and accept them or reject them without researching for yourself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I said vaxxed or test negative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China is banning "sissy men"   from TV ahows, so we can expect them to disappear from American movies and shows. Sadly, democrats will embrace the idea becasue it's China.

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Twitter agreement and business contracts are different universes. You do read a business contract and if you can't understand it, you hire someone to translate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm curious, why would you want to make it easier for conservatives to ban abortion and gay marriage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It does require people to identify themselves. In fact, voter registration is an accepted form of ID. Do you think it would be ok to get benefits without any identification? With no ID people could sign up to receive checks under 15 different names. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats think black lives matter more than white and Asian lives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cordilleras keep proving th3y are hypocrites, they are defending riot police when it;s a protests they hate. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# it is not unusual for people new to driving in the mountains to burn up their brakes becasue they don't know how to use the transmission to control speed. 

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats  know as much about economics as a 1st grader knows about physics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# why are you encouraging people to be morbidly obese by praising that woman for posting a nude photo? That is not a real body, that is a body that puts people at risk of dying. Obesity is a huge factor in COVID deaths. This show cares more about being PC than lives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You mean as the child dies from a heart failure or cancer? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I actually think very few people know much about socialism and communism.  You and I have talked before and you have a misconception about both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's actually hurting becasue you have to print the money and that causes inflation. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The 13th Amendment solved he problem of legal slavery in the US. 

The 2nd Amendment solved the problem of tyranny in the US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You just can't resist talking down to people can you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is going pretty low. Just becasue yo hate fissile fuels you are accusing Americans of killing native women.  I have known a lot of oil workers and they are not murderers. 

Native women going missing in Canada is a huge problem and it is believe to be native men selling them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awwe poor Muslims being discriminated against. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DOD did admit UFOs are real. They didn't say they are alien or dimensional. they said they have no idea what they are,.  They are Unidentified Flying Objects, #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millions of people out of work, a strategic pipeline hacked, war in Israel, and she is still fixated on the Capitol riot.  All she does is play politics. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Where does it harm society? Just so you know, I'm, not talking about the extremes the left takes, just actual transsexuals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Do you realize the US and EU have 0oligarchies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yea all of us southerners are getting knocked up by our cousins. #HASHTAG##USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If you say no one says she deserved to die, you haven;t read the crazies leftists on twitter. And Sicknick did not die at the Capitol. He died 2 days later from a stroke. The autopsy said it was not a homicide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# He is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm shocked, all the questioners are democrats #HASHTAG##HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No one was standing on anyone's neck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do #HASHTAG# close their eyes to the horror Hamas does in Israel? Is it to them just about white vs brown? It surely isn't about facts. I guess their old KKK days are still in their hearts, they hate Jews. 

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Guess what, you can find pics of every president with Saudis becasue we have to work with them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# All th3y had to do was kill the,. 90lb woman to end the problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 3rd deadliest day in a 20 year war.

#HASHTAG#  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aren't pretty much all democrat mayors up north socialists? Being a socialist is nothing to brag about. That means you love controlling people. Socialist is the opposite of freedom. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one tried to overthrow rte US government. This kind of slanderous speech should have consequential.  How do democrats keep getting away with this rhetoric, #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This proves BLM is a fanatical group. The founder is defending Smullett by saying you can never believe police. I wonder if they are going to burn any cities over this.

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You really missed the point. 60% of all electrolytic is provided by fossil fuels. So these cars are really running on fossil fuels. Saying coal is just a snarky way of saying tha with less words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Tea, but  the bosses don't fight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thee people think being a doctor or mechanic is the same as making a bed.  I think these people need to go see a maid when they get sick. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can see why the audience was bored, just two women hopping around looking mean and doing nothing. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It as democrats who suddenly stopped voting across the country at about the same time.

Are banks racist for requiring an ID to open an account? Are grocery stores racist for requiring an ID to cash a payroll check?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Listen, I didn't save her useless tweet and don't care to search for it. You need to go take a chill pill and calm down. LOL I am more interested in the fact she is now starving yourself to death so cabbies can get some free money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# is just learning lobbyists write most of the bills she passes? This is why republicans won't pass a lot of democrat bills, they are full of crap like you're com0laining about. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And we would still be executing people for daring to say the Earth is not the center of the universe. But things haven't changed a lot, people are going to jail for saying masks don't work or that everyone doesn't need a vaccine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Apparently climate change doesn't matter when it comes to politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# She does concentrate on a few corporations, but over all she claims to hate them all saying they are greedy and take money from the poor. 

AOC did not get elected on grass roots money, she was given lots by large PACs such as Justice Democrats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why do you think elected officials shouldn't be held liable for taking bribes? Why do you think those bribing should not be held liable, You just want to cannibalize the rich?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# in case you forgot the brow thing. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That actually happened, they were arrested.

You still don't answer my question. Why was she shot and not some big scary man? She is 5'2".  I saw a big man with horns standing on the floor and he wasn't shot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# is promoting violence. You should be sued for causing all the damage and lives lost when those riots begin. And it's nearly possible for anyone to get a fair trial when shows like this declare people guilty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have known a lot of people like that. I had a close friend with two children who was basically a grifter. she knew how to do all those things.

Democrats don't get we want to help people, but the current system creates generational freeloaders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That was well into the war.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good paying jobs that tax payers will pay for. This is a pyramid scheme. How odd that only unionized companies will benefit from this tax money. This is clearly a payoff to unions so they can donate more to #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If US military can cure Ebola in Africa, maybe we should fill hospitals in US with soldiers to cut cost #HASHTAG##HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The national guard is being called in becasue they expect leftwing terrorists attacks if #HASHTAG#  is found innocent.These peo0ple are why the boy was armed, to protect himself from terrorists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What good is a debt ceiling if it's not really a limit? And I guess #HASHTAG# have been lying when they say these bills are paid for. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I understand the problem of politicians being bought by corporations. That just means we should vote those people out, not limit the ability to donate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# your hosts need to get educated on biology. It is far better to have babies in your 20's than when you're 40. Risk get higher the older you get.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It was the government making the contracts.

I do have a question, something I don;t understand. Why are medallion holding cabbies joining unions, so they can go on strike against themselves?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 1%

This is how much in the US. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It'-+s not an invasion if they vote for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep. Biden did say, "If you don't vote for me, you aren't black."

According to dem terminology, Ted Cruz us a person of color.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't doubt racist things have been said. I don;t doubt there have been some racists on the show. I am saying there has never eve been an all white alliance formed just to kick out the black people. There has been no open racism like that until; now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow, you think someone being trans does harm to you? I'd love to hear details on that. Were you ever bullied in your life? Go ask any one who has been they will tell you how it affects them all their life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nothing will change your mind. You will see this as white vs black and you have said Treyvon was killed because he was black. Yea, them Hispanics are hunting down and killing black people because they hate POC. LOL. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER#  put out a fake documentary where Baby Wallace says he gets out of the car and is shocked to see the noose. At the time he said a crew showed him a pic on his phone. The loop, like in other garages, had been there for years.

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Then go read books by Thomas Sowel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A single mother with three children not working qualifies for welfare. why does she need special attention? Also, where is the father and why isn't he paying child support? Lots of questions here that should be asked. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right, all Abbott did is tell us what will happen, he isn't ordering anything.

Abbott had nothing to do with the power grid issues, An independent committee controls all that.  Apparently the greenies controlling th power grid didn't expect cold weather because of global warming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I actually have resd the twitter agreement word for word. I have owned many websites and had to read agreements and laws so I knew not to violate them.  Not reading a half million dollar contract is stupidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Writing what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER#  the lefty show talked to the host the other day. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Compared to liberty. I remember when democrats protested to be free of government. Now they protest begging for government control of their lives. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I spent my life troubleshooting and know the only way to permanently solve a problem is to find the root problem. To lower crime rooted murders we need to remove the crime. I'd say most crime murders are drug related.  Legalize all drugs or maybe just the least deadly ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have been questioning why oil prices are up and why gas prices doubled.  We know for sure some increase in oil prices and inflation is the cause. I think thee is more to it. Weakening of the dollar has to be a major contributor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I'm just telling you the history of those regions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or you could just produce electrify with nuclear energy. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Do you watch anything not CNN or MSNBC? Don't listen tome becasue I will tell you things you don't want to hear.  And one more time, you are not worth the effort to dig up info you won't believe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER#  if the US is so evil, why would  Afghanis come here? It sounds like the writers and producers of this show thinks the US is evil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No clue, but we can only hope. Maybe they took some of the homeless illegals home with them. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Racist Democrats, I'm shocked #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like you want a more communist country. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It died when conservatives took it over and people found out they couldn't change corrupt Washington.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh cool so you agree that all 30 million illegals should be deported. So you don't think sex workers have a right to do what they do? You must not really be a democrat or someone who cares about women's rights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They have been melting every since the ice age ended. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how arrogant democrats are. They are openly admitting they are working with social media to silence people they disagree with. This is exactly what fascists do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Hip hop has some music, rap doesn't.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>