<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The Final Dispatch of Father Hudgins, a Lansing priest who died in a road accidentFr. David Hudgins, a priest of the Diocese of Lansing who died in a car accident Jan. 3, 2022. / Diocese of Lansing

Lansing, Mich.,  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope Francis sends condolences for death of European Parliament presidentPope Francis meets with David Sassoli, president of the European Parliament, June 25, 2021. / Vatican Media.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope Francis removes from Vatican doctrine office archbishop who is believed to have banned same-sex blessingsROME (AP) — Pope Francis took the first step Monday to reorganize the Vatican’s powerful doctrine office, removing the No.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cardinal Marx ‘shocked and ashamed’ by Munich abuse reportCardinal Reinhard Marx, pictured in June 2016. / Degreezero via Wikimedia (CC BY-SA 4.0).

Munich, Germany, Jan 20, 2022 / 09:20 am (CNA).  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christ Has Redeemed Our Suffering‘The Deep Places’ book cover A personal review of ‘The Deep Places’ by Ross Douthat National Catholic Register

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook ‘Kills’ Charity’s Petition Against Forced Marriage of Christian Women and GirlsNew report from Aid to the Church in Need. “We are horrified that our campaign which aims to help suffering women has been censored in such a

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice Sonia Sotomayor: the Bullying Pro-ChoicerLbcstud562 Justice Sonia Sotomoayor pictured during her visit with law students on March 12, 2013. COMMENTARY: During oral argument in ‘Dobbs v.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mary’s revolutionary MagnificatA Reflection for the Wednesday of the Fourth Week of Advent“Mary remained with Elizabeth about three months and then returned to her home” (Lk 1:56).

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘We all weep for these victims’: Nigerian cardinal responds after gunmen kill 200 peopleNigerian Cardinal John Onaiyekan speaks at the International Eucharistic Congress in Budapest, Hungary, Sept. 9, 2021. / Daniel Ibáñez/CNA.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simple Advent Revisited: As Christmas nears, rejoice and reorient toward true joyThe third Sunday of Advent is known as Gaudete Sunday. (Pixabay/Gerhard G.)Editor's Note: For the 2021 Advent season, EarthBeat is revisiting  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NABRE: New American Bible Revised Edition Kindle Edition

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singing through Advent, in praise of the Mother of the RedeemerDetail from "Virgin Mary Annunciate" (1431-33) by Fra Angelico 
 The liturgy for the Fourth Sunday of Advent has a distinctly Marian dimension to it  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope meets children assisted by Santa Marta DispensaryBy Vatican News staff writer A festive Christmas atmosphere marked the Pope’s Sunday morning’s meeting with a group of children, their parents and  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oklahoma governor’s clemency of Julius Jones took ‘tremendous courage,’ Archbishop Coakley saysArchbishop Paul S. Coakley preaching during Mass in the cathedral in 2021. / Archdiocese of Oklahoma City

Washington, D.C.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Archdiocese of Cincinnati to reduce 208 parishes to 57 ‘families of parishes’CINCINNATI (AP) — Cincinnati’s archdiocese has unveiled a final restructuring plan to consolidate its churches and schools that serve nearly half a

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: The spiritual capital punishment of faithful CatholicsAltar with chalice and Missal in the Basilica of St Nicholas in Rome (t0m15/us.fotolia.com)  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope Francis to struggling parents: Don’t condemn your kids. Pray to St. Joseph instead.Below is the text of Pope Francis’ weekly Wednesday audience, delivered on Jan. 26, #URL#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Bishops Try to Keep Focus on Eucharist, Not Politicians, in New DocumentJulio Cortez (Clockwise from left) Bishop Andrew Cozzens of tthe Archdiocese of Saint Paul and Minneapolis attends a news conference at the Fall

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pushing for more papal pressersPope Francis answers questions from journalists aboard his flight from Athens, Greece, to Rome Dec. 6, 2021.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catholic Bishops of Ukraine and Poland appeal to leaders to refrain from warBy Linda Bordoni “It is with concern that we learn the news that the recentrounds of talks between Russia and the West have not led to an  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Newsnn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home as Haven: Cultivating a Christ-Centered Domestic Church‘That house was a perfect house, whether you like food or sleep, or story-telling or singing, or just sitting and thinking best, or a pleasant

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catholic Priest in Nigeria Shot Dead on Christmas EveFather Adeleke, who was in his late 30s, had been ordained a priest in 2017. The murder and kidnapping of Christians in Nigeria have multiplied in

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infographic: Annual audit tracks increase in allegations of historic abuse incidentsThe latest annual audit of children protection sponsored by the U.S. Conference of Catholic Bishops’ Secretariat of Child and Youth Protection,nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former priest withdraws pleas over child sex abuse after judge’s rejection of sentencing agreementFreeBirdPhotos / Shutterstock.

Detroit, Mich., Jan 12, 2022 / 16:39 pm (CNA).  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘A Life of Service to God in Jesus Christ’: Churchman Reflects on Witnessing Work of 6 Popes and History in the MakingThis memoir recounts many stories of papal history through an eyewitness.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couple to Couple League Launches New Fertility WebsiteStarry night Studies show that Millennial and Generation Z women are hesitant to embrace hormonal contraception and desire more natural methods tonn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Pro-Lifers Know About the Women Getting Abortions in America — and How to Reach ThemMANDEL NGAN ‘Love Them Both’ was proclaimed by pro-lifers during the March for Life on Jan. 21 in Washington, D.C.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope Francis: ‘I accepted the resignation of the archbishop of Paris not on the altar of truth but on the altar of hypocrisy’On the flight back from Athens to Rome, Pope Francis surprised journalists by stating that he had accepted the resignation of

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LA archdiocese sues local school district in dispute over allocation of federal fundsThe sun sets at the U.S. Supreme Court building in Washington Nov. 29, 2021. (CNS photo/Leah Millis, Reuters)   
  Los Angeles — The Archdiocese of  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gaudete Sunday: The Preaching of St. John the BaptistPieter Bruegel the Elder, “The Preaching of St. John,” 1566 John was a prophet not because he spoke, but because God spoke through him.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asking the Right QuestionsGO: You’re both Catholic believers, though your faiths arose in different contexts and are inflected in different ways.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here’s what a young Syrian refugee is hoping for this ChristmasMajed, a Syrian refugee living in Zahlé, Lebanon. / Aid to the Church in Need.

Zahle, Lebanon, Dec 14, 2021 / 13:00 pm (CNA).  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ukrainian Catholic bishops in Canada urge prayers for UkraineBy Lisa Zengarini As Ukraine endures the threat of Russian invasion, the Ukrainian Greek Catholic Bishops in Canada join with Pope Francis and the  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Newsnn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope: Caring for people with disabilities is a ‘sharing of gifts’By Devin Watkins As the Seraphic Institute of Assisi celebrates the 150th anniversary of its foundation, a delegation of staff and students traveled  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NI Bishops disappointed by recent rejection of Abortion BillBy Lisa Zengarini Catholic Bishops of Northern Ireland have expressed "grave concern" over the recent rejection by the NI Assembly in Stormont of an  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New committee aims to build up political candidates who support religious liberty for allAmerican flag and Church. / Quinn Dombrowski via Flickr (CC BY-SA 2.0).
Denver Newsroom, Jan 19, 2022 / 09:52 am (CNA).  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The solution to the culture wars on campus? Radical inclusion.This article is a response to “Will Catholic universities survive the upheaval in higher education?nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNA Staff, Jul 16, 2020 / 04:14 pm (CNA).- Pro-life advocates are calling on the Irish government to respond to statistics indicating a “shocking” level of abortions performed in the first year following the legalization of the procedure in the country. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope Francis was right about pets and kidsPope Francis caused a Category 5 brouhaha on Jan. 6 during what was an otherwise thoroughly ordinary general audience at the Vatican.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your thoughts on NCR&amp;#HASHTAG#;s 2021 newsmaker of the yearNCR chose Los Angeles Archbishop José Gomez as our 2021 Newsmaker of the Year.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 50 years, Gutiérrez&amp;#HASHTAG#;s &amp;#HASHTAG#;A Theology of Liberation&amp;#HASHTAG#; still &amp;#HASHTAG#;What&amp;#HASHTAG#;s Going On&amp;#HASHTAG#;Dominican Fr.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Christmas — Past, Present and FuturePublic Domain Leopold Graf von Kalckreuth (1855-1928), “Children by the Christmas Tree” Are you set to have the Best Christmas Ever?

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philippines cancels Black Nazarene procession again, citing COVID-19 Procession of the Black Nazarene in Manila, January 7, 2010. / Denvie #URL# (CC BY 2.0).

Washington, D.C.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SDG Says FarewellSDG: "When I think about my time at the Register, I think, above all, of movies and reviews that, for me, define my work and my adventures in

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope Francis: Being ‘properly informed’ on COVID-19 vaccines is a ‘human right’Pope Francis meets members of the Catholic Factchecking consortium at the Vatican’s Clementine Hall, Jan. 28, 2022 / Vatican Media.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: Catholics injured in deadly parade crash in Waukesha, WisconsinCatholics and others were injured, and at least four people killed, when a car drove through a Christmas parade in Waukesha, Wisconsin, on Nov. 21.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fear Is a Bad TeacherIn The Politics of Persecution, Mitri Raheb, a Lutheran Palestinian pastor from Bethlehem, makes clear the aim of his thought-provoking book:

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hong Kong bishop consecrated in Cathedral of Immaculate ConceptionBishop Stephen Chow’s ordination as bishop in Hong Kong’s Cathedral of the Immaculate Conception Dec.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vatican cardinal complains the pope’s prosecutors asked about his sex lifeVATICAN CITY (AP) — The lone cardinal indicted in the Vatican’s big fraud and embezzlement trial has issued a formal protest to the court claiming

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brick by brick, this Lego master and disability advocate is building up the ChurchJohn Kraemer lays a brick while constructing his latest church. / Catholic Diocese of Saginaw

Denver Newsroom, Dec 20, 2021 / 11:19 am (CNA).  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From 1996: James Martin, SJ, on the stories of East African refugeesEditors’ Note: In this article from May 18, 1996, James Martin, S.J., who at the time was studying at Weston Jesuit School of Theology in Cambridge. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From ‘Ted Lasso’ to ‘Squid Game’ to ‘Midnight Mass,’ 2021 was a strange but wonderful year in TVThe year 2021 was a strange one for TV. The best shows in 2020 seemed to bewhatever got you through the pandemic—your favorite sitcom or sci-fi

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy are peacemakers who wake up the rest of usPope Francis greets Archbishop John Wester of Santa Fe, New Mexico, during an audience with U.S.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope Francis names new auxiliary bishop for Saint Paul-Minneapolis archdioceseBishop-elect Joseph A. Williams. / Courtesy of the Archdiocese of Saint Paul and Minneapolis.

Vatican City, Dec 10, 2021 / 07:40 am (CNA).

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The horrors of Communism and the resilience of faith in AlbaniaAlbanian poster in 1978: "Marxism-Leninism: Victorious flag" (Image: RobertSchediwy/Wikipedia)
 Although all Communist regimes persecuted religion  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vatican ambassador urges &amp;#HASHTAG#;concrete action&amp;#HASHTAG#; to protect civilians amid armed conflictA group of women in Beirut are seen near Mohammad Al-Amin mosque Nov. 9, 2019.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faith lost and found at YaleIn his 2004 novel I Am Charlotte Simmons, the late “Gonzo journalist” Tom Wolfe chronicles the story of Charlotte Simmons, a naïve young girl from a  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope appeals for help for victims of Typhoon Rai in the PhilippinesBy Linda Bordoni “I express my closeness to the population of the Philippines, struck by a strong typhoon” Pope Francis said, invoking the “Santo  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Notable moments from the Supreme Court arguments over Mississippi abortion lawPro-life advocates demonstrate in front of the US Supreme Court in Washington, DC, on December 1, 2021.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#’sHealthOrganization

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington, D.C. Newsroom, Jun 3, 2020 / 05:00 pm (CNA).- Pro-life advocates must speak out in defense of all human life–including issues of racial justice and deaths at the hands of police, a prominent pro-life lawmaker told CNA Wednesday.  #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French Bishops urge discernment ahead of presidential electionsBy Devin Watkins France’s presidential elections are around the corner withthe first round to be held on 10 April, and a second round on 24 April if  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kenya: Funeral Mass held for 32 choir members of the Mwingi bus tragedy.Vatican News English Africa Service. On Thursday, Kenya’s Diocese of Kitui held a joint requiem Mass for the victims.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope celebrates Vespers for Feast of the Conversion of St PaulBy Christopher Wells Representatives of the Ecumenical Patriarchate of Constantinople, the Archbishop of Canterbury, and other Christian churches and  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[125 employees of German Catholic Church come out as queer in joint initiativeActivists carrying a rainbow flag and a banner with an image of Mary and the Christ Child attend the second "Marzahn Pride" march in Berlin July 17,  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope Francis to youth in Greece: Don’t be ‘prisoners of the cell phone’Pope Francis meets with young people at St. Dionysius School of the Ursuline Sisters in Maroussi, Athens, Dec. 6, 2021. / Vatican Media.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A stolen election, an insurrection, a big lie: Can Catholics unify a country engaged in an uncivil war?Now we are engaged in a great uncivil war. Politics quickly succumbs to thepolemics of rage and recrimination—so much so that reconciling our

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covid-19 restrictions move pro-life rallies online. Here’s what California is doing.A global pandemic cannot stop pro-life advocates from marking the anniversary of Roe v. Wade.nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chile legalizes same-sex marriageSame-sex wedding cake. / Sara Valenti/Shutterstock

Santiago, Chile, Dec 9, 2021 / 10:53 am (CNA).
Chile’s National Congress passed Dec.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cardinal Tomasi Discusses the Reforms to the Order of MaltaCardinal Silvano Tomasi is the papal delegate assigned to Order of Malta&amp;#HASHTAG#;s process of reform.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catholic pro-choice activists project messages onto DC basilica in protestMessages voicing support for abortion rights are projected onto the Basilica of the National Shrine of the Immaculate Conception in Washington, D.C.,  #HASHTAG#://t.co/CzO46uVZs5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekday Mass will start Monday 6/22 &amp;amp; Weekend Masses on Saturday, 6/27 &amp;amp; Sunday, 6/28June 19, 2020  We have wonderful news! Starting Monday, June 22nd, we will have Mass at 8:30 a.m.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[St. Paul, Minn., Jul 27, 2020 / 01:01 pm (CNA).- Some pro-life advocates say that the recent push for racial equality in the US can be an awakening to the importance of their cause, and how the two problems can go hand-in-hand.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington D.C., Mar 10, 2020 / 02:00 pm (CNA).- Pro-life advocates praised the Secretary General of the Organization of American States (OAS) Tuesday for stating that the right to life should be protected from conception.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need new ways of telling Jesus’ birth story to our children—and to ourselvesI cannot remember a time when I did not know the nativity story. I loved feeling that I was a part of it, too: During Advent, my nighttime prayers as

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marquette Diocese&amp;#HASHTAG#;s LGBTQ restrictions blasted as &amp;#HASHTAG#;cruel policy&amp;#HASHTAG#;A banner hangs outside St. Francis of Assisi Church in New York City following an annual Pre-Pride Festive Mass June 26.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New book invites readers to build better relationships with our own bodies(Unsplash/Milada Vigerova)   
  "Take this, all of you, and eat of it: Thisis my body, which will be given up for you," a priest says in persona  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Podcast: What you need to know about Pope Benedict’s record on sexual abuseAn investigation into sexual abuse in the Archdiocese of Munich and Freising released Jan.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes, you should thank God for failureA Reflection for the Friday of the First Week of Advent: Memorial of St. Francis Xavier“As Jesus passed by, two blind men followed him, crying out,

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[R.I.P. John Padberg, a Jesuit historian and a historian of JesuitsOn Christmas Day, John W. Padberg, S.J., died in Saint Louis, Mo., at the age of 95. He had been a Jesuit for 77 years and a priest for 64.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just don’t get the controversy over the traditional Latin Mass.Editor’s note: This article is part of The Conversation with America Media,offering diverse perspectives on important and contested issues in the

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missionaries of Charity Forced to Ration Food in India After Government Blocks Foreign FundsDaniel Ibanez/CNA A Missionary of Charity in Rome, Sept. 16, 2017. The missionaries normally help some 600 people at their Kolkata motherhouse and

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYC pro-abortion activists curse at churchgoers, beam ‘God loves abortion’ onto St. Patrick’s CathedralPro-abortion demonstrators yelled obscenities at people leaving a pro-life vigil at St. Patrick’s Cathedral in New York City on Jan. 22, 2022.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paid Abortion Leave For City Employees Poses New QuestionsJuan Francisco Gomez The new approach has led to a disagreement among supporters of legal abortion.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vatican cardinal: Tonga&amp;#HASHTAG#;s volcano disaster is an environmental reminderROME — The Jan. 15 massive volcano eruption in the island nation of Tonga is a painful reminder that despite tremendous resources and scientific  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faith leaders urge changes in bill&amp;#HASHTAG#;s provisions for funding child careU.S. Speaker of the House Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., presides over the House floor on Capitol Hill in Washington Nov.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EarthBeat Weekly: &amp;#HASHTAG#;Pursuit of climate justice is inextricable from the pursuit of racial justice&amp;#HASHTAG#;A man collects water from the Athi River near Yathui, Kenya, in October. He will use the water to irrigate crops on dry farmland.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“And he named him Jesus” or, “Notes on a Scandal”A Reflection for The Nativity of the Lord (Christmas)“When Joseph awoke, hedid as the angel of the Lord had commanded him  and took his wife into

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope to Pauline Family: Preach Christ with prayer and all available mediaBy Devin Watkins The Pauline Family—which is made up of 5 religious congregations, 1 lay association, and 4 secular institutes—marked the eve of the  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope to diplomatic corps: Great challenges of our time are all globalBy Linda Bordoni Pope Francis’s “state of the world” address highlighted critical issues of human and geopolitical concern across the world, hinging  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a world darkened by pandemic and political strife, Advent brings signs of God’s presenceA Reflection for the Sunday of the First Week of Advent“The days are coming, says the LORD, when I will fulfill the promise I made to the house of

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Appeals Court May Wait to Rule on Georgia Abortion Law Until ‘Dobbs’ Is DecidedJonah McKeown Pro-life advocates hold signs at the 45th-annual March for Life in Washington, D.C., on Jan. 19, 2018.nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yemen: Bishop Hinder denounces indifference to catastrophic scenarioBy Linda Bordoni Twice in the past week, Yemen’s rebels have launched missile and drone attacks on a military base in the United Arab Emirates  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday, November 21 2021, Thirty-Fourth Sunday in Ordinary Time Our Lord Jesus Christ, King of the Universe(1) Daniel (7:13-14)
Glorious vision of the Son of Man
As I watched in the night visions, I saw one like a human being coming with the clouds of

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Supreme Court considers abortion case, can we assume the best about our opponents?Pro-life advocates and supporters of legal abortion are seen near the U.S. Supreme Court building in Washington on Oct. 4.  #HASHTAG#://t.co/etcfnZpSOY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chaldean priest: Christians in Syria are in desperate need of helpVatican News The Jazira Region is in northern Syria, east of the Euphrates,on the border with Turkey and Iraq, and is largely controlled by the  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highlights of Pope Francis' second day in CyprusIn this video, we relive the highlights of Pope Francis' second day in Cyprus, which saw the Holy Father paying a courtesy visit to the Orthodox  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro-life advocates: Planned Parenthood can’t just wish away Margaret Sanger’s racism, eugenicsStatue of Margaret Sanger at the Old South Meeting House museum in Boston / Page Light Studios/ShutterstocknnWashington D.C.,  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#://t.co/hAYrimb1Ne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal Judge Issues Injunction Over Military COVID Vaccine Mandate Arguing it Violates Religious FreedomSteve Sanchez O’Connor notes that the Navy has granted exemptions for non-religious reasons, such as allergies to vaccines.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The politics of the pandemic may be shifting, but not the moralitySerbia's Novak Djokovic poses with the Wimbledon trophy in London July 14, 2019, after defeating Switzerland's Roger Federer in five sets.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I Give, Therefore I AmBy Dale S. Recinella Decades ago, in the streets of Tallahassee, Florida’s capital city, the itinerant mentally ill taught me many important lessons  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 questions for Pope Francis, who may benefit from adopting a petPope Francis greets dog owners during his general audience in St. Peter's Square at the Vatican in this Sept. 19, 2018, file photo.  #HASHTAG#://t.co/LvX5J7eexg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope at Angelus: Be transformed by the Word of GodBy Vatican News staff writer Speaking on the Gospel from today's liturgy which recounts when Jesus began his preaching at the synagogue in Nazareth  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Activist group projects pro-choice messages on Washington basilica on eve of March for LifeTwitter post by Archbishop Salvatore J. Cordileone of San Francisco on Jan.20, 2022, reacting to an activist group’s projection of pro-choicenn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Croatian Rugby Coach Returns to New Zealand to Become Catholic PriestAbove left: Father Antony Sumich, of the Priestly Fraternity of St. Peter, is seen in a trompe l’oeil or ‘fool the eye’ pose in the Canadian Rockies.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marquette to welcome Afghan refugee family to campusBasir Bita (left), his wife Hosnia, 5-year-old son Barbod and 17-year-old daughter Mahdia arrived in Canada Oct.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas Food and Feasting: Where Cooking and Liturgy UniteBruce Yeung “When we sit down at our kitchen tables, or our dining room tables with friends and family members, we are experiencing a foretaste of

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wednesday, November 24 2021 Week 34 in Ordinary TimeWednesday, November 24 2021Week 34 in Ordinary Time

1st Reading: Daniel 5:1-6 etc
The writing appears on the wall and Daniel interprets its

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watchdog Group Calls Out Biden Administration’s Religious Exemption Tracking SystemSaul Loeb President Joe Biden speaks to the press as he arrives at Allegheny County Airport in West Mifflin, Pennsylvania, January 28, 2022, as he

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A vibrant poetry program guides Jesuit high school students in their search for empathy and justiceEditor’s Note: Joseph Ross, a poet who has taught English for 33 years, is now in his 10th year at Gonzaga College High School in Washington, D.C.nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bishops affirm dioceses&amp;#HASHTAG#; sainthood causes for three U.S. laypeopleJoseph Dutton, a sainthood candidate with the title of "Servant of God," is seen in this undated photo.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Word of God Sunday: Causes for CelebrationWilliam Freeman Most American Catholics will hear the New American Bible (NAB) translation at Mass, as it is the approved translation of the U.S.nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Court denies religious exemption on vaccine for N.Y. health care workersProtesters demonstrate outside the New York City Department of Health offices on Dec. 6, 2021.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: Hundreds of sex abuse lawsuits filed against New Jersey Catholic priests during 2-year windowTheodore McCarrick arrives at Dedham District Court on Friday morning, Sept. 3 for his 9 a.m. arraignment / Joe Bukuras/CNAnnBoston, Mass.,nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope Francis baptizes babies in Sistine Chapel for 1st time since COVID-19 declared a pandemicPope Francis baptizes a child in the Sistine Chapel on Jan. 9, 2021. / Screenshot from Vatican News YouTube channel. See CNA article for full gallery.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Spirit of St. Nicholas: Christmas Gifts From EWTNThis sweet statue celebrates the true meaning of St. Nicholas and the miracle of Christmas.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope, US Bishops praying for victims of deadly tornadoesBy Christopher Wells Following the Angelus on Sunday, Pope Francis said he is praying for victims of the tornadoes that struck at least five U.S.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ronald Rolheiser&amp;#HASHTAG#;s &amp;#HASHTAG#;Essential Spiritual Writing&amp;#HASHTAG#; presents Christian message in all its vibrancyOblate Fr.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New St. Francis Xavier Documentary Shows ‘There Are No Limits’ for Missionary DisciplesA scene from ‘St. Francis Xavier: To the Ends of the Earth’ portrays the saint baptizing new believers in the 16th century.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[War &amp;amp; PenanceThe necessity for universal penance after war turns on a recognition that bloodshed is evidence of sin, of deep brokenness that needs specific

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope slips out of Vatican to visit record shop, gets CDPope Francis leaves a record shop in Rome on Jan. 11, 2022. (Screenshot from YouTube channel of #URL#,  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are the laity supposed to be?Pixabay
 Back in the 1950s, Dorothy Day, the co-founder of the Catholic Worker Movement, began to articulate a vision that was largely ratified at  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope’s and Roma people's teams in football match against exclusionBy Vatican News staff reporter At the initiative of Pope Francis, the representatives of the World Rom Organization and the "Pope’s Team - Fratelli  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Newsnn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Temperature Check/Comprobando su temperaturaJune 23, 2020  We will be checking the temperature of all who come in for mass.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sister Jeannine Gramick Has Not Been ‘Afraid of Closeness’ to Radical CausesPeter Kramer Sister Jeannine Gramick and Episcopal Bishop Gene Robinson attend the premiere of ‘Saint of 9/11’ during the 5th Annual Tribeca Film

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spanish Bishops: Report That Only Vaccinated Priests Can Minister Was a PrankCourtesy photo A priest bows before the Eucharist, housed in a gold monstrance.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a sign is a wink from God(Unsplash/Austin Chan)   
  No one else in our group paid the sign much mind. Even to this day, I'm not sure why I noticed it.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A look at Catholic newsmakers of 2021Cardinal Robert Sarah offers Mass in St. Peter’s Basilica for his 50th anniversary of priesthood in 2019. / Credit: Evandro Inetti/CNA.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vatican’s Cardinal Turkson says he offered to resign at end of his term  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Padre Tío Tilo: Rutilio Grande’s niece talks about her childhood with her martyred uncleAna Gladys Guzmán Grande was only 7 when she decided to confront Rutilio Grande, S.J.“I want you to tell me, are you my uncle or are you a priest?”nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Podcast: In Christmas messages to the Vatican and the world, Pope Francis stresses humilityPope Francis’ Christmas messages to “the church and the world” (“Urbi et Orbi”) and to the Roman Curia focused this year on the theme of humility.“He

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prívate Mass IntentionsMay 5, 2020  Good morning dear parishioners and friends of Sacred Heart. Here in our Parish we are praying for all of you and your families.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the Irish Changed PenanceUndeterred, the Irish monks maintained their alternative practice and disseminated it in their missions abroad.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever the obstacles, Biden&amp;#HASHTAG#;s Build Back Better plan must help undocumented immigrantsMigrant families and immigration advocates in Washington call for a pathway toward U.S.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catholics and conscience in the midst of fear and coercion(Image: Luke Jones/Unsplash.com)n In late March 2020, Eric “Smith” 1 was getting his sixth-grade theology class ramped up on Zoom.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#://t.co/bXUfCemNdf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope in Slovakia condemns discrimination, prejudice against Roma peopleBy Robin Gomes “Judgement and prejudice only increase distances. Hostility and sharp words are not helpful.   #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Newsnn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From child soldier to Catholic priest: Father Mbikoyo lives to give hope to the hopelessSouth Sudanese refugees queue to receive water at a refugee camp near Kosti, Sudan, June 2017. / Aid to the Church in Need.nnWashington, D.C.  #HASHTAG#://t.co/Oli1ZKxYnN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Presider’s Page for 23 January (Third Sunday in Ordinary Time)Opening CommentThe Word of God is the focus this Sunday, read by Ezra the priest in the Old Testament reading, and by Jesus in the Gospel.nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Truth, FinallyWhy would there be a saint for whom Jesus would make a lie true? Not every time Elizabeth lied, one presumes, did her words become, suddenly, not

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vatican calls for joining forces to stop fishers’ rights violationsBy Robin Gomes Noting there are still too many human rights violations thatfisherfolk suffer at sea, the Catholic Church is calling on international  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theotokos: The Mother of GodAndrei Rublev, “The Nativity,” 1405 Orthodox Catholic teaching has held together the mystery of “one person/two natures” from the beginning.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Archbishop Gallagher concludes visit to South SudanBy Vatican News From 21 to 23 December 2021, Archbishop Paul Richard Gallagher, Vatican Secretary for Relations with States, paid a visit to South  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Portuguese Bishops urge citizens to vote in upcoming electionsBy Linda Bordoni The people of Portugal go to the polls on 30 January to elect a new parliament, and the nation’s Catholic Bishops are reminding  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syrian refugees inspired by meeting with Pope FrancisBy Vatican News staff writer On Monday morning, the last day of his 35th Apostolic journey abroad, Pope Francis received nine young Syrian Christians  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Newsnn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro-Life Advocates Mustn’t Lose Hope and Joy Amid Struggles, English Bishop Saysnull Bishop Mark Davies of Shrewsbury preaches at St. Columba&amp;#HASHTAG#;s Church in Chester, Feb. 15, 2014. Bishop Davies drew on St.nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The roots of de-Christianization and the commercialization of Christmas(Image: Ron Dauphin/Unsplash.com)
 “Happy Holidays” has transformed the seasonal greeting of “Merry Christmas” into a defiant statement of Christian  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our founding fathers warned us about QAnonHundreds of our fellow Americans gathered in Dallas, Tex., in early November to witness the second coming of John F. Kennedy Jr.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Catholics behaving badly: Making Jesus weep!Bishop Joseph Strickland of Tyler, Texas, speaks from the floor during the fall general assembly of the U.S. Conference of Catholic Bishops Nov.  #HASHTAG#://t.co/qu48wH1BmN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Francis again makes surprise appearance at Immaculate Conception statueA firefighter places a wreath on a tall Marian statue overlooking the Spanish Steps in Rome Dec. 8, 2021, the feast of the Immaculate Conception.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Popular Marian icon in Rome gets conservation check-upThe Salus Populi Romani was checked by Vatican art restorers Jan. 20, 2022. / Holy See Press OfficennRome, Italy, Jan 20, 2022 / 19:00 pm (CNA).  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#://t.co/ipTInwF8L5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More example than exhortation: Pope&amp;#HASHTAG#;s 2021 illustrated teaching on kinshipPope Francis visits a COVID-19 vaccination clinic in the Paul VI hall April 2 at the Vatican.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Religious leaders critical to success of Puerto Rico debt restructuringA Puerto Rican flag flies on an empty beach at Condado Beach May 21, 2020, in San Juan, Puerto Rico.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro-life and pro-Black: Meet a woman who’s changing the conversation about racism and abortionOn the latest episode of the Gloria Purvis Podcast, Gloria speaks with Cherilyn Holloway, the founder of Pro-Black Pro-Life, an organization that

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro-Life Advocates: As Illinois Repeals Parental Notification, Unborn Children and Young Girls More at #URL# The Illinois House voted to repeal the law by 62-51.nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can a snowplow metaphor help white Catholics understand racial privilege?(Unsplash/Franz Roos)   
  Over time, I've come to care less and less aboutthe comfort of white people such as myself when discussing the  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Prayer Amid an Epidemic By Kerry WeberMarch 13, 2020  Jesus Christ, you traveled through towns and villages “curing every disease and illness.” At your command, the sick were made well.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real authority   “Let us walk in the light of the LORD!” (Isa 2:5). Isa 2:5; Matt 8:5-11 Today’s readings contain two very familiar sentences.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UN: $3.9 billion needed to help desperate YemenisBy Robin Gomes Civilians, particularly women and girls, are bearing the brunt of the conflict in Yemen, where access constraints and a funding  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There’s still time to see The Chosen’ Christmas special in theaters (but you better hurry)A photo of a scene from “Christmas with The Chosen: The Messengers,” a Christmas special released in December 2021.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because my hands are small compared to God’sit is easier to trust God with worlds than with sonswhose hands fit in mine. I mean to reduce the divineas I would a fraction: dividing life and

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at the faces of migrants; help them, pope saysPope Francis holds the hand of a man during a visit with refugees at the government-run Reception and Identification Center in Mytilene, Greece, Dec.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Documentary tells the story of “a great player, but an even greater man”(Image: Screenshot / #URL#)
 MPAA Rating: Not ratedUSCCB Rating: Not ratedReel Rating: 3 out of 5 reels
Baseball is, I think, God’s  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Combatting lies about sex abuse and the Catholic ChurchWe hear a lot these days about systemic, oppressive power structures that damage various racial, sexual, or gender identity groups.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#://t.co/nf2AXzsTzA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When You Suffer with Christ, Look Up, for Your Redemption Is At HandRegister Files Titian, “Christ Carrying the Cross” The moral lesson of the end times Gospels teaches us the value of mundane sufferings.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[European Churches issue appeal for COVID-19 vaccination and preventionBy Lisa Zengarini As the Omicron variant of COVID-19 spreads to more countries, European Churches are strongly encouraging everyone to observe  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the State Dropped Charges Against Father James Jackson, Why is He Still Being Prosecuted?Joe Bukuras/CNA Father James Jackson, FSSP, appearing at a Nov. 15 arraignment before the Rhode Island District Court.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope: Consecrated life is the “gospel” for today’s worldBy Robin Gomes “Everything we do is at the service of the Gospel, and you, in particular, serve that "gospel" which is consecrated life, so that it  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opening to the WorldLate in the summer of 1963, I entered the novitiate at St. Joseph’s Abbey in Covington, Louisiana, thinking I’d arrived into a tranquil and

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope Francis to Swedish Academy: Social media promotes monologue instead of dialoguePope Francis meets members of the Swedish Academy at the Vatican’s Hall of Popes, Nov. 19, 2021.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After year of divisive debate, US bishops approve tepid document on CommunionA bishop looks over paperwork during a Nov. 17 session of the fall general assembly of the U.S. Conference of Catholic Bishops in Baltimore.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30 January 2022. Fourth Sunday in Ordinary TimeWhat happened in the Nazareth synagogue can happen today in the church. We may carry prejudices with us into our places of worship, and if we do, we

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope Francis: The Word of God rekindles hopePope Francis conferred on Catholics the lay ministries of catechist and lector at a Mass for the Sunday of the Word of God on Jan. 23, 2022.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#://t.co/vmUrAmcqM8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Links: Cardinal Burke to celebrate Mass, Democrats need to talk economics, the New Right of American politicsChicago Auxiliary Bishop Joseph Perry and U.S.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New anti-Covid measures for entry to Vatican and Curia officesVatican News As of Thursday 23 December, access to Roman Curia offices willbe permitted only to those in possession of a certificate attesting to  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some parents dissatisfied with COVID-19 safety protocols at Catholic schools and parishesStudents at St. Paul Catholic School in Memphis, Tenn., in May (CNS/Karen Pulfer Focht)   
  Even before yet another coronavirus variant arrived in  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope Francis: Religious persecution is ‘insane’ and ‘inhuman’To discriminate against or persecute those who profess their faith is an intolerable act that threatens the fraternal bonds shared by humanity, Pope

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal group joins outcry over removal of Nigeria from religious freedom watch listThe flag of Nigeria on a military uniform. / Bumble Dee/Shutterstock.

Denver Newsroom, Nov 23, 2021 / 15:14 pm (CNA).  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope appoints new bishop for Auckland, New ZealandBy Vatican News staff reporter Pope Francis has appointed Bishop Stephen Marmion Lowe, currently bishop of Hamilton, New Zealand, as the new bishop  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report on abuse in Munich diocese: 497 victims in 74 yearsBy Salvatore Cernuzio At least 497 people were abused in the Archdiocese of Munich-Freising over a period of almost 74 years (from 1945 to 2019).  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where have all the food miracles gone?A Reflection for the Wednesday of the First Week of Advent“Then he took theseven loaves and the fish, gave thanks, broke the loaves, and gave them

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Let a thousand rites bloom and flourish!The Chapel of the Holy Trinity in Lublin, Poland, showcases a unique mix of Eastern and Western architecture and art.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This historically Black Catholic parish in Cleveland takes community to heartI will be the first to admit it: I did not imagine giant red robots to be part of my first trip to Cleveland.Onnn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Notre Dame and Georgetown among schools sued over financial aid conspiracyThe University of Notre Dame in Indiana and Georgetown University in Washington are among a group of some 16 private educational institutions named

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cardinal Dolan laments attacks on houses of worship in Religious Freedom Day messageRemains of statues vandalized at Our Lady of Mercy parish in New York City, July17, 2021. Credit: Diocese of Brooklyn.

Washington, D.C.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The decline of reading and the rise of stupidity: An interview with Mark BauerleinDr. Mark Bauerlein, seen in a 2011 photo, is the author of several books, including "The Dumbest Generation Grows Up: From Stupefied Youth to  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The legacy of Pope Benedict XVI: Reflecting on his new biographyThis February will mark nine years since the historic renunciation of Pope Benedict XVI.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dobbs Day: Here’s what it was like at the rallies outside the Supreme CourtThousands of pro-life advocates gathered outside the U.S. Supreme Court in Washington, D.C., on Dec.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#’sHealthOrganizationnn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23 January 2022. Third Sunday of Ordinary TimeNeh 8:2-6, 8-10.  Ezra the Scribe set out to re-establish the Jewish Laws, to bring his people back to the religion of Moses.
1 Cor 12:12-30. As

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thou shalt not share false witness(Unsplash/Kristina Flour)   
  How bad should you feel if you share a Facebook post or tweet that turns out to be untrue?  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By toppling Roe v. Wade, Supreme Court could finally end ‘tragic trail of human carnage,’ pro-life advocates sayWASHINGTON (CNS) — The chairman of the U.S. bishops’ pro-life committee Dec.nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspired by Pope Francis, Laudato Si&amp;#HASHTAG#; institute at Oxford on a mission to better the world with researchThe Laudato Si' Research Institute is housed at Campion Hall, University of Oxford.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro-life vs. Pro-choice states: If Roe falls, what would the abortion landscape look like?Screenshot of CNA graphic showing abortion policy by state. / Jonah McKeown/CNAnnWashington D.C., Jan 19, 2022 / 14:30 pm (CNA).nThe U.S.  #HASHTAG#://t.co/UfcBVRyYJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Catholic universities survive the upheaval in higher education? The next 10 years will tell.Editor’s note: This article is part of The Conversation, an initiative of America Media offering diverse perspectives on important and contestednn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catholic archdiocese of Malta says it could not have foreseen alleged ‘land grab’The Archbishop’s Curia at St. Calcidonius Square in Floriana, Malta. / Frank Vincentz via Wikimedia (CC BY-SA 3.0).  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrate Christmas at the VaticanDaniel Ibanez The Nativity scene and tree at the Vatican come respectively from the Huancavelica Region of Peru and Andalo in Trentino. TV Picks 12.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resetting Abortion Laws, and Children’s Books for Christmas (Dec. 3)Chip Somodevilla Police use metal barricades to keep protesters, demonstrators and activists apart in front of the U.S.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday December 19 2021. Fourth Sunday in AdventSunday, December 19 2021Fourth Sunday of Advent
1st Reading: Micah 5:2-5
Salvation would come from insignificant Bethlehem — to unite the nation

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Notre Dame mandates COVID booster shots for all studentsUniversity of Notre Dame / Peter Zelasko/CNA

South Bend, Ind., Dec 8, 2021 / 15:01 pm (CNA).  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope praises Cyprus as an open and welcoming nationBy Vatican News staff writer Following his meeting with Catholic clergy, religious, and catechists gathered in Nicosia’s Maronite Cathedral of Our  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#News

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the women with ‘I Regret My Abortion’ signs at the March for LifeThree women at the 2022 March for Life who have struggled to cope with their decisions to have abortions shared their experiences with CNA.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amid strikes and protests against Italy’s vaccine rules, a Catholic thinker warns of government overreachStefano Fontana, director of the Van Thuan Observatory in Trieste, Italy. / Courtesy of the Van Thuan Observatory.  #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>