<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# NZ is relentlessly shilling cannabis but they banned smoking &amp; massively tax tobacco. I believe there is something about tobacco which is healthy, which is why the globalists don't want you to smoke it. ðŸš¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We should build a British naval base in Cambodia to counter China. #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not to mention that Rishi Sunak keeps raising the price of fags. Which is why we need #HASHTAG#. ðŸš¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But the leftists said Britain would be an irrelevant backwater after Brexit? ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We could solve the energy crisis almost instantly by switching to nuclear power nationwide like the frogs have done. â˜¢ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Every single MP who supported masks &amp; lockdowns needs to be strung up in Tower Green.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So why's Dr. Puppy Killer on TV saying people need to get endless "booster shots" forever? He doesn't seem to want to stop at four. How's the quadruple-vaxxed country of Israel doing right now, by the way? ðŸ‡®ðŸ‡±]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How could anyone possibly side with Pakistani grooming gangs over Tommy Robinson? He might be unlikeable personality-wise, but he's one of the few people bold enough to speak about such a huge scandal in England. ðŸ‡µðŸ‡°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But I thought there was no risk of the vaccinated spreading COVID? ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[England was 5% Moslem in 2011 (probably 10% now) but Moslems comprise 18% of the prison population in Britain. I think if you only count England &amp; Wales that number goes up a whopping 25%. â˜ªï¸ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So you're excusing "minor thefts by the islanders"? Maybe the Hawaiians shouldn't have robbed people? ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This person should be doxxed &amp; locked in a psych ward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I do appreciate the power of money. London is the #HASHTAG# global financial center for a reason. Because nobody can match Anglo adaptability, financial secrecy &amp; tax dodging. Others have tried &amp; failed miserably. ðŸ’·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because they want to increase the grain supply to feed Africa's growing population. Cattle are big grain consumers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The energy crisis sucked though. But it sounds like we'll have another one soon because woke hippies are shutting down all the nuclear power plants. â˜¢ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Viktor Orban has copied National Socialist Germany's policy in Hungary where if a couple has 4 kids, they never pay taxes for the rest of their lives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Parliament should pass a law banning any future implementation of vaccine mandates, mask mandates or lockdowns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She is a typical liberal, they are all wannabe dictator totalitarian psychopaths. Stasi Horseface thinks she has the right to tell you what to do with your own body &amp; your own live, which is why she banned smoking. ðŸš¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They've been brainwashed by 80 years of "Holocaust" guilt propaganda by the (((media))). After WW2 the ðŸ‘ƒ concluded that the only way to prevent fascism from rising up again was to make the White race extinct. They see every White person as a "potential fascist". âš¡ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That means you don't have any moral high ground to criticize the left for wanting the same. Just so you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If something isn't done by Bojo soon, people will start taking the law into their own hands. This is how you end up with anarchy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I want to see a similar trucker convoy protesting smoking bans in Australia. ðŸš¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Are you invalidating an English person's lived experiences? Seems pretty Anglophobic to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I love it when leftists try &amp; claim these invaders are desperate refugees fleeing "persecution" when they're just sitting around in tents in Calais all day. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There has been almost zero "terrorism" since the surveillance state &amp; phone spying laws were passed. "COVID" has now magically vanished as soon as vaccine passports are locked in place forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ironic given that it was a Scottish King who created the Union if the first place. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Many Aboriginals can't speak English fluently and use a creole language instead. What's the issue here? I'm sick of American grifters jumping on any excuse to talk shit about my country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lord Miles continues to be an absolute madlad. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Britain was really "hostile" to immigrants, the English wouldn't be outnumbered in London, Birmingham &amp; Manchester. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Literally nobody except the (((media))) cares that Bojo ate a bit of cake in the garden. This is astroturfed nonsense to try &amp; oust Bojo so his successor can bring back all the COVID tyranny. ðŸŽ‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sunak will almost certainly be the next PM. His job will be to act as the new technocrat globalist puppet of the Bank of England to "put a brown face on White supremacy" while imposing more crippling austerity measures on the indigenous population.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Time for #USER# #USER# to prepare for British boots on the ground in Kyiv. #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I will never, ever support Albo because he's a rep*blican. ðŸ¤®]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The thing is, just because you don't war with others doesn't mean that others also don't want war with you. ðŸ‡·ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¨ðŸ‡³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's good news. I've seen polls showing that a lot of Mexicans in Texas vote Republican. I think Greg Abbott got something like 45% of the "LatinX" vote in the last election, as the leftists would say. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This entire "pandemic" was a psyop by the Deep State to take away people's freedom of movement &amp; bodily autonomy by making them fear an "invisible enemy". They did the same thing with "terrorism" in the 2000s to justify a surveillance state &amp; phone spying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Another backstabbing fake "Tory" shows his true colours. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I wish I had a bf who could give me a foot massage. ðŸ¤¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The real question we should be asking is: Why are so many of the wealthiest people in England not even English? Last I checked, there are 19 billionaires in the UK. I think only 2 of them are English! The oligarchs of Britain don't have any blood loyalty to its indigenous people!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's why leftists always lose arguments, all they know how to do is scream epithets at people. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, Captain Cook's life shows how non-Whites were always primitive savages long before the British ever made contact with them. He writes about how the Hawaiians constantly robbed him &amp; the Aboriginals immediately tried to kill him as soon as he arrived in Australia. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Same goes for the boat loads of invaders crossing the English Channel every week. They interviewed some of them in the tents in Calais &amp; they said they only want to go to ðŸ´ó §ó ¢ó ¥ó ®ó §ó ¿ for money. They don't want to stay in ðŸ‡«ðŸ‡· because ðŸ‡«ðŸ‡· won't put them in hotels on the English taxpayer dime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm sick of seeing that Greta twat everywhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I don't get why the BBC is so insistent on doing this. Do they think people believe there are a lot of African police officers in England? Is it just some woke screenwriter's fantasy for how they think England should look? Is it a deliberate erasure of the English from England?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Britain is greater than Russia will ever be. Russia is a shithole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Starmer should be laughed at forever for this picture alone. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[90% of tweets I see on my feed are from "trending topics". How do I get rid of this rubbish?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# From France? Yes. From Britain or Australia? Never. But that will probably change soon. ðŸ˜–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# One Brit is worth a hundred Russkies. ðŸ”¥ðŸ‡·ðŸ‡ºðŸ”¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The left's only consideration for deciding whether they support an abomination or not is "Does this hurt White people and/or make the lives of White people worse?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Luv' the Royal Navy
Luv' the guillotine
Ate' Papists
Ate' the Welsh

Simple as ðŸ´ó §ó ¢ó ¥ó ®ó §ó ¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Can confirm, I've been trapped on this prison island for over a year. ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And they're going to try to justify this White genocide based on a total lie like "climate change".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Of course not, they would celebrate that as "diversity". Because "diversity" just means "no White people".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Labor is run by Anglophobes. The main reason they want to cut off British immigration &amp; flood Australia with Asians is to they have enough voters to win a republic "referendum". Which is literally the antithesis of "democracy". ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Aborigines were a Stone Age civilization when the British arrived in Australia. I think they'd feel better if they stopped feeling so resentful of our success &amp; instead embraced being part of our glorious Empire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I can't take someone who looks like an elf seriously. ðŸ§]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're so lucky, I've been playing since Christmas &amp; haven't found a single shiny yet. ðŸ˜“]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Moderna doesn't require its own employees to be injected with their poison, so why should anyone else take it? ðŸ’‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nadim Zahawi &amp; Sajid Javid need to be held accountable for the inhuman cruelty they imposed onto the English people with their tyrannical lockdowns &amp; mask mandates for children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# There is another way we could get rid of the Manchester bomber very quickly &amp; easily, but I can't say it on Twitter. ðŸ‘€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is obviously a dumb boomer who thinks that any &amp; all incidents of tyranny are "Nazism", not an actual National Socialist. But they're going to try &amp; frame it that way to smear the truckers opposing COVID tyranny. ðŸ’‰ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You should play Rule Britannia at the end as well. ðŸ‡¬ðŸ‡§]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Senate is more likely to elect minor parties &amp; independents though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Glad to see the frogs standing with the wogs against the Turks. ðŸª³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# All non-Whites crave Whiteness &amp; desire to become a part of Whiteness. They envy our beauty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maybe they're secretly moving troops into Ukraine?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nobody except for a minority of woke leftists in London cares about the BBC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's awesome, and I bet they're fun to paint too. I've seen some with pretty crazy colour combinations. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Africans are colonizing Britain right now. That's why the African population doubled in England between 2001 &amp; 2011.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The "Northumberland independence" nonsense is just a way for the Celts to try &amp; fracture England.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes. Twitter is where all of the breaking news &amp; major cultural movements spring up now. Most (((journalists))) have Twitter accounts &amp; they regularly involve themselves in the cultural discourse here. Twitter is more important than TV now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why are the frogs interfering in Britain's internal affairs? He's getting French warships to push these savages into Britain's waters!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm so happy to hear that the English are resisting efforts to carry on the COVID hysteria for another year. ðŸ´ó §ó ¢ó ¥ó ®ó §ó ¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Imagine unironically believing in "White privilege" in the current year. ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The last time I went to Sydney, there were so many Chinese I thought I was in Taipei. ðŸ˜–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because Cecil Rhodes died ten years too early. CANZUK would solve that problem though. ðŸ‡¬ðŸ‡§ðŸ‡¨ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡³ðŸ‡¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Everything sick &amp; evil in this world can be traced back to commies &amp; ðŸ‘ƒ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I can't wait for this cuck to lose his seat at the next by-election. ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I like Mormons because they're racist &amp; have lots of White kids. ðŸ‘¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That's not surprising given how eager they are to take bribes from communist China. ðŸ‡¨ðŸ‡³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think of Mosley every time I hear this song. âš¡ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's experimental mRNA gene therapy. The clinical trials don't even conclude until 2023.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's funny how the left loves to say "England couldn't win without African players!" but then why do all the African football teams suck? Wouldn't the 100% Nigerian football team of Nigeria kick England's ass if the secret to success was having African players? ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It also led to Clement Attlee opening England's borders to the entire world. ðŸ˜–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Or who think that an Indian born in England is "British". ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Macedonia has a cooler looking flag than Russia &amp; Ukraine though. ðŸ‡²ðŸ‡°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How do you feel about Labour MPs like Barry Gardiner pocketing Â£500,000 in bribes from Chinese spies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You can get Double Filet O Fish now. I like eating them because they make me cum more. ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Forget Russia, Britain needs to invade Australia to liberate us from this evil COVID tyranny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's why I'm hoping the British economy will collapse. 99% of foreigners are only in Britain for money anyway. In America all the Taiwanese in California went back to Taiwan as soon as the economy turned to shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We wouldn't need Voter ID if so many Pakistanis &amp; Bengalis hadn't been caught engaging in voter fraud in recent years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow, that supply chain looks based! ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Cyclists don't deserve safety, they are lowlife scum who ruin the lives of motorists every single day. ðŸš´ðŸ”¥ðŸš—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# By "reset relations" he means "become a Chinese client state".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That would be every single Jewish person in Ukraine, which would amount to between 200-400,000 people. Would that be the largest airlift in history? ðŸ¤¯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning everyone! ðŸ¤—

I hope all of my followers have a lovely day! â™¥ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nobody even knows about his hit single "1 man 1 jar". ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I don't think this prison island has good weather at all, it's hot, humid &amp; sticky all year round. It's insufferable. I need to be back home in ðŸ´ó §ó ¢ó ¥ó ®ó §ó ¿ where you have lovely cold &amp; rain all year. ðŸ¥°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfortunately, it seems that all of the best US states are also the hottest. ðŸ¥µ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# &gt;It's way less than 50%

You're right, the SNP only got a whopping 46.5% of the popular vote in Scotland's last election. Which is only slightly below 50%. ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Is she young? People under 50 who aren't obese have nothing to worry about from COVID.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I don't believe Brussels would have allowed Britain to resist adopting their currency &amp; open borders indefinitely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# When that one dementia patient is commander-in-chief of the armed forces, from a foreigners perspective he does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The difference is that UKIP only supports net zero immigration, which would still allow 350,000 Africans &amp; Asians to colonize England every year. The NBU opposes all immigration &amp; wants a total end to foreign invasion. âš¡ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Every time I see pictures of Los Angeles I'm amazed by how much it looks like GTA5. Rockstar captured its feel perfectly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Correct, this is why you see European leaders sucking up to Moslems. Europe doesn't have its own oil &amp; has had to always rely on foreign oil imports. We can't get oil from ðŸ‡·ðŸ‡º because we hate them &amp; we can't get oil from Asia because they're a competitor of Europe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Baked potatoes taste disgusting with the skin left on. ðŸ¥”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Excellent photography. The colour saturation levels are just right. ðŸ‡³ðŸ‡´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I will never quit smoking, I will never stop driving my car, I will never stop eating meat, &amp; I will never eat bugs, no matter how much the woke hippies want me to. Simple as. ðŸš¬ðŸš—ðŸ¥©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Bojo looks like he eats a lot of pork pies though. ðŸ·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One little incident at Chernobyl which only killed a few dozen people &amp; now the woke hippies are terrified that a tiny bit of depleted uranium is going to destroy the planet. ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Gweagal shield wasn't "taken" from Aboriginals, one of them dropped it during a skirmish &amp; then Joseph Banks picked it up after the battle was over. ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, I am. I'm trapped on this prison island because the totalitarian tyrants in charge won't let you leave unless you take the heart attack vaxx. ðŸ’‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Don't you know? There were millions of Africans in 13th century England! The BBC said so, &amp; they would never lie to me. ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This isn't "patronizing", many Aboriginals in Australia can't speak English fluently. The ones who live in the bush speak a hybrid creole language.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Even acknowledging the existence of a "British race" is considered "far-right extremism" today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're welcome, tons of people have Tomoko avatars now. ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black "people" are only 13% of London's population yet they represent 48% of all murder suspects. ðŸ—¡ï¸ #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I knew just from the picture that she was âœ¡ï¸ before I even saw the name Bernstein. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder that Norman England banned slavery with a Council of London ruling in 1102, earlier than every single other country and people on Earth. You can even go back earlier to 1080 when William the Conqueror banned the sale of slaves to non-Christians. ðŸ´ó §ó ¢ó ¥ó ®ó §ó ¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nuclear power is the safest, least polluting &amp; most efficient form of power ever invented. But the woke hippies in charge of Anglo-Saxon tyrannies won't use it because they're scared a little bit of depleted uranium will destroy the planet. â˜¢ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've been told that bullshit my entire life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They spent three years spreading non-stop lies &amp; hysteria over a flu with a 99% survival rate &amp; now they're trying to do damage co tell &amp; act like they were on "the right side of history" the whole time. ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I never drink anything with sugar &amp; I still think water is nasty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And what's funny is, it wasn't even the Eskimos who burned the churches. It was White leftists who burned them down when the Eskimos told them not to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Meanwhile England is being colonized by foreign savages crossing the Channel &amp; we're on the verge of another war in Europe because half the country openly supports the enemy &amp; the other half is trying to appease him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I going to say that as well. The English don't need seasoning because all of our produce is fresh. ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not going to pretend I'm an isolationist who doesn't want war with Russia just because I know that's the popular position which most of my followers have. That would be dishonest. 

I want to be honest: I am an imperialist. I hate Russia &amp; I want war with Russia. ðŸ”¥ðŸ‡·ðŸ‡ºðŸ”¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In a game for global conquest, you have to play to win. ðŸ‡¬ðŸ‡§]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Australia has always treated Aboriginals like shit. The Northern Territory is almost entirely Aboriginal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# YouTube recently claimed a speech by a Christian pastor was "hate speech" because he said "God made us male &amp; female". ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That story get memory holed pretty quickly, didn't it? Why hasn't the traitor Barry Gardiner resigned from Parliament?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# First the courts let off the anti-Whites who tore down Edward Colston's statue, then they let off a 20-year-old African who sexually abused a 12-year-old girl, &amp; now they've let off an illegal invader who set fire to our barracks. The courts are the enemy of the British people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They think it's a good idea because they hate the indigenous British people. The terror &amp; humiliation is the point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is she really grinning, or is she just having trouble fitting her huge teeth inside her mouth? ðŸ´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The invaders openly admit they are only colonizing England to live on the dole &amp; prey on English women. But it seems Bojo is asleep at the wheel because the boats keep pouring in despite him saying multiple times that he will stop this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# All these spineless worms want is to be loved by the BBC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# At least Bojo can be entertaining at times. All the others are boring soulless technocrats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Even as recently as the early 1990s, England was pretty much a mono-ethnic state. The Scottish filth ruined that. They are the #HASHTAG# enemy of the English &amp; always will be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And Africans are at the bottom. Which is why the (((globalists))) want to reverse the Natural order &amp; place Africans at the apex of society. It's about humiliation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I love it when anti-Whites say "Britain caused ethnic conflict in Africa by putting multiple ethnic groups together in the same borders!" then turn around &amp; say that importing millions of those same people to England won't cause any problems at all. ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rise of isolationists to power in America should send two messages to Britain: 1) We cannot rely on ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸ to be our attack dog anymore, and 2) Britain must strengthen our military to engage in unilateral offensive military operations globally, without American support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is the single most important media platform in the world now. And that is largely due to Orange Man utilizing it so efficiently during his presidency &amp; causing it to explode in importance. Twitter is now the main place where TV news networks get their content.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sounds like you've been gaslit by Yank propaganda. The last thing Britain should be doing is importing that shithole country's sexually repressive Puritan "culture". ðŸ¤¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I've always despised Jeremy Hunt. He's related to one of the greatest Englishmen in history, Sir Oswald Mosley. But he chose to produce mongrel offspring with a Chinese woman. If he's willing to discard his own Whiteness, then he's willing to discard England's Whiteness too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Correction: Countries other than Britain do not redraw othersâ€™ borders by force. ðŸ‡¬ðŸ‡§ðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Are you denying that the Arabian monarchies are the primary financiers of Salafism being taught in English mosques?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Did you know that Australian Aborigines were not legally considered human until the 1970s?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# An MP in Australia said in Parliament that a healthy 21-year-old in his district got myocarditis from the ðŸ’‰ &amp; YouTube censored the video.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Aww, thanks. Now I'm making you extra. ðŸ¥°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And Vladimir Putin isn't ruining his country? Russia is one of the poorest countries in the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You should just start enjoying the drug addiction instead. ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's so sad to me to see how half of our society now endorses such disgusting cruelty directed as the unvaccinated. The deep state is bringing back segregation in real time. ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This has been done on purpose because the woke hippie scum want to force everybody to stop using cars &amp; switch to bikes because of "muh global warming". ðŸš´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# By "taking back control", they meant that the British government would be the one importing hordes of invaders into England, instead of the EU. ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think they're afraid that people might start questioning why nurses who are exposed to COVID patients on a daily basis refuse to take the heart attack vaxx. ðŸ’‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scottish "people" only have two forms of interaction with English people: 

"I hate the English! ðŸ˜¡" 

and:

"How dare you say the Scottish hate the English? ðŸ˜¡"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Has any Moslem MP brought up the fact that Christians are statistically the most persecuted religion on Earth today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I do like J-pop, but not as much as Britpop. I unironically like One Direction. â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once Rupert Murdoch dies, you will never see the left criticize the (((media))) in any way ever again, because every single other top media proprietor on the planet is âœ¡ï¸. If Rupert Murdoch wasn't a Gentile, the left would be completely silent on everything he does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# America is led by a senile dementia patient who shits himself &amp; falls asleep in public. Britain can't rely on America to be our attack dog anymore. We will need unilateral military intervention if we want to stop Putin taking Ukraine. ðŸ‡¬ðŸ‡§]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I love it when boys have nice soft hands! ðŸ¥°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Australia has implemented a much more successful strategy than England by only importing non-violent Northeast &amp; Southeast Asians for cheap labor instead of importing violent Africans &amp; South Asians like England has done. ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡º]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I love seeing right-wing American grifters spread this video around like it's some sort of epic own because you literally know nothing about Aboriginals in Australia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's because Holland doesn't desperately need Russian gas like Germany does after the woke hippies shut down all their nuclear power plants. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When are the police going to investigate Pakistani Moslem grooming gangs or the illegal invasion taking place in the English Channel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If Tory MPs are dumb enough to stage a coup against Boris they will be wiped out in the next election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm a monarchist &amp; think of England when I see this. And I think it's wonderful. ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡ºðŸ‘‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is the only way you will get American liberals to support invading Ukraine. ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In England all Commonwealth citizens can vote in British elections &amp; run for seats in the Commons, which I'm fine with. If you're an imperial power, I think all parts of the Empire should be allowed to participate in the political process.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Please go to England &amp; enjoy yourself fren. ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why exactly does the British Police Force need an "LGBT+ network"? I thought their job was policing? ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The ruling class supports abolishing private property &amp; forced wealth redistribution, but according to Alex Jones they're "fascists"! ðŸ¤ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What a sorry state of affairs we're in that Indians are putting up statues of White men in Britain while leftists are tearing them down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good luck getting Africans to stop eating fried chicken. ðŸ—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Poor Mokocchi, Kii-chan should leave her alone. ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the same playbook over &amp; over: The deep state creates a fake "invisible enemy" which they use to scare people into giving up their freedoms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm thinking of running for the Commons when I return to England on a single-issue campaign of lifting the ban on menthols. ðŸš¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't know about that. I smoke about half a pack a day &amp; my voice still sounds the same to me. Plus it looks sexy as fuck. ðŸ¥°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It was great seeing people on Twitter calling out their nonsense in real time though. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Now that I would definitely support. Emperor Hadrian had the right idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That's not a problem, the Bank of England can just print more paper &amp; then raise taxes to remove some of the other paper from circulation. ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nothing wrong with a bit of coke every now &amp; then. ðŸ¤·â€â™€ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because their bodies are trying to tell them they crave meat, but vegans have brain damage from protein deficiency so they're oblivious to the signs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing to see here, just the warden of the world's largest prison openly taking orders from Davos. ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡º #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I'll believe it when I see it. But as of right now, the separatists have complete control of every lever of power in Scotland. I don't see that changing any time soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I hope they play Rule Britannia as well. ðŸ‡¬ðŸ‡§]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I don't like Sunak because he keeps raising the price of fags. ðŸš¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did they mention the astronomically high obesity levels among African women in the US?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's the problem. It should be illegal for any of these savages to claim asylum in England. We owe them nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# All Gypsies in Europe should be deported to India. Especially since India has actually acknowledge that Gypsies are part of their diaspora.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The Anglosphere has become nothing but totalitarian tyrannical shitholes ever since COVID hit. The Dominions are dead to me except for the purpose of providing more manpower for the British Armed Forces. âš”ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Thanks for further validating the stereotype of cyclists being the most smug, annoying &amp; insufferable people in any society. ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Their "reparations" are a one way ticket to Africa. âœˆï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Scottish being vegans would certainly explain a lot of their nastiness &amp; stupidity. ðŸ¥“]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So you block me just because I refuse to parrot Russian nationalist propaganda? ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hopefully some of the British prisoners can make him feel a little less lonely, if you know what I mean. ðŸ†]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The key is to let the hate make you stronger. ðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I never thought a failed state like Wales of all places would finally come to their senses. What's going on? ðŸ¤¯]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>