<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What are your credentials &amp; accomplishments to make you such an expert on such matters?

Here are just a few of mine.

Ph.D., J.D., M.B.A., M.Ed., M.Div., B.S.

I'll let you google my net worth, bio, businesses and background.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[N.I.G.G.A. Omicron da Don bout 2 sweep in &amp; take out mo niggas than a federally subsidized KuKluxKlan manufactured levee b/t Lake Pontchartrain &amp; the Gulf of Mexico in New Orleans. Read dat back. When da levees finally break on dis pandemic &amp; a variant breaks thru all vaccines,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had students, faculty &amp; administrators at my other HBCU alma mater Howard University refuse 2 acknowledge my PhD. To this day, while all mail from my alma mater Yale University is addressed "Dr. Alexander Hamilton," mail from Howard is always addressed "Mr. Alexander Hamilton."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe every American who refuses to get a vaccine should be denied emergency room treatment, preventing from traveling, be fired from their job, prevented from earning a living, pay more 4 health insurance &amp; not be allowed 2go2 a grocery store or other public accommodations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same thing 4blackLGBTQ. No blackLGBTQ person should ever delude themselves into believing that any white LGBTQ person will put any black person before their own. They will flip that race switch on a dime &amp;this is precisely what DaveChappelle is getting at. 
RACE BEFORE SEXUALITY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh &amp; it should be known that Mr. Harris dropped the "Cleveland" from his last name when fell sick with AIDS &amp; finally came 2 terms with his belief that a gospel giant in the black church used the foster system to foster his perverted pedophile fetish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But niggas like that don't get elected. Black folks, like folks, prefer dey elected niggas nice &amp; docile, soft-spoken &amp; nonthreatening. Julian Bond didn't give a fuck bout confronting white folks to dey face &amp; he had the intellect to do it at a high level. John Lewis did NOT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get this. A good number of people who voted 4 BarackObama in 2008 &amp; 2012 turned around &amp; voted for DonaldTrump in 2016. Doesnt make sense? No, it makes perfect sense. Obama didnt do shit 4 poor people of any race&amp; that opened the door 4 a man like Trump to cast himself as savior.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Disrespect has been normalized in this country in a way thats dangerous&amp; contrary to nature. Only pure unfettered violence can correct such behavior. In nature, fear of death&amp; survival controls all. If society ever falls to the animal kingdom people like this will perish quickly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Too many people ride Lebron's dick and get mad when you don't ride along. Hence KD's "Lebron fanboys" comments. Thats also a big reason why Kawhi Leonard turned down playing w/Lebron. Yall Lakers fans keep up dat Lebron-can-do-no-wrong bullshit &amp; see how many good players come-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Finally, since U always defer to Lebron, defer 2his post-game comments on Westbrook that lauded what he did well. U are a horrible basketball analyst. You are a fan &amp; NOT a sports analysts. You can't do both. Either you're going to competently evaluate a game or root 4 your guy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus was Aramaic NOT Aragayic. People have an uncanny need to see themselves in mirrors on walls in other people's homes. I just don't get this. If you travel the Earth always looking to see yourself in others, how will you ever know who you really are?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lemme jus cut straight 2the point:

WE WANT TO BE WHITE

I dont make this conjecture lightly. 2B white is 2B normal&amp; black aint neva been normal in America. Normalizing blackness has always been a bridge 2far 4wypipo.

Therefore I choose 2 sit on this side of the bridge by myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not all white folks bad and I'd rather live in a place where dey want to keep law &amp; order &amp; not have a race war than in a Dem stronghold where they want to empower the woke police &amp; defund the real police. Nigga, I'm out here sounding like Booker T. Washington at a GOP convention]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U see it was never about sexual harassment. It was all about power &amp; damaging Cuomo's brand so badly that he wouldn't be able 2 sustain a campaign for president in 2024. There are good number of people inside the Democrat establishment that don't want 2C-
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think of the implications this has for Cam Newton's career. The media was pushing a narrative that his alleged unvaccinated status was jeopardizing his teammates health, but Cam was away for 5 days during training camp while Covid spread thru the Patriots facilities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We didn't get shit out of Obama's presidency, but weez wuz jus happy to see a black face in power. We were in love with the picture of a black family in the White House stepping off Air Force One &amp; I must it admit, it was a pretty picture indeed, but that's all it was. A picture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You should read really Dr. Hamilton's viral post on comments like yours. He actually uses your exact language 2describe how many people would rather delegitimize others simply b/c they disagree. In the minds of your ilk, the only real "Dr.'s" are people who agree with them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only mafuckas who should vote for angels is angels. The problem is: AIN'T NO GODDAMN ANGELS DOWN HERE. These holier than thou ass voters need to be judged by their own measuring stick. Give them the same judgment they try to project on others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This question is easily answered by observing which churches the black homeless people line up at 4 soup kitchens. Here's a hint. It damn sure aint at the Rev. Dr. Senator Raphael Warnock's Ebenezer Baptist or any other black church in Atlanta. Real talk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our airwaves are just polluted w/way too much personal animus masquerading as journalism. No fucking way I as a black man sit by &amp; be silent on some white man like Skip Bayless calling Russell Westbrook a "psycho." No fucking way man. I would have lit into Skip Bayless' ass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Take not Russ plays better when the game is very up tempo. He scores more point &amp; has better shooting % when the game is fast pace. No one else on the Lakers can keep up w/him. When AD &amp; Lebron are in the game, the pace is waaaaaaay to damn slow. The top teams play waaaay faster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The unchosen, often bewildered, will initially not understand this behavior, but will feel the cumulative affect of being rejected by the herd. They will be continuously ostracized &amp; will be ultimately fired, demoted or eliminated from the equation altogether.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 2of3 Imagine how good many teams would be if players made up in rebounds&amp; assists what they failed 2do in shooting. U hv a ton of high scorers in this league w/low rebounds&amp; assists in a game. Those 11 assists means Westbrook is responsible for at least 22 points more if 3pters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yall still want a few companies picking winners &amp; losers? A few gatekeepers controlling what information gets shared. We are reverting back to the old model of a few companies controlling the dissemination of info. The internet was supposed to change that.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shit, I even locked da wife in da basement fo a few weeks of quarantine when she finally made it back from caring for elderly family members out west. Bitch, you betta get yo fine ass in dat basement. I slid her a plate under the door for a few weeks. I monitored her w/cameras.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that starts w/fresh blood. This wait-your-turn-politics has got 2 end. Rep. Gregory Meeks, like most of his CBC colleagues, believes the CBC should always defend incumbents: "When you're on a team, U look out for your teammates." But who dafuck is your team? CBC or black people?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[replaced her ass w/blond haired blue eyed Megyn Kelly, many screamed racism. In my mind, even if it was racism, black people should never expend any capital or energy on someone like Tamron Hall who for years behaved as though racism was no big thing as long as white folks were-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Da only way U free yoself from all dis shit is 2achieve independentwealth BY ANY MEANS NECESSARY. Stay legal tho. Realtalk. I'm so gung ho bout achieving independentwealth that if I had a big ass &amp; some big titties, I'd be calculating how many table dances I needed 2buy 100 acres]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me put it a different way. Given the history of how this country has treated black people, how smart is it for black people to be this damn dependent on government? Should we not be striving for a level of independence that immunizes us from the shenanigans of politicians?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 3 o 3 

Finally, how can you harp on Westbrook's turnovers when LEBRON JAMES IS THE ALL TIME NBA LEADER IN TURNOVERS.  It's like Russ can do no right &amp; Lebron/AD can do no wrong.  This is a TEAM game &amp; the Lakers are NOT a great TEAM right now. Stop dumping all this on Russ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This why it took T.O., a top 3 WR of all time, 3 ballots to get in the HOF. Likability over merit. Meanwhile in the HOF are murderers, crackheads,  thieves, child molesters &amp; every other thing under the sun, but none of the mattered b/c the HOF was about PLAY ON THE FIELD....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&amp; Smerconish is not alone. Check out Charles Blow's vitriolic article entitled "I'm Furious at the Unvaccinated" where he vilifies people who see the world different from him &amp; then turns around &amp; wonders out loud about why the country is so inflamed that-
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-having been doing so for some time. Vaccinated people can still spread the virus, especially when they are unmasked. Yet the unvaccinated are still being blamed for increased Covid infection rates &amp; I've said nothing about CDC's failure to keep data on-
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Big Lie is that black people were ever a threat to poor white people. That black people were ever a reason for their bad lot. That black people were ever the reason for their suffering. That Democrats never wanted 2do the same thing 2 poor whites as Republicans. Exploit them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm not defending anything but WINNING. You can try to put a team of choir boys all U want. Gimme some liars (AB), crackheads (Michael Irvin), murderers (Marvin Harrison/Ray Lewis?), child molesters (Lawrence Taylor), racists (JonGruden &amp; others) &amp; I will beat U all day everyday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Respectability negroes claim they are playing an "insider game shaped by whiteness that can work 4 black people." Bullshit. You're trying to play a game that wasn't designed 4 black people to win. Instead of playing by their rules, it's time 4 Negroes 2 rewrite the damn playbook&amp;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Although he'll never be my GOAT (&amp; neither is MJ, Wilt Chamberlain 4 me), he's a better man than MJ ever was &amp; I have nothing but admiration &amp; respect for what Lebron has done on&amp;off the court. My remarks here are strictly about how the media covers him&amp; those who play with him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nevertheless, black people should be very leery &amp; suspicious of black people who come to them by default. If black people weren't your first love, if you only came to "Us" after white folks rejected you, U can't just default 2 black people &amp; rebrand yourself as a freedom fighter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shit, even HarrietTubman freed a nigga or two or three on Christmas eve. They were her blood brothers. She came  back for the wives &amp; chillun. Thank God no black man slave catcher actually existed to catch her, like in dat bullshit movie w/British Nigerian actress Cynthia Erivo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ladies &amp; gentlemen, meet perch pontificator Howard Bryant. He is not only an ESPN sports commentator but he is also a Major League Baseball Hall of Fame voter, who under the Hall of Fame "Morals Clause," casually says,  "I'm not voting for steroid guys" to enter the Hall of Fame. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again, this shit is criminal &amp; treasonous &amp; we hv allowed 2many people 2rise 2lofty heights in this country who care more about people outside this country than within. Shit, think Oprah who built a school 4African girls overseas while black American girls right here suffering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scary shit. Dats why Ugot 2stay healthy during dis pandemic or yo life will get reduced 2some1 elses vaccine politics. Dats why I'm staying away from eerybody UNLESS some1 finds me an easy button dat actually works. Jus know that vaccines are NOT the easy button U think they are. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Washington would have made a big example of Steve Jobs. That arrogant laugh he gave Obama would have been reduced to whimper &amp; begging for life under the brutal isolationist founding father George Washington, who often viewed immigrants w/great suspicion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think Andre LEON Talley, who despite all the recent posthumous accolades being bestowed upon him, the so-called "Pharaoh of Fabulosity" died penniless, deep in debt &amp; being evicted from a rented mansion.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dont want 2B fucked wit&amp; the humanbeings dont respect shit dey dont fear. The problem w/disrespect is the people who lob it dont fear shit&amp; dey dont fear shit b/c this society prevents most people from being reminded of their mortality&amp; just how easy they could lose their life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Cute. When U are independently wealthy w/several businesses&amp; a high networth, U hv time 4 whateva U want 2hv time4. DrHamilton also has staff that monitors his socialmedia across several platforms. How bout posing a thoughtful response instead of takin shots at people U dont know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# He has done no such thing. You don't get to laugh at others &amp; then get mad when others laugh at U. LGBTQ people bullied another human being n2 suicide. Dave Chappelle treated a trans woman better than her own community treated her &amp; you are refusing to address that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your hell is my hell. It's our hell. We didn't start this fire, but we gone burn TOGHETHER. Hence, Dick Gregory's crab analogy. I once asked Mr. Gregory about Shirley Chisholm saying "black people behave like crabs in a bucket, crawling all over each other."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah not one morsel of you gentlemen's remarks remotely addresses Dr. Hamilton's commentary. Changing a conversation to the one you want to have instead of actually addressing the actual thesis at hand is a big no-no here. Wrong space for you. Cheers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be clear, I didn't reveal any of the allegations, just that allegations existed &amp; he might want to take a closer look at his behavior w/his congregants to make sure he wasn't doing anything that could be construed as unethical behavior. Now privately, I knew it was much worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or what if white folks were willing to give "Us" the Native American deal? Our own Negro reservations, no taxes, none of our internal disputes can be handled by American courts &amp; we have our own police force? Would you take that deal or would you cling to them 13% ballots?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because married women tithe less. Especially black women married to black men. Ain't no real nigga bout to let money leave his household &amp; find its way to no pastor's pockets. In addition, many of the sermons are anti-men. Stop me if you've heard shit like this in church before:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# would you agree with her if you knew that if the government ever did such a thing, it would immediately lead to a civil war?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be clear, I hate all this shit &amp; I especially hate that we have been reduced to this type of bullshit on American soil, but there is no sense of quarrelling with the reality of where we are now. This is why I work extremely hard not to put myself or my family in harm's way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gimme Booker T all damn day. Hell, I'll take it a step further. If white folks offered you a billion dollars to never vote ever again to never participate in American democracy, would you take it? Now before you answer that question, remember, black people are only 13% of the US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It blows my mind how many people jus believe shit they see on TV w/o hearing the other side. This is flatout bullshit. I dont believe any of it. This is media spin. No fuckin way AB leavin that much money on da table. They were limiting his snaps 2stop him from gettin incentives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need U2 get this. Whenever U C some1 go unscathed for something other people are destroyed 4, there is a reason why the powers that be decide 2keep such people in place. The rules are somehow different for them. Bill Cosby went to jail denying what Charlemagne proudly admitted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In fact, FredHampton might B da closest thing 2 Jesus on American soil. He lived his life fightin gov't. He was sold out by a undercovernigga from his own sect dat was working w/government. Many of his disciples denied association w/him after his assassination.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never ever never ever never ever allow myself to be alone with any woman NOT my wife. When I was a professor, dean &amp; minister, I had multiple cameras installed in my offices. Shit, I even travel the earth w/a body cam in tow, for da police &amp; for lying women.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or what about the 15yr old girl who killed a pedestrian &amp; laughed while running him over? Now if U say Aaliyah nor any other under age girl can consent 2sex, then how can they consent 2murder? Why not just give all children under 18 get a freepass 4murder?
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why I don't trust any black LGBTQ who puts their sexuality b4 they put their race. In my mind that means you belong to white people. I've said it before &amp; I'll say it again: Gender &amp; Sexuality are the two biggest footholds white supremacy has in the black community.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This would also mean that the narrative that AB is all about money would be patently false b/c in the face of losing potentially $1 million in incentives, he chose his health&amp; safety. But get this, neither #USER#   or #USER# mention this- #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook would even overrule group moderators on groups the moderators founded. I discovered that even though a moderator approved a comment 4 posting, Facebook stepped in &amp; blocked it. This shit was maddening. Put simply, Facebooks picks winners &amp; losers, but NOT 4 celebrities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just as Jesus sought to tear down the religious hierarchy of his day, I too am of the same mindset as it relates to the role of church &amp; other religious institutions as barriers to true emancipation. In many ways the black church as become an extension of the Democratic party in-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the day of bloodshed comes-what should we do w/people who spent their pre-Civil War 2.0 days vilifying &amp; bullying the unvaxxed, who became so sick &amp; tired of their rights being stripped from them, that they decided to pick up arms against the very country they claimed to love?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never mind the stories of Atlanta area cops puling over Eddie Long's Bentley in the middle of the night w/young lads in the front seat &amp; the good Bishop had his pants down w/the young man's face splattered w/the Bishop's seed - all this while preaching anti-homosexuality sermons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic Johnson might as well said, "Master Jeannie, you deserve better slaves." Are you fucking kidding me #USER#. My nigga it was not to long ago when all the good white folks &amp; their Negro minions were hammering you 4 QUITTING  on the Lakers.n#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 of 5nnWorking on enormous piece on antisemitism charges against Nick Cannon, IceCube, DeSean Jackson &amp; hypercritical pieces by Kareem Abdul Jabbar &amp; Jemele Hill. Consider this thread your primer. Lets go. The picture below is not in America but Israeln#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put simply, I don't take disrespect well. Unfortunately the world is filled with it. There is such a culture of disrespect in this world such that violence is always percolating just around every corner waiting for the wrong words to drip off an offending parties lips.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID JESUS

Up next church founded by prophet who lived his entire life in protest against government now joins government 2demand its citizen parishioners get vaccinated. Church joining the government for anything is the greatest example of anti-Christ.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To bring all of this full circle, consider the fact that Brown v. Board of Education might have been decided the other way had Chief Justice Vinson had not died suddenly of a heart attack shortly b4 the case was decided. 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why most geniuses are not discovered until after they die. It takes people awhile 2 come around 2their ideas. The artist becomes like "The Watcher" from Marvels "What If." He has the ability 2correct the path of his artistic universe but swears an oath to never intervene.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[***pussy doesn't cloud his judgment, women can't control him or AS Michael Eric Dyson once posited, not putting "LOINS OVER LOGIC."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4) Nigerian is the new black. So is biracial &amp; People of Colornn5) Colorblindness &amp; interracial are synonymous for keeping black people apart.nn6) The narrative of the absent black father is being pushed hard (The Bachelor, Obama, Kamala).nn7) Light, bright damn near white are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are real life consequences out here in deez streets 4 crossing the wrong person &amp; U should move accordingly. Don't fuck w/nobody &amp; realize that if U should ever decide to take something of value from someone, they just might decide to respond in kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 1st president GeorgeWashington would be called a xenophobe in todays cancel culture-"we-are-the-world"-woke-mob that seems 2pull all the levers of power in this country. Maybe this was b/c immigrants tried 2assassinate him, which why he had all dem mafuckas publicly executed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America First is more than just a campaign slogan. Its a way of life that the foundingfathers of this nation embraced brutally, especially the isolationist President GeorgeWashington, who expelled every immigrant when he learned of an immigrant led assassination plot on his life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your family members are the original architects of white supremacy, forcing entire nations to bow down to your clan. You &amp; your European comrades destroyed countless generations of black people across the world. Everything you have, slave labor gave you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found this very interesting. Some good white folks reaction to Dr. King's assassination.nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Are the only people that can have a doctorate are the people w/whom you agree? All of Dr. Hamilton's credentials are public knowledge &amp; easily googleable. We don't require agreement, but demand COMPETENT disagreement. Unfortunately your retort doesn't meet that standard. Cheers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm no democrat or republican, but democrats are a very weak party. Larry Elder is probably going 2B the next governor of California &amp; shit, maybe even in future presidential candidate &amp; all of this is the fault of Democrats. They moaned &amp; bitched about Gov. Newsome so much dat-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jus interview a few black homeless folk in Atlanta. They will tell U that white churches will feed U quicker except the Hosea Williams Feed the Homeless crew, but thats one organization &amp; not a church. The point is you can't depend on niggas either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our society tolerates &amp; protects the disrespectful in manner contrary to nature &amp; unhealthy for society. There is only one proven cure for disrespect: violence. Hence, the Niccolo Machiavelli question, "would you rather be loved or feared?" Fuck love. Give me fear all day long.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 all those unfettered capitalism freemarket folk, riddle me dis: would U object 2 defense contractors selling their weapons 2 da highestbidders around da world regardless if those bidders are nations hostile 2 da US? Fuck no. In defense contracting, we demand U PUT AMERICA 1ST.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am of the perspective that any woman caught lying on a man should get the same time in prison a man would have got if he was convicted. Think Nikki Yovino, who was convicted of concocting rape story against Sacred Heart University football players.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh &amp; do not be surprised if Jay Williams gets pushed off First Take just like Max Kellerman for his takedown of Smith. ESPN has created an echo chamber for Stephen A. Smith that rarely allows him to be competently challenged &amp; he peddles a brand of bootstrapism that harms "Us."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YO. ISN'T THIS SOME BULLSHIT? I'VE BEEN SITTING HERE PLAYING THIS DAMN WORDLE GAME FOEVA AND MY WIFE JUST WALKED IN THE ROOM AND GUESSED THE DAMN WORD ON THE FIRST TRY. UGH.

Wordle 222 5/6

⬛⬛⬛⬛⬛
⬛🟩⬛⬛🟩
🟨🟩🟩⬛⬛
⬛🟩🟩⬛🟩
🟩🟩🟩🟩🟩]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In udder news, jus got my invitation to Lil Nas X's baby shower. I heard Satan is the father but he refused 2 pay child support. Dats da reason LiLNas snapped his neck in Montero. Lotta mafuckas gone lose dey mind over dis 1. LUV IT. Troll on my nigga.
#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These media personalities don't realize they are playing with fire or better yet stoking the flames of civil unrest which very well could break out n2 full civil war. If we are at the point where its ok for an irresponsible press 2 ask if its ok to mock dead people, what's next?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I took the time to address the congregation directly on this matter by saying "this world has already programmed this child to make herself look small to make others feel big. This is unacceptable. If someone has a problem w/your accomplishments, THATS THEIR PROBLEM, NOT YOURS."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BookerTWashington recognized DrDubois' talent&amp; wanted him at Tuskegee Institute after da Ivy League rejected him. However Dubois was delusional. Dubois thought b/c he was da 1st nigga dem Harvard crackas gave a PhD, dey was gone let him teach dey good white students. NiggaUcrazy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They benefitted from a fight they did not wage. They are made or bought by white people &amp; benefit from being the Shiny exotic negro in a sea of whiteness. B/c we have been hardwired to embrace symbolism &amp; NOT substance, we fail to hold these mafuckas accountable at our own peril.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the more nonsensical I think it is for any of us to think there is always gone be food in the store, gas at the pump or anything or anyone there to help, rescue, or save "Us." If U continue w/that mindset, U are putting your family at great risk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He's too old now to log that type of play. Only allow Bron to play point in the final 5 minutes of the game. All other moments, decrease his on-ball usage rate at the 1 &amp; increase it at 2-5 depending on the opponent..&amp; if they are going to keep Russ, they hv to speed up the pace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What she didnt know is he has hidden cameras all over his office. He outed the woman in front of the entire class while giving a lecture on "ethics &amp; morality." He used her &amp; the videos as a case study regarding what people are willing 2do 2 get ahead in a capitalistic society.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hear me well. Vaccines are giving people a false sense of security &amp; the goal posts are being moved as to what constitutes "fully vaccinated." While Dr. Anthony Fauci says only the original vaccines count as fully vaccinated, other doctors/scientists are-
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The idea of marriage &amp; monogamy is becoming less appealing in a time where women have so much power that they can damn near destroy a man at their leisure if they want to. Just ask the ghost of black anesthesiologist Rajaee Shareef Black,
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need not know the subject matter of a panel, but when I see from the get-go everybody has the same position, I avoid dat shit like the plague. I don't do echo chambers &amp; this is exactly what many of our news outlets have become.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one likes a bully. And that's just what our media &amp; its vaccinated minions have become - bullies. God forbid vaccinated people start dropping dead like flies a few years down the road when the long-term side effects of all these vaccines become more readily apparent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History is filled w/black people flaming out in white spaces&amp; then running back to black folk to survive &amp; thrive. Once they are no longer the darling of white folks eyes, they then lean into their blackness &amp; get black folks to rally to their cause, whatever that cause might be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again, I dont expect whitefolk 2collectively care about "Us," but heres the kicker: I don't expect most black folk 2give a shit about me &amp; my family. Slavery &amp; Jim Crow destroyed us. Think I'm off kilter, ask any Wakandan, I meant Atlantan, which churches in ATL feed da homeless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hey Captain Vaxx, how do his vaccine status? Stop projecting your vaccine bias onto him. FYI I got family members in ICU w/COVID right now &amp; all of them were vaccinated. Stop looking for stories to confirm your preconceived views about the unvaccinated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Careful MrPaul, humanbeings create celebrities &amp; the stages they occupy. No1 has Teflon skin. Every1 can B touched. We all bleed. The minute a celebrity arrogantly dismisses a fan, that same fan can instantly B transformed 2 a mass shooter at 1 of your events. Proceed w/humility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HEAR YE, HEAR YE, THIS IS A PUBLIC SERVICE ANNOUNCEMENT. THIS PANDEMIC IS NOT OVER. I REPEAT. THIS PANDEMIC IS NOT OVER.

Remember, the number one strategy for staying safe in this Covid world is NOT masks or vaccines, but QUARANTINE. That means no concerts, sports events, clubs-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or what about gay black actor Jussie Smollett who supposedly attempted to peddle the LGBTQ victim card to bigger studio payday by concocting a hate crime? And he was literally willing to criminally expose two Nigerian men to prison to cover it up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# As I responded before, you are part &amp; parcel of the media culture in this country politicizing vaccines, demonizing the unvaccinated, driving a wedge between Americans &amp; then feigning innocence if someone calls you out on it. All athletes should block you &amp; avoid you at all cost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor white people in America are much like the German populace after World War I- poor, defeated, resentful, &amp; thirsting for revenge. "I want my country back," isn't just hyperbole. It's a battle cry, a call to arms. Anyone who dismisses this as just talk doesn't know history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop me if U've heard dis shit bout MLKday B4: "Its not a day off but a day on." Nobody says that about white folks holidays like 4th of July when big beer bellied bubbas be out BBQing &amp; downing Coors Light. So my new MLK  day motto is:nn"Dr. King was killed so dat we can chill."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are creating "Negro Imperialists" and we're doing so because we have accepted white people as the benchmark for every goddam thing we do. Just ask Haiti how the Duvaliers worked out for them or ask South Africans how the ANC is working out for them.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 3 of 3

You are letting Skip pull you to his side to much on Westbrook &amp; its coming off very personal as the "Bash Russel Westbrook Show." In addition, there is no way you can criticize Westbrook on turnovers when LEBRON JAMES IS THE NBA'S ALL TIME LEADER IN TURNOVERS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah, we don't do grammar policing, tone policing, pronoun monitoring or any of this gotcha type nonsense. Dr. Hamilton is the wrong person for you to engage w/in cyberspace or anywhere. You might want to avoid him &amp; his posts at all cost.

Tam veri studio volumus atque.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-return&amp;shoot 2 of his former coworkers live on air. He chronicled what he felt was their racist treatment. Think about how many workplaceshootings occur b/c some1 lost dey job over some politics shit where a group of workers conspire 2 hv them cancelled. 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Show me how the New York Times censorship actions cant be interpreted as anything other than loving Biden &amp; hating Cuomo. Yet aren't these the same type News organizations that claim moral journalistic superiority over networks like FOX News because they are supposedly objective.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But that doesn't answer the question of why you haven't been shut out of sports &amp; removed as a HOF voter. Barry Bonds was never convicted of anything but U pled out &amp; got probation for assaulting your wife. You should be judged by the same measuring stick.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats why I married a woman w/a big ass. So if we ever go broke &amp; have nowhere to go, at least we'll be able to eat. Shiid nigga, women always got a way to eat. When times get tough, dey can always sell ass. Even if she got a pimp, he ain't neva gone beat her too bad as he ain't-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the 1st shots 2our next Civil War ring out, U will find me at ChairmanFreds grave in LA, fantasizing bout da Rainbow coalition&amp; how we could hv righted the ship B4 it was too late.nnwishin I had more time 2 convince poor whites 2join our fight.nnwe aint yall enemy.nndey are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I am wrong, then how dafuck does it take the jury even an hour to deliberate over a case where we have a Samsung-Apple-Android-Vizio-Sony-LG-240Hz-10,000K-Ultra-Wide-Picture-in-Picture-High-Definition-video w/extra crisp showing exactly what happened? A nigger hunt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dubois believed this shit too &amp; when it didn't pan out, he wind up stuck at an HBCU in Wakanda, I meant Atlanta. Dr. Dubois neva wanted to be at Atlanta University &amp; only wound up there b/c the good white folks at Harvard chewed him up &amp; spit him out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FOX News is to conservatives. Now ask yourself who does the anti-guns pro-abortion AJC article benefit and who does it hurt? IT HELPS STACEY ABRAMS &amp; hurts GOP. Do yall think its a coincidence that both Abrams &amp; the author of the article are Spelman grads. #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Jewish people have no such crutch or forcefield against holding their oppressors accountable, which explains why they have gotten far more in their fight against Nazism than black people have gotten in their fight against white supremacy....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U would neva see whitefolks en masse joining a black chorus against 1 of their own. Yet our people will accept a huge paycheck from wypipo 2do the same. I had the opportunity years ago 2take this bait 4a gig at FOX News, but turned it down. And what about the hypocrisy of it all?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't. That would never happened &amp; if any black American dared show up on the shores or at the airports of any of these so-called black run countries demanding &amp; asserting any rights over their own citizens, their citizens would kill "Us" on sight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not 4 any1 force fitting themselves n2 a box 2 make others feel comfortable. I wasn't born w/enough middle fingers to shoot at people who participate in this ruse. Nevertheless, I'm only bringing up Titus Burgess, the "ode to black penis" man 2 make a point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-we shouldn't just create a space for the nigga who flamed out with white people. Remember Tamron Hall saying, "when a black woman comes up to me asking how I made it as a black woman, I stop them right there &amp; say everybody had it hard." Yet when the good white folks at NBC&amp;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Niggers were the invention of wealthy people. Niggers needed to be created to make the wealthy wealthier. When the façade falls &amp; poor whites realize they've been manipulated &amp; exploited, in their eyes, violence becomes the only option to right the ship. Hence, Civil War.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is bad, very bad. In fact given the number of lives lost to this virus &amp; the fact that this lab was purposefully making viruses more lethal, the actions of any American involved in this should be considered treasonous. Nevertheless, here is how U voted 2 deal w/this. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's only true if you're listening 2 a voice bouncing off the walls of your echo chamber. "Sensible" is relative 2 your tribe. Step outside your tribal walls &amp; discover a world anew filled w/human beings w/other ideas about what is "sensible" OR just stay in your echo chamber.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hence Malcolm X's quip, "ain't no black folk eva fought 4 freedom. We've only begged 4 it...Concerning nonviolence, it is criminal 2teach a man not 2 defend himself when he is the constant victim of brutal attacks."4 Malcolm, fighting was literal, throwing hands &amp; shooting guns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Even CNN's own Dr. Sanjay Gupta admitted on Rogan's that CNN lied on him. Unlike your employer, Joe Rogan actually puts on people who disagrees w/him. His show is not the echo chamber CNN is, which why legacy media has such low approval &amp; is fast becoming irrelevant. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I sprang from my bed to see what was the matter,
I tore open the shutters and heard all this chatter,
When what to my wondering eyes did forbade,
It was Steve Harvey lecturing black people on how to behave,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now, they'll say I'm comparing apples &amp;oranges. Never mind apples &amp; oranges are both fruit. Remember how all the TV Negroes were calling for Cleveland Browns Myles Garret to be kicked out of the league for swinging his helmet at Mason Rudolph for calling him a nigger?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Playing more means more turnovers. Harden&amp;Luka average more turnovers but play less. In addition, the turnover argument is nonsense because LEBRON JAMES IS THE NBA ALL TIME LEADER IN TURNOVERS. In addition, Melo, KD, Steph and a shit load of other top players are in top 50 in TOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a white owned restaurant in Buckhead. HOW ABOUT STOP PATRONIZING RACIST BUSINESSES &amp; BUILD YO OWN SHIT? UGH. This shit is beyond maddening. We can't imagine life without white people. We too damn dependent on them for everything. This was not the case before integration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FUCK YOUR STORY

Excellent example of how people peddle experiences 2persuade others. This happens all the time in many facets of life. People use experiences as an argument when its not. If this juror lied 2get on the jury, the verdict will be overturned.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never returned 2 my parents home &amp; from a hospital bed, I was rescued&amp; my college journey began. Had I returned, I would have been certainly killed. I say all this to say, from that day forward, I realized the meaning of that scripture: "there is life &amp; death in the tongue."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why JoyReid has no business reporting on anything Covid related. She has demonstrated that her vaccinebeliefs are rooted in which party is in office. This is JOURNALISTICALLY UNETHICAL. She is a flatout  political hack whose opinions move w/the wind of the party in power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So are U saying this as your personal opinion or are you speaking on behalf of LDF? Or do U purport 2speak on behalf of black people?. I didn't know vaccine mandates was a civil rights issue &amp; if so, not quite sure your personal perspective is representative of most black people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[believe that all or most Georgian are anti-2nd amendment or at least feel that people should be forced to attain a concealed weapon permit to carry a gun &amp; that most Georgian are pro-abortion. Now there are approximately 10.62 million people living in the state of Georgia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never mind the lab-leak theory was initially dismissed as "right-wing conspiracy theory," but now that argument is seemingly more plausible with even social media outlets like Facebook reversing course on people posting on it.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's just how rare I am. I say this NOT to boast, but to point out just how few black men make it to this rarified air. I know of only 1 black man w/as many earned degrees as me &amp; only 1 black male with more earned degrees than me. What is sad is all of us dealt w/unemployment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here me well. We need something like this for every TV talking head &amp; newspaper reporter &amp; journalist. I want all of their private lives to be open books. Their cell phone pictures, videos, IP addresses, &amp; every other morsel of information about their lives should be fair game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo, hear me well. In my perfect world, I'd slaughter all these type people. Real talk. These are the type people that cause all of the conflict in the world &amp; mankind would be better off without them. Send them to meet Jesus. We allow human beings to act contrary to nature.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't give a fuck that she gave a few million to a few uppity niggas at Morehouse. She made her bread &amp; butter in this damn country. I have actually run into students from that school who look down on American black people. That attitude was honed &amp; sustained by Oprah money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I'm a Trump supporter b/c I disagreed w/U on Russell Westbrook? Fuckoutta here. Keep your prayers,  &amp; religious zealotry. You know nothing about me, basketball or that Nazarethan prophet U Phariseetically boast of. Your trite prayers would be better used to cure your ignorance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many women want you to believe that the reason they are getting more seats in university classroom, in administrative seats &amp; in corporate America is b/c they are more qualified than men. Bullshit. It's b/c you are less threatening to the man who sits at the head of the table.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, a more progressive black Ferguson, MO Congresswoman like Cori Bush out here in a sleeping bag &amp; cot by her damn self on the capitol steps highlighting black people being evicted during the pandemic &amp; the entire CBC is NOT rallying behind her? 

Fuckouttahere 2.0. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crux of the matter is U can dream of escaping blackness like Alice Walker or rapper Eve or Tina Turner by marrying a white millionaire or billionaire &amp; flee America 2live a fairytale life in a French Chateau, Italian villa or perhaps even a British palace like Megan Markle,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After U've sucked a nation dry of its natural resources&amp; when the exploitation of people reaches a feverpitch, society implodes&amp; war breaks out. Sprinkle some pandemic on top&amp; all hell breaks lose. Then comes the hard reset&amp; the rich retreat 2their high fences, barricades&amp; yachts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is becoming increasingly clear is how the weight of all that contributed 2 her own declining health, obesity &amp; depression. Although she was able 2 squeeze out a few more decades than Ward, at what cost? Her estate now in turmoil w/a huge backtax bill.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the post-pandemic world, some competent journalist in the future will write about how American journalists were derelict in the duty in failing to interrogate the work of scientists like Jean Heller did. They will write about how journalists vilified the unvaccinated, often-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Bro, you literally tried to check someone on some shit you didn't actually know and another person who was actually at the game called you out on it. Maybe you should stop repeating SkipBayless/ShannonSharpe talking points &amp; generate an original thought.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now riddle me dis: despite all that "AB is no longer a Buc" talk, 24 HOURS LATER, THE BUCS STILL HAVENT CUT OR RELEASED ANTONIO BROWN. Now keeping in mind that reporters question from above, check out this excerpt from a release by ESPNs Adam Schefter:
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop w/this faux outrage &amp; brutal hypocrisy. U still gone read &amp; watch eerything Harry Potter&amp; Ustill gone keep up w/DaveChappelles every word. #USER#  has almost 14 million followers who say fuck you &amp; her damn near billionaire status insulates her from your cancel culture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I guess you could &amp; many do b/c many black folks are not up on game to the ruse. The problem w/being window dressing 4 white people is that racial mannequins can always be removed at random. When a black person is cast out by white people &amp; white folks say, "next nigga up,"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congressman Cummings was fighting for immigrants even up until his last breath. THIS IS FUCKING HORRIBLE. Just Google the stats surrounding the plight of black people in his district. In fact, look at the benchmarks for his district from when he was 1st elected up until he died &amp;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Psalm23 said "your rod &amp; your staff shall comfort me," this scripture wasnt intended 2B a blueprint 4 pastor-congregant relations. At the P.B.I. we believe the only thing that should be rising in the church is Jesus &amp; not pastor. Think otherwise at your own peril. Expect us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Bro, it's more than that. It's a team game, but it's like both Kevin Love &amp;  Chris Bosh hinted at. On Lebron teams, everybody gets blamed BUT LEBRON. That's why Kyrie got the fuck up out of Cleveland and why KD said he would never play w/Lebron....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh shit, Wakanda is falling. Somebody call Killmonger.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Your writing is tabloid masquerading as journalism&amp; is filled w/personal shots at athletes. If any1 dared needled you, piled on &amp; made fun of U the way U take shots at a number of black male athletes, you would not be able to take it &amp; you would cry that people are bullying you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloomberg's Allison Shrager says "fuck James Brown," "it's no longer a man's world" &amp; she holds up as evidence the fact that women are achieving more degrees than men. She then concludes that this in unhealthy for society for "people w/o college degrees are more prone to-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Have you actually researched Howard's admissions data?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Good. We'll plaster those words on your casket when they finally come for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could go on &amp; on here, but I only need say there is a ton of money, opportunity &amp; prestige in gaining victim status. Think about how many gofundme's raise significant sums of money once a person has been victimized in some manner. Now some of these are legitimate victims.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# 4. Consider the fact that it took a reputable INDEPENDENT news organization like "The Intercept" which filed numerous Freedom of Information Act Lawsuits 2force a release of more than 900pages of National Institute of Health gov't documents that revealed Dr.Fauci lied 2 Congress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sharpe has allowed Bayless 2put a battery in his back&amp; launch PERSONAL VITRIOLIC DIATRIBES at athletes in a way he never personally experienced as a player. Give him an ounce of his ownmedicine&amp; do a nationwideTV interview of the whitewoman who accused him of brutal sexualassault]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Meanwhile, our democracy is suffering at home. Americans are out of work, suffering under a pandemic &amp; we can't even meet our own needs. We're having to borrow money to pay for infrastructure b/c we can't afford to make repairs to our own house. Resources are NOT infinite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-to hear more than 1 side of an argument&amp; not just live out their lives in the same echo chambers that many traditional news outlets hv become. I will have more to say about this later, but for now if you think I'm off kilter with my critique of traditional media, consider this: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# America ignored Christians in Syrian, Hindus in India, Buddhists in Taiwan. So what? None of that matters. It is not America's job 2police the world. We literally cant afford this mindset anymore. We have a huge federal deficit, which required Congress to increase the debt limit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its even sadder to see black people or biracial people or black immigrants or any person w/an ounce of black in them embrace such a narrative UNLESS, that is, "black" is no longer the category for "Us" to be casting our lot with. Perhaps descendants of slaves is a better choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I hv no dog in dafight. Just tryin 2understand how Ujustify 1 &amp; NOT da other. I guess a fetus has no civilLiberties. Make it make sense. Nevertheless I'm w/comic LouisCK on this 1, NOT on his masturbatory exploits but on his argument dat only women should hv da right 2kill kids. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dr. Hamilton's credentials, accomplishments &amp; net worth speak for itself &amp; we would be happy to publicly compare his stats &amp; achievements to yours on a platform of a social media platform of your choice or even right here in this thread for all the world to see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unlike Africa, in America, rich whites convince poor whites that their problems are the fault of "Us." Hence, the creation of "niggers" was paramount to make white supremacy pop in America. You needed to created an underclass so low, that even poor white could feel superior OR-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it ok 2mock obese people who die of diabetes complications? Is it ok 2mock drug addicts who die of overdoses or alcoholics who die of cirrhosis of the liver? Is it ok to mock gay people who die of AIDS? Tell me precisely just how far does your morality-free logic go?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So TrickDaddy, Boosie&amp; FlavaFlav walk n2 a bar...
&amp;dey mamma tell dem dey all got da samedaddy.

NIGGA-any woman out here tossin TrickDaddys salad&amp; flossing her teeth w/his booty hairs should hv a tongue&amp;lips transplant &amp; nonigga should eva kiss her again.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank U kindly for taking the time to read the work of Dr. Alexander Hamilton aka A-HAM.

If you dig the content, please feel free to support us via CashApp: $ahamllc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feminism only works b/c men allow it. To be specific, a few white men at the top allow it. Without those white male powerbrokers, no woman, black or white, would have shit other than an apron &amp; spatula to eke out their days in a kitchen. Sexist? Yes. Reality? Yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# and will you educate your followers on Jewish racism against blacks?nn#URL#://t.co/0N7xTCN7Vjnn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I awoke from this nightmare, looked up on the roof,
Hark! there was Saint Oprah in a jolly Red Suit,
Her &amp; Gail were raving about Michael Jackson &amp; R. Kelly,
shaking like a bowl full of weight watcher's diet jelly,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When whitefolks come for U, you're done. So done that 11 white jurors are left to bully 1 lone negro juror n2 cosigning an acquittal OR what if out of all the Negros they could hv selected 4 jury service, they found the 1 Uncle Ruckus ass nigga whose holding up a guilty verdict?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Both Ms. Willis &amp; the GBI took the off duty cop's word as gospel that Mr. Phillips tried to run over the cop &amp; that the cop was "in fear of his life" hanging from Phillips car as the pulled off. Watch the video again. Do you see a cop hanging from a car?
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# U speak in racial language when its advantageous 2U. Thats how U got 2 where U are by becoming adept at Crayola politics, playing the diversity game &amp; being a better version of the fictitious "blackness" that white liberals love. 

Put simply, U got 2where U R by passing as "Us."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Your mentality is why the Lakers will never win another chip w/Lebron. On every Lebron team, everyone is expected to sacrifice their game EXCEPT LEBRON. This formula will no longer work in a league that's gotten younger &amp; faster &amp; where Lebron has gotten older &amp; plays way 2slow-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Very interesting comment. Chicken or the egg. Which comes 1st, love or fear? Feared white women long b4 dating age, long before meeting my wife. Fear got me to adulthood in 1 piece. U have 2B alive 2love anything. Put simply, my parents raised me to NOT end up like Emmett Till...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if Dave Chappelle made his contract negotiations w/Netflix contingent upon them giving Monique a great contract? Sounds crazy? Well that's just what Jessica Chastain, a white actress, did for Octavia Spencer, a black actress some years ago.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can understand how the police did mistaken identity. They do kinda look a like...

dafuck?

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even today, many of our celebrated pastors &amp; preachers are a part of a ministerial apparatus that props up pimps, pedophiles &amp; predators in the pulpit &amp; puts preachers b4 parishioners. I am of the perspective that the black church has wrought as much harm on black people as help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ANGELS &amp; DEVILS

I'll have more 2 say about this later but 4 now, I'll tell U what an old cat told me years ago: look around your inner circle &amp; imagine hearing these words on TV, "anonymous sources say." Whoever U can project those anonymous mafuckas to be, get rid of them now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish my daughter would do some shit like that. Automatic cut out da will &amp; disowned. Just think, it was actually a black man, Jeremy O. Harris, who wrote a Broadway play where interracial couples role-play master-slave relationships as couples therapy.n#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NIGGA

Yall ready 2get a 10th booster shot?

Delta&amp;Omicron just went out of style.

Covid just released a new album &amp; its a bigger hit than Delta &amp; Omicron put 2gether plus shes more infectious.

Ladies &amp; Gentlemen, I give U the new Covid-19 Variant: IHU.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But men of all races suffer too. For men at the top tend to hire women over men as women are less threatening. You can even see this in HBCUs where U often have a male president at the top &amp; women administrators all around them. Think Howard University.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All this at the so-called premiere institution founded exclusively for the education of freed slaves &amp; named for a Union forces Civil War hero &amp; Commissioner of the Freedman's Bureau, which was also founded for the explicit directive of providing aid to FREED SLAVES.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In ministry theres a cruel joke regarding the differences b/t pastors w/a D.Min. vs. pastors w/a Ph.D. The joke goes: "A D.Min. or Doctor of Ministry is a degree 4 niggas who wanna be called doctor." The joke is rooted in the fact that a D.Min. is much easier 2attain than a Ph.D.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sift out their biases &amp; how it infects their reporting. The mere raising of certain questions &amp; not raising of others is an indication of bias &amp; the narratives they are trying to shape &amp; push. Perhaps this is why Americans are searching out other news sources as they are wanting-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now imagine everything U just read being applied 2poor whitefolk who are 1 step above us&amp; Mexicans. U see that racial facade is fast unraveling&amp; poor whites are discovering that rich whites hv long viewed them as nothing more than white niggers. Put simply, the gig is up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the black church, there are a ton of black preachers who call themselves "doctor," but either haven't set foot in a university classroom or they simply have not achieved a doctorate degree. In fact, a close colleague in ministry once told me his father in ministry asked him:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the FBI papers, agents claim that famous gospel singers supplied pussy for Dr. King &amp; his comrades during their civil rights road trips. Who dafuck dey talking about? Now before all you Aretha Franklin worshippers go spouting off, consider the circumstances of her upbringing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But how can I trust U when I know the 1 thing that can eradicate the virus, U wont recommend it &amp; pastors wont preach it? QUARANTINE. B/C if U dare quarantine, it removes THEIR HAND from YOUR BANK ACCOUNT. I need U 2get this. Neither vaccines or masks work better than QUARANTINE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But it's not he doesn't fit them. THEY DON'T FIT HIM. &amp;that's why I want the Lakers 2trade him so they will have no 1 else to blame for them being horrible. The Lakers are a bad team, with or without Westbrook. Get rid of Westbrook now so yall can see just how bad the Lakers are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It challenges U in ways dat can make U combative, angry &amp; refusing 2 accept. We need more truthbearers, people willing to stand on what thy know until the world takes notice. Notice, I said "know" &amp; not "believe." I don't operate on what I believe. I operate on what I know.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>