<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Bimbo Usagi is what Imma call this girl from Euphoria #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insecure, Now Apocalypse did this... both shows had interracial couples where the pairs were both people of color... i feel like biracial castings and ir relationships on tv is a covert way to continue white adjacency yeah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2000s style: Anna Nicole Smith outside of court. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paula and Kai were so hot together omg. #HASHTAG#. Goals. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not the on the spot call out. 
But I'll say this "homicide is a more therapeutic approach" is my FAVORITE line and the way she bunches up her hair. 
She was iconic. Should've had a death scene.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanting mixed or biracial people to call themselves Black or projecting Blackness onto white passing people is weird. We shouldn't be centered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way her face turned on at 1993-1996 ....yeah she's a beauty queen #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Columbine rage affected so many movies. They would chop them up due to fear of blame for violence in schools (same w violent video games) and it reminds me of the post-9/11 racist patriotic era in American movies and television as well. But tht era fucked up horror. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mixed chicks deep conditioner...show is some BLACK people #USER# hurry up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[mysterious working class bad girl enigmatic dream girl, object of affection totally unattainable and vast, yet vague, concussed even...a memory of a person- you will never understand #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Scream 4 should've ended when it fades w Jill in the white. Wasn't tht the original plan?? Leave Sidney's fate on a cliffhanger. And the intro to Scream 5 would be the hospital sequence and then a time jump w Kirby in college...that's what we deserved back in 2013/2014]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frankie J. Alvarez, &amp; O-T Fagbenle in 'Looking' HBO "Looking In The Mirror" (2014) dir. Joe Swanberg #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Where is this written cus that's what I'm choosing to believe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carrie Bradshaw wearing a button up, Nike sweat pants and heels...she's an icon. she's my family. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I actually think that's very admirable. It's how I feel abt Cinematographers vs Directors. 
But I do think ppl now Google or IMDB makeup and costume designers these days much more often. And both have credited Alexa as well &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moment of silence for Hunter Schafer wearing an AEON FLUX shirt in this #HASHTAG# interview 
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't give a fuck that she's not biracial but China Anne McClain is the girl I wanted to play Eartha Kitt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The way she should've been able to make this single/music video combo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah. So the footage of Big/Noth will be removed in the finale or future episodes?! So stuff was shot I guess and now won't be shown. Honestly revisiting the original Sex and the City....his presence hasn't affected it. The show is more than one man.

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanna bét up a yt boy so bad #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I see, and I think that's valid. I wish they didn't bank on shock value and controversy but instead leaned into the ways in which these things can lead them down dangerous paths. 
It's not all fun and games]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[70s horror film 'Frogs' (1972) dir. George McGowan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An iconic property like Nancy Drew is being modeled after Riverdale, when both properties original material is beyond iconic and distinct. It's sad. WB could have an EASY hit on their hands if they just adapted Scooby-doo into a conspiracy college show. Hello?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harry is my little old Jewish uncle omg... Charlotte apologize to him!!! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She blacked out her abilities. In Birds of Prey 2 they are unlocked, and the team finds they don't need to save her. I think Ella was great as Cassandra and I want her to have a chance to play a comic accurate version (a fighter!) and be mentored by Barbara Gordon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who knew a geeky neckbeard basement dweller who is white, polyamorous and a leftist who loves geek culture was a sexual high for some people. Room for everybody let's say that!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[kevin abstract we know you love white boys!!!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barbie Ferreira when ppl pull up her tumblr n word saying/ and pretending to be biracial era &lt;33 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# episode 3: n-the chef from Max's house? Recgonize from Wendy Williams! Carla Hall. Gorgeous Queen. nOk?so?Brown teacher girl... Reema! husband is unattractive...these hbo shows love pairing up interracial couples huh. Reema being outed by the whites...hmm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this tragic mulatto + "post-colonial/greatest asset" conversation around Meghan is REALLY giving those "mixed/biracial people/couples are a sign of anti-racism and in the future everyone is brown." fetishism takes tht are just so weird, racist and yes.... colonial. Stop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rick Fox in Ugly Betty season 2, "A Nice Day For A Posh Wedding" (2007) dir. James Hayman #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is this the girl from Scream or Batgirl or Westside Story?? ALLL em cashew types look the same to me. Hope the stans get her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Film Parallels blonde women at the grocery store: n-RuPaul in Crooklyn (1994) n-Carey Mulligan in 'Promising Young Woman' (2020)n-Charlize Theron in 'Young Adult' (2011) n-Nicole Kidman in 'Stepford Wives' (2004) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wayans..they are so hot. 
Totally Spies?? Aww that's so cute. 
I definitely had a 3AM staple of watching Kitchen Nightmares haha.  Or the QVC kitchen/food playlist. 

These days toasty tok compilations on YouTube, skincare videos, Sex and the City, Gilmore Girls, does it for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ig: sadiqdesh 
Before the Prada fall show #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Every HBO, CW and Netflix teen drama. Back in the Boy Meets World days interracial couples were progressive. Now? An agenda and erasure. Yup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The family angle. Scream 4 is kinda a remake of 3... The laying next to your killer relative. I feel like Sidney Prescott is a tragic figure but her humanity is so interesting. Her empathy w Roman and Jill. It's sad. Her family trauma runs deep henny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alicia Burke for 'Dujour'
(October 2020)
David Roemer - Photographer #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ran my fucken mouth abt miss im not r&amp;b twigs...but #HASHTAG# is great and the description of it being like a comfort introspection in the time of the pandemic/isolations ....yeah i feel tht. time to listen to the new summer walker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I never rewatched it. I should tho. It was wild. Peak of AHS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry but I can't wait to be 30 so I can date and have love affairs with lovely and hot 50 year old men with silver hair and sexy dad bods. Purr. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bc they don't pay it forward to poorer Black ppl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't necessarily think about it like that I think if you are rich and you are perpetuating capitalism then you are a bad person - if you can help someone then why not help someone it is a net good that helps the entire demographic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was Kelvin Harrison Jr. And Lil Nas X meant for the same role!? Of Kelvin the one tht went to Meech??? 
Cus that would've been 3 Black boys....omg we could've had it all rolling in the deep #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i haven't seen that film since i was kid, and i was so obsessed with it-late stage like around my pre-pre tween years. As for Roger Rabbit, it's been on my list!
what are some allegories of this nature u personally relate to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why mitski gotta song called crack baby
why is it so good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It looks like woodsboro...and the visuals are nice. It's literally just the ugly filter holding this movies vibe back rn #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[too, but I don't see myself after having experienced the full gradient of basic sex- shaming or hating on men with small penises. I feel like there is a place in sexuality for every adult- and the sky is limit when it comes to pleasure. Some people are just boring lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Madonna looks like Him from Powerpuff Girls...she's always stealing from queer culture :( 
Queen!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I honestly wouldn't say shit if we saw some Indian girls, a Japanese American, some Muslim baddies...but it's like...just white and biracial thts it lol..nHmm...bored!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sydney's characterization is changing. The show is too. Also? Ethan Hawke? Damn..he looked hot in this. Ew @ Christian Slater showing up. They have guest STARS! after 9/11 I suspect the writers scraped some ideas bc the show is changing direction and feels more pro-US #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 TV Shows To Know Me:
-Sex and The City
-Charmed
-Sharp Objects
-Euphoria
-Ziwe
-Betty HBO
-La Femme Nikita
-I May Destroy You 
-The X-Files
-Twin Peaks #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Smartie. 
Like sorry but I'm in my Alias era]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Blade Runner 2049. Was not impressed w Ana de Armas, but I loved her in Knives Out. I finally got the hype. 
Now Rian needs to cast Meagan Good in Knives Out 3, and reunite w her after Brick (such a good movie) or else!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way Megan Fox was committed to playing mean popular pretty girls who oppressed blonde women in the 2000s. I mean??? Ugh it's a subgenre!!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I understand and I can relate. Why is it so hard to have interracial couples w two brown people? Like? I really think studios just want to find a way to keep whiteness centered. So they'll give us lightskin POC/ambiguous representation but ALWAYS compassed against white ppl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kimberly/Chalamet looks like Emma Chamberlain. I want Willow and Whitney together. Kimberly's boyfriend looks so old. Lol. Max is it?? Hate him. Veronica Mars would've k worded him. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Y'all are so fucken corny 
Like?? You scroll down and everybody is talking abt the same shit and using the same buzzwords on current events to go viral. Loser!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...I guess they don't want to face the reality. Idk abt Diahann but I know Pam Grier and Eartha Kitt were mistreated by the famous Black men of their eras. 
Ppl wanna be selective!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jamie Lynn Spears you will NEVER be Ashlee Simpson, Elizabeth Olsen, Elle Fanning or Solange Knowles!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me waiting 3 years of anticipation to watch Euphoria and LIVING for Maddy's hallway/bathroom scene. Peak of 2022 cinema methinks! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anti Vax &lt;3 I'm just stating that being bedridden, feverish and in pain for HOURS or days bc of the covid vaccine doesn't feel necessary when so much of the world is ignoring rules and doing what they want. Why do I have to keep being inconvenienced ? Sacrificing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fixed myself an Oat Milk iced latte w coffee I ground myself...this morning (first time!) + Vanilla, and  Everything bagel chopped salad kit....love those (lettuce, cabbage, onion). Added freshly ground black pepper and minced onion w lemon and dill tuna. Into brine-y tastes rn. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kinda wanna french kiss Peter Chung, Gregg Araki, and M Night Shyamalan, and Richard Ayoade ...hot directors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eartha Kitt was ignored by Black men so she had a threesome with Paul Newman and James Dean...two of the hottest whites of Hollywood...she's too good!!! nWhat we're not gonna do is disrespect her to big up Blk men who didn't fw Black/biracial  women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like a broken record. I don't like the fans tht are #HASHTAG# antis. So many comments abt the non binary/trans characters and "I miss the old show" ok? So go watch it. Or pretending Charlotte wasn't ignorant and sheltered. She literally calls herself a WASP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like tht Sydney Sweeney got to showcase her range and not just her breasts. The sex scenes were beautifully shot and not lingering on her nude. But interestingly they specifically shot around Elordi so as not to show his butt. Just don't show anyone nude then. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A very iconic 2-3 season run but tbh it would've been better as a very good 12 episode miniseries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring Maggie Q and Paula Patton AND Thandiwe Newton back to Mission Impossible challenge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sidney won't be around to fight Ghostface forever. Nor Gale. I'm glad they are back and this isn't a remake. But I'm perfectly ok w a new core cast. So long as we get Justice for Kirby in this or Scream 6. She was primed for New Final Girl Trilogy a decade ago :( #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm mostly here for the nostalgia, mythology, choreography, intrigue and fashion/ style...as w Bond films. Not the politics. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#90sWitch . But it's important to be aware of such things of course. It's a good show so far but I can feel the pro US sentiment lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how does native american reparations lessen the anti-blackness lana displays??? .... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am BEGGING DC for a Birds of Prey follow up focusing on David Cain and Shiva, a Harley &amp; Ivy solo, and a Huntress project. I'm too glad Black Canary is happening. But put respect on Cathy Yan and Christina Hodson. They know what's what! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh ? I didn't know that lol I thought it was wholly unique each time they had a new incarnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's weird. But I do think Black Adams proves intriguing. I do wish they had proper ethnic and cultural representation from behind to infront of the screen. Dwayne/Rock being a fan of the material doesn't justify tht. Looking vs Being!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Scream 4 was released later it would've been obvious and heavy handed as a social commentary on internet fame/and influencer culture...for whatever magical reason...it is so striking watching it 10 years on and seeing EVERYTHING come true. Totally predicted all of this. Wow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love that the finale of Halloween H2O and Scream 3 take place in the same house...the legacy. 
Omg Selma Blair was considered for Jennifer Jolie? I could see it. But I wish she was Angelina instead so we'd have her and Parker interact. Why did Alicia Silverstone turn it down?:(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jessica Jones noir detective series/or Disney Plus film purr. Let's go. Elektra solo. Let's go!!!!! Daughters of the Dragon (fuck Iron Fist!) Let's go!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colin Farrell in 'The Killing of a Sacred Deer' (2017) dir. Yorgos Lanthimos, cinematography by Thimios Bakatakis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lashana Lynch as Nomi, 007 in 'No Time To Die' (2021) dir. Cary Joji Fukunaga,  costume design by Suttirat Anne Larlarb #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Y'all were right. Jessica Henwick ate down too. Brilliant young actress and she has to be the new Action Hollywood Girl. I need a Resurrections sequel where she has scenes w Trinity NOW. #HASHTAG#. Likely last film I'm seeing for a while in theatres BC of covid restrictions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Omg I love u both omg omg omg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Omg Sydney Sweeney is Felicia Hardy/Black Cat confirmed purr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She's so ugly. I don't like that we have to spare words BC she has body image issues as if tons of Black ppl don't... I don't have to be nice or respectful to a 40 year old racist like Khloe the ogre. She radiates eerie energy and they say she smells like earring backs!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't give a fuck abt celebrities breaking up personally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh. Ppl are bringing up tht Sidney Poitier's family is white/biracial as hell. And then others r saying "so?" BC so is Diana Ross, Diahann Carroll and Eartha Kitt's/or they married/dated white men + the convo abt BM often ignoring BW to fw white women back in the day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what in the prom night ass flowers in the attic... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Gentlewoman
'Power Play'
(March 2021) 
Daniel P. Shea - Photographer
Grace Bol - Model #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So did Azealia Banks audition for Faye or was it Minka Kelly-Biracial Lover's role??? We need to knownn...I think it was for a stripper or something, no? #HASHTAG#... Could u imagine Zendaya and Azealia in a scene together....so like heavy metal and reflective]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think this is a lesson tht even near white passing or lightskin, mixed biracial people are "still Black" ..but tht some people can willingly choose to benefit from an oppressive, racist, imperialist structure and even when they experience the lows of it, protect it. Yup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She was in twin peaks, some cannibal movie and Baby Driver !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I thought of DeWanda as Storm. Def w those eyes. But I would prefer a taller actress for that role.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Blackout is her Velvet Rope era methinks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Eternals is honestly such a good, distinct and fun movie. It was so mythological! I loved tht aspect and the cast chemistry. Need more!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Watch Ken Park if u wanna basically say a working class Euphoria but with unsimulated sex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keira Knightley in the green dress from 'Atonement' (2007) dir. Joe Wright | costume design by Jacqueline Durran, cinematography by Seamus McGarvey #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wait list for booster shot &lt;3
another weight lifted off my back, my small back!
i heard all the vaccine appointments were booked-which is so annoying, it's like a race- the hunger games when new vaccines become available. It's stressful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like the Black people in fandom/geek culture who are intent on defending their white friends who get regularly dragged for being racist...probably deeply desire to be whipped by them, adjacent to them sexually and platonically. Like...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Started casually watching Golden Girls. The actresses were in their 60s playing 50 something's. Interesting bc #HASHTAG# is portraying the same age. And fans are PISSED abt the repeated themes of aging and disability...yikes. the original SATC explored aging often]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learned a lot of pop choreography in Quarantine 2020 and I can confirm it's a great cardio workout, as well as a general vibe. Who Do You Think You Are is one of my favorite Spice Girls songs! I want to be Mel B BADLY....so I love doing tht one. As well as Blackpink singles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are all the Pineapple bad girls???? The bad girls from the ISLANDS???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The next things Megan Fox needs to secure is a spot on Hulu show (would've been great on High Fidelity season 2 but they played w us, so I'm thinking How I Met Your Father or Dollface season 3), and a John Wick type of film with a good budget. Atomic Blonde sequel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Megan Fox and FKA twigs in their cringe era :(((((]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Britney Spears Star Search flashBACKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe even a little hand toss...cus he was fine as fuck. Actually I'd just have a threesome w the hot preacher AND the angel. It's what Eartha Kitt would've #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also I'm not gonna watch Peacemaker but I love Danielle Brooks to death. Hope it gets 5 seasons. Purely for her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i remember the tagline on bbckids was 'two 15 year old girls experience forbidden love' ...didn't know this show would be such a good, memorable program...gosh. Sugar is a biracial/black girl and she is definitely the type of character y'all would stan if the show came out now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who cares abt the cw wanting to sell. Warner Bros give Prudence Night a spinoff NOW!!! Hbo Max? Netflix...? I'm calling u rn #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I feel like everyone in euphoria is becoming a bad girl... Even Gia had her moment lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brittany Murphy would've ATE Sharp Objects...could u imagine...like the areas of tht performance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope the world is thankful I got my vaccines. I feel like so many people have sacrificed during this pandemic and have not received any sort of catharsis. My first shots were at City Hall. Went well. This pharmacy I went to for the booster was not a vibe at all. Ghetto! Ghetto! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wondering if these are white women who wrote this article. Hmm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danny Glover..so sexy. That's a Black king right there. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sinead O'Connor was right abt the Pope. Free her NOW!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I made a black tea yesterday with real allspice as well as orange peel rind. Gonna water cleanse my hair and then do a hair rinse &lt;3 
Stay safe. Idk what will happen in the next few weeks. I'm staying IN!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have to laugh. They keep pushing Mal Mattress as the Angelina Jolie of her generation when the only white w demonstrated range is Margot Robbie. Gal Gadot can lead several deaths on multiple Niles...but she'll never be what her agents want her to be. Ever. Can't act!!!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# None of the Netflix shows were tht good after their first seasons. Save for Daredevil season 2. Luke Cage after season one part 1, and Jessica Jones....fell off. Good talent. Bad writing :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah girl...whole neighborhood knows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twin Shadow (George Lewis Jr.) style #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Brad Renfro. My baby :(((( 
Yooo listen. Anyone with a brain that is aware of Singer allegations would call into question McKellen- an out gay man...who has been silent throughout the DECADES of stories abt Bryan. I feel the same abt Jackman, and Stewart too. It's suspicious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Millie Bobby was at a film premiere and looked stylish....and got posted on filmupdates would ppl be crying in the quotes??? Jodie Woods is literally an influencer...she has over 1 million instagram followers. Pls educate yourself before raising your hand. Fkn dugnuts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'dve fucked Sidney Poitier and Belafonte #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I'm gonna sleep thru this booster shot, and overshare on the internet cus tbh I have a craving to act impulsively on the Grindr and tht would be #HASHTAG# decision making. This feels safer! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't get nor support dog mask wearing gay pup culture. It reminds me too much of slavery. I have similar sentiments abt interracial  couples doing BDSM/ kinks. "White Dom" = raceplay always. Idc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[anytimee i seee black gays in dog masks calling themselves pups i wonder if they let white men call them the n word...it gives, it EVOKES slavery...maybee i'm ignorant...i don't care. i said it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I agree. It's up close and in your face and we get it. Try sumn else!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sydney Sweeney the range.  Y'all was right I wasn't w y'all in the beginning when you hyped  her acting but now I am - when she was in the hallway and she was crying breaking down and then laughing and then like kind of like smiling and confident in her delusion woah #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An aside,...This is so funny bc Jenkins said this and then Wonder Woman 1984 still looked stupid!!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# wait you typed this out and I'M the illiterate one...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i have a dark academia Black girl story/tv pitch that really gives off this vibe...and it's what television needs rn! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important. So it's always like you're holding out for someone but you never ever find them. And it's depressing. So it's like do you divest and get with a white boy or do you continue to wave through these murky Waters looking for something that is I guess really rare here??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think bimbofication is stoop. Just like the yassifed/yassifcation shit...like I know I'm a hater, and I often have a negative reaction to popular things but it's bc it's uncool to me when the general yt public adopts shit that I was doing a decade ago...like ? Catch up stinky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't care ...stop projecting. My mom's literally biracial. I'm not invalidating shit. Colorism benefits those of us (me) who are admixed or mixed, so if Black women don't wanna claim interracial ppl...I don't care! Like...it's valid. Boohoo. Look at the big picture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Azealia Banks said Kanye's scalp smells like a chicken nugget when he get in the bed and tries to tell his wife she ain't enough for him.....the AUDACITY of men w bad smell!!!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Snyder Daredevil??? ...shut up. That would eat. Esp if he did Elektra too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow he hates Black people tht much?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton was first brought to my attention I think...via Lizzie McGuire so I always associated tht woman w Hilary Duff (who's done more for gays than Clinny!) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ....manipulator teas. I hate tht. Typical artsy uwu goth tattoo boy. Ew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scream is a y2k film.... Motives are incidental... It's 1996 but the anticipation for the new millennium was there. Interesting. The fear and the change prophesied for the future... The angst of the Gen X teenage demographic. And then Scream 4 feels more like 2020 than 2011...wow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No I'm not a white boy w no lips he'd never!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Like....we are so lucky we had a film w Meagan Good AND Devon Aoki!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think Jules/Kat/Maddy and even Cassie's dealings with men remind me of myself, and a lot of my old friends..but there's a way to do tht without making it seem like a fragile young person is the one "in control" when environmental factors are at play]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carrie, Samantha &amp; Miranda, 
'Sex and the City'• "The Baby Shower" (1998) Styling by Patricia Field #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wait shut up... Erika de Casier is Afro-Portuguese??? She's my sister!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Truly ... Honestly say for like Sky Ferreira I can't think of like another white girl who literally just sits around minding their own business and when they drop music it's a banger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She looks like Lexi ..Marsha is it?? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# When I heard about him holding a Gregg Araki film screening like last summer or something I was so offended I didn't get invited.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's honestly not quirky or unique to know something from the 90s. Remember how the mid 2010s were ALL abt the 80s? Well, we got passed tht...the trend is over. Why is it unrealistic Euphoria characters are dancing to Biggie? If they played Nirvana y'all wouldn't say shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Year end lists are kinda fucken like not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[teenage girls, LGBTQ/Black/ people, of color have better film critiques and reviews than the classic idea of a film critic-which is always a white man imo, we have a different perspective outside of what's traditionally upheld.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faye from euphoria reminds me of the white girls I grew up around (in the white ghetto!) tht ran around w chokers, water guns and dogs w their tails cut off and lawns tht smelled like excrement and barbie dolls. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're not progressive enough for this? Charlotte is projecting BC of Rock. This is good!!! Writing! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ashtray is a real motherfucker! That's my son! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# it's gonna b so painful watching Moon Knight bc Gaspard isn't here anymore like fuck im sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[....imagine teething from the sap of white supremacy so good and so deep u assert the false equivalence of Black people calling a white man's mowry out with "dehumanizing mixed race people".  Y'all are too old to confuse anti-sean COONery with "anti-interracial dating". Grow up. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The pandemic ...2 years nearly.. has been such a time of isolation and loneliness, and the times of celebrations for graduations, birthdays, marriages, funerals, all had to change BC of the virus. So many people aren't experiencing their "fun" years too. It's sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Y'all are so obsessed w her it's insane!!! Y'all are ugly are too. Like incredibly so! 
Like.... I don't understand having a one-sided beef with someone you don't know on the internet. Like I thought that was over by 2013.... It's time to grow up!!! And start moisturising!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chanel Oberlin would literally hate the gay men who idolize her. Same w Maddy from Euphoria...like you're the geek tht spams her insta... NOT the "one of the girls" gays that she trusts and values!!! Learn the difference!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to it. Peaks are 16, 18, 21, 25, 30, 35, 40, 45, 50 I've decided. And probably more! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# getting offended bc a Black woman called biracial children 'non black' is a little weird...find another priority...no need to cape. They don't know u!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I genuinely think ppl are uncomfortable w Non-Binary people. The imperfect use of Black/women of color needs adjustment + subtly should be employed more but I fail to see why so many fans are mad. Y'all are annoying. I like it a LOT. Stp it now! Emmys for Nixon #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vox Lux meets Nightcrawler, Perfect Blue, Black Swan and Girl Interrupted = Britney Spears biopic. Particularly fascinated with the period in which she was followed by paparazzi, &amp; the "lost" years like 2010 and the personal moments, not necessarily recreations of iconic moments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It Chapter Two was the worst sequel since Avengers Age of Ultron. Both shite!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# he's hot as fuck...i love a grumpy ass detective, it brings out the wayward Michelle Pfeiffer/Robin Givens femme fatale in me...makes me wanna meet up at a diner in the rain and play word games over coffee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think social media has made it so that we are reactionary versus nuance ...many of our opinions are based of immediate assumptions vs the grand or large picture. 
Even I have to learn this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretending Keanu Reeves and Jason Momoa are not white passing doesn't help mixed race people of color &lt;333 acknowledging someone as WP isn't an erasure on their ancestry :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I kinda feel like you should just leave the season as it is without removing already planned or shot scenes. But I understand Noth is now an issue- but I hope it doesn't have an effect on plot. Perhaps this opens up a finale spot for a Cattrall zoom call cameo? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Black/people of color shouldn't go to white therapists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[his name is E.T. Chong, and he's bothered me for a minute. Not in a 'one sided beef with strangers' type ting, but in a 'adjacent to whiteness non-Black, using BLM liberal woo woo politics as a come up, and excuse to continue the self-hate white men fetish he has. Cringe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout to Eternals for having a Black/Arab gay couple. Too many white interracial couples I feel these days. It was refreshing to see a big, Black man and a lebanese man in heart warming love. That kiss. Yes! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Jensen Ackles bullied by 20 year old mexican bad girl Jessica Alba? Love this song turn it UP!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# why is calling biracial people biracial or mixed a controversy..but then people have issues with the weird colorism uprising happening and erasing monoracial Black people and brown and darkskinned people....u can't have both. It's not insulting to say the truth!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Misspelling grip as gripe BC I love to nag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer Han from 'Clueless' (1995) played by Nicole Bilderback #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No need to mince words. She hated MLK she was a racist. All she had was that chanel suit. Everything else was a mess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Period. Same. Or binge watch comics explained videos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YouTube needs to make a block button so I don't have to see tht Hyram character show up in my feeds everytime I search for a skincare video. Like the girls said he used random little African kids in his brand photos...I h word when mfs do tht and genuinely find him annoying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# white men laughing at white women for doing the exact same shit they do...hmm...missing the punchline here mommas... like why are you laughing, that's your sister!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, it's not far off from CW. But I also think that this is an HBO film so it's going to be less flashy than a theatrical film - but it's definitely looking homemade which Barbara Gordon does do in the comics- making her own suit. Im going into Batgirl w an open mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Naomie Campbell + Grace Jones should be the visual blueprint for MCU Storm. Gone is the basic biracial cashew shit they did at Fox w Halle Berry and Shipp, who- even if not untalented were WRONG for the part and on top of tht always under served. Hate those X-Men films.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black 29 year old NFT story is a BIRD ass story. We don't care. Stop pushing tht weird crypto shit! Y'all really think ppl in the future are gonna be dealing in links vs augmented reality of our current tech....pls get out of here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Could u imagine a nihilistic dark academia colored Gossip Girl series run by Gregg Araki? The areas it would go??? The guest stars?? The music??? 
I'm sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rue having real teenage skin... I love tht #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Premiere bad/it girl from the early 2010s. I miss the pre-tattoo Amber Rose era #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg I remember when Nico Tortorella was gonna be an It *Boy. They used to be so hot. I hear they're a weirdo IRL tho...like yikes. #HASHTAG# n*They r Non-Binary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grindr app is full of rapists and once they got rid of free trials and the ethnicity filter u can barely ever find Black ppl ....so it's pointless. Then again how else do u meet queer ppl in a restriction era pandemic??? Fucken sickening ....traumatic. disturbing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't smile because I have responsibility to the fashion community just like Victoria Beckham. Like who smiles and photos and selfies? Stinkers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# but they had a lot of silent or dead widows from the Red room and I didn't really enjoy that I wish they gave them more to do. I hope we see a sequel with Yelena where we see the former widows as a team. Hard question I don't really know what either of these movies say abt women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly if I was nonBlack and someone said my work basically made them uncomfortable re: the legacy of colonialism and featurism ...I'd engage in a respectful and understanding matter versus the way the designer did. I see a lot of biracial people doing this shit too #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i can sometimes tell a person's age based on how they speak on a podcast..but Black people's speech patterns aren't as predictable.... like they'll hint abt being like late 40s and i'm like oh whoa wow...never knew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ltw's husband Herbert can like ....get it. I love a handsome Black man. He looks like he has a lite dad bod too....my thing. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think one of the women will be queer, and if they are with Sara Ramirez...tht will be dope too. I am just tired of seeing interracial couples EVERYWHERE on tv, bc it's always white x black... I would be A-ok if it was South, East Asian, Indigenous and Black pairings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[which has offensive dialogue every 30 seconds or homophobia baked into Chandler, Joey and Ross. Anyways, I'm disappointed some loud fans are complaining abt #HASHTAG# bc it's the best thing since the first movie. And feels natural if you KNOW the original SATC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HBO Max give us High Fidelity season 2 purr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# like wtf is a bipoc* person?? mfs ain't even using the acronym correctly.... it's a new 'poc' term meant to umbrella all non-whites together and distract/detract from the issue white supremacy and antiblackness are. *Black, Indigenous person of color person? Really...like..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# how come they never answer if Jesus was white or not??? Like ...I want to know wht Black christians think Jesus looked like...actually all non-whites who go to churches tht are ran by their community]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got hotter 
And you got grosser... Do like...over u!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Basically what I mean is if you could be happy with a non-black why are you waiting around centering black men who are always treating you like shit? Like aren't you kind of like a freaking idiot for doing that? But I feel like for me Black love or like sexuality intimacy is so #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only time you'll see Bella on my page is rn. Alexa ate! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the next Scarlet Witch project gonna include some Roma people or...?? Just continue to not explore that very interesting aspect of the Marvel lore? It's what right. Easily could add a Romani supporting character.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>