<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Atiku/Obi giving off that Obama/Biden vibes. 

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is this a religion thing or a Nigerian thing? This ravenous stupidity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Nigerians started their own #HASHTAG# , it'd be filled with girls who ate transport fares and stopped picking calls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have drunk dialed.... So sad rn. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yes. It is important we stop praising a govt for paying salaries and requiring tangible plans for development. I personally know the impact the presence of just the Ama Breweries has had on my hometown. Enugu needs plans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No. That's creepy asf. Which 14y/o thinks of sacrificing their unfuckingborn child for dick?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #HASHTAG# men love my #HASHTAG# also #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# men love me. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure NCDCgov would be interested but sure,  no harm in asking. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is so not too much to ask for one's daily bread. Dunno about soft ones though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.#USER# . A friend told me about you guys few nights ago. I love the work you are doing and would love to be part of the journey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You forgot me"

Average Nigerian: nooo, ah, how can I forget you, am I mad? It's just that ..

Legendary Nigerian: yes I did. Come and lynch me. I am at 1/3 Pound  Road, Aba. Wen u reach there, tell the keke guy to drop you in front of Oja's shop. It's just 50naira to my place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# He actually can. Your pastors can actually can. The bar isn't that low yet. I know an artist that stopped selling paintings to fraudsters. It's that simple.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# Such an astute military commander #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All around you, people are battling with mental health. All you say is suicide isn't an option. Wouldn't it be best for you to research on diff mental health challenges or just shut up? Because you sound retarded and that's the sadder part— that you chose not to educate yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Lemme just say, as a first born, y'all young ones are so annoying. My brother hasn't returned my polo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like there is a passive aggressive message whenever Twitter does this. Like we know you didn't do anything now but don't do nothing if you were considering it, mate. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[brand yourself into anything on social media and have people believing that perosna

It's cool. 

Just like being a drug dealer or illusionist, people only start running into troubles when they start believing their own BS!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Enjoy your vanilla. Keep it moving, ma'am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Rapists! Criminals! #USER# is an idiot. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does this feel like hearing that I was born out of wedlock?🥺 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Good Muslim role model. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rape is not in our culture; and so is every act, speech, teachings, thoughts, assumptions, figures, and failures that have made us sleep and watch this abomination go on and on. 

And no, a rape case doesn't have to trend for us to talk about rape.

Chukwu aju!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Bravo judges #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "friendzone" and "big head" in the same tweet don't make sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mom is opposite but worse. She perfected the art of passive aggression. Instead of shouting, she'd cook and come serve you. Your mind will kill you. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# That Antifa was viciously violent didn't come into it #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# We,"white men" are very interesting #HASHTAG# - Just in case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One time in my teens, an overzealous aunt thought I was possessed and bundled me off to Awhum monastery. I sulked all thru the one week prayer camp trip till I got lost and found the water falls. For the followingtwo years, I visited the falls and caves every month. It's glorious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lemme quickly create an account for my coke bottle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me to bae: this is the last time I'm showing you something from the internet. You never laugh. 

Also Me: lmao, babe check this out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# #USER# Sorry #HASHTAG# and #HASHTAG# are registered for #HASHTAG# or #HASHTAG#. Even … #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is a beautiful thing to have, honestly. As rich as English is, I feel it is suffocating to sustain a refreshing worldview.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# He only did it because he hated black people. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# I love preachy, judgey Catholics! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear WCW,

I bought a new fan. Would you like to come over so we'd pop the bubble wraps together over wine? 

Yours sincerely,
Oja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I pin this tweet as a point of contact...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# .#USER# , I'm reading this and a lot of countries are coming to my mind and you are right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You people are mad and I'd love to join your digital marketing team. Damn, I love you guys. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Being with the heaviness and emptiness of a consciousness that wants to die in a body that is yearning to live is something you need to humbly  sit to understand if you genuinely want to. But if all you feel is the anger towards him, maybe you should speak at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Portlandia | What About Men? | IFCn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About society, about Twitter, about marriage, death and suicide. She mentions a movie she saw the night before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You mean "indabos—wetin". Please stay in character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are a country of numb people. We are not asleep; you can wake someone who is asleep. We are numb. No stimulus can get us to act and drive change. A stimulus like a Video evidence of a governor shoveling bribe into his pocket can't get us to act. New hashtags but we can't feel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Narratives after passing 6 generations by word of mouth. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I thought I mistakenly clicked on another tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It could be something they love which that religion happens to provide and has absolutely nothing to do with a god.  I have a friend who doesn't believe in god but will never miss a Sunday service because of choir. He loves singin and will give hours in a week to choir rehearsals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think experience in the verbal structures of each language determines understanding of speech acts— Semantics. So while they may not pick up on "English based sarcasm", they can sell you with say Igbo based sarcasm and have you looking like dindin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is closer to spoken word art than science or even religion #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: We need more illegal immigrants like this #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It is conventional wisdom that one's grasp on sanity has to be tenuous to produce such. Operative word - CONVENTIONAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why is no one talking about the guy on Twitter wanting to £&amp;&amp;-_ a pregnant woman?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But these days I have actual back breaking tasks and I’m not having fun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: What's the uproar on this beauty? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#  #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew I should get me a box and some birds when y'all started comparing Beyonce to MJ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Country hard my sister. Had to reduce screen time or go hungry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What did they do? Why are they being dismissed. Did they engage in extrajudicial killing or torture? Why aren’t they being persecuted?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do not want anyone else to kill cercei apart from Greyworm. And if Arya does it, on God,  I'll sulk for weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: RT #USER#: #HASHTAG# has zero tolerance for #HASHTAG# but ok with beheading children? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So, no use of social media. In my case, I check WhatsApp and email in case of emergencies since I turn off all notifications before sleeping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And craziest too, and they don't even tell you beforehand sef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Apparently, #HASHTAG# don't hate - but everybody else does.  #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Actually it is "hanged". Hung is for inanimate things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now you see why I'm of the view that the idea of beauty is a flaw in human thinking. And I'm always grateful that art exists outside this concept. Time too. So I believe you can raise your child without emphasizing beauty or the lack of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, it's that big paschal candle I'll pour on you. Lent will be over in a few  hours dear, you've fought the good fight(I doubt). After tomorrow, we can revisit candle wax on areola.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I know I'm supposed to be pissed at these women but I can't help pitying them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Finally! Someone understood the gay agenda! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# See her nose like control oyel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.#USER# will yap about devices till you pass out. I like him #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ehe na. She already got her unsullied, her dragons, and the leader of the night's watch eating her out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That's why you'll go to (petty people's) heaven. Ezigbo nwa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Woukd have invited you to come and eat but it's a destination something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# More so because this affects us all. Every young person has or knows someone who has had a SARS experience. I’ve had 3.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You people are mad on this app ooo. So you will tell someone who can and cannot attend their own hangout? Hian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is obvious you have internalized so many stereotypes about short people including the anger issue. So, I can't really trust your assessment. It is ok to have your preferences. Frm your writing, you clearly are disgusted by him which is terrible and I suggest you work on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think even goats would be closing their mouths if they could help it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# I think he is most upset that Democrats in 1820 were the real fascists. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is messed up on so many levels. Funny thing, it isn't an isolated incident. Quite common in universities for those who don't have to balls to have conversations about threesomes. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# i'll smack you into next week if you don't do as you are told now!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# #USER# They're cops. They don't count. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Thought you antifa folks were all about no hate.. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So if I'm on a date with you and you are pressing your phone, I'm gonna stand and leave you with your phone and the bill. 

PS. I know this comment doesnt have anything to do with the tweet. Don't drag me pls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I just texted my own mum on WhatsApp. Nonsense. She'll hear it today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He is a buhari defender. I think you got your hopes up too fast expecting sense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anger isn't necessarily a negative thing and it is important we express it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You should try Fernando Pessoa or Rilke or Boleslaw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think it flawed the book as the narrator is always either naive or biased. In the case of TFA, you will understand that, among other instances, Okonkwo killing Ikemefuna wasn't necessarily coz he didn't want to seem weak (as the narrator concluded).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Tell that to my cousin who wants to study law because of 'Suits']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# I can't wait for the #HASHTAG# to demand his job over this #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The kinda thing you stand for isn't one that can be met with a simple lifestyle change. It is about people's mind. So you might find you'd have to preach for long before it is noticeably internalized but you are not alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# We need more homeless ! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nothing says bougie like apple and Heineken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# I wonder if #USER# will call him a terrorist? n#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I stumbled on the #HASHTAG#. 
My mother, "Ijeoma", was born during the war, my father at 14 fought in the war and I "stumbled" on it. Found lots of books on it at age of 13 and began devouring them. We should not forget nor have to stumble on it. 

#HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# #USER# And those Jews were so inconsiderate, existing and whatnot. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are tied of dying, 

Dying makes living a numbing dream. 

We have given and given endlessly till all we have is this voice as we cry to anyone out there; save our souls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Because pastor's wife doesnt automatically have a degree in clinical psychology. Y'all should stop all these abeg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I'd love to learn how to draw henna. Just to use it to bond better with my partner. Where can I learn?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# #USER# Cept for those Trannies in the military amirite? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# But I thought ANTIFA was being peaceful? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# It's because of the gays. It's always our fault! #HASHTAG# 🤣]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Here's Antifa beautifying Parisn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Partner: what do we do tonight? 

Me: same thing we do every night, Pinky, try to #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# #USER# Scary antifa, they should be ashamed! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Anyway, this black Lexus in traffic is hot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think its for kids. And the layout is tacky. If I don't want to talk to you , I won't. You'll see me online, viewing your stat. You can't do nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I'm gonna camp here and get the full gist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish these words can carry the weight of what I feel but each day I step out the door, I think about death a lot. The value of human life is low in Nigeria and it is not humbling.  Instead, it makes life tasteless on this side of the sun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# BUT WHAT ABOUT THE TRANS PEOPLE IN OUR CHILDREN'S BATHROOMS?! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just another day of tech disrupting culture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I often find it super sad, especially when such ladies are vocal about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you think we should do to sexist arts that are dope like some Patty Obassey songs. 

#USER# 
#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I'm trying to see how it connects with the issue at hand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Somebody drop that pic of Olamide walking out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one has ever called them the good guys #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anytime Soka opens his mouth, I start laughing. 

"Youuuu waaaaaaat, enrolled in waaaaaaa? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Line 1 I was like "no way he can find a way to blame women for this". But typical Nigerian man is that resourceful. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: RT #USER#: Trump is a racist and black people hate him.  #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once a Nigerian starts losing an argument they begin chanting "let's agree to disagree". No! I got you by the balls and I'm not letting go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Eminem singing of Trump and it felt he was talking about Buhari. Uncanny!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You can claim temporal insanity. Everyone will goan rest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Couldn't possibly be illegal votes for Democrats #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# #USER# But they wouldn't do those kinds of things......The #HASHTAG# told me. nn#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# #USER# Wait.....Anti-Fa was there?? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What's ile igbe please. I need it for my citation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Out of the shadows of the past we come to cheer you. Boys of the old brigade of gallant CIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[from the university bookstore.A boy didn't subtly invite you to come eat coz he knew you are too stupid to admit you were broke and famished]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: No way...didn't see THIS coming #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Was getting a big weighty for me there. Happy to connect with you here, Zainab.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# #USER# Politicians should be restricted to looking out for their own self interests! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Mixing palm wine with anything at all is already recipe for mayhem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Currently teaching Goldsmith's She Stoops to Conquer. They complained of the language. I spent last night designing a way to break down the language issue. Today, teaching, dude kept murmuring something. Was too distracting. Next thing I'm yelling "shut up!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been respecting you then one day evidence turns up that you once wished somebody"happy womb escape" and voom, respect gone, just like that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I hate fat people. I think they should be taxed more. I think they should only be allowed on Facebook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Well then. Me and my other POCs can sleep easy tonight. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg. This is unbearable. I'm going to literally die of lonesomeness. I can pay any amount for human contact just to....

Nvm, "Money Heist" is out. Phew!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Africa is beautiful. We just don't get the right coverage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s fascinating just how much the film #HASHTAG# highlights confirmation bias — the tendency to interpret new evidence so that it confirms one’s existing beliefs.

1. The ones so neck-deep into gender roles who get turned off by the idea of helping out their men say THIS IS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# #USER# And off course, black people ain't racist #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If it was my cousins, something would have been done about it already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I kid you not but if not the hype other people generate towards my birthday, I'd be forgetting every year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Going forward, TL gists should be well arranged]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What changed? 

For me it was three things that happened simultaneously around the time I was in senior secondary. 

1. My proficiency in English was being rewarded. In fact, much of my becoming the senior prefect was due to that proficiency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have heard this line many times and it has proven to be an effective tool to shutting up voices for truth. We see through it. But to answer your question, if the platform is to run like that (a business), it shouldn't masquerade itself as a voice for truth. They chose a hustle #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spend between 5 and 6 hours in Lagos traffic everyday. The idea of 5 hours daily reading  sounds badass. But then there is the guy that cant wait to slap me through the window and take my phone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I know how it feels to be born and live in this place. But the most tragic part is believing nothing can be done;than there isn't any good. Dont let them win, bro. I'm assuming you haven't totally lost yourself to the woes of this nation. We can still do something. Speak out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is a given. But you can't deny the harm those have especially given as men don't become men overnight. They arrive there with the conditioning from more amenable years as boys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And then, there are the rude ones that give you heart attacks from the way they start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is going on in Benin is no longer #HASHTAG# protests. I’ve been stuck on the road for 2 days now. Last night they were beating up an old truck driver for not giving them money. 

They are burning cars. The violence I saw last night was much. 

Kindly retweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My own is that they should grow up, their constant splitting games are no longer cute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: RT #USER#: Obviously we need millions more immigrants like this #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Some kid sent that to my fb messenger.  First shit I saw today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# #USER# Don't be ridiculous. Gay people can't be sexist! n#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I so want to high-5 you rn and walltz out here with you in slow-mo like in deadpool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I better come home to light today or I'm gonna sulk all night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No, we don't experience it. When someone says stop, fucking stop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #HASHTAG# is out ? Well the liberals should be 100% satisfied now.....n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# As if you ever took a literature course. And before you mention Ng Lit, that ain't a literature course. It's kinda like a Lit GS course]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chukwu Okike Abiama, I see what you are doing for others ooooooo #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I doubt that there any people more romantic than the Igbos, intact, words can be inflected to reflect the emotion you feel towards a person while speaking to them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: RT #USER#: Some days it's tough being vegan #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The bed is absorbing 70% of the strokes. Try this on the bare floor, give me feedback anon. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so underrated. Started this with some friends in Enugu and it has been a blessing. Usually the highlight of our week. The conversations are out of this world #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What's it called. Coz I'm doing it for game night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everytime these guys appear on the TL I lose respect for Nigerian girls. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Haven't quite thought about it as something you "give" though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# #USER# So you know a Muslim but haven't been beheaded! How is that possible? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I believe we can still have those conversations even after elections. Goad them to have a town hall meeting with us for discussions. The trend here is "empowerment" which is basically just one politician sharing money to attendees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣even great Rome as spoken ill of by charlatans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG##HASHTAG##HASHTAG# (my muslim repellent of choice!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# With practice, it'd become second nature to you. Maybe it was easier for me because I was introduced to it, with incentives of corporal punishment, during my formative years. But I do think with practice you'll get the hang of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Made smoothies everyday after I got mine. Can't remember the last time I ever used it. #USER# has cashed out Sha. We move. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m not gonna lie, I felt personally attacked in a lot of places watching the arguments on #HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is a big issue if someone apologizes perfunctorily like that. It is a big red flag and you shouldn't overlook it. Don't ignore your gut feelings. When you meet, make a list of sincere questions to ask her. I could help with that. You have great instincts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You'd find yourself asking deep existentialist questions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Silly #USER# liberals aren't logical. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to be untouchable. To brew with confidence and a belief in what we can do. So that we can open doors and stare interviewers and critics in the eyes and let them feel the heat of what we are. We are not to be clouded by the flaws in human thinking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's just empathy. Even trained soldiers are prevented from knowing who's bullet kills a condemned critical in firing squads. Just humanity. 

Anyway, place your orders for these cuties and pay on delivery #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy is gooooood. His work ethics is out of this world too #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What if kissing unleashes an crazy side of her? What if it'd make her tie you up and make you choke while she watches. She just saved your life and you are here whining.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I loathed the "London picture" fever with my entire being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That's precariously close to colonialism. Ooooooh, I see what you did there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# Priest ALWAYS has the best legendaries #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In a way the post implied "kids that read". So except kids who have zero interest in readin. The ones that are into books, 80 is a bit of average. You get what I mean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No. I meant the cardigan. Who stretches such a beautiful cardigan for no reason? Retards, that's who!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[🎶🎶The meme wey we get oo I no go fiiiinish. Amen. Too much meme no go killi person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cue in soundtrack while pressing out some Sunshine dish washer***

Somebody saaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaave meeeeeeee!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# All hindus must be racists! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# Are millennials into anything?! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# #USER# 😲 How can this be?'I thought all white men are racist? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Like if she didnt , she is robbing God of his Glory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My mum flung the centre table and redid her wrapper five times coz she found out from me that I kissed a girl. I got a call from all her siblings and father that same night. I was 17.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Trust me, I've seen them turn an academic conference for a journal into a banquet of eulogies for themselves because they were invited as special guests and the small money they'd drop (or pledge). But enugu needs this. If we and the govt are walking same path, it'd be easier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I do. But maybe there is something wrong with me coz I tend to root for the underdog, so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You not getting off easy. All you spoilers need to he held accountable...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Just has to be. Gives me headache when I wake and nightmares when I sleep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But ndi nwe m na ndi m nwe, I was wrong. Lady kept staring, apparently lost in the  entertainment that is unfolding rather quickly before her. Next thing, one of the boys unknowingly flung a finger in her direction. Nothing major.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# #USER# And don't forget the thousands of cheering Muslims at the rally. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny how this tweet is a template for a lot of leaders now. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Abandoned The Myth of Sisyphus in 2013. Maybe I should try it again.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>