<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Wounded Warrior Project 5K raises money to help injured veterans ‘Carry Forward’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ukraine conflict is ‘not inevitable’, Pentagon chief says #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protected: Questions from the parents: Q&amp;A with Charlotte Country Day School #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sarah Palin Paints the Town COVID #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dori: Seattle K9 killed in line of duty mourned; loss triggers memories for dog owners #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Diego Unified approves redistricting map meant to increase racial minorities’ representation #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raskin: Trump ‘Owes’ January 6 Probe ‘His Testimony’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detroit Police: Amazon Driver Confesses To Lying About Carjacking #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Jersey Residents Battle Inches Of Snow, Rough Road Conditions #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Targeted Surrey shooting leaves 2 seriously injured: RCMP – BC | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom Convoy 2022: Police report no injuries, ‘no incidents of violence’ after first day of protest #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chicago Bears Hire Colts Defensive Coordinator Matt Eberflus as Head Coach: AP Source #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man sentenced to 25 years to life for attempted murder of 4 Nassau County police officers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Rogan posts photos of Tesla’s Cybertruck on IG, says it’s ‘coolest car I’ve ever seen’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHOTOS: Winter storm pummels East Coast with high winds, deep snow #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giving on 10: American Cancer Society brings back Daffodil Days campaign #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covid live news: Russia reports record 121,228 new cases; UK to start vaccinating vulnerable children #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State of Texas: Amid concern for soldiers in Operation Lone Star, leaders work to address issues #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gardner makes history with top gong, Starc named AB medal winner #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liverpool close to spectacular £50m Diaz transfer after beating Man Utd to punch #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are Asian women the target of xenophobia? – The San Francisco Examiner #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 On Your Side: NYC restaurant loses weekend of business over untimely gas inspection #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[14 guests at Ohio hotel, including at least 6 children, hospitalized after carbon monoxide leak #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police investigating North Denver shooting #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China backs Russia’s ‘security concerns’ in crisis with west over Ukraine #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayer and Prostitutes: Redeeming Love Tackles Faith-Based Romance – LA Weekly #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scans reveal hidden lung damage in some Long Covid patients #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 Killed in Multi-Vehicle Collision on Highway 138 [Phelan, CA] #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ash Gardner awarded Belinda Clark Medal #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fighting ongoing in Syria’s Hassakeh as SDF raids ISIL hideouts #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[’14 people never came home’: Taoiseach and President pay tribute to Bloody Sunday victims #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 Firefighters Injured At Laundromat Fire In Dorchester #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Best Redhead OnlyFans (Top Only Fans Red Heads)  – LA Weekly #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the pandemic’s unequal toll on people of color underlines U.S. health inequities – and why solving them is so critical #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Irish clowns defeated orange Toronto cops #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crypto Rich Emerge as New Buyer Pool for Luxury Real Estate #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michigan High School Students Participating In Safe Driving Campaign #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perth dad charged with drugging and raping two women he met through ‘Sugar Daddy’ site #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanasi Kokkinakis, Nick Kyrgios seek doubles crown on milestone day for Australian tennis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should Delaware allow terminally ill patients to end their life? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ASK AMY: Dad moved in, now – how to get him out? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bus Driver Shortage Causes Metro To Slash Service Citywide #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ecuador vs Brazil LIVE: Latest updates from World Cup qualifier #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boris Johnson urged to ‘go back to the drawing board’ on controversial National Insurance rise after PM and Rishi Sunak double down on plan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Diego journalists honor slain Tijuana colleagues at Mexican Consulate #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Authorities search for burglary suspect after high-speed chase ends in downtown LA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adams to NYPD’s 35,000 Cops: ‘I’m Here for You … New Yorkers Are Here for You’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gardai investigate alleged sexual assaults on teenage girls in Sligo #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Best Chinese Dating Sites: Meet Chinese Online #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside the life of Gunther IV – a German shepherd who inherited £280million #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Hag Gives Readers the Good, the Bad, and the Merle #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caesars Sportsbook NY promo goes deep with $1,500 match, free NFL bets | amNewYork #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday Sport: Tyrone face Monaghan in National League, McIlroy takes joint-lead in Dubai | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadine Dorries faces squealing lefties: HENRY DEEDES watches Culture Sec shredding the licence fee #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sue Gray report: When is inquiry due, what does it mean for Boris Johnson and who decides what happens next? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Action plan for overhaul of parks and wildlife service to go to Cabinet #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AG guidance to New Yorkers following expired eviction moratorium #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liverpool sign Colombia forward Luis Diaz on long-term deal from Porto #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Harlem vigil for cops shot in ambush, Adams and other leaders pledge to shut down the ‘iron pipeline’ | amNewYork #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taliban, Western officials hold landmark talks on food crisis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The cold-weather anxiety about the Texas grid is real. But so far, this winter is pretty normal | Houston Public Media #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USMNT Head Coach Gregg Berhalter Praises Matt Turner’s Incredible Work Ethic While Confirming Goalkeeper’s Transfer To Arsenal #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indigenous, Native American tribes are pushing for voting rights #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Onion Looks Back On The Greatest Quarterback To Lose 3 Super Bowls #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate meeting proposes national methane plans #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin’s aggression behind sea change in Ukrainian attitudes toward Russia #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ceremony in Quebec City marks fifth anniversary of mosque shooting #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Post-Brexit residence status: Sweden rejects more Brits than any other EU country #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tribal eviction plan pits Native American authority vs. civil rights #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rifle used by Kyle Rittenhouse in Kenosha protest shootings to be destroyed. Bail money to be split up, with actor Ricky Schroder to get small percentage. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virginia Republicans push for changes in marijuana law #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senegal vs Equatorial Guinea: How can I watch live on TV in UK today? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bay Area Projects to Benefit From U.S. Infrastructure Funding #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syrian refugees face yet another struggle as heavy rains flood displacement camp #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic Republic of Congo court sentences 51 to death in murder of UN experts #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Pegasus, Life Is Good runs away from Knicks Go #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harry and Meghan weigh in on Spotify row saying they expressed concerns about COVID misinformation last April #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Week in Review: Criminal Justice Leaders on Same Page This Week #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brighton PD identifies 83-year-old woman killed by car backing out #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man arrested in Lakeside with ghost guns, burglary tools #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Raiders star Damon Arnette arrested in Las Vegas on gun and drugs charges #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giannis Antetokounmpo’s 38 points sink skidding Knicks #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPDATE: Fire Burns Pleasant Hill Senior Living Facility; Injured Resident Rescued From Balcony #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghan women’s rights activist ‘hopeful’ after talks with Taliban delegation in Norway #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adams Once Lobbied For Raise The Age Law — Now His Push To Roll It Back Faces Headwinds In Albany #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BNSF's proposed Arizona rail intermodal facility would be 'transformative' for the region #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Oakland County Priest Pleads Guilty In Sex Abuse Cases, Sentenced Up To 15 Years #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Park is ground zero in Colorado’s wolf controversy. Ranchers want to know if anyone hears them. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sundance Review: Emergency Is Quite a Ride #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joni Mitchell removes songs from Spotify ‘in solidarity with Neil Young’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Portugal picks new government with $50B of EU funds on table #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Southern California Airports To Get Millions From Biden Administration Infrastructure Law #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House shooting in Fort Worth lands person in the hospital; police are investigating #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Philadelphia Seeing Snow-Covered Roads, Blustery Conditions As Nor’easter Pushes Through #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Onion’s Test Sweatshop Helps You Design Your Dream Kitchen #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future Leaders Winner Passionate About Math &amp; Science #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeff Bezos insisted on naming rights after $200M Smithsonian donation #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China to receive significant payments for years in deal to return Irish businessman | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emmerdale killer Meena faces being EXPOSED as village learns SHOCK truth #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jacina Ardern in self-isolation as Covid cases rise in New Zealand #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Living a longer and healthier life is not all about genetics #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British diplomats meet Taliban for humanitarian talks in Oslo #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regal, Madison Int’l Realty Split on Brooklyn Theater Closure #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police Search For 3 Suspects After Armed Carjacking In Oxford Circle #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In blow to telecoms, California’s net neutrality law upheld #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Essential Workers Brave Treacherous Conditions To Keep Tri-State Area Residents Safe During Nor’easter #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shooting at apartment complex leaves man in critical condition, IMPD investigating #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brooklyn Beckham and Nicola Peltz ‘want to spend honeymoon in space’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honduras: Chaos in congress as politicians brawl over election of new president #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday Morning Constitutional: Big Rig at Fault In Deadly Richmond Bridge Crash #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bans on fossil fuel heating in new homes gain steam as world aims for net-zero emissions | CBC News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teenager and man stabbed to death in Doncaster town centre #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Escape to the Chateau’s Dick and Angel set to leave their iconic French home #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family Says Lax Security Allowed Killing Of Rapper Drakeo #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boston Properties Sees Leasing Uptick, Raises Crime Concerns #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former DUP leader Edwin Pots fails in bid to become South Down candidate #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Potential Replacements For Supreme Court Justice Breyer #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carroll County deputy, jail staffer die in accident #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six arrested after investigation into robberies targeting Asian women in San Jose #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Storm Corrie to hit UK with 90mph winds one day after Storm Malik #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lily James defends raunchy sex scenes in Disney Plus series Pam &amp; Tommy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rangers Start Fast, Then Come Unglued And Fall In Columbus #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Symphonic Exploration of That Time the US Kidnapped and Imprisoned More Than 100,000 Japanese Americans #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“He Was Not Afraid To Die.” NYPD Officer Jason Rivera Mourned At St. Patrick’s Cathedral #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Services held for fallen Texas DPS special agent Anthony Salas #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PGA Noms Boost Tick, Tick … Boom! and Being the Ricardos Oscar Odds #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cocaine worth €3.1m found in vehicle at Dublin Port #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prosecutors in Floyd killing probe use-of-force training #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OC Developer OK For Two Inland Empire Warehouses #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daywatch: Rick Bayless says omicron will devastate Chicago restaurants without federal relief | Obama Presidential Center will dedicate public space to Hadiya Pendleton | Bears hire head coach #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boris Johnson still on his feet as Conservative rebels fail to land knockout blow – but PM could still face sucker punch #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FanDuel promo code: 30-1 NFL odds, free bets this weekend | amNewYork #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State failing to protect sex workers – Amnesty #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspect Arrested After Deadly Stabbing at Spring Valley Apartment: SDSO #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Movie star Bridget Fonda seen for first time in 12 years after quitting acting #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sears: We’re ‘Challenging’ Politicians Who Deny Poor Kids School Choice and Send Their Kids to Private School #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officers Will Join Organization ‘Operation Neighborhood Safety’ At Gas Stations On City’s South Side #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 priests, 2 lay people beatified in El Salvador #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pennsylvania court strikes down state’s mail-in voting law #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Child vaccination rates are alarmingly low as doctors contend with rise in pediatric COVID cases #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sarah Palin Spotted Dining Out in NYC Again, 2 Days After Positive COVID Test #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘I don’t fall into male or female’: AFLW player Tori Groves-Little on coming out as non-binary #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Praises Canadian Convoy Protesting Trudeau’s Vaccine Mandates #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lamar and Yuma schools cling to Savages and Tribe after being told to drop Native American mascots #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grossmont and Cuyamaca College employees not receiving reasonable vaccine exemption accommodations – #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Medved: Core contradictions in MAGA world? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden promises to nominate a black woman to the US Supreme Court for first time #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adelaide’s leading rider given lengthy ban #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hochul Extends NY Mask Mandate Additional 10 Days After Court Battle #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘A trial will happen whether he wants it or not’, says US attorney #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Mom’s Farrah slammed for claiming she’s a LAWYER after exit from Harvard #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Prioritizing Antiviral Pills for ‘Non-White’ People #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduates in England hit by higher loan repayments #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeding San Diego surpasses 100 large-scale food distributions – #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding COVID booster shots and at-home test kits | Houston Public Media #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas is short thousands of workers at state health facilities | Houston Public Media #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let the games begin: Nominations for Houston's Inno Madness bracket challenge are open #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IMPD investigating deadly west side shooting #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Memorial Park Conservancy schedules public unveiling of land bridge, tunnels #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Catskill zoo hits the market for $3.6M #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gay’s 30-yard FG lifts Rams over Brady, Buccaneers 30-27 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trucker convoy’s park-in protest gears into 2nd day in Ottawa – National | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least one child among 9 killed, 1 critically injured in North Las Vegas crash #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Counsel For Michigan Redistricting Commission To Resign #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 Dead, 1 Injured After Shooting In Forest Hill #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hundreds attend commemoration event to mark 50th anniversary of Bloody Sunday | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cross-country truck convoy reaches Canada’s capital to protest COVID restrictions #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fiery North Korean Defector Charged Under New Propaganda Law #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghanistan’s Taliban have started their first talks in Europe since takeover #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Downtown Commission: Demo Request Denied, Fulton Project Approved – Columbus Underground #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World’s tallest Holiday Inn is back on the market for $187M #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK PM To Visit Ukraine, Hold Call With Russian President Vladimir Putin Next Week #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MyAnna Buring on mission to talk about mental health as star ‘saved’ by therapy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Walker made the surprising decision to stick with the North Carolina Senate race. 3 reasons that stuck out.  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a paw-ty coming up at the Original 40 Brewing Company – #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin’s oligarchs will have ‘nowhere to hide’ with widened sanctions if Russia invades Ukraine – as UK ‘rules nothing out’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elon Musk offered teen $5,000 to shut down Twitter account tracking his private flights: Report #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SD First Responders, Nonprofit Announce Lawsuit Challenging City’s Vaccine Mandate #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which Too Hot to Handle Season 3 Couples Are Still Together? They Say… – E! Online #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Hospitalizations Jump As County Reports 6,314 New COVID Cases, 22 Deaths #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man, teenage girl critically injured in triple Brooklyn shooting: cops | amNewYork #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raanta returns, helps Hurricanes beat Devils #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the middle of a pandemic, I felt alone and disconnected. A warm and welcoming church in Normal Heights changed everything #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard ‘Dick’ Duchossois, Chicago horseracing icon and longtime Arlington Park owner, dies at 100 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lisa Smith travelled to Turkey to study under Isis propagandist, court told #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Levelling Up: £1.5bn pot to ‘breathe fresh life into disadvantaged communities’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brooklyn Park Police Investigate Carjacking Outside COVID-19 Testing Site #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Censure sensibility: Once rare, party censure rises amid polarized politics – Cronkite News – Arizona PBS #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latvia hopes Canada will extend, expand military mission amid tensions with Russia #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Are you better off?’ Public Safety Round Table held in San Diego – #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Francisco Mayor Breed Getting Geared Up For 49ers-Rams NFC Championship Showdown #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow ‘Bomb’ Unleashes Blizzard On Eastern US, States Declare Emergency #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coronation Street star Kate Ford on ‘struggling’ with her endometriosis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indian village mourns family who froze to death on U.S.-Canada border #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rejected by New Zealand, reporter turns to Taliban for help #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish man reunited with family after being detained in China for almost 3 years #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[District Attorney John Kellner, a Republican, is running to unseat Colorado’s attorney general #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fort Worth Firefighters Save 7 People Trapped Inside Burning Home #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shaky start for Stellantis bid to grab larger China stake #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Reports of Tom Brady’s Retirement, His Camp Says Not So Fast #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>