<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - This is some serious next level Frankenstein shit #HASHTAG# asking her daughter for an egg. Only #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - if this continues #HASHTAG# and #HASHTAG# #USER# can stay home. #HASHTAG# is speaking positive things into existence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# spitballing here but hey #USER# #USER# and the rest of #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# politicos, how about getting the borough another hospital?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Excuse me but don't politicians both #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# have to win the majority of votes in each state in order to get that state's #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# media specifically #USER# &amp; #USER# are phenomenal at live fact checking candidates. #HASHTAG# was  stopped from misinforming on #HASHTAG#. oh, #USER# is great at moderating debates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# this is why #HASHTAG# follower like #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# "pieces are falling into place" Question: is that place the garbage or stolen? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# residents that are ignoring the #HASHTAG# request and get angry at #HASHTAG# for shutting things down must also hate it when public #HASHTAG# are #HASHTAG# after someone drops a deuce in it too. #HASHTAG# is worse than crap in the pool. #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I did you one better! I BOUGHT A SNOW BLOWER for the first snowmagedon this season!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I said this back in 2019... Sadly it is still true.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - has there been a white US dude seeking a black bride from abroad?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It turns out:1) #HASHTAG# is just a word 2) #HASHTAG# is just a piece of paper 3) #HASHTAG# is at the mercy of those willing to honor it.

#HASHTAG# of #HASHTAG# is no better than any other corrupt government, it's just business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That maybe but listening to the debate and #HASHTAG# sounds not... sharp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# We will see IF IF IF the accusers proceed with a criminal case. If they do not... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#  well deserved!!! Well Said!!! Congratulations to #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# - E #USER# is enabling politicians cause crusaders into REALLY believing anyone can do anything about #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# on #HASHTAG#
OMG #HASHTAG# just got passionate with no political speak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# there is a set of words used over &amp; over again in all proyect development refusals: manufacturing jobs, green jobs, climate change, and gentrification. These wish lists are great when there is ZERO details by the developers &amp; the politicians. #HASHTAG# are they talking about?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching #HASHTAG# only to realize how little planning goes into #HASHTAG# #USER# stories. That could've been the anchor movie to its universe outside its disastrous TV presence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sick of all the pump &amp; dump schemes the #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# come up with. All are rooted in over promising &amp; under delivering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# - all passed in their 80s... Not a bad age to go. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# This is what I call stubborn. and before the whole concept of "Defund" is equated to "civil rights" "civil disobedience" and watnot. Stop it. Words matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is doing well and can be reelected. #HASHTAG# get to work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# loss is #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# gains. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# is not the hill to die on. Eye on the price #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me understand #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# needs #HASHTAG# help to defeat #HASHTAG#? 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm sure there was some sort of religion or faith based organization. Judaism was around so. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# the Black officer was very lucky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# but #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# should not run again #USER#. #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# will be best served by a fresh set of eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put an asterisk next to #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#2020 *=60 games #HASHTAG# WorldSeriesChampions*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# - #HASHTAG#'s owner is one of the richest man on earth, pays close to zero taxes, and seems to side with liberal causes (ie #HASHTAG#) - #USER# what is wrong with this picture?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# how quickly we forget the 63 days of January2020.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no way for #HASHTAG# and #HASHTAG# to come out ahead on this. The #HASHTAG# damage is irreversible. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - remember when #HASHTAG# was supposed to be a secret #HASHTAG#? meanwhile there's #HASHTAG# doing business with guys named Bijan &amp;  Ekim. heck #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Doubt it.  The more this conflict lingers on the quicker it will fade from memory. We will be reminded of it every new years eve as a end of year recap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# you've your case. I appreciate your detailed explanation. I too knew a few DJs, they similarly explained the whole timing thing, made the down beat a thing of myth &amp; spells, 'ohh I got them jumpin'. In the end, DJ still playing other people's creation like a museum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# When she is not " playfully " undermining her co-hosts she is quite a joy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This must be every #HASHTAG# mantra forever and ever. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fully expect many #HASHTAG# test kits will be stolen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# you cannot have "trans" men vs women period.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Was he presidential tonight Van?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - #HASHTAG# bad 5minute bits turned into a bad hour show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# is overrated it's not better than #HASHTAG# The "we dont talk about Bruno" hook is relatable to everyone &amp; everything now cemented in pop culture as a thing JUST LIKE "Let It Go" once was for little girls &amp; so the numbers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - Ok I take it back, DiSarcina is not a good coach. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - #HASHTAG# has the receipts and she is cashing them in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - my buddy tells me the company he works for is actively consulting with lawyers to see how to fire employees not willing to get vaccinated against #HASHTAG#. I'm sure they are not alone. #HASHTAG# bite you hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - #HASHTAG# cameramen are really rubbing it in, they must have heard #HASHTAG# &amp; crew talkin smack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# hey... #USER#... Still a full dodge by #HASHTAG# cat wait to rid of him! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# or #HASHTAG# all must commit to overturning #HASHTAG# and bring back SQF, the #HASHTAG# anti-crime unit &amp; keep #USER# in check. #USER# #USER# #USER#. #HASHTAG# will return!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# como decimos en ingles: If I have to explain it then you'll never know :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Good stuff. Pase por ahi 3 meses atras.... Not bad. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - Hands down #HASHTAG# had a better debate. Where was this #USER# 4 years ago? However, I heard ZERO plans from her and is basically relying on #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# remaining in power to tow the party line which supposedly is what #HASHTAG# wants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# - #HASHTAG#'s owner is one of the richest man on earth, pays close to zero taxes, and seems to a darling amongst liberal circles and causes (ie #HASHTAG#) - n#USER#. To boot doesn't #USER# former #HASHTAG# press secretary work there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ok, wait a minute - #HASHTAG# is not just jumping into the #HASHTAG# for #HASHTAG#, he is doing it as a #HASHTAG#! So he is finally out of the political closet! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&lt;#HASHTAG#&gt; #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# is so #HASHTAG# they are actually beggin #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# to #HASHTAG#. Why? Everyone knows the less of them around to vote give #HASHTAG# an edge to survive the #HASHTAG#.&lt;/sarcasm&gt; #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You know... If #HASHTAG# beats the #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# mayoral establishment candidates running, one could argue voters are looking for a softer form of #HASHTAG# &amp; a tougher form of #HASHTAG#. In other words could be a true moderate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# should take lessons from #HASHTAG# on how to deport #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# + #HASHTAG# = #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Enough run way for #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - ok WTF was GersonBorrero talking about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# did not visualize all his options. not good instincts and not a good arm at third.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - #HASHTAG# as #HASHTAG# is surprisingly good!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It appears #HASHTAG# is not the only one not knowing what to do with its content. Neither does $T.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Another casualty caused by the #HASHTAG# of #HASHTAG# where #HASHTAG# but things are no so bad so says #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why people are leaving #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# and the #HASHTAG# . #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It seems #HASHTAG# does not get out much. BTW, imagine demolishing those HUGE homes and building four 2 family homes in their place because, you know, the #HASHTAG#? #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# the only pragmatic talk has dealt with #HASHTAG#, everything else has been red meat with fluff &amp; buzz words for the masses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching #HASHTAG# with #USER# on #USER#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Back in my day that would be a total clusterfuck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me watching #HASHTAG# with #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER#? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching #USER# pretty ironic #HASHTAG# and by extension #HASHTAG# had a problem with #HASHTAG# in #HASHTAG# protesters and all. Today real residents are complaining about a homeless shelter. Jobs vs. the Homeless. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - That first sketch is the funniest shit ever!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# the #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# comparisons to any northeast state conveniently neglects population density, sprawl, and weather. #HASHTAG# is wrong too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# Derrick is the worst deli employee in #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# - smart and more often than not is good in congress BUT her rants are often bait pandering to the uber #HASHTAG# left not from this planet. Wear her blocking as a badge of honor. #HASHTAG# is the true star &amp; work horse for sane people &amp; the #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - It kind a rubs me the wrong way how #HASHTAG# smiles at every stupidity that is - sometimes -resonating positively to #HASHTAG# crowd and people who want to support him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# call me #HASHTAG# but Miya aint exactly white. Which makes the whole thing kinda worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# get the foam pads with sticky glue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remotes, wallet, key chains, any small item that used to be preferred in black will now be white. I cant find *it*!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting to see every theoligical/philosophical cliche explored by every science fiction time bending tv show or movie before it, condensed in the season finale of #HASHTAG# . The themes are mind bending to those who have not lived long enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - Guy, endorsed by #HASHTAG#, wants to be #HASHTAG# comptroller, has earned 8 speeding tickets in 5 years. I've ONE in 30 years!!! Think about that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - Not E offering an opinion of substance in his #USER# program. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - how great is #USER# on foreign policy &amp; #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The booze intake?! For a belly like that, which screams of liver damage, how much booze was he having? I down, 1 1/2 of whatever is in my mini bar (manhattans, vodka limons or rum &amp; cran) - If I cut down any further I'll join the mormons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Exactly. Just because your elected pol "looks like you" doesnt mean thinks like you or shares your interests]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - How did the polls get it wrong again? simple: everyone seems to lie to #HASHTAG#, not to #HASHTAG#, or #HASHTAG# pollsters have figured out how to parse out the lies. #USER# red polls were consistent in putting #HASHTAG# ahead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wait, I take it back. #HASHTAG# does believe she scored points with her insane question.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much for a #HASHTAG# - #HASHTAG# worth less than $3K while on sale by several dealers for more than $5k. Aint that something? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# this right there is a significant factor. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# are responsible for #HASHTAG# bad poll numbers. Inner squables are a bad look and make #HASHTAG# look competent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# without #HASHTAG#?!How?! #HASHTAG# dies of a heart attack after doctors say his heart is fine. Still wondering why #HASHTAG# with #HASHTAG#? There are no guarantees in life. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# voted for communist Muslim that happens to be black. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# is in a forever state of disrepair, despair, wishing it all  to disappear. #HASHTAG# you did this. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# and all the politicians elected in that borough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# thats 9% too high.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If you are serious, the only choices should be 1) #HASHTAG# 2) BuckShowalter 3) #HASHTAG#.  the last was a great utility player for the #HASHTAG# hard nose grinder. Not sure if you have the appetite for that trial and error. Do the right thing for the franchise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Safest big city, what judge would let these thugs out without bail? we'll never know because with #HASHTAG# these animals will be out in no time. this is NOT what #HASHTAG# is about or protect. #HASHTAG# are the enemy until you need a friend #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - #HASHTAG# is not singer, at best she can string together words in a melody and jump around a stage but there is no musical magic. Just sounds kudos to her agent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - if your starter is going to  allow a run he might as well be on the mound to do it, or save his self.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# - It's a mistake for #HASHTAG# to debate #HASHTAG#.  One flub, one gaff, one lapse, and suddenly a 10 point lead in October shrinks to 2 points. #HASHTAG# has nothing to gain and everything to lose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I like #USER# not sure how he manages to regularly piss off both the left and the right... then again, I don't watch...

... carry on. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just when one believes to have heard or read every dumb take there is to be heard or read, another one that is worse appears! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#  dont riff #HASHTAG# stick to the script... and that guy could get a hair cut? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fact: Everyone who leaves #HASHTAG# spends at least 6 months comparing their new home to it but that eventually fades and morphs into what took me so long?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In the end, what is one supposed to do? Go back &amp; fort with a comic, his fans, and those against #HASHTAG#? No thanks. He is a big boy and is doing just fine without any help from me or anyone. He tried to help #HASHTAG# and look what it got him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# it was that woman who first went on #HASHTAG# years ago to pitch the #HASHTAG# reform stuff. Sane folks sounded the alarm... and here we are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Oh come on... give him a pass, he did not mean to kill that woman. Not his fault she was in the way between the bullet and the guy he actually meant to kill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - looking like that, what kind of hardship has #HASHTAG# endured exactly. Viendose asi que clase de dificultades vivio la susodicha?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Admit? there is nothing to admit. no ones fault that there are people with severe skin tone complex in need of validation through a movie that offers a small view of Latin immigrants from a certain #HASHTAG# neighborhood with a dream. If this is #HASHTAG# culture I rather be sleeping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I get the 51% over 49% math. The does not answer to the fact a large chunk of that 51% came as a favorite number 2. In other words 'I like you as a default 2nd, not as 1st'. Garcia was everyone's favorite 2nd Choice! How from a rational logical stand point that is 1st winning?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - two things black people: never plea guilty and underestimate the power of a good attorney. oh #HASHTAG# is mad #HASHTAG#. Been there, I know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What is your party's agenda, platform, and plan, and #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# are not plans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# in all honesty #HASHTAG# ads have been worst! The fingah!!! F-him!!! I mean really.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't call the #HASHTAG# family #HASHTAG# unlike those poor black folks who turned in their daughters for that #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - Ximena  money grubbing is gross.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - #HASHTAG# back to #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Have not watched political shows in such long time, forgot #HASHTAG# was still alive ruining *it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah... that was a silly thing to say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Bobby Valentine does not have the 2nd best record in #HASHTAG# history #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm sorry but I am done with this particular rabbit hole. 

Form  3rd party or something.

Go #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At this point watching the #HASHTAG# just to hear #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wonder how Manhattan's incoming DA will handle that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Were my ears deceiving me or did I hear on #USER# that #HASHTAG# #USER# asked #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# &amp; #USER# to release all #HASHTAG# prisoners? #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Let us know when you campaign in the #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG#, and the less #HASHTAG# friendly neighborhoods in #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# reminds me of that old #HASHTAG# "Hows your dic... tation machine?" 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I trust you know more than you let on. ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# his evil machinations have created an invaluable partner for #HASHTAG# in #HASHTAG# and more importantly a dangerous &amp; determined enemy for #HASHTAG#. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# got the biggest crowd ever! Too bad it was to over throw the government. Imagine if they exercised #HASHTAG# remedies!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tried to stay away from ever commenting on the matter but that looks like #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Make that two.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I understand &amp; hate the entire concept of #HASHTAG# cannot wait to see it implemented YES! IMPLEMENTED! In the rest of #HASHTAG# just to see the entire #USER# voted out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That may very well be but if (#HASHTAG#) have to explain that ideology as #HASHTAG# is you're losing the argument. #HASHTAG# basically says that and the results speak for themselves. Guys in NYS are running around killing common sense projects #HASHTAG# &amp; voters are keeping tabs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# All I know, if she is the one, I'll vote for Sliwa #HASHTAG# #USER#. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# are glorified &amp; overpaid security guards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# oh nooo get ready for #USER# go to TOWN on #HASHTAG#. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# is a can do candidate! She is a work horse! But is a novice at politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# when manufacturing is mentioned, what kind of manufacturing we talking about? furniture, auto, solar panels, widgets? 'Cause the waste manufacturing creates will fit perfectly in any commercial property and neighborhood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# OMG I read Adelle! Thank goodness she is not THE Adele]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Just heard #USER# say... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ... so... Assange is a... Hero? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While everyone on #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# was praising #HASHTAG#, I was probably the only one who saw through that wench. f - You - Cee K #HASHTAG# who chose NOT to give #HASHTAG# her #HASHTAG# seat. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...and why not?! Kanye, IceCube, Diddy, who is next?! #HASHTAG# got almost half a billion dollars!!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Stringer is not at all impressive, he gathering attention because of his longevity. He, as the rest are, is talking about making sure _____ doesnt happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# new #HASHTAG# variant follows #HASHTAG# and it's called
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# meets #HASHTAG#
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oops - got ahead of myself. Clicked the actual video and #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# To be fair, there is never a good time to raise #HASHTAG# for #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# once this #HASHTAG# pandemic ends &amp; every vaccinated person proves the #HASHTAG# people wrong, will humanity get a well deserved apology?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# - "The (federal) government is the enemy until you need a friend" - #USER#. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Good for #HASHTAG# to see live long enough to see his presidential legacy change right before his eyes. From worse to not so bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No other movie has been in promo mode for this long... have a bad feeling about #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That red between Tampa &amp; Orlando must be the angry hold-ups that have not sold or died yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# gotta keep tabs on the mops &amp; perps from a distance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: nationwide voters are tired of #HASHTAG# idealist paralysis &amp; in fighting. It makes them look weak, befuddled, in disarray, and #HASHTAG# incompetent. Voters are fickle and nowadays short of patience. #HASHTAG# is a message.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He simply is down with #HASHTAG# other peoples money. Many can respect that until is your money. We knew that already not sure why it's different this time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# People are sayin.... those very shifty blacks, its gotta be worth coming out to vote during a pandemic so they loaded up on xerox copies of ballots and pulled them out last minute, handed like 3 at a time... I dont know... to the clerk to scan... we gotta check strongly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Currently you get taxed more than twice. Income (wages) Interest on savings, dividends (capital gains/stocks), property. Currently, high end taxes are 37% on wages. every other tax is percent wise much less.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Luckily #HASHTAG# is doing fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# hard2 believe whitesupremacist R going to gather at polling stations in #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# that's why cops exists #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - Ximena   has an itchy nose. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# publishes data that favor's their bosses narrative but goes contrary to their union's narrative. In the end, do #HASHTAG# crime victim's &amp; their families believe it? do I, do you, do we BELIEVE it? Statistics tend to make liars out of our own eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The only violence being interrupted is the grubby hands not fighting within to get a piece of the grift. Scamming #HASHTAG# tax payers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 52% too low]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# None of those beat the biggests busts of all #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG#... If we are keeping scores that is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# See #USER#? he gets it - and that's all that matters. #HASHTAG# don't need to be corrupt to be brought up on charges and be ran out of town. Often by other democrats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - how many of the #HASHTAG# are from #HASHTAG# vs. Imported from out of state?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 'luckily very few #HASHTAG# care what #HASHTAG# thinks of our leaders' - said #HASHTAG# voter during #HASHTAG# tenure. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That big break on property taxes depends largely on income. Many folks exceed that threshold. The medical services is a plus because of how much WE have paid into it, dont want to leave money on the table.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# To be fair, where is one supposed to get counterfeit goods nowadays?! #HASHTAG# has been virtually cleaned up! These entrepreneurs have to earn coin too! Besides, this is part of the "grit" folks wanted for #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# last first &amp; part. Most people don't pay attention or care about #HASHTAG# local or otherwise until it impacts them personally or financially in real terms. Fluff &amp; platitudes are easily spotted, they are turnoffs and thus the low turnouts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - #HASHTAG# in #HASHTAG# is the result of a #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The problem is, of course as it always is and always will be, enforcement. How do you, when do you, where do you? Careful not to inject race, culture, &amp; priorities into it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# - Which one of them is going to move my meth neighbors out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - is like #USER#' hair is on fire! oh wait. I know of NO ONE who didnt see these levels of crime coming, #USER# called it back in 2012! The proverbial #HASHTAG#. Blame #USER# for this. They gave 0 support to Lotha &amp; #USER# (pining 2B Mayor still)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# cant wait to hear about hair plugs vs comb overs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# will not engage into a military operation with boots on the grown in #HASHTAG# until #HASHTAG# and #HASHTAG# commit open genocide. Unlike #HASHTAG#, where Assad killed his own people, #HASHTAG#UkraineConflict #HASHTAG# not yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Something tells me, #HASHTAG# makes the whole movie R.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Secret sauce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I remember the disapproving tweets aimed at #HASHTAG# when he came out in support of #HASHTAG# but #HASHTAG# dont vote &amp; is not real life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# should take lessons from #HASHTAG# on how to deport #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# + #HASHTAG# = #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Lots of fluff with fabricated numbers from un audited fake institutions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When did #HASHTAG# begin charging to see if they could get in an earlier flight? #USER# asked for $75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - me thinks they got the horses to go all the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Keyword there, most. BTW - I see what you did there, total deflection. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'd venture to say the clergyman would be above all, since he would be on the take from all. From the poor, to the criminal, to the doctor, and the politician.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - Was #HASHTAG# testing new material?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - would it be cruel and wrong to put these mopes in solitary confinement? #HASHTAG# make it stop. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watched a pile of #USER# movie trailers &amp; they can't figure out how to string their story lines together! #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG#, endless #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# &amp; they can't figure out how to make a cohesive complementary story line. #USER# kicks ass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Next up #HASHTAG# is going sue in #HASHTAG# and have #HASHTAG# overturn the election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No rudeness received or perceived.

Again - all politics are local. Progressive talking points might work well in some sects of the country, not so well in others.
Not sure why, or maybe it's the #HASHTAG#, the left of the left is hemmed up to disagreeing with that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# on #HASHTAG# - Notwithstanding the ridiculous #HASHTAG# question, the more the candidates spoke the less appealing they became. Advantage #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG#,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Agreed.

The #HASHTAG# based polls were more realistic, or better said, kept me grounded.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wants to keep his supporters off the polls?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He is what we always knew he was - an asshole. Just like #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# and the rest of #HASHTAG# in #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# should NOT have any debates. 30 years of debate winners have not determined who wins the election for the office. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# has nothing to gain by debating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# "Mom, that guy on the 2nd floor looks at me funny. The other day he told me I looked good on jeans" - oh hun dont mind him he is just friendly, now hurry up we are late to your middle school Xmas party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - The flamingly embarrassing #HASHTAG# is these judges are critiquing the dancers for a lack of feeling while dancing the "Rhumba/LatinBallRoom" to a disco beat. Can't producers cue some #HASHTAG#?! Cheap Bastids! HOW IS THIS SHOW STILL ON!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# red meat for the base.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While #USER# &amp; #USER# want non #HASHTAG# citizens to vote in local elections #HASHTAG# citizens dont want citizens of #HASHTAG# using their hospitals - #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# with #USER#: #HASHTAG# - Totally pooped on the idea/reality that folks are leaving (in my case planning to leave #HASHTAG#). When driving a car you don't focus on the hood of the car, you focus on the road ahead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# getting lots of play on #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# what's the $DIS #HASHTAG# stock play?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - a note on #HASHTAG# impeachment. #HASHTAG# was impeached by a more credible political body TWICE!!! #HASHTAG# is just a word.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# was right #USER# #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>