<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Judeo-communist-socialists always wave those flags. You must not get out much.#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton has been on the government tit her entire life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#. No wonder Hindoos call me claiming to be #USER# technical support.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can deny Christ's resurrection with impunity if you're a Jew. But if you are a gentile you'd better not deny the Holocaust.-MichaelHill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, to read the writing on the gold tablets...#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shooting up funerals seems to be the latest in Afro-American fashion.#USER# #USER#Politics #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just when you think #HASHTAG# can't become more hateful, she calls people with different views from hers, a #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who wrote all of that wonderful German light opera of the student prince variety?#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# DISAVOWS NATION-BUILDING! #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #HASHTAG#'s a dumb fuck. We are #HASHTAG# fighting individual evil, or group evil, we are fighting the entire Moslem world. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one asks dual citizen Rham why his Israeli homeland doesn't take a few hundred thousand illegals and visa violators.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President-Elect Trump: I will not accept a salary as president! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homosexuals should have their own country, just like the Jews have Israel.#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The big question all politicians must answer, what are you going to do for White Americans? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oye vey. Itz another Holocaust I tell you. I must tell the #HASHTAG# that I read it in the #USER# . #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politicians "promise" to change the weather...#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guy talk and one-ups-man-ship are common among men.#USER# #USER# #USER#News]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vanity Publications. Jeff Bezos has the #USER#  Carlos Slim has the #USER#. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Muslim woman wearing a #HASHTAG#, is a sign of her submission to #HASHTAG# (law).
#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re-inventing the wheel at #HASHTAG#.#USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Hillary Clinton gets elected the United Methodist Church won't be "united" for long. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I use it, once &amp; awhile. I think it is still relevant. I doubt the AP Stylebook would agree.#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ivy League Graduate?#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING NEWS:
Hillary has asked Ahmad Khan's father to campaign trail to tell Islamophobic Trump supporters there is nothing to fear.
.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: 
As America votes, the whole world holds its breath, waiting to find out if crime pays. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The day before the Muslim attack in #HASHTAG#, German police raided 60 homes to arrest people for anti-Muslim immigration Facebook posts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, there haven't been any real Nazis since 1945.#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kasich violated an oath he took in writing...doesn't look good for #HASHTAG#.#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a public service that #HASHTAG# has investigative journalist Chuck Johnson ip banned. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How enlightening---Jews talking about Iran. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo of Donald Trump grabbing a pussy... #URL# #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this the 1917 law #HASHTAG# kept using to defend Hillary? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does your mother suck Jew ass in public?#USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oye Vey Department: US Congress Passes Bill to Protect Jew Feelings in Europe ===&gt; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was The Iran Deal due to Blackmail from Hillary's Server? ===&gt; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The House Democratic leadership should be disciplined and sanctioned for the gross violation of #HASHTAG# Rules they have committed. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where's the link to the Wikileak---not your screen shot.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bede was living on the edge back in 700AD.#HASHTAG#.#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We live in a time when the head of Germany wants to destroy Germans, and the head of the Catholic Church wants to eliminate Christianity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike "Penis" Pence, as he's known in #HASHTAG#...#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diversity mongers hate White Americans. Regardless of what White Americans may say or do. That's the way it is.#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not interested in a Protestantism that tries to out Roman Catholic the Roman Catholics or out Jew the Jews.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regardless of what they might say, when it comes down to the voting booth, people are NOT going to vote for a woman for President.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Questionable, but, interesting. A must watch... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's starting to look like Huma is a spy, and Hillary covered it up to save her own political ass.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kasich says he will move to Croatia and run for President there---not kidding.#USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The spook should be a little more considerate of his neighbors, and act like a college graduate not a sophomore.#USER# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do Jews have a death wish? If not. Then why do Jew politicians all support More Moslem &amp; non-White immigration? #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the exception of Alger Hiss no high placed official has violated the 1917 law except Hillary.#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oye vey itz another Holocaust I tell you. Hate crime investigation underway ===&gt; #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dunno...could be 58% among White Catholics. I wouldn't want to bet the farm on being that precise.#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jared Kushner, Swedish Jew?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: Huma Abedin is another Alger Hiss. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's July, you just might.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What no pork kebabs?#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember this exchange live.#USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gwen who?#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latinos have a form of Roman Catholicism that lends itself to devil worship like Santeria etc.#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that the #HASHTAG# has gone all in on homosexuality, I wonder how Roman Catholics can deny it? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to stop Muslim terrorism is not to allow Muslims into the USA. #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since the 80's every corporation has hired these "schools", and had special training. Trump U was nothing new.#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No the stage unions are complaining about it too.#USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's #USER# going to do for White Americans? Not for Jews, Syrians, Blacks, Mexicans...#USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brittanee Drexel, teen who vanished in 2009, was raped, shot, eaten by alligators, FBI says | Fox News | #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How come none of them want to move to Mexico, or Haiti, or some other garden spot?#USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has been warning publically for at least 5 or 6 years that Anthony Weiner was a national security risk.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hundreds of radical Semites, of the Jew cult variety, will be in Cleveland next week for the Republican Convention.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to tell what #HASHTAG# of drugs Hillary is ingesting.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll be unfollowed by more Christians for denying the holocaust than you would for denying Christ. It's bizarre.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boo Hoo Hoo...#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C'mon. Ryan defeats an unknown with no political base and it's a big deal?#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why wasn't the #HASHTAG# twitter account suspended? They routinely harass people who they don't like.#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Two Hundred Years Together" was written as history, not historical fiction. The Red Wheel was historical fiction(?)terrible translation too #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now the immigration "melting pot", has turned into the immigration "pressure cooker".
#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[17 of the 9/11 terrorist gang were in the #HASHTAG# legally. Right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when #HASHTAG# politicians were all for the American immigration melting pot? Before it became a pressure cooker.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The elite in this country want to discuss serious issues 1) Trump making a fat joke 20 years ago and 2) banning Pepe the Frog. --#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rally Tomorrow!!!#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why hasn't Solzhenitsyn's "200 Years Together" been published in English? Aye, Mister Wolfe? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#T #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no Salvation for Muslims, Jews or other pagans.. The only way to Salvation is through faith in Jesus Christ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was thinking Yale too.#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think he went with Pence to make the big Republican money in the mid-West happy. Indiana is like #HASHTAG# without hills.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The French have it precisely right: Strict gun control + tons of Islamic refugees = zero terrorism! #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Presidential election is shaping up to be a referendum on the 2nd Amendment. One Hillary Clinton will lose.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must Watch: Hillary lying her ass off...#USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharp rebuke from who...Jeff #HASHTAG#? #USER# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm distantly related in the way back, to the Speaker of the House, when that bill became law in the 1790's.#USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Complain to your mother. Maybe she cares? I don't. #HASHTAG#.#USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats have never accounted for communist-socialist support at their rallies. Including formal endorsements.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good reputation...#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top #HASHTAG# politicians Biden, Kaine, O'Malley call Trump a fascist, and worse, but, Trump is a pro-life advocate, they are not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fact that Clinton had a private server set up outside of the secure government network for official email is in itself illegal.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton does have serious health problems---it's obvious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember the Bible story of Abraham being ordered by God to sacrifice his son. Just another delusional Semite hearing voices. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama gave billions of untraceable taxpayer dollars to Iran. How much more abuse will White Americans take?
#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, and the Jews killed and starved MILLIONS in Russia and the Ukraine during communism-socialism.#USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just remember the Roman #HASHTAG# politicians in #HASHTAG# want to bring more Muslims here to the #HASHTAG#. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big shift in German politics taking place, no one in the #HASHTAG# reporting it. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By all observers the Jews were considered the filthiest people in all of Europe, now they are lecturing Americans on health issues. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've always thought it was interesting the Jew's Talmud admits that the Jews killed Jesus Christ.#USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tempting God isn't a good idea. One the Jews have never learned.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaking of Irish Roman #HASHTAG# assholes...Ryan is one of the biggest.#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember: Donald Trump and David Duke have been getting their names in the newspapers since the early to mid 1970's. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing with most journalists is that they can dish it out, but, they can't take it.#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neo-nazis or #HASHTAG# members attacked by communist-socialist-anarchists?#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Jews are oppressed victims, and definitely don't run Hollywood or international banking!" #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The news outlets have put so much anti-Trump stuff out there that it has no shock or propaganda value anymore.#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pathetic, this is a new low.#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Puerto Ricans are American citizens, and can vote, but, most won't vote.#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump was bashed by the infallible #HASHTAG# by name---that's a 1st in American and #HASHTAG# history! #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jim Comey is a fine Irish #HASHTAG# lad, who prays his #HASHTAG#, and attends #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# daily.#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must be a radical communist-socialist-anarchist.#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to let #USER# know, that we know they are owned by #HASHTAG#, and #USER# by #HASHTAG#. #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone know why we are taking in these so-called "Syrian" refugees? #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Century Link needs better service and lower costs. Shouldn't charge customers for repairs. Can't buy a decent desk set today.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #HASHTAG# hate "Angry Birds?#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary "Black Lives Matter" Clinton will be singing a different tune after last night in Dallas.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chuck Johnson has the scoop on Machado...#URL# #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, what do you want. The little bastard over here raping and killing our kids?#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who really cares what Larry the Cable Guy thinks about anything? #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why hasn't Solzhenitsyn's, greatest work, "200 Years Together", NOT BEEN PUBLISHED IN ENGLISH.#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My View: Why do illegal Aliens Think They Have a Right to Protest ANYTHING in #HASHTAG#?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't like it? Complain to your mother. Maybe she cares about what you think. I don't. #HASHTAG#.#USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What makes you say this...???#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, the Roman #HASHTAG# niggers down in Brazil are holding 4 or 5 American Olympic swimmers hostage.#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your lead isn't a Duke quote, and Duke has always been smooth. Heck, he's a PhD. Don't be such a hack.#USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did Obama claim he was born in Kenya to the Harvard Law Review of which he was the editor.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pepe wants the #USER# to print his story of being groped by #USER#. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure Trump wants the facts, not bullshit from the CIA.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A #HASHTAG#? #HASHTAG#? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#---shot up a showing of "Angry Birds".#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Roman Catholic Pope attacked #USER# by name---a 1st in American and Papal history! #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't Donald Duck a licensed Disney character?#USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe those children will be able to shake off the Jew cult, maybe they won't?#USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not big on Revelations, or James. Besides the Synoptics, of which I like John the most, I like Acts, and some of Romans. #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Mexican (Roman Catholic) federal, state and local prison population says it all.#USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I report all radical Semites, Muslim, Jew, or other.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ricky should file a disparity of treatment complaint against twitter a business engaged in interstate commerce.#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By all reports: In cash, on pallets, delivered to Iran.#USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are old enough to remember, Sweet Old Bill Clinton went to Communist Russia before it was cool.#USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alligators, not as dangerous as Muslims and other #HASHTAG#.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Jews really think the world revolves around them. Good Example: The Trump "sheriff's badge" poster controversy.#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 Notre Dame Players Arrested, 1 for Tackling Policeman - ABC News - #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[O'Malley is an Irish Roman #HASHTAG# asshole who would get us into more wars for Israel.#USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most people really loathe the talking heads on #USER# and #USER#. Can't stand to watch those channels anymore.#USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Holy Roman Catholic Biden speaks...#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The point is, there wasn't much division among White Protestants, the so-called Evangelicals in 80%+ for Trump.#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Venice Beach Ambush: A Beverly Hills Surgeon on Being Pistol-Whipped and Left for Dead #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh. How wonderful a Jew actually said something bad about Israel. I'm sooo impressed. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young #HASHTAG#.#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's ass backwards, or bassakwards...#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What movie was playing in #HASHTAG#? #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If any of these characters had spent time outdoors, they would know they were going to be alone and have prepared for it.#USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even with all of the TV and cable news outlets aligned against him---Trump is still in the lead. That's huge. Think about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turn on the TV to get the news, and all you get is anti-Trump, and anti-White propaganda.#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been drinking the Kool-Aid again Sam?#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most people pay State estate taxes, and will pay State estate taxes regardless of what Trump does if elected President.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is just something Italian's like #HASHTAG# do in Roman #HASHTAG# Church basements like #HASHTAG#.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Socialists, communists, anarchists, Trotskyites, the entire spectrum of the radical left is in the streets against Trump.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: The last time the Clinton's were in the White House, Hillary's hubby was getting blow jobs in the oval office.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Editor &amp; Chief of Deutsche Welle has come out strongly in favor of a burka ban in Germany.#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look what happened to Monica Lewinsky.#USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump promises to raise the average Black #HASHTAG# from 70 to 95.#USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your ears open for the words "counter intelligence".#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's "fo-tees" as in "numba fo"...#USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Islam is a non-White cult. Those Whites who believe in the Islamic cult believe in miscegenation. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to #USER# , the #HASHTAG# shooter attacked a theater showing "Angry Birds" and "Alice in Wonderland". #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# (((Kazin))) Really understands White Americans...#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What people with acreage do out in the exurbs is a lot different than Latinos doing urban chicken farming.#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#. Is "Frank" Luntz ashamed of being a Jew? Are you? How big is your nose? Big enough to stick it in my timeline.#HASHTAG#.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The signatures will never be accepted as real...paid Mexicans(?) circulating the petitions.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just doing a job White Americans don't want---you mother's ass.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Scandal Checklist

1. Called somebody fat 20 years ago.
2. Followed Tax Law.
3. Had a private "guy chat" 11 years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no responsibility for any Mexicans, Roman #HASHTAG#, or anyone else living illegally in the US. None.#USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These same Jews want all around protectionism for their Jew homeland Israel.#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cuckservatives: Nancy French Admits To Sexual Relationship With Family Pastor In The Washington Post #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#.#USER# Trump very deftly showed the Mexicans (Roman Catholics) the back of his hand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some White men get into it with a bunch of #HASHTAG# niggers in Brazil, and where's the #HASHTAG# and others? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Typical delusional Roman Catholic waiting for the next #HASHTAG# Pope. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the cost installed? What's the cost of operation? How many years is the payback at what %?#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: #HASHTAG# pray the #HASHTAG# after the 2 most powerful #HASHTAG# in the land rule for homo marriage. They just don't get it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ben Franklin was such a racist he didn't think Germans were White. #HASHTAG#. #HASHTAG#.#USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington’s game of good terrorists vs bad terrorists: #URL# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# members attacked by communist-socialist-anarchists in California?#USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a country anywhere in the world with a large Muslim minority that doesn't have a problem with Muslim terrorism?#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French Female Police Officer Stabbed In The Throat In Toulouse ===&gt; #URL# via #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[None of the other Irish #HASHTAG# pussies,  like O'Malley, Kaine, Biden...have ever been in a locker room or comedy club.#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between Hitler and Obama: Under Obama the Jews, communists, and, homosexuals are in charge. #HASHTAG#  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no such thing as a "free lunch"...#USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Obama doesn't want to call it "Radical Islamic Terrorism", why not call it "Moderate Islamic Terrorism"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's what the Greeks say... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like my old friends in central &amp; southern #HASHTAG# are underwater in the Yellow Pages. What a mess, Buffalo Creek redux.  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPDATED: Man killed in Lorain Taco Bell drive-thru robbery identified - #URL# … #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protestants are not like Roman Catholics, we don't have to believe anything that we disagree with---NO #HASHTAG#.#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thia is one of those fake news stories everyone is talking about.#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grand jury to hear Hatfield slaying case ===&gt; #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right, the fund raiser was in Charleston, WV 25304.#USER# I wonder how they did?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to The Great Khizr Khan, #HASHTAG# hates Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that really important news...#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Grief counselor", that's Yiddish for #HASHTAG#.#USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of these Holy Roman Catholics, and the Cardinal hasn't tried to exorcise Hillary Clinton. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>