<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[And I'm not even talking about white anarchists here bc fuck them. I'm talking about APOCs and anarchists who happen to be Black. It's no shade to the concepts of class conflictuality, prefiguration, &amp; even anti-politics as a modality but come on. I feel like I have diff concerns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well the gay men copied Women of transgender experience tbh. And those gay men happily team up with cis straight men and cishet women against the gworls #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# People need to go back to the drawing board. You won't understand Genre without also understanding Fanon's notion of sociogeny. But more broadly, you cannot adequately address why centering the "female" is an issue if you simply want to substitute "male" in the liberal academe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They don't want to confront the question of neocolonialism which becomes a primary contradiction in the road of developing via RCBO. They are not willing to deal with the entangled issues involved with internal contradictions around sexual predators, gang abuse, DV, etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is in response to that, and it's victim blaming, pathologizing implications, that people caught in between various crises had to try and formulate different explanations for why the dimension of human experience evolves and can be changed by conscious, collective action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defund and Community Control are the good cop and bad cop of the nascent neocolonial takeover of 21st century American fascism. nRemember what Malcolm had to say about foxes and wolves. Aint just applicable to the dems and repubs. Leftists move like liberals and conservatives too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A whole lot of niggas sounding like this fascist ass crakkka ass bihhhh #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then there is the "new jail" plan that comes out of the supposed closure of Rikers. A new jail to be built in the Bronx. They putting up a jail but ain't doing shit about the real issues we face. Disgusting. Fuck this new mayor BTW and his transitional housing team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In December them socialists was Wilding saying that nonbinary identity is a manifestation of "postmodernism" and the same accounts you see ppl are mad at for saying that TMA and TME is a real distinction, was the same accounts checking these socialists for their enbyphobia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I also have another ex, a cis male, who been online stalking me and that's on top of dealing with some intense family shit that came up between Thanksgiving and Christmas wrt to my transness. The common denominator in all this is transmisogynoir period and it's exhausting asf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... can emerge in our struggle. Since gender expansiveness in precolonial, ancestral, indigenous genres, identities, experiences, roles had a material basis: it is totally possible for those with neocolonial/assimilationist class interests to fold even modern "transgressive"...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 4. Ungendered

In the work of Hortense Spillers, she argues that Europeans essentially used hypersexual reductions of African people's bodies to reinterpret our pre-existing ways of being, kinship structures, and notions of gender on behalf of the slavery project...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Due to technical difficulties and scheduling conflicts we gonna push #HASHTAG# to Monday 27th December 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conscious Lee took some shit from AfAA recently too. I can't remember if my comrades had to push him to cite or not. But yeah. He really snooping on all the Black maGe especially TMA radical accounts. Everyone should keep the foot on his neck til he give that platform over imo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like when I walk through my home borough there's something emanating from the landscape I be feeling, that crescendo in certain areas, like along the Bronx River for some reason. Especially as KY awareness of my family history and of the organizing history here grows, I feel it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[by some feminists. It's simply a liberal/progressive iteration of the conservative trans panic "they are trying to destroy the nuclear family/Western civilization/the church + take away jobs and opportunities from us and force an agenda." That shit gets repackaged and distilled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's always interesting to see who says this because in my experience these phrases aren't used as often at least not anymore. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisheterosexism coming for us all transmisogyny be the anchor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This then goes into why focus on the Scriptures can easily be used to silence us as Black people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nah bc why "BITCHMADESTUDIES" is going into one of my songs tho I really be carrying lmaoooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm very intentional about words that I use when talking about Black QTGNC people. When I saw that I was "assigned Brotha" or when I say "masc Shawty" like I use our slang/kinship terms intentionally to specify our Black ways of relating to gender/sexual expanses tbh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want for my transition to give very much gender confusion and yet sexy in every gender all at once.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not lost on me that you are white tryna push back on what I said, which is both scientific and historical/material accuracy, to universalize Sex Dimorphism as a "prominent" feature of human organization. But you can take that white Man religion shit to someone else mentions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's because folks were insisting on national/class interests in the struggle against segregation that some ppl sought gains from the State. Segregation was outright fascism and while some ppl wanted civil rights for bourgeois reasons, otherwise were fighting to help ease up...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And especially when I'm talking with other Black trans folks. It helps me to keep track of my needs but also to keep watchful about theirs. It takes discipline. I don't do it 24/7 but in the moments I'm led to, it's very powerful, grounding, calming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It depends on the person. It can work. Some ppl find it weird but yeah I'm the type to state my intentions like this. But it gotta be someone I already had a vibe or connection with in some way tbh #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and the reason why is because "masc" then becomes a substitute for "men" and "males" who presumably don't need anymore Representation and are therefore either "taking up space" (transmisogyny) in the gender convo or "betraying" it as is said of trans men and transmascs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone using 'she' or "presenting femme" don't got the same gender expanse, class interest, or racialized subjectivity. So how misgendering and perception of their physical appearance impacts them both externally and internally is not gonna be uniform. Overlooking this, however]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the gorls are either DJs, rappers, spiritualists, theorists/activists, or some combination of the four lmaoooooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I have watched cis men and even cis women use the fact of their racialized ungendering to try and include themselves into categories like maGe and TMA, so no, I'm not relinquishing distinctions just bc their structures have dynamism. That's not good theory or propaganda to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yall be using these cartoon avis and not showing face in video chats and spaces and so niggas don't be knowing who ain't dark skinned until suddenly pics pop up and I don't like to see it esp bc of how we get down in the Anarkata Turn if dis u you better check yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right. Cuz at the end of the day I invited then to the Twitter space precisely so they could tell me they @ themselves and they didn't bc THEY the ones hiding behind the "social networks and these computers" talking like "they some shooters" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And as much acceptance as there is now, especially around anime, if you grown and grown folks is still calling you an oreo then you must be doing sumn wrong lmaoooo vuz who is even still saying that shit in the 2020s???? I think some of yall Blerds just lie for clicks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This also means that noise pollution and the smell be hitting different up in the Bronx (bc of my sensory issues, it's certain neighborhoods I can't be in for too long without getting overwhelmed). The Bronx also gets overlooked by most "organizers" too bc they all be transplants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alot of people joke about looking for a sugar parent and never think about how the folks interested in being one want control/power. Similar to how people be like "I wanna be a housewife; no more muling" and don't think about how Husbandry in a bourgeois society is exploitative]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7. None of these liberal/representation ways of Hypervisibilizing Black trans women and transfeminine people benefits us materially or socially or politically in the long run bc it is a bourgeois way of coercing our modes of living. And doesn't resolved conservative lies abt us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's really wild how the mechanics of political reaction (where working class frustrations are coopted and directed downwards as an attempt to reclaim and conserve hierarchies in the face of crises) plays out on a micro-level in the ways that trans folk, esp TMA folk, experience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we speak today of rest as/before resistance if there is a plantation keeping people from resting? Can we ask ppl to divest from labor and to stop dreaming of labor if we aren't using "the magic of the hands" to transform what keeps people from resting, keeping us working?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The process that went into the Anarkata Statement needs to be replicated for each unique Black context, preferably with a different label devised for the local regions in consideration, focused on an advanced theoretical, practical, and speculative treatment of BAR and BRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yall be like "as a negro of non-black experience"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White transfems have an investment in maintaining Western womanhoods and therefore they be gaslighty about how Black people across gender expanses are oppressed by patriarchy and cisheterosexism. If anything "oppression olympics" is applicable to white trans women tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tangentially related: while my conlang expresses Habitual Be through evidentiality, AAVE does it through a combination of both tense and aspect. Or maybe it's only a Tense? Or maybe it's only an Aspect? Language is complicated yo! 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US based white anarchists trying to translate European derived white anarchist traditions without addressing the racial contradictions of the latter and the fact that they get magnified in the US which has a uniquely fascistic and nativist approach to any Leftism is goofy shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yall be living with or dating disabled ppl and "makin space" for us based on YOUR own self-interest with no cogenerative approach to what that's supposed to mean, and then paint us as abusive and manipulative, of taking advantage of you, when our needs start conflictin with yours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No shade some of the women led orgs be right along with the cis/het men pushing homophobic and transphobic fuckery. But yeah for the most part it's women and other marginalized genders actually carrying Pan Africanism forward while brothas water the shit down via neocolonialism #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This not even unpopular atp but sis can NOT sing #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still laugh at the question "are you gay?" now lmaaaaaao that shit cracks me tf up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And as I struggle to teach myself this, after having spent years Adultified in my Closeted youth and Infomammied in my Egg days, this Chrysalis period also involves keeping anyone away from me that interferes with this very needed facet of my inner transformation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White anarchists was deadass calling my comrades "opps" for tryna call out what happened to Antonio Mays, Jr (and other Black folks who got shot) and it was so reminiscent of "Pan Africanists" accusing queers of calling for "Western intervention" when we discuss our human rights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I be upset with how much I try to do for my own community some and paid dust by bitches simply because some people are legit anti-communist/anti-anarchist. And yall given them platforms or loom to them as leaders in Black liberatory thought too which is incredibly bizarre to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strikes on Rikers, buildings burning in the Bronx, a cop ass mayor in a city with a standing army for a police force, ongoing housing crisis and EJ battles, a pandemic, kids being set up for death in schools that were already carceral, chile the struggle in NYC is wildin wildin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know what this means and it could just be my imagination but I have had lots of dreams about revolutionary struggle, many of which have come true. I don't necessarily know if it's a spiritual gift or anxiety/ptsd + autistic pattern recognition at work (I think it's both)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But will non-TMA folks in the TGNC community listen tho? Or are yall gon keep platforming bullshit like that nonbinary blackness article? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't like taking selfies but here's one. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I came out to my lil brother he gagged bc I told him I swear my upper body strength vanished after I started my journey lmaaaaaao now I can't open cans or nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It REQUIRES a class analysis and class is not something that can solely be parsed by lived experience. The point of lived experience is to illuminate, not replace and be a substitute for class analysis; but class analysis is still the essential framing and grounding yalk cmon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not the bellbottoms with the tight as shirt from far away I def thought that too lmaoooo #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That doesn't make cisgender people TMA to me although Transmisogyny does, again, as the fulcrum, impact the way they navigate racialized sex imposition and Western bourgeois gender norms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is true even of alot of gworls ourselves and it's a problem #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[by supposed feminists and queer radicals as "you all are taking up space" "you all have privileges because of your hypervisibility" and all the various iterations of Socialization + sex class theory used to silence us and surveill our bodies, presentation, behaviors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My grandma dark skinned. My grandpa kinda light tho lmao now that I think about it #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This, however, is not how BMS theorizes the oppression of Black men and masculinity. So I don't understand why any trans men and transmascs would turn to it. BMS centers cisheterosexism and sexual dimorphism; it doesn't start from a material analysis at all, either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anarkata. Prison struggle. Black Marxist feminism. Trans liberation/Self-Determinism. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You would think that Afrofuturists want to move accordingly but they don't. Most Afrofuturists are liberal. Then I go to ATR spaces that have self-proclaimed radicals present and they radicalism don't be scientific or developed enough for me, and often times is just liberalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# and what they have done is groomed certain people under the Umbrella to believe it so that our own community could do their TERF dirty work for them. Trans folks assigned so-called AMAB try to gain access to this too if they aren't the gworls via a weird respectability politics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The deal breaker for my severance with the institutional church was ableism and abuse apologism. Theologies of liberation helped me with answers for every other subject. But when it came to those two, it came up short. And I just could not abide after that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[making me think I'm bi lmaoooo bc why else do I feel most validated talking to transbians? Hmmph. I definitely don't relate to transhet gworls in terms of these discussions tho bc I cannot imagine centering how i discuss my trans womanhood around (cis) men tbh it don't gel well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It *does* come from white supremacist actors. It *has* been used to help advance fascistic agendas on the ground. It *is* contributing to a spike in cultures of disinformation and anti-establishmentism that prioritize conservative politics of the body/health that are ableist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Pathology of Patriarchy" by Sanyika Shakur and then my own works "To The Ones Who Can Fly: A Message from the Whirlwind" and "My Gender is Marronage" (the original version) and then "My Gender is Marronage: A Revisitation." Reading these w "Black on Both Sides" (Snorton)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's not to say there aren't cultural specifics that developed here but it is to say that the phrasing of "descendants of slavery" to differentiate us from "descendants of immigrants" is not true to our shared/ongoing history of forced and coerced migrations and transportation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At some point making a discourse solely about obvious opps to the erasure of people who actually about shit starts to look sus to me. And makes me feel a kind of way bc I don't want to spend 24/7 arguing with elitists, yt/cis/lite/abled ppl when us marginalized folk could build]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conlanging is my neurodivergent special interest and I wish I could infodump about it more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm using the term "modality" because I wonder if these phrase constructions are riffs on two types of grammatical moods in linguistics. So we have a negative ("not the") &amp; generic/indicative ("it's the") mood. But posed thru   "improper" sentences too and used for diff reasons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think of it as an example of the Anarkata principle of care work and militancy. We talk about the whirlwind alot in the Anarkata Turn too so that is why I focused on breathing. And I speak of Black trans folk as those who can fly so thas why I draw on this Watchful breathing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember when I had a dream about the subway struggle before it happened. I had dreamt I was doing some speech; and months later that shit actually came true it's so fucking wild. I stay having dreams about the struggle though tbh (it's bc of stress/ptsd I feel like)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My name is literally Bl3ssing, hun. I literally walk in that on a daily. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyways I'm glad my particular neighborhood is negro asf bc I swear it is way easier for me to navigate intra-communal transmisogynoir than it is dealing with it in nonBlack settings. I don't understand gworls who say it's the other way around lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No shade! This why my path don't be letting me deal in astrology and tarot tbh. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And that's honestly something I think Black socialists and anarchists should be uniting around in the struggle against neocolonialism and Western imperial domination, tbh. All across the world fascism and the carceral state keeping bourgeois relation in place, in. patriarchy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It truly is a gag how when we are closeted they tell us "you a girl, you a girl," and then when we hatch, go through our chrysalis, and then flap our wings and fly, now suddenly they don't wanna keep that same energy. She spoke nothing but facts. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By this, transmisogyny becomes the fulcrum of maintaining patriarchy in general, of advancing transphobia against all gender expanses, and of mounting a fascistic counter revolution to protect the nuclear family, church, eugenic pseudoscience, and capitalist/Western society]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really like that I added a "click" phoneme to my conlang. The word &lt;&lt; Ťahu &gt;&gt; for example, that &lt;&lt; Ť &gt;&gt; is a "click" phoneme. &lt;&lt; Ťahu &gt;&gt; means "the sun" in my conlang. It's understood as a boat that travels the sky hanging droplets of water in the air for the stars to drink]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8. In fact, the conservative narratives that the ruling class pushes against us are often reinforced by or strengthened by the Representation ways of relating to Trans women and transfeminine people. Liberalism is therefore putting a target on the gworls' back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If funny how the trans umbrella includes nonbinary but there's a whole crop of nonbinary people who distance themselves from transness. Then they wanna turn around talking about exclusion and erasure. Yall be reminding me of how these Blerds act. "I'm not like those trannies"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking about some "let Him use you" and some "say His name" hmmmmm #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm very much in a until yall are ready I'm on hiatus frame of mind bc I'm not putting myself thru an infomammy experience ever again. I'll step up when bitches actually done did the study like I been saying and they ready to get a move on. Bc tbh I been ready for dat action]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never seen a trans organization that gatekept nonbinary people out the umbrella. Alot of this shit yall say on the internet be cap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When biomedicalism and "trans inclusive" forms of sex class theory show up, this is also a way of weilding sex dimorphism, ableism, social control, and ideological policing under patriarchal cisheterosexism to render certain gender expanses no longer transgressive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lorenzo, like many BARs, explicitly talks of understanding the possibility for a transitional period, and even of the use of certain (partial) demands to get there, all while still being anti-State, autonomist, and understanding that these things have to be done from below tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this may not have been intentional. Sometimes ppl just do shit bc they don't have any other tools to deal with things. But it's still ableism and a recipe for particular kinds of abuse and manipulation that disabled ppl often experience in intimate partner &amp; domestic settings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And in confronting it ideologically that is going to mean pushing ourselves and folks around us to move past their individualism, especially for people who are turning toward reactionary political interpretations of Black history and watered down views of the term bodily autonomy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conspiracism is inherently antisemitic and anti-materialoat. But I would expect less than attempts to tail cryprofascist thinking from yalls camp of "post-left" foolery over there in the anarcrakkka political milieu #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't understand why people insist on marginalized the THEORETICAL and analytical contributions of the Black underground, prison, street revolutionaries but it bothers me quite alot. Even other Black folks from the Hood be doing this sometimes if I'm being honest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think when one if the character spoke of hearing thunder int he grass that shit had me gagging. Read this while I was a foster kid. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the leftcons + leftlibs are totally willing to be two faced in allowing it to happen while also critiquing it, even go at each other's throats, just to build their organizations and platforms and campaigns, their grift, and their varying hopes at a comeuppance. Opportunists!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are not fighting over ideas. Cabral said this is about land and bread and water. What did STAR demand? Housing, education, and more. This is a material struggle and the gworls are on the front lines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually I think it's four or five gworls who have submitted to Rv, I need to check again. But yeah. Several of us be throwing down on there because the content on there can actually keep up with the shit We stretching. Most of these other publications do not have the range.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You supposed to learn from past relationships once it's over. Imo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tupac was done kind of sus idc what nobody say. Between them eye lashes and the way he came onto Hit Em Up this nigga gave very realness with a twist #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah. Some of their ideas of what the "effects of spiritual death" are were very ethnosupremacist and transphobic but some of them included things like Greed and love for power/wealth. Jesus being seen as trickster/thief is called the Ransom Theory of Atonement I think #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the men be doing this too tryna pressure trans folk to fit their very rigid expectations. It's so violent and you can't advocate for yourself in these situations bc they paint it as an attack on their identity if you call it out. This is why I'm moving tomgay for 2022. T4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like these niggas turn to pidcadt because they have a neocolonial investment in chasing a bag, in becoming celebrity-adjacent. Because of decades of being told that representation in media and the political apparatus will give them power that white supremacy robbed of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah i didn't realize this at first either. They teach us so much lies. I can drop a resource link if ur interested.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "We not the same/
I'm puss in boots/
Turn a ogre to a mouse/
Finesse yall out yo house too" 

- Queen Vee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So when I hear about similar dynamics happening to the gworls who date outside the TMA continuum I always bring an analysis of (claim to) material power and projection of traumas used to enact it. Bc that's generally how transmisogynoir seems to be working]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But each day something goes down that makes me realize just how full of Blavity Blacks these movement spaces be and it is never not a kiiiiiii lmaaaaaaaaao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grow out loud. I put my best foot forward. If I stumble then I will learn from there. Truth and principle is my guide. Not perfection, nor optics. People will lie and make shit up though. All I can do is my best and be accountable when it is required of me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I remember u explain a similar point about how math clarifies our underlying of oppression. Would love to keep learning more from u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think it's bc ppl associate "dating" with exclusivity nowadays, that what would otherwise be called courtship prior to that exclusivity is now termed a "talking stage." I don't have issues with it inherently it just depends on the intentions behind it and who I'm fw it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[should just be dismissed as already itself immaterial. Yet folks pick and choose when they wanna jack a Scientific versus Utopian account of their tendency. It's okay to be Utopian about gender they feel, and claim you looking at "genre" when really u doing race first hoteppery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want her to apply pressure and thas only bc I see if for her based on what she done gave so far #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's funny how enbies is mad at the very dolls who was just defending yall when them socialists tried to say that nonbinary identity is inherently bourgeois. The gworls "erase" yall supposedly even our insistence on a TMA analysis is what allows us to theorize all transphobia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And sis used that b/w photo lmaoooo this whole shit a mess ngl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emmy wished on a dragon scale, yall. That’s what started them dragon tales. All around the worldz the dragons flew and Emmy and Max just knew what to do. So they climbed on the backs of they lil dragon friends and now they adventures ain't never gon end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transmisogynoir really has some trans men and transmascs so angry s the gworls like we caused yall erasure to the point where yall really finna team up with the muhfuckin ASHIES around BMS to mount representation of ur issues? Chileeee no.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care to be in other ppl dating choices but the weird antics I see online is just... if yall like white cis men just go be that over there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo I used to have to sleep at night in a car, get up in the morning, sneak into a house I wasn't allowed it but a few hours per day due to transmisogynoir, shower, eat, rush to work to bust my ass at a restaurant, get off at night, travel by bus or foot or uber. Chile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why I'm Anarkata bc neither authcoms nor non-Black anarchists provide me theoretical clarity on the forces that go into why revolutionary projects and movements can descend into the very class antagonisms they claim to be struggling against.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When I first started the Undulatrix, it was when I was 10. I was trying to speculate: how would indigenous peoples use our relationship to water in response to land relations being taken away? I was specifically tryna imagine the kinds of social values &amp; myths we'd create."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Chileeeee this why I get do frustrated with the Black Radical Intelligentsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 2020 rebellions have punctuated a burgeoning queer/trans-led abolitionist tendency that has immense contradictions. This is true even if those participating weren't aligned accordingly: for the ruling class has interpreted the rebellions in that light.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was what pushed me out and also what catalyzed, alongside transphobia from family and community, the precarious positions I been in as far as health and finances (and I already grew up dirt poor anyways so). Most of my learning came tho: from revolutionary movement spaces]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel my spirit head again and I loved her, I loved her fiercely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yooooo! That's exactly why I had to leave behind BLT's interpretations of enslaved folk syncretisms. Like choosing to situate them Hush Harbors squarely into Christian *cosmology* will always lead us back to Eurocentrism imo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Niggas tried to recreate sex dimorphism under the guise of "gender as performance" LMAOOOO #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engaging with the medical industry feels alot like negotiating contracts and pay in the workplace. It be feeling like a labor struggle feels in terms of the mismatch in self interest, the need to self advocate and know ur shit and make demands and press and press. It's tiring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing about African faiths is that they make the ecogenic context of it all more apparent than Western ones do. But that doesnt mean they can't be repurposed for bourgeois ends as we see with so many of these ppl dese days. I'm tired of seeing the Spiritual Negrosie tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The conversations I be wanting to have are not suited for social media. I be wanting to discuss how harm within TMA only spaces looks. I be wanting to discuss how harm within dark skinned only spaces looks. I be wanting to discuss how harm within disabled and lumpen spaces looks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What makes it worst is that he actually stole the idea from Kwanzaa from a Black woman and rebranded it. He competent tarnished her intentions after the fact by piling on the misogyny with abuse and just outright horrors. Fuck Karenga. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The movie was so ass tho lmaoooo so idk #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to collaborate with some folks to figure out how this ep will help move tangible support toward marginal Black TMA ppl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to be SUPER Christian, like the passing out shit on the street type Christian das why when they try to argue with me I'm like no honey I be knowing them Scriptures AND various doctrines and to this day I read up on them so I can know what they are pushing abt TGNC ppl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. Black ppl were so much more self-reliant, institutionally speaking,and self-conscious, in such a way that we would have more unity and autonomy today if segregation returned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TME ppl be the first to be like "well I experience that too" and that's why I think it's important to name that the word "affected by transmisogyny" is speaking about when you are affected by a particular kind of structure. No other kind of transphobia is weilded in this way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't realize my piano has a setting for underwater and rain sounds but now I might wanna do a lil performance of my poetry I dropped in November. Lemme see a lil sumn sumn. Time will tell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so glad my Closet and Egg days were never as someone playing a cig. I played naggotry (nonbinary edition lmaaaaao) not faggotry and really dodged a bullet in terms of seldom dealing with cis men]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is said that nobody listened to the Whale's song and those in the Ocean also didn't listen to the human's cry either. Both were seen as tricksters, liars, foolish, for trying to have life leave its origin point in the Sea.

( Some thoughts on baby's crying going unheard )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too many of yall base ur issues with "organizers" around the former as the frame of reference, in ways that erases the existence of the latter. And it’s usually a reaction to whiteness and its many expressions (cisness, antiblackness, neurotypicalism, etc) tht u use to punch down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultimately what is being protected by Transmisogynoir is bourgeois relations, institutions, and interests. This is a class struggle, a decolonial struggle. The conservatives like to hang that truth out in the open, but the progressives (feminists, liberals, queer radicals) do not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kings, Queens, and Shamanic Beings: Blaqessentialism and The Hotep Gender Trinary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think it's an important text to read but should be approached w caution bc it can be triggering. Me and the Kats was going over this last year in our studies #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is really when I start askin what movement spaces do these anarchists be in. Putting blackface and redface and yellowface and brownface over petit bou anarchisms is not gonna make it any less white tbh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We don't spent too many decades extending grace and patience from within white/APOC organizations, petit Black anarchist circuits, and Black authcom and radlib-abolitionist movement spaces. And tryna struggle with yall in good faith and being paid DUST all the whiles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Incels and niggas who were called simps as a kid lmaoooooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There was never any stable argument, via the Scriptures, for a natural or even theological reason why African faiths, or trans "lifestyle" should be demonized. No, this demonization was less about how satanic/heathen those things are inherently and moreso about the Mission of...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She thought she ate and he think she about to let him eat 😭😭😭😭 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait til me and my boys can perform Elegy for the Dolls Who Fly again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But ur not Black so it doesn't matter how you feel. "Boi" is a Black QTGNC term. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lemme drop this piece I wrote on transmisogynoir, on revolutionary criticism of TMA hypervisibility, and on the divide and dule tactics being played against the Trans* umbrella bc of anti-colonial views of our struggle being replaced by liberal ones. 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real niggas sniff each other dicks to make sure the homies been faithful. Black men don't cheat!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Centering lived experience above structural analysis is exactly why TME ppl refuse to believe that transmisogynoir is the fulcrum so yes I'm good on that false dichotomy. Lived experience without theory can only get so far; theory devoid of lived experience is equally useless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. When Black trans women and transfeminine people are discussed, there are often claims that we "take up space." on the flip side, there are claims that people are "centering" us, being solidary with us. But neither is true. We are Hypervisibilized as part of a class oppression.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Niggas be like "don't make sexuality your whole life" and then compare their relationship to God to the marital union. Yall literally squeeze Creator into your sexuality but then mad at us queer and trans folks for simply existing as ourselves? Leave us tf alone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The conversation about "rest as resistance" is making me think back to flying African folklore. I often turn to these myths to help me reflect on my struggles as a Black transfeminine radical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But at the end of the day I definitely didn't think that was the primary contradiction in the situation. It was hurtful but the gworls there were like "while everyone is screaming WE HAVE NOTHING TO LOSE BUT OUR CHAINS yall have to remember that WE HAVE OUR LIVES TO LOSE"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discernment is key to figure out when what situation calls for what and that takes time, it's messy, so I'm not reading or wagging fingers. Just making an observation and intervention that I know has helped me and which I hope can help someone else]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I move through Black Radical Tradition by way of Third Worldism and Autonomism. I am guided by the prison struggle and the Panther legacy, especially anarchist thought which came out of it. I am grounded in a Transfemimist Material Analysis (TMA framework) and Black Ecology.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So to me that just sounds like yall wanted to hoard resources and shit for your lil club and when a fascist comes along that's the perfect scapegoat to do your dirty work all while distancing yourself. Is that not how neoliberal America and the pigs relate to the vigilantes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But these naggots was trying to use the veneer of concerns for my health to pressure me into political liberalism, into an idealist vision of anarkata politics, and also into centering interpersonal relationships with them that didn't match up with my boundaries + comfort levels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Idk some niggas be the actual dangerous mfs all while claiming they in danger lmao I peep the antics from afar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When bourgeois relations need to conserve themselves there us always somehow scapegoat supposedly threatening the sanctity of its institutions or spaces. both conservative &amp; liberal forces use sex dimorphism in varying ways to portray transgressive women's gender expanses as such]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Basically the convergence in particular structures conditions specific types of fascistic forms of suppression, which also generate a certain kind of civil rights battle emphasis in each context; all of these have to be dealt with as a totality if we want Self Determination]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was not willing to subject myself to that process, especially not when school is fucking expensive and racist as shit. And then it became clear that with my undiagnosed neurodivergences I wasn't gonna be able to function in school anyway. Finally, I was harassed by a neofascist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would yall prefer? Us just remain silent while transphobic feminists and chasers groom enbies of any AGAB and trans men and transmascs to be divided and limited in themselves as well as engaging in shared transmisogynoir against the gworls?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of you muthafuckers are opps to me. All of you "run" our organizing and community and creativity spaces. All of you ensure that our movements are stuck in liberalism and/or proximal to conservatism. All of you are trash and BAR bitches like me will get it with you if we must]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An example. White folks say heaven is above. Our traditions see the earth as sacred. But some of our traditions also locate divinity in the sky. Now wht if, in the name of not centering whiteness, ppl overlooked the latter traditions, assuming tht only Europeans have aerial gods?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is incredibly narrow, overly subjective to act as though a structural and material analysis via historical materiality is not important in our struggle for liberation. I really think some of yall are just folks with political opinions rather than committed revolutionaries tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[things about punk and rap, both aesthetically and politically, folks are drawn to. Alas, alot of Black anarchists are antiblack and bou ass mfs who only want to fuck crackers. Which is why, while many BARs are Black anarchists, not every Black anarchist can be considered a BAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patriarchy is inherently misogynistic. Patriarchy's misogyny is especially violent toward gender/sexually expansive women. And that violence is heightened when sex dimorphism, ableism, social control, &amp; ideological counterinsurgency converge to mark these womanhoods Transgressive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you liked rock, anime, and had other nerdy interests and bitches called you an Oreo, it's either bc 1) you thought it made you better or separate from others (they punched up) or bc 2) ppl were directing Christian, allistic, and cishet biases against your interests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People think sexual dimorphism is the basis of one's class positioning. Blame white supremacy using the former to falsely universalize and naturalize how it constitutes the latter. Now, unfortunately even those claiming to be anticolonial take it for granted or on face value #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyway I mentioned this because this sort of thing goes into why ppl framing Christianity as a pacifist religion are wrong. It isn't pacifist. The Jesus-as-thief model of atonement are easily translated into colonial violence if indigenous culture is always framed as deviltry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That excuse gives very much "a few bad apples"/"thin blue line" energy to me. And yes, I'm suggesting that you anarcrakkkas move like cops because at the end of the day yall are settlers &amp; the State/racial capitalism positions yall as a social-garrison to protect property/nation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like old camera quality is partly behind why ppl so mystified around colorism. Not even just black and white photos, but also picture in color from the time periods before the social media/smartphone age. Shits had ppl looking darker than they actually are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't yet recovered from when me and my comrades was doing mutual aid distros and it was like I used to have to dodge sexually invasive comments from folks outside our team already but the more I started wearing dresses the worse it got and it was always both cis men &amp; women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Being from ny everyone here says it, even myself, but it still bugs me and I'm always tryna unlearn it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stepping into someone else's affairs, cherry picking local beliefs, presenting Jesus as the real version of said cherry picked aspects of the cosmology, demonizing all the local truths that aren't coopted for the sake of missionary activity. So many translations of the Bible...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cisheterosexism is used to regulate all gender expansive included that of people whose identities map onto their sex assignment (cis folks). Transmisogyny is often the fulcrum even in those cases. Hella cis men fear "emasculation" precisely bc they know this deep down inside]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All these authcoms like to do is lie and erase BARs so they can maintain they standing with white MLs lmao #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yall Taylor Swift stans thought you was finna eat me up but you don't understand: I am Nsambu Za Suekama. I don't fear niggas on the internet lmaaaaao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do not agree with the idea that the internal colony thesis avoids is not commensurate with an analysis of settler colonialism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They can't. They broke. And I don't mean this is a classist way. It's because of how fucked the economy is why so many of them are turning toward the podcast shit in hopes of getting a bag as a social media influencer/micro-celebrity. Wish they would build for revolution tho tbh #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Are you gay?" used to be the most terrifying question as a kid and now it's just plain offense to me if someone even has to ask bc it's like wait do I not exude TRANNYDOM and FAGGOTRY to you from the top of hills, darling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yup. This is why I'm tryna focus right now on Body Doubling reconciled with a focus on subsistence and PE. I wonder if that, Event-Scenes, and formal organizing were more developed modalities that worked alongside each other and gave room for people to flit in and out of each]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wilderson is real intentionally about framing his criticism around the issues with "postcolonialism" as an ACADEMIC discipline, all while suggesting that those problems are isomorphic with the only tangentially related framework of "anti-colonialism" as a set of radical movements]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmaooooooooo I go from saying "girl" to "chile" to "bro" mad times lol #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now when anarchists when will anarchists stop tokenizing "POCs" tho lol 😆 bc they be moving like the authcoms on that front #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's also like Black trans people are living through Jewel Crow segregation so why would I ask for a return to Jim Crow on top of that? Ppl on Twitter trivialize our history like this shit is not serious. Mind you Jim Crow 3.0 is on the horizon and it won't be hidden to be honest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# instead of tryna clamber over each other up to the top (from "Lowerarchy Theory" a parable in "Wild Thing Wisdom" by the Afrofuturist Abolitionists of the Americas).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nah I was bout to chew you up lemme dm you lmakkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to make a playlist of all the songs that used to give me gender euphoria as a kid. I remember when my brother would come at me for "liking girl songs."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally lmaooooo like the Eve vs Adam, Adam vs Eve narrative is tired! The "What do you bring to the table" versus "if you lead properly I will submit" wars need to end. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In truth, you cis men pathologize yourselves when you think Suits and being Together is what is gonna get us free. Because it assumes that you are oppressed because of being "ghetto" and shit like that. It also relies on deeply (trans)misogynoiristic rhetoric simultaneously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I agree. I just don't think those pillars will come from a categorical insistence on being anti-organizational and anti-theoretical in the way certain anarchists I encounter seem to be implying. In my opinion we gonna need ideology and movement to address hierarchy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soon as he started "rapping" over a decade ago his shit became trash. He is also a fucking liar, abuser, and overall whack ass human being. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really wish I could pull an Area Scatter and disappear into the woods for the remainder of this phase of my transition. Going through my Chrysalis in an age of cameras and photos and shit is not fun. Too much scrutiny and too much external interference about a certain Look]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I have grown tired of hookup culture too and I barely engaged but that's bc even in "no strings attached" situations it don't be much different. It's honestly wild how trash people are across genders. Lmao. I been thru bullshit with folks under the TMA continuum too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It has allowed things like EJ to become a conversation. It has been forcing ppl to reckon with the structural causes of differenxes in mortality rates for Black birthing people. It has allowed folk to question the BMI and IQ and expose how anti-fatness, ableism, racism connect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reclaiming tomgirl to mean a transfem who gay &gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "I'm not trans, I am [insert variety of non-cis identity] always reads very much "Im not Black I am Dominican" to me, like okay Transness vs Cisness is how gender fugitivity is politicized. Use the labels you will but distancing oneself while also still tryna push aside ppl]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>