<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He reached up and turned it off as they arrived. Street sign in the shot. Can see his had and hear the button clic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is it the lighting or are they both literally talking out of the side of their mouths #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why not let him walk into scotus and get his needs taken care of forthwith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The Yale astro. dept. checked and replied that Ms. Greene is still on the Christmas card list]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is reality like gerrymandering, can I get a hard number here please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Rudy as in "you want to talk, but first let me tell you about these great burglar alarms I'm selling"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The sheriff's dept. or whatever gov. agency fingered him doesn't have standing to make this id and then prosecuit him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Does Koch have more influence over the chamber than the individual dues paying local businesses that join the chamber to hopefully boost their sales. In posting this, maybe the individual business owners should unionize, lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tsunami comes from earthquake. Tsunami warning tower not earthquake reinforced. Kind of reminds me of Fukushima Daiichi : emergency generators in basement, tsunami floods basement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And now doj is busy with a bunch of new investigations and won't have any time for this old news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thx #USER# #USER#
  #HASHTAG#
(Clic an arrow, Scroll down for cams)
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's what commercials are for. "Free" Broadcast TV is just like cable/streaming 
(c/s) TV except c/s charges a premium, say $100 a month, for getting their signal and still includes commercials.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good informational list of current Dtrump litigation #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Getting to the Heart of Science Communication, A Guide To Effective Engagement #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putins trying the "nuts like trump" tac #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My Areo press.
35-40g pre ground or grind your own coffee, brew per your choice then add water to make 16oz., save in an insulated carafe, drink in demitasse (3oz cup) portions so over a few hours the coffee is hot and perfect for each cup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You guys decide. ff to 34:00. I find it so sad. All the assholes at the capitol that day and one person is shot.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since HBO doesn't like comments: 
Friends. The one where they get back together, 
and go to CHEERS #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And shoot some hot mustard inside the dog? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# But this investigation is going to take a year, right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think I meant to retweet in support of your tweet. I'll try again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I guess the latest spire was completed. 
From Jan 2021; #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why, they are obviously selling something. Is the Heritage foundation a tax exempt non profit?
Yes #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Bill does have  a point. lol He was an ass years before tfg managed to do his damage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ok, so when the shares lose value you pay the company $, got it, sounds fair #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thermobaric; 1st blast vaporizes a fuel cloud that mixes w the air and settles into spaces like buildings,  2nd blast ignites that vapor/air mix. Very indiscriminate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good thread on the 1/6/2021 inserection from eyewitness #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The "novel strategy " the families used ? 
I don't remember]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Seen this photo a lot lately. Keep wondering what the story of the painting is. I sfnf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a lense effect? Since this is a place where humidity is often in the 
90+% what I envisioned is a  group of water misters, the natural wind, and colored point lights to visualize to the compression of the air flowing around a large object.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do one of these on the most offensive Twitter clic bait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Big city must have broadcast antenna tv AD. And a new android TV has lots of 'free' internet choices too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# What is Richard Donoghue's current job? sfnf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If any of these people didn't have a headlamp on their bicycle, accountability would have been immediate. fyi #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Send the officer and his buddies the the Michigan state Capitol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cpac started in Orlando. More terrible quotes on the way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Not to worry. SCOTUS knows that the counting of ballots is not to be messed with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Saw a tweet of a R flyer someone picked up off the floor of the Michigan house or senate listing words to use and words to not use. No one said 'the D should do this.'  They should]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It like a boat in a hurricane ends up in your yard. You get to keep it right. re 45 visits hurricane aftermath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Doesn't DOJ have standing to deal with Barr's trespasses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Testing the self destruct debris radius maybe?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maybe this seemed like a good statement at the time amid the chaos and fear of Kabul. #USER# has certainly been at the heart of the moment over and over these past years and I thank him for his reporting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "a former government official"? Good to knowq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I was pinging #USER#, she said she found it. Where's your link please tb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thermobaric vacuum bomb? (Thx re bbc) #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tokyo Olympic Silver metal for sale #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Miley. You know the target. A band.  Some songs. Voices. Some crew making magic in the dark. We can't stop. We run things, things don't run we
Don't take nothing from nobody, yeah.
Well done!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost like stop the draft and end the Vietnam war...
Not #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What little I know nft is connected to bitcoin. To create an nft you have a bitcoin wallet, register the nft somehow and link that registration # to the wallet. Then you can sell it. To buy it's just like buying anything else with bitcoin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# and not with one sentence at the end of next week's show. Do a proper story on an important subject.
(60 ' did you steal the bit where all the eyeballs lined up from #USER# ?) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm wondering how deep is the ocean at the site of the event]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yes w64, unload the ballast, but then it might tip over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I guessing this is a tuckerism. The identical sentiment popping up over and over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# With all that experience he must know all the ins and outs of the depth of defense #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It says these anti-union groups send mailings to people likely to opt-out of a union. (These anti-u groups ID these people by their social media posts.) My ? is how do they get the personal info of these opt out people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ask the writers about strikes. 
Can we join the Chamber of Comerce, go to their meetings and let the local business owners know that an upcoming piece of legislation is bad for the entertainment biz and therefore bad for the local economy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Because it was the USA border patrol across the river in Mexico making sure their maga friends were OK and doing a little theater catcalls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Got a friend in Hollywood. Lost touch over the years as he became too famous. Would his agent ever pass along a message? No]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "Healthy soils are the key to feeding the world" if those are really your words RM and you want to reach a wide audience maybe you should keep your ignorant insults and politics to yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brain plaque 2018 study w some notes I can re find for a Twitter minute 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Of course.
 Like
bone saw not working?
Is it plugged in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Scalise was also on "Meet the Chuck Todd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Re about the men in black breaking windows with a claw hammer and a black umbrella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And the damaged car rebuild industry. If it seems like too good a deal, it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Mike Richards should be the new head writer for NCIS. Just saying, he's so self confident and connected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suicide thoughts. International phone help lines #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just saying; blocking on Twitter is a good thing. It puts all the misinfo types like #USER# in a rubber room bouncing off the other misinfo's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aspire "news" app for your phone. Domestic violence "auto call for help" app #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# All of those 5, 6, 7 year old cases doj has been perfecting, none of those(just saying) is as important as what's happening right now, today. We have vital problems that need addressed in time to be resolved before the next election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good #USER# thread. This is why it was so strange when the GOP launched their voting machine concerns #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is diesel fuel mining equipment? Presidential hopeful Doug Ducey thinks so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nice! 
Who else saw the drone on Lab Padre?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Anyone think the viruses are pissed because the humans have not managed to stop 45]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #URL# note; Wikipedia, how useful and free. If you can donate to Wikipedia please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Citizens united, voting rights and gerrymandering so far from chief Justice Roberts. Anything else on your to do list cjr? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And then when a ruling comes out after a few years "you don't have standing " , omg. But the scotus can come out with a ruling in a week if they feel like it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Same w numerous seditious members of Congress. Garland won't arrest them because it would shift the balance  and allow D to pass laws. (Odd calling our current situation 'balance ')]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Asking A. G. Garland, nicely, if he's investigating anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's it, make a quorum what Greg Abbot says it is. In fact why bother with elections at all. They are so much trouble. Just select your candidates and appoint them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# reporter #USER# on the problems w/ the largest national voting machine Co, ES&amp;S #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# My sympathies too Felicia. This tweet sounded good and I see your strength!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes vb. Do I sense an adjustment in the Twitter algorithm? Note the placement after your tweet:
. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is AZ rep John Kavanagh arrested yet? He clearly commits a felony here #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# This man is locally insulted with a #HASHTAG# hash tag nick name. Like #HASHTAG# and #HASHTAG# . Except that the cast of the local Iranian version of #HASHTAG# might be executed for making such a joke. God is not funny!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And false equivalency still getting top rate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# All a diversion so that one cow could escape]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Dic read Democracy in Chains by MacLean for the libertarian sources]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An example of a too good to be true program. I'm thinking Chinese then I look at the tag, "Xi truth " lol #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched an exclusive behind-the-scenes tour of the #USER# Super Bowl Halftime Show stage on the #HASHTAG# app.

Watch here: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why are we here? In large part to chief Justice Roberts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She quit because it wasn't a success "they didn't take one hostage! I quit"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[good Thread on usa truck bridge blockade prep by #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I don't know if a misinformation push, like the former guy does, can use beauty and transcendence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# YF: "What else could possibly go wrong"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And then W threw the guy a roll of paper towels?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bronze is made of copper and various other metals depending on the desired properties. So yes a copper and zinc mix is called bronze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is why scotus does not have standing to make rulings on medical matters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 6840 Hollywood Boulevard The star will be dedicated in the category of Television at 6840 Hollywood Boulevard in front of Jimmy Kimmel Live.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is there live recording in the court? Unfortunate interruption]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Fingers move down, go through the mic stand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Seems like ALEC and Sen Joe "on my boat" Manchin is ALEC #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I just got some reasonably priced 3M N95 masks (for yard and hobby work)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Menopause. And too many products have not been proven safe #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The blackmailer evidently thought Matt's culpability was worth $25 million. Something is there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Didn't the fbi investigate and found it was a pre existing garge door pull thingy? I can see how no one noticed it before #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The little guy at the end of the clip. Lifts face shield up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# John Yoo, great. Anybody know what Alberto Gonzales thinks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The last few minutes of Sullivan's Jan 6 insurgents video, has someone from infowars trying to get the rights to the video. Standing outside the Speakers lobby doors saying, "I got the shooting"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# the Khwaja Rawash Airport is open for arrivals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With an egg cream mix, explained right the first time #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Floyd verdict read 15 year old that called for help is shot 4 times by PD #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, really Joe. 
Walk out to the mound, get the ball from Merrick and send him to the  showers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Or if you like L. A. I re-watch BOSH every few months. Like Mimi Rogers' character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes MN. Chuck has been an ass forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# LoL the real arc is in Grant co KY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 290 votes (2/3) needed to expell a member]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And Sio2 is going to build a new plant? I guess they have the specialized machinery they require already on hand?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm wondering about a lot of sheriffs, being elected, have morphed into acting like they are independent of the legal/justice system #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If he hadn't included the date story, oh, and the short skirt remarks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Do pacific islands still use the ocean as their landfill? Saw or read that sometime in the recent past]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# So sad it's 4more45 right? Good choice so are you feeling Lucky 3:16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simple lies vs the nuanced truth. Will the media grasp this?
Maybe PBS Frontline, for one episode #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Fortunately sec of treasury Mnuchin has 2016 movie production experience with "The Suicide Squad" (pitch; don't get in the running car, lets hide behind the people w no masks)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm guessing there is nothing new about Nostradamus in your future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's but the planning of the Doj and scotus took place earlier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's like the ticking clock the law gives congress. Every two years there is an analogous change of power. The previous congress no longer exists and with that, legality regarding that congress, also goes away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This #USER# grammys tv production needs an Emmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# .
I see a series of anti climate change comedians. Is it a club? What's the profit? Glacial used to mean something that moves very slowly #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Our mind tries to make a 3D image out of the two similar but different images and some of the little rainbow sparkles appear to be floating in space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Love your work and your words. It seems words are a powerful tool the D can use. Why can't the D get on message and get together and promote a unified approach like the R do? The word of the day &amp;c.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Sen Whitehouse on buying the Supreme Court 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yea well no wonder, you live in Russia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tina could have used that last night #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does opening for gop (don't hand him a gavel) Kevin McCarthy count #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So congress could sue the DOJ so we can see the Barr docs that Garland covered up? Or sue the DOJ to not make up law with an opinion by one guy. This time it's Garland. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Your doj at work. This crime happened in 2016. Was it slow walked for 4 years or were there that many "i"s and "t"s that kept popping up over the last 5 years? re 6 days ago #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# no Ben and Jerry's for israeli nso pegasus and no #USER# for Dubai until we see a live Princess Latifa 
(no pay wall) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm not defending AB, but it was an ambush imo. Did you see the John Sullivan 40 minute video that captured the moments ? (aka Jaden X) Something so wrong about how the events unfolded and culminated with her sticking her head thru the window and being shot in the neck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And it's making Brass keys magnetic lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Got my 2nd Pfizer shot today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Looks like mother nature is pissed ay GA
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Have you made 50 tweets with your amazing discovery 7. What an ass. All the artists prerecord. Don't want the chance of dead sound on a worldwide live show]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Google... it's filled from the bottom so the plastic cap gives the 'top' that rounded shape. That's all the removable plastic is for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Doj continues climbing to the top of the plateu. Enough low hanging fruit to run this out away from the $ and organizers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# AG Alberto Gonzalez favorite phrase "I do not recall"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Full time job, as a little one. Changes and new discoveries one moment to the next]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It's all or nothing then? No, tfg is a distraction. So are Bannon and Meadows. While Doj operates like we still use typewriters and set type by hand. 1. Voting 2.John Roberts scotus 3.womens' body autonomy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Garland is busy trying to take over the E. Jean Carroll rape case for tfg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That was great. Olympics. Very dramatic - 
US Equestrians]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# To paraphrase tfg's ag barr: I'm musing on the word "must"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This vs what happens in a Tour de France crash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Wheres your rt link. I won't believe you unless you have a Russian TV link.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm light sensitive and I got some 'blue blocking' glasses for computer work (they look orange) and I now use them for driving. No pain from opposing drivers with their brights on or even driving toward the sunset.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I've recorded neighbors' barking dogs and played it back to them (to the dog, not the neighbor)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Look at the foxNews headlines on yahoo news. All emotional tweeking. Same idea here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think a top down approach would work. Arrest tfg and witnesses below would be begging to testify]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes "barbaric roe v wade." Let us legislate back-alley coat hangers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I got a feeling and I can't let go - them to the prime video TV series]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Az gop vote research in Montana #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Is there any solution to the snail pace the courts move at? Our computer reality moves at one speed. Courts are ruled by a calendar. Bannon gets J6 subpoena Sept 23. Noshow Oct 14. Surrender to fbi Nov 15. Dec 2021: Fed wants April,  Bannon wants Oct. 2022 for his one day trial .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Halftime, it's Compton CA, the houses are all white, Eminem rises up out of a jail that blows up &amp;c #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I knew, just from Twitter, a week before 1.6.21 that something was going to happen. The warnings for BLM to stay away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, local targeted school boards need help #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I use when I write a sarcastic tweet. I don't like having to figure out if it is sarcasm. I use it but have heard sarcasm described as 'mean spirited']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I always thought w McCain's turnabouts, it felt like blackmail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because apparently Garland is the Swiss army knife of AG's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Thanks for the answer on how long for jwst to complete one orbit of L2 . Half a year, amazing #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Has Ye gone to Moscow to speak with Pu yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Send your Liz Mair's God-given-free-speech donation to #USER# 's USA-CONSTITUTION granted free speech suit
 (re Mair's "God-given..." reference here nunesvfreespeechDOTcom/ )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There is that long game. I also thought we were in the middle of the Koch Dominion et al end game. Now I'm thinking they have no end game, just an end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horrific bastarards (and a virgin mary) at scotus, coming soon to a usa hospital near you #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# All I can afford is the plan that consists only of deductibles at least that what it seems like. If we didn't have to bargain for healthcare we could bargain for pay or conditions. What is Pete talking about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 20211201 #USER# you had me except for that giant red flag about rewriting the constitution. Chaskoch has been pushing that for years and you want to hand him the whole game. lol
 read: 
Democracy in Chains
 by Maclean]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How do we know when doj is not investigating ? Live At 16:00 Garland says he's  investigating a number  of white collar crimes. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# your new advertising model (3 adds every 10') is the worst fu*king thing ever. It makes movies unwatchable. Like most orgs. trying to monitize, does anyone sit and experience what you create?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Has Dershowwitz mentioned Dick Cheney yet? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# If politics influencing doj is a crime, ie a law, then prosecute it. If not and it is useful as tfg and barr proved, then use it for the good to save our constitution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Like that time you couldn't get your new handbag in the color you wanted. I feel it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You could be a member too. Looks like anybody can join]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# 
United we stand 
Divided we fall 
Where we go one
We go all
(The last half is abbreviated WWG1WGA)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# To make up a quote Maynard G. Krebs might have said: "What are those cats doing?" (the 39 members lol)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# What we just learned the last 4 years with tfg is that a nonpartisan independent doj is nice but it clearly is bs. Do whatever is necessary to save our democracy. A weekly Monday lunch at the white house w potus and AG would be a good start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The gerrymandering boat left 10 years ago because the dnc didn't get active 10 years before that after gore v bush happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# After I finish eating my lunch sitting on a pile of used windmill blades and solar panels I am dealing with, ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ok, sounds good. Is it leap year? So the 31st!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Biggest crowd ever, like he always wanted, to show him how happy we are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just saying, maybe the NSA knows what the govenor was talking about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Unlike saying the Treasury SHALL turn over taxes, lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Says a faceless troll and, you know...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Let's see how long Meadows takes. This J6 work is interesting but it's just a distraction if the monumental voting f-up isn't delt with forthwith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Or in other words the police are getting the maga crowd behind their line]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Re Gifford shooting was 
1. 8. 2011 ff abc article the next day
The palin add below #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# agree tdc. Have you witnessed a total solar eclipse? It just seems too f ing perfect to be chance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How many palpate? I get the feeling that at the Dr's convention they give seminars that advise to not palpate. Some kind of liability thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm looking forward to the money laundering segment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I want interviews with tfg about how bad his jail conditions are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Remember when Google used to rank searches by truthful popularity. Then they found out how much revenue could be generated by accepting payments from foxNews &amp;c for artificial promotion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If we can't prosecut a potus while in office and we won't when they become the former guy, and use the doj to defend him because he was potus at one time and drop legal action against him because he's no longer potus? Congress, POTUS, &amp; what's the 3rd branch again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great thread for MLK. Thank you Ida Bae Wells #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I always wonder why bathrooms and kitchens have sharp edges and sharp point corners]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>