<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s all fat chicks and limp wristed male feminists nodding along in the comments. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And yeah, I get it. I get doing it once. Or twice. Or in rapid fire after a bad break up. 

But … how can you be over 30 and not realize this is no way to live your life?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You don’t believe that New Yorkers in parking lots won’t yell at you for being in their way?

I’ve gotten honked at or yelled at for not pulling out fast enough once in my#USER#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right? She’s a straight shooter. And has decided that all college educated people are insane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just goes to show that people of different races get along great when they are part of the same religion. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Color without their consent.nnIt allows white saviourism, even as Covid lockdowns starve millions in the third world.nnBlack Americans, Latinos, many Africans, Australia’s aborigines…have all made it clear they don’t want the damn vaccine.nnOh, but the White Man will make them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Near future? I doubt it. 

In the end, they probably were too young and have more growing to do. 

Maybe they’ll reconnect someday. But…maybe it will be a sad, sweet memory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect last name.

Perfect name, full stop. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If he mandated vaccines for immigrants, it would be seen as an international human rights violation.nnMandating for citizens? Meh. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, the kids have bought into the premise, so we are going.

But I’m taking my own car.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My brother knew his current girlfriend when they were both younger, and he thought she was “too young” to date back then.

I think she was like 21 or a bit older and he was early 30s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On young people &amp; partnering up (or not):

We have a good friend who is 30. Smart, educated. Had a stable, if meh paying, job. Girlfriend of 2+ yr we assumed was “the one.”

Decided to go to grad school. Instead of going locally, moved back to live w his mom while in class. 1/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Being gay I’m sure you were more scared of aids a little before I was. I was blissfully unaware until college. Boy, howdy, did freshman orientation do a number!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The CDC says adults should walk around 5 miles per day.

I live in a fairly rural area and get like triple the exercise of most city people, and still only clock 3 miles per day on my phone.

Where even would most Americans be able to find 5 safe miles to walk?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surrogacy by the wealthy and by affluent and influential gays is doing more than people know to turn everyday people against “the elite.” #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Haha. Yeah, kids can get themselves in trouble with poor taste. Man, I have loved some crazy guys in my day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adult men have always had nudge-nudge, wink-wink fantasies about “barely legal” girls.nnBut with the internet, as well as input from countries where child/teen brides are common, has ballooned into whole belief systems that revolve around IMAGINARY teenage girls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right?

“I held my nose when we entered Kentucky.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government is a protection racket. When the govt fails to protect people, they find other protectors.

Same way people in the provinces of Rome eventually relied on local generals, and not the power of the empire itself.

This, ultimately, is how America will fracture. 1/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is very true. And even when they are not bots, they can simply be bad actors.

It’s often not worth the hassle to figure out whether someone is a real human being or a well designed AI program. If someone is contradicting you, they are provoking you. Best to ignore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whelp, we went out to dinner, came back and they were already broken up.

Older a kid left for a friends house. Broody is (I assume) out in their studio.

Only downside is the laundry room is in the studio and husband needs to put stuff in the dryer…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a day when I realized several people I thought were okay had very messed up ideas about young people and sexual ethics and I had to block them.

Oh, well. For me, some things are beyond the pale.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is 100% true.

The trans trend affects everyone, but it has the potential to affect gay and lesbian kids worst. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recently realized that I’ve blocked 400 accounts over the years. I don’t even remember why in most cases. 

I wonder if I should mass unblock them and start over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ah. Well yeah he speaks in the voice of the old, sick and angry. But the middle is shifting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As for Broody, older Kid and I assume he’ll sleep with someone else within 48 hours, and absolutely knock up the next girl he dates. 

If so, good for him. He wants to re-create the family he never felt he had.

Older Kid isn’t ready for a family yet. At 19, that’s okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While it is true any woman can find a man if they are willing to be realistic, folks underestimate how much small differences make in a woman’s “market value.”

People say my 2 daughters look very alike, but Older is 2 inches taller, slightly slimmer and is more “feminine.” 1/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Australia considered aborigines “fauna” for the early years of its existence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You hear that everywhere with Gen X: “My parents got divorced and I dont want to have to go through that, so I’m not gonna marry.”nnMillennials I know often don’t even seem to bother to marry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Broken young people make good targets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Everything now is sad beige, mustard and terra cotta.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Living in society requires giving up some freedoms.

Alone, in the woods, you can walk where you like, shit where you like, eat what you can find &amp; discard what you don’t need.

The point with covid restrictions is they GO TOO FAR.

I already gave up what I was willing. NO MORE. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Haha. Yes. That is true.

But you hear so many stories from these women. Like friend of mine (total nutcase) convinced doctors to give her malaria meds for a trip. (She didnt need them.) Then she proceeded “have an allergic reaction” to meds.

THEN claimed to have gotten malaria.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I can imagine. I don’t know the answer. Gay men seem to repel one another, like 2 same sides of a magnet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oddly, my brothers wife’s mom read some of my books. She liked them and always asks why I didn’t write more. 

I think some families are just supportive like that. 

But my fam has always been private]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Anda they gotta be-a sayin’ it, like diss… “Ay-a wanded it Yestahday!” #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Douglas Murray’s avatar is freaking me out because I always associate a certain type of head shot with bots. Yet he adopted exactly that aesthetic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well they need to know something before 13. Most girls have their periods by then. I’d assume a lot of boys are getting to puberty, too.nnNot to mention some girl told me what sex was when I was 5 years old, at catholic school, in 1978nnI think the cat is out of the bag. Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Certainly the democrats don’t need it anymore. They got their totalitarianism. No need to keep pandering to the lunatic fringe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah, it hit me hard, too, because my 16 year old has said this exact thing to me ,many times.

I’ve seen firsthand how they’ve had their whole lives cancelled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Could be. My brothers girlfriend got terrible back pain as a symptom. Hope you feel better soon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I hate when friends try to get me to “break up” with them. It’s a personal opinion, but I feel it deeply.,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# White people are only 25% of the population. I dont think most people here know what “BIPOC” means.nn(I’m not sure I do. POC is people of color, but…oh wait. “Black and indigenous?”)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, it’s possible the state of Hawaii just doesnt want to tell people how many cases there are because

1. People would want to limit tourism again, and we cant afford it.
2. It would demonstrate how we wrecked our economy for 2 years over nothing #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This does not surprise me or even bother me.

What is annoying is my parents’ lack of willingness to accept they’ve transitioned to the “post-grandkid” phase of life where they have no choice but to accept the ministrations of those who are willing.x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Right????

I’m turning 50 next year, and I am SO GRATEFUL for my family. I see my parents being over 70, and having siblings, spouses and kids is HUGE. My mom has no siblings, and its very painful for her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow. Amazing. Welcome to the world of sanity!

I left the left around the time of the Parkland shooting. Not pro gun, per se, but that whole thing was so fake, I couldn’t take it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m starting to wonder now what people in modern world feel like is “too much injury” for a child to go through.

I grew up in 70s/80s. Almost died of salmonella age 1 because parents gave me raw milk. (Which my parents DID NOT freak out at seller for.)

Then, they lost me 1/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who had “Claire Lehman attacks Maajid Nawaz for demanding a civil rights inquiry into Australia’s placing Aborigines in Quarantine camps” on their 2021 Bingo card?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I thought it was genius. A movie to mark an era or a generation. Isn’t a Netflix subscription like $9.99 per month?

Get it for a month and watch Squid Game while you are at it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, if you want society to be better, you need to hold YOURSELF to a higher standard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh, believe me. I know. My last one lasted like 6 months. But i did enjoy it while it lasted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah wait, apparently she got asked for her number today. 

Crisis (may be) averted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It’s hard to say. Depends how much money he has. But basically yeah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As pissed as I am about the rat attack, it’s not the end of the world.

I can gather enough eggs for another hatch in the next 72 hr, &amp; hatches only take 18 dd.

It’s just annoying. As that’s 5 dozen fewer eggs I have to sell at a time of year when they aren’t laying much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sarcastic Northeasterners do not go over well here. 

I’m from NY, and I cannot tell you how often I walk by a tourist from NY who says something that makes me cringe so hard…and take several steps away so nobody thinks I’m with them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demisexual means “no casual sex.”

Of course you can’t just say “no casual sex” because that sounds prudish. So instead you need to pretend to have a special and unusual sexual orientation. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But I honestly think that a lot of “mostly gay” men in the past were perfectly happy being married to women.

Some women may not have minded it, either.

Our modern need to de-mystify human relations left us more confused than ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Im thinking about buying this one brand that used to work for me. But now I’m wondering, if it worked so well, why I got rid of my old suits from that brand. :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Frankly, if you want to be annoyed as a northeasterner, you should spend time in Northern California or Seattle.

Books have been written about the culture clash.

I’ve lived it. It’s real.

By comparison, Hawaii is more like NY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, and I cannot stress this enough…

Just as some people are addicted to Covid hysteria, other people are addicted to being outraged by Covid hysteria.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Haaaaa. No. I like my guys the opposite of how I like my jeans; skinny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hooray for fascism!

Put them in camps, next.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s weird living in a state that is as family oriented as Hawaii.

It must be hard living in California or New York where the government is expected to act as mommy and daddy to hordes of children and young people whose parents are MIA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tyranny has taken on a life of its own.

We know now that the vaccine doesn’t stop covid. The CDC has admitted it, Fauci admits it, vaccine makers admit it.

So why are we still doing this? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Become too Yin.

It’s become too soft and flexible. It’s become too safety seeking.

Bicycle helmets and car seats are yin, and you find as many enthusiasts of those among men as among women.

Literally no one believes Rachel Levine is a woman, but we all are supposed to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As someone who grew up in a less-than-optimal parental situation…the issue I have as an adult is not that my parents parentified or emotionally neglected me as a child.

My issue is when they belittle or infantilize me NOW.

Believe it or not—kids do get over things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when we didn’t care what people like this said or thought? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ive seen this and it was utterly ridiculous. I was born in 1973, and literally at no time in my life did I feel like there was anything I couldn’t do because I was a woman.

If anything, people UNDERsold the natural limitations of being a uterus-haver. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Also—and this is big thing—it feels like for middle class &amp; above kids, the line between gay/lesbian and “trans” is getting very murky.

It’s rare to see a gay/lesbian kid under 22 who doesn’t see themselves as gender non-conforming to a degree they consider undoing their sex.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parent is explaining to me how things in the US havent changed since the Civil War and how there are all these white people who think black people are inferior and who resent anyone not white being in the country.nnThis is what people who watch CNN truly believe now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Those would do right up my buttcrack. I need my granny panties.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social media gave marketing and PR people the ability to interfere with human word-of-mouth by creating false accounts and fake news stories.

I don’t think we’ve realized yet how badly this has affected society.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FWIW, moral relativism has seeped into all corners of our society. Not just “the left,” as people believe.

A culture without a sense of right and wrong is one doomed to fail.

We are doomed to fail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We fought about my whole life.

As a scientifically minded person, I have always believed there is such a thing as “reality.”

My father, a corporate lawyer, believes there is no such thing as “reality.” It’s all a matter of argument.

It took me 49 years to see his point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh it’s long past being stoppable. I’m just wondering if the scratchy throat I have is due to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And yeah, I guess it’s because they are overworked, but it’s also because they are more used to their normal life.

My husband and usually own vacation rentals, so we are well acquainted with how miserable a lot of people are on vacation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, black Jew apparently means someone who is neither black nor Jewish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My feeling is that “Christians” is a very broad brush. I’m not a fan of the Youth Group Christians around here because they’re mostly a mean-girl clique. But It’s not like I know All Christians Everywhere.nn(We also have a ton of Jehovahs Witnesses, LDS and …some other group.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course, the idea that allowing oneself to be hurt in a relationship just to show how much you care is juvenile and sad.

BUT—people who have acted a doormat in the past actually make good marriage material. 

They won’t walk over something small.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# These guys don’t understand women, so they don’t get that women are perfectly happy not to have sex with anyone if there are no attractive partners around.

Them wanting women to be virgins is just sour grapes.

Like me hating women who are better than me at sports]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The funny thing is 20 years ago, I found out one of my brothers thought our upbringing had been abusive. I was like, “Nahhh.”

Amusingly, he was kid who was treated best. Though…maybe he related most to my dad, who got the worst of it?

“I’m not mad at you. I’m mad at the dirt!”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cosseted millennials were upright youths, but went hog wild starting in the late 2000z. (Saw this w our 30is friends)nnNow … I don’t know. Zoomers are scared of everything nnNot sec, per say, but they are obsessed with STABILITY.nnWe will see what they do…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This sounds like a good book, but respectfully, I am more than aware how far up sh*ts creek we are without a paddle…and am utterly unable to do jack sh*t about it.

What am I supposed to do, go to DC and set myself on fire in front of the White House??? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The amazing trick is how they mirror you, especially early on. “I’m from New York.” “I lived in New York!” “I like to snowboard.” “Me too!” “I have a dog.” “I have the same kind of dog.”

All while making TONS of eye contact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here’s a pickle:

On one hand, a crazy hottie does well to date someone whose family is equally or + crazy, because said man doesnt mind crazy.

BUT if they have kids, said kids may be super crazy.

So maybe its best for a crazy chick to marry the most sane guy who will have her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traffic heading into town is so bad due to all the freaking tourists that I am tempted to turn around and go home…and try again after January 10th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Exactly. The behavior is “crazy” and like with most crazy behavior, you want to slowly back away. Not engage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# My vet (who I hate but I don’t want to have to drive further to a different vet) believes it has the right to “require” full courses of vaccines. They even insisted on giving my Frenchton an extra one, since she got her first shot “too early.”

Ugh. I should really switch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I finally had a good day. Didn’t cry once.

Progress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A woman in my professional circle years ago was transitioning. I thought this was unfair to her husband. (Can’t recall if she had kids or not.)

But if a guy marries you as a female, I think it’s kind of abusive to pull a bait and switch like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don’t see any way he would be able to support her in the manner to which she has become accustomed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who say #HASHTAG# is about “dumb republicans”, are playing into the exact stupidity the movie makes fun of.

Culture war frivolity. 

The truth is, no one in charge has a shred of integrity. Jonah Hill could have been Hunter Biden. Meryl Streep” Trump or AOC?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, I never thought it was a great idea for Trump to run again, but his behavior around the vaccines is beyond the pale.

He’s not a God and he’s not the devil. He’s just a reality TV star who became president people people hated Hillary Clinton. He did an okay job at the time. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don’t know how old he is, but he may be 30, which would make him 11 years older.

I’m a big fan of “half plus seven.”
(Frankly, most adult men I see don’t want to date anyone under 21. Which I support.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotten out of a relationship with his neighbor…a single mom who although very pretty, he had always felt that he was far superior to intellectually.

Despite having been unwilling to commit to this woman in any way, he was utterly enraged when she found a new boyfriend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It’s the flip side of when the Boston marathon bombers were called “dark skinned” because they weee Muslim. When to my eye, they looked like a couple of white guys.nn(Fwiw I grew up in NY)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Importantly, ABC stores do NOT require any sort of pass. (Neither do shops). So you can buy food and whatever at the ABC store no problem. Which is easier a lot of the time than sitting down at a retmstaurabt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Whoever holds the power acts like a tyrant. If you want to know how politics works, watching the behavior of middle schoolers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Branch Covidians are fine with this. They are fine with masking forever.

They believe they are more “clean” than those who live in the unwashed hinterlands of flyover country.

If they could wear little crowns to show their superiority, they would. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting point from Edward Dutton: one reason Narcissists/Sociopaths/Borderlines &amp; other fast life-history strategists create chaos is because that is world in which they thrive.

Why Terrorism is Going to Get Worse; Much, Much Worse . . . #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But bottom line is I know more about brainwashing and cult stuff than most people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I say *most women* dont go home w strangers from bars, what I mean is “women u would want raising your children.”

Are you looking for a woman with a decent education who eats right, knows how to cook &amp; who has no relatives in jail?

She’s probably not sleeping w strangers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right?? So tiresome.

I’ve mentioned how ridiculous it was to me that Hawaii, which at time time wasn’t letting anyone come and go due to Covid, had BLM rallies.

The is No. Black. Underclass. In hawaii. None. Black ppl make good money in Hawaii and were never here as slaves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s a fantasy.

They know those men do not exist in real life.

The problem w the m#USER# obsession with ephebophilia is that it further tarnishes the idea of marriage and the conservative project in general. 

No, it is not “trad.” 

It. Is. A. Sex. Fantasy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a family member who makes movies and now that I think of it, I haven’t seen a single movie or tv they have worked on since a short horror bit they did as a project in film school. 

Oh—and one other.

But they must have been part of 30+ productions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I say this as someone who had a lot of great, awesome, non-related men in my life as a little girl.

But none of them invited me to their home, or in any way led me to believe we had any sort of relationship as “equals.”

That shit is effed up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As someone who does not believe in waxing myself to the point of looking like a newborn…I also hate “cheeky” bathing suits.

I surf, and the break I go to has a cliff above it, where old dudes hang out fishing.

I dont like having to worry about what of mine is hanging out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16yo ranted about the BS she’s taught in Social Studies.

I said, “The problem is history needs to be told from a POV. But today, they try to tell it from everyone and no one’s point of view.”

She said, “They tell it from the point of view of the UN.”

#HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way to understand time in Hawaii is to imagine “official” time is Japanese, but regular time is Polynesian. 

Where tourists get tripped up is knowing the difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# There are always people who manage to find nice dogs at the shelter. But even Cesar Milan said that most dogs who are easygoing, trained and housebroken do not end up at the shelter.

I can see this. I’d have no trouble rehoming any of my dogs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MOTHERFUCKER SOMETHING ATE ALL MY FUCKING CHICKS!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah my run in was nowhere near what a lot of people go through, but it was still extremely disturbing. I’d always thought I was the type of person who couldn’t be hypnotized. I was wrong.z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I’m not saying an adult man SHOULD want to date my kid.

But her ex was 22. I could see her dating up to 24 or 24 and it not being too weird.

But truth was…Broody was always kind of immature.

Real grown ups want to date other grown ups.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s simply a fact.

It’s no surprise that it’s people in rich parts of the country continuing to push this covid nonesense and expecting the rest of us to be jabbed and masked like cattle.

They believe they deserve to never have inconvenience or pain.

as I’ve said, I grew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious. My mom who believes I’m obstinate for not getting vaxxed is currently refusing to read a book for her book club because she is boycotting Amazon.

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The thing is: there is no reason for them not to be having sex.

There are fewer social sanctions than ever. Birth control is more available than ever. The AIDS crisis is over.

What we are looking at is an actual waning of biological urges. 

They can’t be bothered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I should encourage husband to do something similar. His dad is a swim coach.

As for me, I need to come up w new outlets, too. 

Lest I cross the line into becoming an animal hoarder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I always say that the medicine of today will seem barbaric in 100 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s amazing to think that within my lifetime, Paisley was once a thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Older Kid’s bestie is gay, and besides having the standard case of 20-yo gay boy manorexia, he basically dressed in drag. The little lesbian she used to work with wore a chest binder and went by a male name.

Experimentation? Perhaps. But…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This girl is speaking the 100% TRUTH.

This pandemic has ruined a generation. My high schooler feels her future has been stolen. Exams cancelled, programs postponed…

It’s criminal. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# To begin with, they are richer and more successful than us. My husband doesn’t mind this, as he’s usually friends with his wealthy clients. But I find it intimidating. 

She’s also a half foot taller than me, and better at sports.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s all part of a weird cultural moment when men are very angry at women and want to inhabit the identity of those they are jealous of .

Same reason we have such viciousness from the trans activist crowd.

Love ME.
Look at ME.

Tell me I’m pretty!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back in Seattle, people adooooooored fucking with anyone, especially New Yorkers, who were in a hurry.

In the Pacific Northwest, being in a hurry was seen as itself rude.

So any time you were in a hurry, people would do anything they could to trip you up and slow you down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian aborigines defending themselves with bow and arrow against those who would vaccinate them.nnThe rest of Australia could learn a thing or two from these men. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# This is not even a little true, nor even should it be.

The easiest time to train a dog is when it’s a puppy. Adult dogs that get given up for adoption OFTEN have behavioral problems. Like—it’s probably more often than not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well one has to realize peer approval really does matter. Teens learn a lot from those their age and slightly older. These are the people they will spend the rest of their lives living and competing with. 

I’ve also noticed kids often say they believe one thing &amp; do another.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People with anorexia are 20 times more likely than the general population to die from suicide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m hearing Australians argue Australia ishuge,  and as an America, cannot understand issues with aborigines.nnAlaska is pretty f*cking huge, 7 no one is dragging their native inhabitants out of homes “for their own protection.”nnProbably because everyone in Alaska owns  a  gun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And you get these young people *furious* that the world isn’t built exactly to their specifications, and they aren’t being represented exactly the way they like in exactly the proportions they like in media.

It’s ridiculous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again on Merrill Lynch guy.

I have 2 kids.

You think nobody has ever done sometimes accidentally that was a danger to my kids?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Older Kid is supposed to stay at our place tonight, and Broody has gotten a sum total of “Absolutely Nothing” out of their studio.

Not a damn thing. His shoes are still in front of the door.

I can’t blame him. I wouldn’t be surprised if she changes her mind, either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My age-related risk of dying of covid, should I catch it, being unvaccinated, is the same as my risk of drowning.

Just went surfing yesterday. In water where I know there could be sharks.

Why, oh why would I be scared of Covid?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They’re a cross between a really amazing wild-type quail-cock I have and the mostly-white females he shares a coop with. It’s my favorite pattern so far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Interesting. I know it’s very socialist there. My friend from Ireland is a super lefty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The annoying thing is I’m convinced most people really want is a shih tzu. Small, not too much energy, short legs. Just wants to be petted.

But they think “small dogs bite” &amp; they don’t know how to potty train small dog.

So they get a lab &amp; wonder why it has “too much energy.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My words are not some powerful spell that makes things happen.

I’m just telling you my prediction. Not my recommendation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe I’m just really congested, and that’s what’s making me dizzy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pain is always balanced by purpose .

People will endure a fair amount of pain to achieve a goal they care about.

But when life has no purpose, everything hurts. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think we are getting close to some nationwide walk outs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my exact point with trying to make “ethical” decisions in the time of vaccine mandates.

If I cancel my citi card, I’d use my Visa. Which is through B of A, which caved entirely and donated a ton of money to BLM.

ALL the big banks have a hand in making our lives shit. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verdict: I skipped it. Realized I have headphones in my purse and never use them. They just sit there in my purse until the dogs dig them out and eat them.

Getting a new Fitbit instead. :) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People#USER# obsessed in the 90s with teen pregnancy and teen sex (because now sex was dangerous) and teen sex became a sign of…Almost criminality,nnSomething poor people did.nnSo millennials waiting until their 20s to be sluts.nnThe drinking age may have also had impact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I struggle to be overly nice to anyone as I’m doing what I can to keep myself upbeat and functional.

Younger Kid has gotten sucked into Older Kid’s emotional universe, mainly because Older Kid’s force field is so huge &amp; intense right now.

The whole balance of the household]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# What’s interesting to me is the divide between local, working class gay kids &amp; middle class and up gay white kids.

Hawaii has a long history of being accepting of mahu/butchie. They are part of the community.

Haole kids express queerness in a totally different way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids like mine who were born circa 2000 aren’t exactly running the show now. (That;s on Millennials) but they aren’t rebelling against anything, either.nnWhy would they?nnTheir parents (aka us) never gave them anything to rebel against.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The media, and animal rights people, act like anyone who keeps animals outdoors is a terrible, despicable person....even though basically ALL non-whites do this.nnSo, who is the “Nazi” here?nnSame thing with spanking kids. And living in multi-generational homes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I shouldn’t poke fun, as I was anorexic and know the long term damage. But maybe that’s why it bothers me so much.

I literally bring this kid food at his work sometimes. His vertebrae stick out when he bends over. :(

(Ugh. Being young sucks, doesn’t it?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The worst part is that thongs never left. They just got hidden under ultra high rise jeans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to stop talking about “Don’t Look Up” before somebody tells me they didn’t understand that the title was about not looking “up” at the people at the top of society, lest we see how corrupt and mentally ill the whole system is.

…and then I will have to shoot myself. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having grown up in a situation where I was often terrorized by rage, I have made some observations about it.

1. Rage is a sin.
2. People who display rage do so because they feel entitled to hurt others.
3. People only display rage if they can get away with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad day. First I get intimidated by a fat lady in an N95, and then a fat man gets on my case for having my small dogs off-leash on a dirt footpath where not another soul was walking.

I hate this world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh for sure. Absolutely. But I also think young people will claim to believe whatever is fashionable. And it’s not like I think anyone is going to hell for casual sex. I just dont think its a good idea.

Some people have to make a mistake or two. I know I did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is indeed disgusting.

using this for political gain and to make money for big pharma is sick. Just sick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So long as you not only were “local,” but also stayed local, folks didnt much care what you did.

No one ever wore masks outside here on the outer island where i live, though we never dropped our indoor mask mandate. And people were already throwing “ragers” last winter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I’ve decided I don’t like muting, because then I can’t see when people retweet me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry i keep circling back, but this man said not only do they test for covid before going to Red States, but they avoid eating * drinking in public in Red States.

Can you imagine? 

How much disdain for a place can you have? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s the corollary to “70% of the people who have ever been alive are alive today” and “half the money in circulation in America right now was printed in the last 2 years.” #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don’t think of either one of them as “more attractive”, but it’s more that I notice boys/men respond differently.

Men are very attracted to the “wounded dove” type girl. It’s kind of insane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I’ve started to realize why this one guy I knew, who seemed totally flaming, married a woman. 

He confided in me that he’d slept w hundreds of guys. But only 2 women. They were choosing to adopt. (Make of that what you will.) and he often seemed to get cruised. 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is that a corgi?nnYeah, I dont know that any dog on the planet gets as much time and stimulation as it would like. But I certainly wish that more people who just wanted lap dogs would just get lap dogs. nnI feel like crappy dog owners in the 1950s turned everyone off small breeds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right now, with family life sucking as badly as it does, I’m really sad how many friends have been lost and relationships broken over the past 5 years.

Wokism, Trump backlash and finally Covid.

I have one close friend, my brother and my husband. That’s it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun fact: when I was in college in the early 90s, we considered the generation of people who came before us in the early 80s to have been total whores.

People who imagine there was a straight line between “the pill” and today fail to realize sexual trends wax and wane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# For a long time, Australia categorized the aborigines as “fauna.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is absolutely ridiculous how much Broody loves Older Kid. His eyes light up when he finds out she’s nearby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hawaiian democrats are basically the same as California republicans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’d also like to say for the record that it is possible that Covid really does affect non-whites worse than it does white people.

This may not even have to do with socioeconomic factors. Black people are way more likely to be diabetic, for example. 

In other words, I dont know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The type of man who thinks grown men should date “barely legal” girls ages 16-22 overlaps with the kind of guy who thinks “Eastern European and Southeast Asian women know better how to choose a man.”nnThey want to use their age or money as a lever of power to get a woman they]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Older Kid was waxing my eyebrows for me, so she decided to practice her “customer service” banter.

“Are you enjoying your time on the island?”

So I said, “Yes, but I can’t find anywhere to convert my dollars into Hawaiian money.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah, I was thinking that when I wrote it. I meant it to be a shorthand for “gay and lesbian” as it has a shorter character count. But I do get it.

The thing is that mahu and butchie don’t quite overlap w gay/lesbian. So…I struggled w phrasing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ve seen it with gay people, fat people, people of various minorities…early representation of these groups is often insulting in retrospect. However, even insulting representation IS representation,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make pedophiles fear vigilante justice again. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The movie Idiocracy foretold President-as-tough-guy-action-hero way before Trump was ever in office.

In fact, if someone didn’t know the year Idiocracy was made, they’d think Comancho was based on Trump.
 
Even Back to the Future mocked the trend.

A stupider and]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covid hysteria, unlike CRT, is not baked into our institutions. It came out of nowhere, and will likely disappear as fast as it arrived.

I never got covid, but I was like patient zero when it came to covid fear. I just got over it fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She should be upset. It doesnt make any sense. 

And now the school counselor is going to get involved, and it’s the counselor’s job to console and care for this girl WHILE ALSO making sure nobody admits that the emperor is wearing no clothes.

Therapy with a side of delusion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# God I hope so. I’m not hopeful for some reason though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is especially true as there is no such thing as a “true identity.”

People are many things to many people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While I’m talking about men…

The WORST way to find a girlfriend is to “approach” women.

If you are walking up to women you don’t know &amp; attempting to build a romantic connection, you’re gonna fail 99.9% of the time. 

Meeting women is like business. It’s all networking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is a Duke able to do whatever the f*ck he wants, and the poeple be damned?

because that’s what this is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That’s only online. If you were a straight guy and motivated, you would have figured out that kind of stuff when you were younger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we need in this country is small tweaks. What we REALLY need in this country is for people in the media and in government to stop making these insane, absolutist, histrionic statements.

Nobody wants an all or nothing country. We all want choices. What we disagree on is the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They aren’t victims. They are damaged. And if you are seduced into their world, they will damage you, too.

I’m just sayin’.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Haha. I don’t know. I had to make several of the same mistakes more than once.

But I do think past behavior is the best predictor of future behavior.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lack of employees kept employers on my island from forcing everyone to get vaxxed or lose their jobs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women is to know women and to like women.

Hating women is NOT the way to get women.

Being jealous of, angry at, resentful of women WILL NOT GET YOU LAID. Certainly not in the long run.

Being friends with women will at least give you the tools to…not seem like a tool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I dont mean to make it sound like she’s borderline or anything. But… 

This was a pill I found hard to swallow. And I learned it the hard way in my 20s.

My husband’s mom is a pain in the ass, which is the only reason he puts up with me. LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ve had a lot of mental health problems in my life, but I’ve also been very lucky.

I know a woman very similar to me who is less privileged. She’s had 7 kids by 3 different men, had kids taken away by CPS, is obese and will likely die early.

My circumstances buffer my crazy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We need more centering, calm, containing Male energy. But the psychopaths in charge like the destruction.

One doesnt see as much out of control powerful women in Hawaii (Maisie Hirono notwithstanding) as one does in mainland college towns and big cites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That, too. Sometimes it feels like us and our unvaxxed friends are the only people around who DONT have covid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Listen, when the story is told, we are gonna call it “Nortans.”

That’s how it’s gonna go in Hawaii. It will be a cute variation of a tale told on many continents. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Frankly, I think the big problem is our modern reluctance to humanely put dogs down.

The original point of the shelter was to give people an opportunity to find their lost dogs. It was never meant to be a pet store for defective pets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And yes, precautions up the wazoo.

And yes, young people today dont know. They are totally cavalier. It seems so strange. I was convinced in my mid 20s that the next guy I slept with would absolutely give me herpes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Similar to me, she went from being a very smart kid to a little adult without ever going through the overtly giggly, Tiger Beat, boy band loving phase. 

My older kid did a bit of that with her bestie. Husband even took her to One Direction. I was happy for her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a big fan of enjoying art for art’s sake and not troubling myself with the morals of the artist.

But how people can worship Michael Jackson (the man, not the music) while showing video/pictures of him accompanied by little boys…boggles my mind.

That sh*t was in public.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lol. Yeah, I dont think I’ve ever been to a town so small it didnt have any non-white people. (Except in Europe, when I was a kid.)nnI think the only people who dont want integration are people trying to gain clout on twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting exercise:nnIf people 10 years older than me were peak slutty, in what year were they peak goody-two shoes?nnMillenials I know all seem to have been goody two shoes in HS, &amp; saved the sluttiness for post-college, even into late 20s. (When people my age were married.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If I could find a t shirt in orange, it would be perfect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young people dont understand that in the 1970s, there were no gay people on TV. There were shows like Bosom Buddies &amp; Three’s Company, that at least mentioned the existence of gays…(a step forward from the 50s/60s.)nnBut it’s amazing that by the 90s, there was Will and Grace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most kids in elementary school still having “wee-wees” and “hoo-hoos.”

By 4th grade, its appropriate to teach about puberty, as some kids will be going through it.

But…ugh. What a mess.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>