<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[...but that's less than half the story...the reason why the vast majority of those 175 Municipalities are "in financial distress" is because the #USER# Mayor and/or his councilors and/or their crooked cronies have brazenly stolen all of the municipal finances. #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...what a joke...it would be funny if it wasn't so tragic...but some ANC-connected,  tuktuk-peddling tenderpreneur is laughing all the way to the bank...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and we love it the most when that big hole is in the road... #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...neither...new Minister...even better: new Government... #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...I'd be sorry to see Alderweireld leave...he's a very solid and experienced center back, the best we have, his positional play and anticipation are outstanding, he rarely makes mistakes and he's a true professional...younger players can learn a lot from him... #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What ABSOLUTE RUBBISH! I'd love to read your analysis because, from my perspective, SA will not survive UNLESS #USER# is voted out of power. So, please, bring it on, bro, give it your best shot! #HASHTAG#!
#HASHTAG#! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# ...meanwhile Juju drinks tea with Msholozi at Nkandla and everyone is like... #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arsenal have offered him a 5-year contract... 😂🤣😂🤣😂 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What an awful situation! I hope somebody is investigating how/why so many Spurs players and staff received false negative COVID test results, then positives. If it gets much worse - and AC sounds as though he thinks it might - #HASHTAG# might not be able to field a team... #HASHTAG#!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...who would blame Zelensky if he told Russia "get out of Ukraine, then we can talk." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Jessica, electricity in Sandown is supplied by #USER# not by #USER#. If you check City Power's Twitter timeline you will see mention of all the power outages in their area they are aware of and are working on. They usually refuse to say when power will be restored.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is this update actually working or is it blocked by Indigo addon like all previous versions of The Crew?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...serves them right for placing their trust is #HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Royal Mint makes 4,000 medical visors per day to help protect NHS staff from COVID-19. Its engineers developed a successful prototype in 48 hours and the first visors are already in use. It's now received requests to supply hospitals across the UK. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...now where have I heard that before..?
Oh, yes...form Cyril himself...multiple times...
#URL#
#HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...like #USER# works with #USER# in Cape Town and the Western Cape]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...anyway, it seems to me it's you who's actually scoffing at other people's beliefs...in your own words: "Fuck it people can't you see what's going on already. This is not about a virus!!!!!!!!!!" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...here's hoping all those police vans come back later loaded to the rooves with red-shirted idiots... #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On this web page #URL# you will see a link to #USER#'s vaccine certificate webpage. It takes you to a blank page; nothing loads. A few weeks ago there was also an email address for queries. I asked twice and they said they're "working on it". #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...Malooti "Handy Man" Gigupta...one of the ANC's smartest and finest... #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...how NOT to win friends and influence people...being Msholozi's nyatsi won't help her now... #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...looks very much like a German 88mm flak/anti-tank gun to me... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...African solutions for African problems... #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW! Well done, Labour Minister Thulas "Firepool" Nxesi! That will surely stop #USER# and his obnoxious #USER# pals! #HASHTAG#! If it's THAT illegal, why not arrest them and charge them right now? #HASHTAG#! #HASHTAG#! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...yes, Ace and Ace alone...it was only used because Ace is Cyril's political opponent, it seems...now Ace is effectively dead in the water, and Zuma has shot himself in the foot, Cyril may be tempted to shelve "step aside"...that would be a big mistake...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...can't imagine why anyone in the US would even contemplate defunding their police forces... #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...I feel safer already... #HASHTAG#! #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...the genie is well and truly out of the bottle now...the rioters and looters have realised that this useless ANC Govt and its pathetic "Security Forces" have no ability to stop them, and no clue how to stop them, so the entire country is going up in flames... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...true, sadly...a very small minority of the worst of the worst ANC scumbags have vanished without trace...Malooter "Handy Man" Gigupta and Dina "Red Shoes" Pule, for example...but the rest float to the top like turds in a gozunder... #HASHTAG# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More to the point, they're ongoing as we speak, and this useless #USER# #USER# has made far too little effort to either prevent it from happening now and in future or to catch and punish the perps...many of whom are Cabinet Ministers, their families, friends and cronies... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...but don't worry...Mr. Fix #USER# will sort everything out in no time... #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...just as I thought...you actually don't understand what you're distributing...not the content, and certainly not its implications. High time you got off Twitter and got yourself something remotely resembling an education. #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...ironic that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...a bit like the conspiracy theories...currently]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Answer: Hillary's emails. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent! I didn't realise this matter had gone to trial. I REALLY hope Shivambu is convicted, jailed and thrown out of Parliament as a consequence. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chair of Govt's MAC, Prof Salim Karrim, says current increase in cases (~330/day) not yet cause for concern but Dr Harry Moultrie, an epidemiologist at NICD, says parts of SA's healthcare system will be overwhelmed by rapid increase in COVID-19 infections: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ivermectin is a cheap anti-parasitic drug that has been widely used to treat #HASHTAG# in poor countries, particularly in S America. This paper on a controlled clinical trial in Bangladesh reports some success in reducing the recovery time after infection. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I very clearly remember a dingy basement in Joburg CBD where Look &amp; Listen resided - long before it moved to Hillbrow - and all the very best and latest vinyl LPs could be found, usually as expensive, high quality overseas pressings. That place was truly heaven on earth. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More proof, if more is needed, that there are two Justice systems in SA; one for ordinary citizens like you and me, and another for useless, lying, looting, cruel, heartless ANC cadres like Thandi "Piggy" Modise... #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and you trust Sexwale to tell the truth, the whole truth, and nothing but the truth..? Hint: ask his ex wife... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...along with Bathababalas Dlamini, Carl "Bootlicker" Niehaus, Malusi "Handyman" Gigaba, Tina "Hotlips" Jomat Pettersson and Tony "WaBenzi" Yengeni, a founding members of the Saxonwold Shebeen... #HASHTAG#! #HASHTAG#!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...yet another big win for #USER# and their Tripatite Alliance partners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[..."reroute the fiscal input"...is that the new term for "affirmative budget allocation"..? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Assuming Harry Kane's head is back on again: 
To start: Left Son - Centre Kane - Moura Right.
Substitutes, if necessary: Gil for Son, Scarlett for Kane, Bergwijn for Moura.
If HK's head is still MIA, rather start with Scarlett in the centre. Give the lad a chance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...so you'd expect this "mighty EFF propaganda machine" would have been working overtime during lockdown...after all, SAns have had lazy day after lazy day to digest "pearls of #USER# wisdom"...but instead they've "treated" us to #USER# 's idiotic book club...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not only does Ivermectin have no effect whatsoever when taken to combat #HASHTAG# the very best anyone can hope for is that they don't get very ill or, heaven forbid, die from the side-effects. You know this. Why do you persist in spreading lies? #HASHTAG#!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really hope the ANC gets its arse kicked on this one. They f#$ked up big-time, and then they were prepared to sacrifice the IEC's credibility as an independent institution to save their bacon. With any luck they'll lose the case with costs, but the damage will have been done. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...the ANC and the current (abysmal) situation SA finds itself in are another story altogether...many SAns believed in Nelson Mandela and his promises of a better SA...sadly, after him, the ANC's promises and "leadership" have been exposed as the lies and frauds they are...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...good heavens! ...they might get a job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# IMO no, not for #HASHTAG# as it is now...he's a top player but Lingard is not a playmaker or a dead-ball specialist, or a central midfield controller - all of which we need badly. He would look to slot into the positions Lucas, Gil, Dele, Bergwijn, Lo Celso and Son occupy now. So no.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...it's as much a uniform as what Cyril Ramaphosa was wearing. #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...now you're beginning to understand why #USER# has no intention to properly educate the hoi polloi...only ANC cadres can be allowed to become prosperous... #HASHTAG#! #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...the top-of-the-range Cepheid GeneXpert model can do 16 samples at a time...I very much doubt if SA has 180 top-of-the-range models...their bog standard model does 1 sample at a time...my money's on 180 bog standard models.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# IMF Makes Available $50 Billion to Help Address Coronavirus "...we have about $1 trillion in overall lending capacity....we have rapid-disbursing emergency financing of up to $10 billion that can be accessed without a full-fledged IMF program." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, it wasn't...it was merely the first in a series of global pandemics that infectious disease experts, and many others, have been predicting for years...and which we now know the world was woefully unprepared for. Thank heavens for well-informed philanthropists like Bill Gates! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's right! Dier was an absolute rock yesterday against WHU, as he has been all season. Why he wasn't called up to play for England is beyond me. If he doesn't go to World Cup Qatar 2022 in November it will be an absolute travesty. #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why on earth do we want/need Mashaba to be Mayor of Jhb? He WAS Mayor of Jhb, and he just walked out on all those who voted for him - and in the process handed Jhb back to the #USER# looters - just because his BFF Mmusi got fired. Mashaba can't be trusted. Period. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why does lockdown need such heavy policing anyway? The observation of lockdown has to be based on people trusting Govt and understanding the reasons why its necessary, not on fear and violence. Irrational regulations, like this one, simply destroy trust and defy reason. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...yet another former adviser to Don The Con heading to jail. Dang! it's just getting so hard to "Make America Great Again"... #HASHTAG# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...so Thulas "Firepool" Nxesi expects us to hail him as a hero for recovering some of these wrongful payments, instead of condemning him as, at best, lazy, stupid and incompetent,  for allowing the wrongful payments in the first place! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's be clear: Eskom loadshedding is just a symptom; #USER# is the disease. #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...I can't wait... #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emerson Royal did well. Zaha is a nightmare to mark... aggressive, physical, combative and continually pushes up against the limits of what is permissible under the rules of the game. IMO, he's a menace and referees must wise up. Talk about being thrown in the deep end on debut! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...Squirrel will call another family meeting... #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NO!!!! REALLY??? ...whoever would have guessed..? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...that and the Patience of Job Award...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...more than 100,000 tests have been conducted SINCE THE FIRST CASE WAS CONFIRMED, and most of those tests were done on either health workers, hospital patients or people with #HASHTAG# symptoms...meaning the rate of infection in most SA communities is a complete unknown...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...true...but this legislation isn't about Govt expropriating land so networks can build towers on it...it's proposing that the networks can access, and build towers on, any land they want, anywhere, without consulting the land's owner, or negotiating compensation! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's #USER# slowly - far too slowly - imposing his "leadership" on the ANC...which necessarily requires that he exorcise the tokoloshes of Jacob "Gupta" Zuma and all his cronies - like Ace "Milkman" Magashule - who still thirst for the Zuma-era corruption feeding-frenzy. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After reading this thread it's crystal clear why Republicans in Congress are so against a Congressional Inquiry into events at the Capitol on 6th January. #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Total waste of taxpayers' money. Shameful! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# More sorry than they are about electing Trump? Not a chance! NOBODY can EVER come CLOSE to the disastrous failure and embarrassment of 4 years of Donald Trump. The sooner they impeach Trump again, and throw him out of the White House, the better. For democracy worldwide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...new drivers' license card machine...different drivers license cards...anyone else see another monumental SNAFU loading..? ...after all, this was all arranged by Fokole "Loser" Mbalula, #USER#'s King of Fuck-ups... #HASHTAG#! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Who remembers this bloke? Richard Hoyle, Joburg's very own millionaire traffic cop? When he wasn't on the official motorbike he loved to ride he could usually be seen directing traffic at his regular spot on Empire Road. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...you had better make sure you select your candidates for this largesse with great care...farming is not easy; in addition to finances it requires knowledge, training, dedication, perseverance, patience, multi-skilling, lots and lots of hard work and a measure of good fortune. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least 144 died in 2016 at the hands of this useless #USER# #USER# and #USER# Provincial Government...but nobody has been held accountable despite criminal charges laid and a Judicial Inquiry still ongoing...and 60 patients are still unaccounted for... #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly! Zuma NEVER COULD BE trusted. #HASHTAG#! ...oh, wait...we already did...so #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#! #HASHTAG# ...everything this useless ANC Govt does turns to shit. Guaranteed. And #USER# is SHOCKED! #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.#USER# is a corrupt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...in Zululand..? ...good luck with that! ...misogyny is alive and well and thriving in KZN thanks to King Zweli, Jacob Zuma and ~10m other Zulus... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Measure the size of the opening - width x height. Note anything down the height of the opening that the blinds might catch on as they drop, like tiling or skirting.  Measure the depth of the opening so you know the maximum width of blind slat to help you choose the type you want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...but Squirrel PROMISED there would be no corruption associated with the #HASHTAG# vaccines...and we always believe him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...which says lots about the relentless progress of technology - from credit cards and PayPal to digital currencies and online trading - and almost nothing about either GDP or notes and coins. Why is this "Chart of the Week"? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hehehehehehehe!!! It's a dog when you're on the wrong side of the science, isn't it? #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...actually, I'm glad he saw the light. He had absolutely zero to gain from refusing to take the knee, and an awful lot to lose. There would have been far less embarrassment and argy-bargy attached if he'd just realised this in the first instance, like everyone else did. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...and because Cupcake didn't make one wrong move during the Zuma era]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...anyone else out there wish that SAn employers could just make like American employers and, when the situation warrants it, just say "You're fired! Get your sorry ass out of here!"? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Misinformation. Please check your facts BEFORE you  pass them on to other people! #URL#
#HASHTAG#! #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...so the ANC is heading for a split along tribal lines...they're not interested in "personality", "ideology", "right/wrong" or "corrupt/honest"...just "tribe"...which is not much different to "race"...what a surprise... #HASHTAG# ...#HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...WELL DONE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...that's what happens when you appoint an arrogant nincompoop as Police Minister...he struts around threatening tourists sitting peacefully on Cape Town beaches...and sits on his hands while rioters and looters empty and burn KZN malls and warehouses... #HASHTAG# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A BIG THANK YOU to SAPS, SANDF, JMPD, #USER# and #USER# for making a start at tackling this huge problem, at last. Please continue to break down and remove illegal electricity connections and prosecute offenders until people learn to pay their fair share. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, Pfizer #HASHTAG# vaccine second dose done and dusted courtesy of #USER# at 1 Discovery Place in Sandton...the admin process was much more efficient this time but crowd management was a bit like a cattle drive...anyway, no complications or side-effects whatsoever. #HASHTAG#!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...but Deputy President David Mabuza is flying to Russia to "seek treatment". #HASHTAG#? #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# OK. So firstly, why do you call the Covid-19 vaccines  "experimental"..? ...each one is different...and almost 4 billion - yes, billion - doses of the various vaccines have been administered wordwide...what would it take for you to consider the vaccines "tried and tested"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesse "The Poison Dwarf" Duarte proving, once again, that all those geriatric Loothuli House bigknobs are just overpaid hot air generators. Spewing out the same old same old horseshit. She knows that we know she knows: #USER# is up Shit Creek without a paddle! #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...reminds me of the SAPS crime stats...sketchy and incomplete, just thrown out there without any explanation, context or narrative...like "here you go; chew on these. We don't care what you make of them; we've got a lockdown to enforce, citizens to bully..." #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...but #USER# STILL hasn't fired Health Minister Mkhize...or any of the useless Ministers in the "Security Cluster"... #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# 

Question: what does a Minister have to do to get fired from Cyril Ramaphosa's Cabinet..? Anyone? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# "It is known that the National Health Laboratory Service...is not close to reaching its target of 36,000 tests per day."

"We all know, and government acknowledges it, that testing is inadequate and needs to be expanded,"

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About bloody time too! All State Capture beneficiaries should have been arrested, prosecuted and thrown in jail ages ago. Ikky has only survived this long because he has pals at Loothuli House but the SAn business community is at last realising that it's dealing with a crook. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm convinced already. Ivermectin doesn't work AND it can have very serious side effects. On the other hand, approved #HASHTAG# vaccinations can, do and have worked, are NOT causing the variants, and side-effects are much, much less frequent.
#HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...clearly her closes ancestors are pond life... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...clearly #USER# #USER# and his useless #USER# #USER# and #USER# aren't going to lift a finger to prosecute any of the State Capture looters so the message is loud and clear: "Help yourselves, comrades, nothing is stopping you!" #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...could be a bit messy for Chelski fans... #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...so #USER# wants voters to believe that this useless ANC Govt paid ~R430m to school "Deep Cleaning" tenderpreneurs and he wasn't aware of it..? #HASHTAG#! #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...or else what..? ...if Harry Kane really wants to go, let him go. Let's make as much money as we can from the sale, but let him go. He doesn't want the parting to be ugly and neither do the fans. Let's just get it over with and move on. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your President Putin told the Russian army to invade Ukraine with no valid justification, to ignore civilian casualties, and to bomb and shell it into submission. Go and tell him to stop first. #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# ...poor little Fraud Shivambu...the "deformation" of his character must really be getting to him...which explains why he's so bitter and twisted...of course, "defamation" of his character would be impossible because he's such a well-known liar, thief, thug, hypocrite and more...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...has anyone ever estimated just how much the Premier League contributes to Britain's economy, directly and indirectly? It must be very substantial indeed... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, #HASHTAG# and #HASHTAG#! ...never mind the failing service delivery and the broken budget...lets first organise some brand new Mercs and BMWs for #USER#'s new "Executive" Mayor and Mayoral Committee Members... #HASHTAG#! #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pfizer and Modena both saying Americans vaccinated in December or January will likely need a "booster shot" (ie. "re-vaccination") in September or October, which will surely use up more vaccine production capacity and further delay first dose availability in developing countries. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and when she doesn't come up with a good enough excuse,  Squirrel suspends her on full pay for a month, like "Stellar" Stella? What good will that do? #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...no, sorry, I won't give you my contact details. My contact details are private. You don't need my details to address these things with store management.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...but don't worry! This useless #USER# #USER# will fix everything with its grand plan called "National Health Insurance"...the biggest, boldest and most brazen looting scam Africa has ever seen!n#HASHTAG#! #HASHTAG#! #HASHTAG#! #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...racist abuse by a white person... #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help me out, Tweeps. Who - which personalities, organisations or political parties - is behind Operation Dudula..? Where's the money coming from? What's the motivation? Who's renting the crowd, buying the Tshirts and KFC, and who's hiring the busses to move this mob? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...because they're "entitled", of course... #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...SAMWU = SA Municipal Workers Union, folks...these are the "overworked and underpaid" bozos who don't fix the potholes in your roads, take bribes from the izinyakas and water thieves, and throw your garbage all over the streets... #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a surprise! #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...sounds like Don The Con all right.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...maybe, but it won't stop Squirrel et al holding out the begging bowl, and some countries that should know better will toss some small change into it...COP26 and the $8.5b pledged by France, Germany, the UK, the US and the EU to SA to wean itself off coal are a good example... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...#USER# 's nose is growing longer and longer every day... #URL# #HASHTAG#!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...and you'd never guess that the biggest owners and operators of minibus taxis in SA are ANC cadres... #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...but they DID act! ...Auntie Pat built the Beit Bridge Washing Line]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been there...done that...when there was still a stone hut at the top...watched the sunrise...never been so cold in my life, before or after...the Tugela had frozen over...surely one of the most beautiful spots in this beautiful country... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# People who are fully vaccinated are far (&gt;90%) less likely to get infected by #HASHTAG# (that's what vaccines are for!) and therefore are far (&gt;90%) less likely to pass it on to others. Read and learn. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...but #USER# #USER# and his useless #USER# Govt have promised to fight corruption and punish the looters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...political theatre....ANC bigknobs doing their level best to distract public attention away from the disastrous economy, rising unemployment and social unrest, widespread service delivery failures and the ever-growing list of evidence linking the ANC to corruption... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why bother? Say the old looter gets convicted and sentenced to 5 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ....and then there's jazz guitarist Al Di Meola, here with John McLaughlin and Paco De Lucia... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...Ace isn't "chucked out" yet...he's just suspended from Loothuli House...on full pay, of course, while all the rest of the party hoypoloi get at the end of the month is another kick in the teeth...and an invitation to the Sauer Street toyitoyi... #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...so Fokole "Loser" Mbalula gives the taxi industry a ~R1.2b freebee...the same taxi industry that deliberately blocks roads and highways, brings the country to a standstill with strikes, and terrorises the public with lawlessness, unroadworthy vehicles and dangerous driving... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who live near Western Cape beaches will tell you that poachers brazenly operate in daylight and are totally unconcerned about "Law Enforcement" because #USER# #USER# connected cadres are behind the poaching gangs and pay bribes to all and sundry. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# ...I hope you will feel the same way in a month's time...but I wouldn't bet on it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...looks a lot like crumbed slabs of play dough...probably tastes like it too... #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...actually it's not very well hidden. Bill Gates and his former wife Melinda have pledged to give away 90% of their wealth...global healthcare is one area they chose to receive their generosity... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power was restored to Greenstone Hill at ~08:00. But my question was this: WHY was power off in Greenstone Hill from ~21:30 yesterday to ~08:00 today? During that period power was restored twice, only to go off again minutes later. #HASHTAG#? #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...yes, some have said that diet and fitness are an issue...I don't know about that, but I can say that Ndombele's the one #HASHTAG# player (besides HK) whose technical skill makes me grin from ear-to-ear and shake my head in amazement...he's such a talent! And he's ours! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I agree: it should be, but for some players it isn't. And for a few of those, it's worth while going the extra mile. IMO, Ndombele is an unusual talent who could become an exceptional player. He's definitely worth going the extra mile for. I think JM saw that. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and Taxi operators will virtually show #USER# #USER# the middle finger, just like they have everyone else, from customers and police officers to other road users and Govt regulators. Time to crack down on them before they get even more ungovernable! #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...the good news for South Africa's armchair (virtual) activists is you can actually have your cake and eat it...

Join #USER# now and start telling #USER# what you think of their draft regulations and legislation BEFORE they becomes law! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, there is NOT "more than enough proof". In fact there is plenty of evidence, and more coming in every day, that the vast majority of "trials" on Ivermectin have been so poorly conducted that their conclusions are invalid, and that Ivermectin can have very serious side-effects. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...a part of this useless ANC Government that's found to be incompetent and corrupt..? NO! Surely not! It can't possibly be true! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[27 years after the end of apartheid poverty, inequality, homelessness, unemployment and declining social welfare grants spark frustration and fury in South Africa. #URL#

#HASHTAG#! #HASHTAG#!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...doesn't look like there are many takers at R70 a pop...probably smells like the water in Joburg's Jukskei River... #HASHTAG#! #HASHTAG##HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who else thinks lockdowns don't work..? They do exactly what they are intended to do: reduce the number of COVID-19 infections, hospital admissions and deaths. They also have dire economic consequences. So wear a mask, do social distancing, wash hands, avoid large gatherings... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# .#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Your conferences don't win investment. Just do this: publicly renounce RET, EWC, NHI, BEE, EE, and the SACP. Reform SA's Labour laws and arrest and charge ALL the State Capture looters. Investment will flood in overnight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The armistice remembered on Armistice Day is the agreement that ended WW1 in 1918]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# ...isn't just what happened in the early 18th century when smallpox arrived in South Africa on a Dutch trading ship and very quickly decimated the indigenous peoples because they had no immunity whatsoever..?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're welcome, Vic. I just can't understand why so many people see lockdowns as evil, unnecessary, infringing on their rights etc. It's a huge nonsense. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and in case you're wondering if they work, watch the excellent TV series "The Long Way Up" where 2 Rivian electric trucks support 2 Harley Davidson electric motorcycles on an epic journey from Tierra del Fuego at the southern tip of SAmerica back to California. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HOW MUCH..? R1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...don't put any more daft ideas into Fokole "Loser" Mbalula's head, please... #USER# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and that's just the beginning...when they really start looking they'll realise the hospital has been completely hollowed out by looters...many of whom are current/former employees...it's looking increasingly likely that CMH will NEVER reopen... #HASHTAG#! #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes! Top defender in top form. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...what a shame... #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...but who can explain why we want to EAT so much during quarantine..? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...are you having issues with #USER# too..? ...I've had a whole string of Payfast payments at several online retailers freeze up on me, and those useless bozos just say it's not their fault and do nothing to assist...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...just wait until taxpayers have to find the money pay R1Trillion+ for each of Eskom's new nuclear power stations, each of which will take 20 years to build, and will be riddled with design faults, construction snafus, labour stoppages and contract disputes... #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...eeeeeuuuuuwwww...40 year old cake..? ...no thanks.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...it may not be quite as bad as the media are saying...this screenshot is from the Rand Water website now...typical #USER# #USER# communications cock-up... #HASHTAG#! #HASHTAG#! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrong and wrong. Lockdowns DO control the spread of #HASHTAG#. However the harm caused by lockdowns can be - debatably - greater than the harm created by the COVID outbreak that caused it. Vaccine-driven herd immunity IS possible if enough people get vaccinated quickly enough. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Level 2 is correct...and you're right...the risk of being infected by your domestic, or any visitor, is significant, especially if you're a pensioner like me. You may want meet her at the entrance to your home every day to observe her and ask some simple screening questions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# ...like Genghis Khan, you mean..? Not a chance. DD's too lazy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and you're a prize twat. Read and learn: #URL# 
Now get off your fucking high horse and start thinking about somebody other than yourself and your AH Libertarian pals for a change! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and the world will undoubtedly be a much better place as a consequence...but will the change be too little too late...only time will tell... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soooo...once again Twitter is shown up as the #HASHTAG# platform for mischief-makers. But, of course, "guns don't kill people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...so what?...like you, Malema, Fraud, Ace, Bathababalas, Yengeni and many others, Niehaus has proved over and over again that he's a total rubbish, a complete waste of time and money who does nothing useful or productive for party or country. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Piggy" Modise really is the pits...HTF can #USER#'s useless #USER# #USER# make her Speaker of Parliament? She doesn't possess anything remotely resembling grey matter, and the average amoeba has more integrity... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A volunteer team of engineers, physicians, computer scientists, and others, called MIT E-Vent, is working to implement a safe, inexpensive emergency ventillator which could be built quickly around the world. #URL# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...can anyone name one thing, ANYTHING positive, that being a member of #HASHTAG# has done for SA..?
 
Prestige? No.
Investment? Nah.
Crime prevention? Uh-uh.
Access to low cost loans? Nope.

Just more cost for taxpayers and a waste of everyone's time.

#HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even if you've had #HASHTAG# you should still get vaccinated. Here's what the USA's CDC says  #URL# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...but, don't worry, Aaron Motsoaledi's, #USER#'s, #USER#'s #USER#'s grand plan to rescue Public Healthcare in SA - the "brilliantly conceived" National Health Insurance Scam - sorry, Scheme - will put a smile back on your dial... #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Originally, I wasn't a big fan of Dier at center back, but I've got to admit he gets stronger and sharper with every game, and his positional play has improved a lot. He was absolutely colossal against #HASHTAG# on Sunday. Dier and Romero could become a formidable partnership. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ...sorry if I was abrupt...TBH, I've had my fill of tweeps maligning the "MSM" for no reason other than Trump's MAGAts think its a clever new conspiracy theory, when in fact it's just part of Trump's devious process to make people believe his lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...nah, boet, your useless "movement" has been destroyed from within by the thousands of lying, looting ANC cadres who have turned it into an organised crime syndicate...and the other useless layabouts, like #USER#, who actively protect them from justice... #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ditto. Excellent player. Top professional. Highly motivated. Never stops trying. Love his fast, direct runs into the oppositions box. Should score more goals than he does; perhaps too unselfish and not quick enough to pull the trigger. Deserves more starts than he gets. #HASHTAG#!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry to burst your bubble, boet! You've almost certainly been given multiple vaccines at some point in your life -  measles, mumps, rubella, chickenpox, influenza, polio, diphtheria, tetanus, yellow fever, cholera...you're no more pure-blooded than anyone else! Bwahahahahaha!!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...well, he's not a contortionist...at least not in the normal sense of the word...I think the top 5 possibilities are:
1) SAPS detective
2) Municipal councilor
3) Municipal traffic official
4) Home Affairs official
5) Minibus taxi association thug #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[27 years after the end of apartheid poverty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...I thought Squirrel had cancelled their ridiculous super-spreader dog-and-pony-show..? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant! That'll fix everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists estimating how fast the curve is flattened in 51 countries determined that arbitrarily re-opening societies can allow COVID-19 to undo that progress much faster than it took to achieve it. Increased testing would counter the disease's spread. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...consequences..? ...not while Cupcake is President...he still hasn't found a pair... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, I have faith alright...that I'll be scammed from here to Timbuktu! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and "Advicate" Dali "Nyatsi" Mpofu can "represent" him again... #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fauci's point, and the point you're not stating, is that an unvaccinated person is about 20X more likely to be infected than a fully vaccinated person, so better to not invite them to the gathering. But you know that; you just don't say it because it doesn't suit your narrative. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and all thanks to the appalling mess #USER# #USER#'s useless #USER# #USER# has made of SA in just 27 short years. #HASHTAG#! #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...no wonder Republicans in Congress don't want a  Commission of Inquiry into the Jan 6th events...half of them were directly involved in one way or another... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...does it really matter of he is..? ...he's done nothing, said nothing of any consequence, led his party and SA nowhere, just been the useless standard bearer for his useless ANC Government...but it probably does matter, because whoever replaces him will likely be even worse... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...I hope not. And I agree with you; Biden is better than Clinton was, but, IMO, is still a very weak candidate. It's a reflection of American politics in general and the sort of person that it attracts. As a nation, they should be very worried. Then again, is SA any better..?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# ...yes, it was, several times, most recently in 1996 as part of the Truth and Reconciliation Commission. In 2002 then Transport Minister Dullah Omar decided not to re-open the original Commission of Enquiry. However the cause of the crash has never been definitively established.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Achievement? Admit it: the spectrum auction was delayed for years and years by #USER# #USER# corruption and incompetence...while YOU were Deputy President! #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...riiiiiiiiiiiiiiight..! ...and you and your crooked sidekick, Fraud Shivambu, have done nothing wrong either...oh, wait, #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet another useless #USER# #USER# success story! The Post Office is in complete disarray after years of corruption]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very true. Surely the US's weak-kneed response to Russia's invasion of Ukraine has emboldened China, which is considering what would be the opportune time to invade Taiwan. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...all the free sauce on the planet can't make up for Spur's badly cooked food, rude waiters and incompetent management...my last meal at Spur was ~5yrs ago and I'll never go back... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...oh, come on...this is #HASHTAG# propaganda from years ago! ...get a grip, man, and grow up! ...if that's the best you've got then just go home, go to bed and sleep it off. #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>