<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[So good to move from #HASHTAG# to the Italian accent English of 2021 Physics Nobel prize winner #HASHTAG# :) #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly what the British media thought of Berlusconi when he was Italy's PM (which was right) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's rephrase that: can they put country before party? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER#  is seeking an innovative and enthusiastic next Chair of Court. see ad if interested or share! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it just me? I was quoted almost 600£ for the, now required in Scotland, installation of networked fire alarms plus 65£ annual maintenance fee. I did tell them that it was an outrageous amount of money for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is more to #HASHTAG# than what you might think. Don't take my word for it but that of #USER# PhD researcher Annie Runkel #USER# ! Listen on BBC Sounds. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I took a very similar photo in 1998, I also visited the twin towers, my 2 brothers, ex husband and I all got into a lift to the top floor to see the stunning views, no security checks, just a working place atmosphere,I still cannot compute the huge void of what is now Ground Zero #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["in response to data from Ucas which showed a 41 per cent decline in the number of EU students applying to study undergraduate courses at Scottish universities" - Scotland extends master’s scholarships to Europe post-Brexit #HASHTAG# #URL# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hi, I'm an academic researching an article on NFTs, I'd like to ask you why you chose Magritte in particular as an inspiration? Also can I ask your permission to  include this tweet of yours, as it appears here, in my article? Thank you in advance!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If you are interested, in this piece "Knocking on Europe’s door: How narratives of fear, insecurity and nostalgia shape collective perceptions of immigration" I discuss the literary origins of such language, and a lot more! From page 60 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the same Covid antigenic test booked here for 50£ in order to be able to fly in Italy costs 25Euros, I thought global Britain was setting the highest standards for market competition, consumers' rights etc. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it just me? the expression "home grown Brits" in relation to lack of workers in some sectors  sends shivers down my back :( #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent thread for fans of Italian history #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nah..no systemic misogyny  here.. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Says a lot about British political culture...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the ones who switch on their cameras go straight to Paradise! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The weather person on the local Dundee radio station has just defined 12 degree temperature as *mild*. I guess it is all a matter of perspective! ;) #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It is an excellent piece by a long time friend of DJCAD, the author gave a very interesting talk to our PG students a few years back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The words "denazification" used by Putin to justify #HASHTAG#' s invasion are an offence to those same Russians who died fighting the real Nazi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note the solemn expression of the prominent men, including a former PM, at the inauguration, not at all distracted by her sexy curves...#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart goes out to them "Young Trump staffers say they are having a hard time dating" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Universities must work collaboratively to address *all* our global challenges! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This resonates with me, my mother's birthday today and I miss her terribly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No prob, pleased u enjoy my tweets, but I can assure u I'm very aware of how privilege works..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mephisto is also known as Mephistopheles, the spirit of the Devil in the legend of Faust. Does #USER# know or even care about the negative connotations? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As a foreigner myself that was also what I first noticed, the point is that we notice more (and often attracted to) what we are not *used* to, it's the appeal of the unfamiliar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miss the "al fresco"  atmosphere so much! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We decided to stay put this year, lovely part of the country Alba almost as nice as Salerno in the Campania region I'm from :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This explains a lot, including the success of Fox News. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I never really liked Science Fiction, I guess I don't get it" #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In my lecture on cyber bodies I discuss automata like the Duck from the 18th c.. They are the real precursors of Terminator! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This sounds very interesting. -College: enrol with us and your family and friends can come, too #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- BBC News - University complaints by students top 20,000 #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stunning violin arrangement of the Italian anthem at the #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, but she is making a simplistic comparison which does not take into account the different media + contemporary cultural context]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here in the UK you would spend 4 times as much for the wine :) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess she liked economy under Trump better #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former leader of right wing English Defence League used to own a tanning shop #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One must contemplate the possibility that he has lost grip on reality, psychopaths do not behave according to theories]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent start of term, first meeting with my new mentee, stimulating discussion about her career objectives, mentorship is not just good professional practice, more importantly it is an ethical imperative to address inequalities in academia and affect change. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I happen to be in the train 'quiet' coach and yet there is a v annoying electrically induced noise originating from above #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's the art critics' job to help sort it out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wee bit of haar in Camperdown park this morning! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent idea! "Italy seeks Unesco heritage status for espresso coffee" cc #USER# #USER#  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The project is led by the Weavers Incorporation of Dundee in collaboration with #USER#  #USER#  and #USER# . -'The best of our city': Plans for 35m tapestry celebrating Dundee unveiled… #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't tell Trump! - "Tinton Falls, NJ, 97-year-old Mayor Vito Perillo wins re-election" #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To fight conspiracy theories we must foster trust in democracy. Governments who run to strategies of silence in their dealings with journalists and citizens, will only allow their enemies to instead frame the debate" Well said #USER# ! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is a bit more complicated than that, research on Selfie has shown how there is a potential for empowering as well!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# that's exactly the way millions of EU citizens residents in the UK felt when they had to apply for settled status (and still do), hope you enjoy your time in Italy nevertheless!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has anyone explained to him that language is a social/cultural construct? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday #USER# I've loved engaging with your opinion pieces over the years (with letters &amp; tweets) &amp; your jobs pages have helped me find the right job at crucial times in my personal life &amp; professional career. Thank you! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was it even legal to wear a police uniform? #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Metamates—not to be confused with Metamucil, a fiber supplement for those experiencing gastrointestinal distress" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This brings memories of a memorable visit. Cannot wait to be able to travel again! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I advice my students not to use a word like *stuff* given how rich the English vocabulary is of alternatives #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh dear..it's going to be tough indeed, I buy lemons every week!! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# conference will take place on 7-9 September at #USER#  Aberdeen, UK. Theme – Silenced Voices. Submission deadline: 14 January 2022 #URL# key notes by #USER# #USER# #USER# and  Miklos Sukosd. Look forward to this already!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Does not answer my question now. A rt of a conspiracy theorist and  anti-vaxxer, come on!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Following in the footsteps of US right wing media here is an attempt to politicize the wearing of masks. Such attempts cost human lives! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sadly robots already can type something like this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very interesting piece on the *human duties* of sovereign states. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in the role of Dean in a great university? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Serious answer is that there are no upsides,Brexit is an ideological project driven by a fringe within the Tory party which has now taken over (mirror image of Trumpism within GOP) &amp; supported by hard left unionism blind to fact that Brexit damages the working classes it defends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Rethink needed’ on UK pension cuts as USS scheme rebounds #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just booked my booster jab appointment in December, straightforward &amp; efficient. Well done #USER# ! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# promises to be a really good match, pity I won't be able to watch the launch of #USER# :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before vaccinations became a political pin ball #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I note that  #HASHTAG# has inspired a great deal of meme creativity #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# To salvage Blair's (and Brown's) successful legacy at home from the discredit of the Iraq war policy, learn and update it to face today's challenges is exactly what Labour should be doing..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This really shows how important the arts and culture are not just in the North East of Scotland -"Aberdeen Art Gallery named Scotland's building of the year" - BBC News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No brainer to avoid group thinking! - "Sage needs more disciplinary and geographic diversity", say MPs #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good for AI-Da it is a robot artist and not a human university  researcher like #HASHTAG# so it will not end up tortured to death in spy enemy obsessed Egypt #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*ALLOWED* -Almost 5 million allowed to stay in UK under EU Settlement Scheme #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It will end when the next generation will rejoin...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# minister for HE  FE addresses the UCU conference "Beyond Covid: what now for Scottish HE" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some good news!!! -Egypt, human rights reseacher Patrick Zaki will be released after 22 months of detention. Him: “I’m fine, thanks to Italy for the support” #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to put an end to this pathetic saga. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# President #USER# addressing the UCU Scotland conference, reminiscing on his experience as a student rep, acknowledging the power students have in a marketised academia but rejecting us vs them logic #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is no shortage of young people in this country to become lorry drivers" #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, the divergence dividend remains aspirational because, in spite of their efforts, it will take longer than they thought to unravel the cultural/legislative ties established during the EU membership, and some changes might be entirely impossible to achieve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# talking about how online learning reduces the skill gap #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Congrats on the exhibition, love the city, unique does not even cover it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# and, thanks to such a tactic, they have a wonderful track record in influencing government's policies, of course]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent example of a truly civic university! "uniting schools and councils behind “place-based” ideas to raise educational attainment from the early years onwards' .#URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is still connected, Brexit could not change geography. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck with this unless they shut down the internet #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those of a certain age the tv serie #HASHTAG# comes to mind #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Ryanair self-congratulatory trumpet and the Irish recorded voice that confirm their punctuality record! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, Simon Reynolds' book Retromania:Pop's culture addiction to its own past was published 9 years ago! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I their mind they might even think that dramatising is a sort of homage to the victim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those interested in neo-fascism / neo-nazism in Italy,  and not just, this book by journalist Paolo Berizzi (who has received personal threats x his work) is a must read. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Too ugly to teach’: universities ‘must end’ anonymous evaluation #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just read your chapter in AI for Everyone?, Really enjoyed it &amp; I found the de-familiarization argument persuasive enough. I have been working on similar themes myself, my latest is here, in case of interest: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The university our community of staff and students want to have? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2nd find of the day: a George Haller painting for 35£ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God Bless, this made me laugh loud! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For once a *professional* RT #USER#: Olympian Josefa #HASHTAG# is new minister of sport in #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a tragedy for British democracy the lack of a competent opposition is at this historical juncture :( #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some *people* could not care one bit. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, but Brexit is not the only cause, the malaise within the English establishment has roots much deeper than the ones Brexit gave voice to. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This sums up Putin's successful strategy in America #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starmer might even consider the possibility that Brexit can't work #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glasgow 'al fresco' is for brave hearted ones! :) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a country has no future its citizens hand their babies over to foreign soldiers :( #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best piece you are likely to read today.... #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hanna Reitsch,only woman to receive the iron cross, nazi aviator who ends up opening a gliding school in Ghana #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby (Canadian) steps I'd say: "presidents signing the final agreements represent less than a quarter of Canada’s 200-plus degree-granting institutions" Not sure this is a *major* push- Canadian higher education makes major push for equity #URL#  #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A man of good hope by Johnny steinberg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# to my mind class and privilege are connected, they do belong to what Peggy McIntosh (who defined the latter) might call the 'big pattern in society'...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extraordinary interview on #HASHTAG# a moment ago on lad culture in the army, could not believe my ears! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Worth stressing that living in a van can be all right for a holiday or a tv programme, it can never be a life choice unless it stems from some kind of trauma or financial difficulties]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We import 2/3rds of our cheese" comes to mind.. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Text hard to read (and with no context) one can only understand the odd sentence like the one when it reads that we are the cause of all our ills...wondering whether the Francesco mentioned is St. Francis...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We shall fight them on the polluted beaches!!!-MPs vote to allow water companies to dump raw sewage into rivers and seas #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #HASHTAG# UK Presidency is in partnership with Italy but you wouldn't know if you consider British media only #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a #USER# supporter it was nice to receive #USER# end of year email, not sure I share the optimism that 'we will look back on 2021 as the year when the rot was stopped, the tide turned and a bold new future emerged' unless that was irony, but hope to be wrong!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dean #USER# welcoming speakers at this morning's event "The Spaces in between" which explores approaches to #HASHTAG# in city living through planning &amp; design, organised by #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[: RT #USER# The Bradford Batman vigilante has admitted to a criminal past, he was jailed five times #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walmart asks its workers to donate #HASHTAG# food to Walmart workers! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girl at the bakery just said: " I like your outfit by the way, you are dressed so nice" nice to hear for a "mature" woman like  me :) #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man behind Gove with the "Get Johnson out" placard during the #HASHTAG# interview #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening right now, love the selection of music from continental Europe! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucky! :-) #HASHTAG# RT #USER#: And yes, it's Donald Trump addressing #HASHTAG# #USER# #URL#"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# would like to hear our thoughts about the fact that children in Leeds are so poor that they even haven't got a bed to seep in so they sleep on the floor. He had not heard of the term #HASHTAG# before. Any thoughts Tweeps besides rage, anger and indignation?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Text book example of cognitive dissonance? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# (1986) is on Ch4 right now, first time I must have heard the word "Dundee", never imagined I would end up living in #HASHTAG# :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look forward to the day when this won't be news worthy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By asking "researchers to do all they can to ensure that scrutiny yields more examples of lesson-learning – and fewer “gotcha” headlines" what gets lost in this piece is political accountability.  #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That moment when your boss asks you to drop one of your admin roles so that someone else has a go at it even though you are the most qualified to hold it. Unis are really good at making the most of their in-house talents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Graduate, bbc1 tonight at 23.30. You are welcome. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent talk by #USER# to #USER# students &amp; staff today. Hopefully back for our Degree Shaw? :) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Certo but class makes a huge difference here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relentless anti-university propaganda masquerading as caring about equality. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should read "gullible Brits blame EU for NI trade problems" #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there anybody more alien to the ideal of a university than Berlusconi? #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I loved the Monica Bellucci episode, her French with Italian interjections to die for :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope lessons have been learnt from the tragic death of Cambridge PhD researcher #HASHTAG# in Egypt - "Overseas collaborations must continue – with eyes wide open" #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is it about despots and horse riding? Remember Putin, now Kim #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why such a fear of boredom and such an obsession with entertainment?? "Why do graduation ceremonies have to be so boring?" Cc #USER#  #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Facts uninterpreted by values are sterile; values without facts are blind.'-  Universities should help break the wall between facts and values #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please someone explain the etymology of the word misogyny to this man! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER#: A bug delayed Apple's much-anticipated HealthKit apps on iOS 8 #URL#"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are British exporters to EU not in the streets? Why are they putting up with the disaster that is Brexit? Why are they not angry? What is stopping them? This is mind boggling!  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covid, Merkel: "If only we were in the situation of Italy". Towards mandatory vaccine #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My local Tesco did not have my fav smoked mozzarella, what they had instead was a 'mozzarella for pizza', a very distant relative of what mozzarella should be. Brexit is really starting to bite, literally!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*home front* - I can almost hear #USER# salivating at the prospect of war #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How timing, just received an email inviting me to a university workshop on "How to be resilient in Academia" Hmm should I attend? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Gender and cultural competence should be 
built into health policy and healthcare services, 
including training and coaching in equality, 
diversity, and human rights for clinicians and 
policymakers" p43 Scottish Government Women's Health plan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So cruel to see such a pic on Christmas day :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth having a monarchy for this! RT #USER#: Stop the world I want to get off. #URL#"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess which is the sexiest language (neither  French nor Greek  :) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There is a character who still has to get tenure..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little Caesar enjoying the world's attention #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old enough to remember when British newspapers were (rightly) deriding Berlisconi's bunga bunga parties...#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Johnson won't impose a lockdown, even though  it might be the wisest course of action, because that would be metaphorically the nail in his political coffin, just like in the US (and much less extent in continental Europe) the tragedy is the partisanship linked to Covid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# it is true that distraction and media noise can be 'weaponized' and thus make us disregard the fights worth fighting, but I still think that this particular war is fought on many fronts, even apparently unlikely ones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arm feeling a bit sore, this #HASHTAG# vaccine is strong stuff!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evidence of how faulty the gov UK system with regard to travel regulations: just got a text welcoming me to the UK &amp; telling to quarantine and have 2 tests done, instead  I do not need to &amp; only 1 test is required! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["With NFTs, America may have reached the logical extreme of celebrity endorsements.' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being anti-racist or  (neo) fascism has nothing to do with *left wing sensitivities* it has to do with human decency #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hi, I'm an academic researching an article on NFTs, can u kindly answer a couple of questions:1) were u thinking of Nelly Furtado's comparison because she had a lot of success before she disappeared? 2) Can I reproduce your tweet in my article? Thanks! Anna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I only wish KS said Let's get Brexit Undone! What's Labour's plan? To renegotiate a better deal for something which has no benefits whatsoever?? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Director #USER# is deservedly awarded an honorary professorship x her services to design. #USER# #USER# #USER#  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glasgow School of Art’s Mackintosh rebuild ‘complete within ten years’
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it just me? Why do #HASHTAG# players shout? Why not use microphones to pass on instructions in each other's ears? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Turing Programne is a very poor replacemente for Erasmus plan, so we will be put in place our own programme" #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["universities are a bedrock for Europe's future" - The EU’s university strategy will help build international bridges #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attending the #HASHTAG# conference from Aberdeen. Only thing you need to know is that the wonderful #USER# is one of the panelists so it will be great! :) #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just had a quick check on the major Italian media outlets, no mention of food/fuel/truck drivers/blood vials shortages. Safe enough to assume this is the case elsewhere on continental Europe? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely due to the celebrity glam of the couple in the pic :) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Obviously aware, not sure what is the point of the double standard argument is however, its existence does not undermine the commendable reaction to the current crisis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- 10 diktats from Brussels that are ruining life in Britain | David Shariatmadari #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Correction: *abysmal* state of British commentary #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One of the reasons for my personal passion x equality stems exactly from what happened with AIDS then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can anyone disagree with this? - "We must end linguistic discrimination in academic publishing"  #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Thanks for sharing, as it happens I'm writing an article on Nfts at the moment :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish we could award a *dismissal certificate* to someone else! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#! RT #USER#: .#USER# 'lets get real here, what's going on' #HASHTAG#"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A virus induced pneumonia might kill you but at least the quality of the air you won't be breathing anymore got better #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never stop learning something new, just heard of *motorcycle football* it originated during WW1 and was popular till the 1950s apparently.  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my fav quotes ever "Research is formalized curiosity. It is poking and prying with a purpose." - Zora Neale Hurston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This brings back memories of when I was lucky to meet him as an undergraduate, sat next to him for lunch at the uni canteen after his lecture  :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr Adeela Shari illustrating the Board Diversity Practice Toolkit "change should concern not just Governing Boards but the whole institution" #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Speaking of life essentials: coffee &amp; sport news!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent interview exposing the *little bit controversial* (by his own admission), views of such an individual. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While others play Churchill at home... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It is more than that, it is anti-EU propaganda like the worst British tabloids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dean #USER# contributing a talk to our fab Speakers' Programme, a brilliant insight into a career that beautifully blends art(istry), education &amp; scholarship. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning at Brexit: UK ‘cut out of Galileo systems we built’ due to Brexit #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are experiencing one of the worst pandemics in history, then you read this and feel renewed hope in humanity's ingenuity. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Joy in small pleasures is the secret x survival!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["surely, in a university, ignorance is no defence. Managerial blah is a crime against words by intelligent, well-educated and well-remunerated people who should know better." - The scourge of managerial blah #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The identity of any celebrity is part of public/political  discourse, ie open to discussion &amp; interpretation, that does not = weaponising, not sure your *genteel* approach to calling out racism &amp; discrimination can have any impact at all in light of what we are currently facing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has anyone asked whether Captain Samantha ever cried while in space? #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# RT #USER#: Kudos to #USER# for choosing The Decline &amp; Fall Of The Roman Empire as his Desert Island Book."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#USER#: Dick Cheney says Obama is leaving a 'terrible burden' for next president with Iran deal #URL#"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talibans just announced that death penalties will from now on not executed in public anymore. They don't even need the *spectacle* of punishment anymore for terror to reign among the population, Foucault was wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And that applauding audience fully buying the fantasy claims!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“there is no substantial relationship between having a vocation-oriented major and longer-term success... the importance of breadth of study for all...” -‘Reclaim the meaning of the liberal arts’, universities urged #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jerry should watch #USER# 's latest bbc serie #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>