<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yesterday in a 150 dollar league i traded rodgers and carlos hyde for mahomes. Good move by me #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# iWhy are you not feeling bryan edwards? Darren Waller i not going to have 3000 receiving yards this year is he? There is an outside shot for ruggs and edwards to hit 900 yards with waller hitting his 1200 yards and another 1000 yards shared to the rest of the team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# imagine wasting a harrison bryant te with a falcons lions stack and claypool in the flex #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# lol at bringing in that drunk to replace herman. If you are going to replace herman you go for urban meyer or just stand pat. Sark is a downgrade or at best a lateral move.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What a stupid article. Haskins could have gone to any of the other 31 teams he would still be an nfl failure plain and simple. Dude is straight stupid as an nfl qb. Nfl busts happen in the middle of round 1 all the time. No need to delay the inevitable and it was smart to cut him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think the final 2 minutes of the episode was the real twist of that episode.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# wwe is paying for the sins for not building a new mega star that fans give a crap about. They gave the streak to a part timer and they had cena go over bray at wm 30. Factor in trying to shove roman reigns down the fans throats for 4 years this is what they deserve imo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# players get to kneel for the national anthem but they will stand for the chinese anthem. oh wait never mind that is the nba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i love getting him at 611 in te premium in a myffpc fbg draft back in may.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He was clearly the problem with the vikings offense it has nothing to do with that god awful o line or the 28 million dollar qb. Enjoy those first down 2 yard dalvin cook runs this weekend vs dolphins team also fighting for its playoff lives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The senate has to confirm the person also. If the same party has the senate and the presidency this is what happens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i gave up mattison and arob for juju and henderson3 weeks ago. I kind of hate losing arob but rb are a premium.  sadly i faded henderson in bestball #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I own so much of him in bestball thank to you and overzet.

You ever doing to show a draftkings bestball team or are you keeping those a secret?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i tried the saints rookie te whose name I forget as my 1 percent play. Of course it was a total failure. kicker chalk donkeys got the win last night #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# raw only has 3 hours. It is hard to get around to new characters on a 3 hour show]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you need to explain how many teams per 12 team league can advance on to weeks 14 thru 16 and what percentage of teams need to score in the highest percentile for weeks 14 and 15 to advance on to week 16. Do you have a page that explains all this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i got dwelley for 1 week then back to waivers he prob goes unless he has like 7 catches for 70 yards then i might hold onto him. dropped higbee 3 weeks ago. I do not think i will ever regret it. Credit to mcvay for putting the higbee genie back into that bottle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# pretty sure in myffpc you will see people bidding 100 to 300 on perine thinking/hoping they will get a top 24 ppr weekly rb to play. Personally my perine bid is much lower than that but it would not surprise me to see a 150 to 250 bid  on perine tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I agree brady needs odell also to go with mike evans godwin and antonio brown. Also bucs need to trade for hopkins diggs and theilen. Maybe then the bucs will have enough wr to support a qb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ekeler owners ran extremely bad and dalvin owners ran extremely hot even though dalvin himself did not put up a score where he was needed. You need to get over your dmont hate he plays behind a crap o line in a bad offense but he had a mega hot matchup vs lions d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# you can say that about the entire te position. If winstom sucks ass or gets injured hill is a cheat code at TE. I will scoop him up in every espn league this week at TE where possible if ahmed is already gone off waivers. Sadly i guessed wrong and stashed dwash over ahmed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ok so if you do not win week 14 the 160 is what you won. if you win week 14 which is what you want you get to go on and win more money. at the very worst you will win 160 bucks. the goal is to get to week 16 and go for the real money. no one entered just trying to win 160 bucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# not a surprise at all honestly drake shares in season long worth as much as cam akers shares at this point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# what a big score. Sadly i did not cash in any of my 5 rainmakers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# forgive my ignorance but why kerryon? I guess a chance he could get traded to another team and pull a 2019 drake making my full fade of him in bestball really tilting. I think that is the only way he becomes an asset imo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# bill o brien was right Just an off night in a game seattle needs more. Not a total surprise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# pretty sure rosman will be ok but rivers for 25 million or cam for a max of 7.5 million and 17.5 million to spend on something else hmmmm. I think i do cam.I get why they went rivers but i would have told him 15 million max.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I totally get it honestly as a gamecocks fan you did what you could. Time to let someone else earn cb snaps to get ready for 2021. Good luck in the nfl. Surely you will be drafted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# in other words all 3 are pretty worthless unless you are in a 16 team league.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# so glad my team that is left is my kelce 11 team. won this week with ben dionate claypool to go. I still hope the game happens because i need those points to help me to my 145 to 150 seasonal avg. Still a longshot to win the whole thing but winning 1500 next week would be nice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Kane in 1997 was such an awesome debut. I miss when wwe would have amazing debuts like that. Dude was instantly over as a menacing heel in 3 mins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# yes trump was at the lab when covid leaked from china. Covid got the dems the white house and division and trump hate. Enjoy your minor victory. no senate. you aint getting shit accomplished. Mcconell will fucking railroad everything #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# socr dave going to win all the best ball leagues with his 18th round corey davis shares #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# 

care to brag and show how many bestball teams on draftkings with a 1 attached to them you wish to brag about? i have 1 out of 50 bestball leagues #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I own a bunch of damien harris in best ball. Because of this I promise you that he will not become a thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Kreese literally showed up on her doorstep and told her lessons are free. Kreese also handled her rent man problem. Kreese asked her was the situation resolved and kreese made the retort is that right? seems reasonable she would be ultra loyal to kreese and his beliefs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# prob a really stupid thought but are johnny and daniel half brothers? Will we ever see either's father assuming 99.999999999% it is not the same dude? Has there been any thought to exploring this arc? Also any reason you kept tory's mother offscreen? I think her mom is hil swank.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# but you might throw an int or get a stack when you drop back #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if the #HASHTAG# must change their team name i vote for the washington sammy baughs. Dude lead the league in passing tds and interceptions (as a defender) in the same season. Put a picture of sammy baugh in his final season on the helmet smiling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Washington is amazing at drafting awful black quarterbacks. Doug Williams was a trade so not drafted by washington. At least haskins might lead washington to trevor. Keep playng haskins. he might get wash to 1-15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# forgive my ignorance i do not get the joke? sleeping as in no worried about his week 1 availability? Not sweating looking for a rb2 as much because they got cmac?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# al bundy was a sexist chauvinist pig who always told people what was on his mind and america loved him for it. does this remind you of anyone that 51 percent of america hates lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i rather the usa resign him he is too amazing to our team. pelosi on the other hand lets trad her to iran for 2 people to be named later and cash considerations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Freeman going to come in for cheap? Likelier scenario for me is jeff wilson jr mckinnon or one of their rookies they drafted takes the brieda carries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i am hating owning any of boston scott in dfs. barber the clear pivot. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I demand all rookie wr drafted in first 4 rounds to do what justin jefferson did last season I think I have very realistic expectations IF we get tee higgins type seasons we should be happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# driskel was low key not garbage yesterday vs a very good steelers defense. Hamler will get some love if he is unowned in myffpc leagues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# sorry keenan and ekeler did nothing and lynn only let herbert throw 1 ball in the 4th for your main event team #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# imo it is so stupid. Ridley will be the Alpha there even if Julio is traded. People acting like he is going to be prime gronk or jimmy graham or kelce year 1.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This cam akers talk has me all kinds of happy as i took him in the 4th round in my 350 dollar ffpc sat night. I also reached for duke johnson a few rounds early.

Why no damien harris or anthony mcfarland talk?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# pence brought up a good point and then she had to say im speaking while she thought of something substantive to say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# cowboys are really the same team with mccarthy. 3 fumbles already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# imagine people showing up for a football game and wanting to watch football instead of being lectured at how awful the world is. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# dk bb team tonight dhen jul rid jtay rjo hig dswif aiyuk mack dharris jefferson goff ithomas cobb thigg boykin bedwards claypool duvernay someone drafted guice and damien in rounds 10 and 11 lol. Do drafts at midnight eastern people seem to be drunk then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# but then dave meltzer would have called you FAT for eating ice cream. Because he is the authority on looks just look at what a sexy beast he is #HASHTAG# when in reality you are the gorgeous beast #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Every year is its own event. Covid will really muck things up this year. Last year the guy who started adams odell antonio brown prob did not do good. neither did the person like me who started conner damien dmont. Bust come in rb and wr form.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# because no one wants to listen to a liberal on radio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# most of his big games came with dusty bit still strong arm joe flacco. He had 1 great game with lock. Sorry at his adp I rather take gallup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# no coach can win with a mediocre o line This is not a surprise. Goff and gurley overpaid contracts. Rams are in for a 4-12 in 2020 and the jags thank you. Enjoy paying ramsey his high price as teams just abuse the other cb. I am sure LA fans will be patient and behave]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you did not project kamara for 6 tds. why does espn even employee you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i think a team rather try kerryon johnson after the lions are out of it in mid october.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i did some 2 te leagues this year. Logan thomas was always my 2nd te in said leagues. I have some of him in dfs also stacked with haskins because i like losing money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# you really need to spend like 10 dollars a week on draftkings dfs. They have contest that cost 50 cents where first place wins 10k dollars so it is not like you have to spend 20 dollars a week on 1 lineup. They also have a 3 dollar contest this week to win 100k.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# they have 2 giants and another washington game. I refuse to believe nfc west teams have an easier path next 13 games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am welcome to be on your podcast via phone call if you want me on to lecture me. Keep in mind i like trump and find him hilarious but we will keep out of the political discourse. lmk if u want me on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# your ceh eliminated me from playoffs but honestly i had a shit team anyways. it was crakrok23 to be clear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# my duke johnson is a bet against david staying healthy. i did not select duke to ever start him until david goes down. #URL# i went 0 wr theory. I prob should have taken mclaurin over dobbins but oh well. at least i made sure to smash kelce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 1 of my favorite fades coming into 2020 but i never thought i would get it right with injury variance. of course i took akers in  the round 4 range who has been just as worthless so i cant victory lap this 1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# good thing i did not start drake over edwards in fantasy today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i vote for purrmaid to be naked 24 7 365 (366 on a leap year). Sadly that was not on the ballot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# hopkins was always a fade with kirk and fitz still around. Evans was a fade for me with jameis gunslinger gone. Godwin should still eat if he is the full time slot guy. DJ Moore is no safe bet to repeat 2019. In auctions i pay up for 2 high end rb I trust and pay down at wr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Not trying to be a hater but owens and rollins were never super over like cena or rock or austin. They are more like bret hart and shawn michaels types at best. Factor in a womens tag title match main event and while i appreciate those 4 they are not exactly must see tv.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# so happy I owned fournette and keenan allen over him in some 2018 drafts #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# where are you taking him in 2021 drafts assuming he has trevor lawrence and a new head coach you are bullish about? Would 6th round be too early? 7th round? Even Perriman if he returns can be a thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He was one of the few underrated good things about the original xfl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# He is not saying trump is better he is saying the dems gave him nothing either so he is voting 3rd party which is his right to say fuck you to both parties on election day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# i do not work for netflix but i can verify they wanted cobra kai originally but they only wanted to pay for a pilot and not the whole first season so youtube beat them to the punch.  episode 1 on youtube of season 1 look at all those views.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 6 highest scores weekly get the win 6 lowest scores get the loss. In the event of the 6th and 7th place team having the same score then give them each half a win.

I think in best ball it should be team kicker. Also i would love an auction format of fbg championship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The nerve of you not to do research on who this character was? Who do you think you are kathleen kennedy? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# falcons deserve that loss with all those stupid first and 2nd down runs in dallas territory through game with studs ridley julio and even hurst and gage. A run play for falcons is a plus for the defense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i do not recall a brandon bolden write up about how awesome he is at running back. Are you losing your touch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i got some 2018 2019 court kings blaster boxes if you are interested. they are going for 215 a box on ebay. In a year they could be worth double that again. I do not know if that is good enough of a markup for you in a years time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# rojo and bucs d destroyed packers brady was a caretaker in that game nothing more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# etn going to the giants to be in a time share with saquon. Or to the lions so he can sit behind swift kerryon and ap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# no one would trade anything for zeke he is expensive and above average at best. Jags found an undrafted rookie who is having a top 5 season for rbs. Jerry should realize you do not pay rbs. He should have never paid zeke a high end 2nd contract. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# was this pre or post guice news? gibson and jrob was the nuts for 0 rb along with edmonds and jwilliams. Gaskin would be here too if not for the injury. 

For all 0rb love lots of wr misses mthomas beckham godwin chark kupp etc. late round wr love to claypool jefferson higgins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# a lo of good this does me on my bench. next week sean mvay will give malcom brown20 touches to show how smart and savvy he is #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Finally something good is on tv. It is not fair to be so beautiful and intelligent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i liked i changed my mind and bid 30 percent for mvs. my wr were landry boyd reagor g tate boykin so i really needed the firepower and he was best one out there. Turns out 12 percent would have gotten the job done #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# mixon was the easiest fade of the first rounders due to bengals crap o line. Now please do not laugh at me who has miles sanders yet to play a snap in 2020 talking down mixon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# this will be the unpopular stance but vince should get a percentage of the money they make on those accounts as they would not be as popular without wwe platform. It would be hilarious to see a big name threaten to go to aew and keep their account open.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It will be a good litmus test to see how much practice is really needed. Most nfl players are not sitting no their couch eating potato chips all day. They work out exercise lift weights etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i was so underweight on lamar today. It is not really a surprise. I remember in pre season we were hearing about some injury he sustained. I think it is affecting his play. He will be a good rebound candidate in 2021. for 2020 lamar owners #HASHTAG# Today was the dream match up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# keep in mind if it was mdavis at 4k vs lions or texans or jags i would be  all over him part of my davis fade is the matchup and i will own some just not like 50 percent. Right now i keep choosing a wash rb and a chubb ajones or sanders rb. Somtimes i even do chubb and ajones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The fact someone on espn put her on tv and thought she would bring in viewers still baffles my mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# considering this show has language and r rated humor i am not sure the shows audience is little kids. it is mostly fans of the 1980s karate kid and the sequels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I am feeling more and more than ronald jones is going to be 2020 ekeler. I have been taking him in 6th round in draftkings bestball leagues as my rb3. I usually start rb rb but sometimes davante adams is there in the middle of the 2nd round and i can not pass on that upside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# monday night joe flacco says hi. ravens offense is just fn broken right now. reminds me of arod with mccarthy in those final mccarthy years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# no garrett griffin talk you worthless fn prick #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# in what world is josh and kaycee all stars? one was one of 9 paul puppets and the other was one of the worst winners in bbhistory. 

Where the fuck is dan and derrick? WE do not need cody and memphis in here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I still wish the streak had been given to a full timer ideally bray wyatt. I also wish we got cena undertaker while the streak was alive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# why did you not tout dennis kelly god you guys are the worst touts ever #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Dante pettis man i was so on him. At least i got to drop him after a few weeks unlike beckham owners who had to go thru that soul crushing season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# going to be so glorious when byron pringle goes off at less than 1 percent ownership]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i loved your work in the movie accepted. I could not picture any other person in that role. Also do you have any hopes for the nfl team in dc with the new head coach?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# wwe needs to create new stars and quit relying on the past.  Let Batista thrive in his movie career. Let Brock enjoy banging 55 year old sable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# never forget #USER# made it sound like sean taylor had it coming with the lifestyle that sean taylor lived. #HASHTAG# If you ever get the chance to watch sean taylor a football life give it a look sometime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I admit trubisky is trash now time to take a big fat L on sam darnold and carson wentz. Also good call on drew lock being the next great afc west qb in the off season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Can we please admit dak is just black andy dalton at this point and not worth a long term contract? He was carried behind a great o line early in his career just like dalton.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i can see dropping kirk for laviska but i rather hold him in a 12 team league if you could. are there no better options to drop? kirk will get some 7 target games at some point imo when teams start focusing more on stopping hopkins. in 10 team leagues kirk is a drop for sure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I do worry that emmanuel sanders will be more of a threat to mthomas than ginn ever was, People forget how amazing sanders was with prime peyton. EVen last year when he got targets he did damage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tyreke Hill and Sammy Watkins are a lock to play all season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# dk metcalf mclaurin deebo had semi decent rookie years also. Jamar chase is a player a lot of people are thinking he has a shot to be justin jefferson 2020 because he played college ball with burrow where jamar chase was the alpha over  jusstin jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# 2015 blake bortles was a garbage time tom brady level hofer. Allen Robinson and allen hurns were i think top 20  fantasy wr that year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# any reason ryan finley did not start for bengals? google says brandon allen started the game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# lets not act like fuller and cooks are scrub wrs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# if rogan does not want to pay a 13 percent state tax so california politicans spend his money on stupid shit well that is his right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i had none of him in my 3 fbc drafts a month ago. Was real tempted to try him. Really regret taking mark andrews over ceh right about now but such is life. At least mark andrews has not opted out and says he will not do so.

dropped damien for d washington in a lot of leagues]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# imagine the 0s of a triple wr core of andy isabella damiere byrd and kj hamler #HASHTAG# This way you can get up to cmac and saquon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# do not worry berry steven montez will have to outduel brady in these final minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# i meant marquise cohen. I have higbee on my mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Looks like all rams rb are just flexes at best for week 1 vs cowboys. I have a 16 team auction league superflex team where the high end rb were all going for such huge money i bought all 3 rams rb for cheap hoping 1 of them becomes a top 12 fantasy rb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# if you did not land on kamara cook d henry jacobs or ajones this was the 0 rb year for sure but even a lot of wr busted imo like evans godwin m thomas etc. Next year i am just starting to take the round 5 wr in round 3 and 4. Julio starting to look like a semi bust also]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# this was a great listen. going to be hilarious if haskins ends up this years new mahomes (prob 2015 cousins is a more realistic outcome) and literally no one sees it coming. IF so sims jr best ball shares are straight fire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# sadly howie was not intellectually stimulating to talk with and janelle wanted some entertainment in the house. I agree it was a sad outcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #URL#

first team i drafted in 2020. it is a mess with no wr qb te correlation. Also i reached big for mostert. I just think if he gets 250 touches he will smash. I like the 2 wr i started with and happy to get hurst in early round7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I would give chubb a real hard look anywhere in round 3. Maybe browns pull a saints 2017 and have 2 top 12 fantasy rb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# of course because i have a bunch of fuller in dfs. now explain chark doing nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# For a 1 qb league though like in ffpc i could not fathom having 2 qb with same bye week. I do hav a team with boyd landry and reagor as my top 3 wr (went lamar andrews and 3 rb early) and i will worry about that problem when the time comes). I hope reagor is popping by then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# pollard getting carries for cowboys to start things off so mccarthy doing what he can to help your pollard bb shares.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ah damn that sucks. There should be legal action someone should be able to take if it is an american company doing that. I am not a lawyer though so maybe there are laws to prevent that. Thanks for the respons. I did subscribe to your youtube channel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# dd you fade mike evans in showdown if so you really are an oracle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i think wash pass rush might get to burrow quickly so it might be more of a boyd game. I think for 1 more week you do m thomas but if you rather do higgins i understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# if rivera is trying to tank to get to 1-15 i applaud the decision. The nfc east winner will not win the superbowl and will prob suffer  a first round home playoff loss so no need to fight for a worthless playoff birth and take the forward thinking move and play for 1-15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# if higbee just has ertz season last season at his draft day cost that is value. Is there a change higbee goes back to just a 250 yard te? i mean i guess but the offense seem to run way better at end of season and higbee looked like prime gronk to my eye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i voted for trump twice but for once obama and i agree on something. We do not need to defund the police we need better more efficient policing by making it a better career to get into with a better pool of job applicants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i do believe arthur smith is a future head coach but steelers got the best D in the nfl.  If arthur smith is smart he waits for that chargers head coaching job to open and do not jump at that shitty jets job. save that for matt patricia and let adam gase go to detroit lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# i hate to be that guy but does rb win when some people started kamara ceh (preoptout) carson. Imagine taking a worthless michael thomas in round1. (worthless so far). Odell had 1 great game. Juju in the 3rd or 4th round so far had week 1 and nothing else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Austin won kotr 1996 and gave the promo of a lifetime. WWE then squandred him facing an out of shape yoko at summerslam. I do think bret helped steve austin keep the seat warm in a upper level mid card feud that still resonates 23 years later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# just got him at 509 in a bestball over the weekend and feel great about it. Took at 303 in late june (a severe reach I know but i did not think he would make it back to me at 410 and I wanted him as my rb2. I still got gallup and metcalf as my 2 top wr anyways who I love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# buy the 2 high priced rb that you enjoy fade the 16 highest priced wr get chark and metcalf do not be afraid to have a bench of 1 to 3 dollar players cause that is what waivers is for. It is looking more and more like 2020 ekeler is going to be ronald jones #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# no those were peaceful protestors going into target and taking everything thos were not rioters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# kenny stills is my late round crush i keep drafting as a bet against fuller staying healthy. i also just did a drafters draft with kelce and mark andrews which is prob way -ev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# it is not like the rock is ever coming back full time anyways. There is a place for a big girl that is a safe worker but she  is not it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# bloomberg lit 500 million dollars on fire to show his love for america]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# ceh has had 2 weeks out of 5 and the other 3 weeks have been miserable. if you rather have ceh over chubb ros with the time share of darrell williams and tyreek and kelce being the focus of the offense well ok but chubb and hunt are the engine of the browns offense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# good thing i started beckham over will fuller #HASHTAG# I almost benched beckham too but i was too stupid to do i sat juju for mvs in a few other leagues and that worked out wonderfully]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# yes alshon is cooked he had a good run but its over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# not good for my miles boykin and devin duneray bestball shares.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# this was obvious after last year. even at his cheap 2020 draft day price i rather go rb early and hit wr in his range.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i get holding jared cook in myffpc because trautman did nothing this past sunday and cook does have top 6 weeks in his range of outcomes. I could not see dropping jamal williams right now. after the game he just had and is 1 aj ones injury away from being a real thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# sometimes life is not fair. be happy you have kamara ajones carson fuller metcalf claypool j jefferson in your other league with qb tanneyhill and te darren fells]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have ceh cmac j taylor dobbins in a 12 team league and crap wr like ruggs and laviska as my top 2 wr and i am still targeting hines (snell and malcom brown are already taken). This was an auction team where i had to pay up for cmac ceh and jtaylor on yahoo hence my wr being meh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i would bitch out and cuff dalvin with matison and later on mike boone. i am doing  25 dollar best ball on fantasy underdog slow draft right now i started miles godwin lamar woods (over kupp) and waiting on my 5th rounder. i refuse to take david johnson as my rb2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# it depends on who the cowboys get to replace dak (when that time comes). He was a great round 4 find to replace romo. Maybe cowboys can do it again when the time comes. Sometimes franchises get lucky like packers going from favre to arod and 49ers montana to young.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# eagles rather pick 6th than 9th. I understand that logic. Winning the game does not ensure a playoff appearance. They ensure hurts does not tear an acl in the final quarter of a meaningless game. You should be happy dallas lost also the win today would have been for nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# just the kind of news july mostert owners want to hear lol. At least i have limited shares and picked up mckinnon on waivers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Jerry Jones needs that money to pay Dak. I hope you understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# after demarcus robinson not coming down with that end zone catch you would think hardman would get more chances starting next week. He is a tough hold for redraft even in 12 team leagues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Naomi got to go get clarence mason to sue on her behalf for the treatment of her.I miss clarence mason. He is an amazing intellignt attorney. Also as good as stephen p new.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# all the girls say he is pretty fly for a ty guy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# star wars episodes 7 thru 9

the female ghostbusters

the last few seasons of game of thrones

sam darnold as an nfl qb
carson wentz as an nfl qb

matt patricia as a coach of even a pee wee football team
(can also include gase, lynn, mccarthy, obrien, dan quinn)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# he smiled because he has a thing for bianca and wanted montez taken out. Everyone knows the real money is in a montez vs dawkins feud where he paid vegas to poison ford so that maybe 7 of the viewers that are left will give a crap about a ford vs dawkins feud lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ok just ignore that ship of ventilators trump sent to cuomo or ventilators that were not even used because cuomo was too stupid to make the calls to get them set up for use. Yes everything is pence and trumps fault]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# this is why you can not do bestball until the day before the season starts davis #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I only have kelce at te. Prob a major risk but the te on waivers are all trash anyways. perhaps i should have cuffed him with ricky seals jones but i am feeling frisky. also looks like i will win my week 13 matchup so i get to do 4 fbg teams in 2021 #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i never expected 19 tds again but those jamal williams tds are pretty painful as an ajones owner. still it could be worse you could have a share of cmac saquon zeke etc and now even kamara is in some kind of hell hole timshare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So glad I cuffed with gurley with john kelly the past few weeks. #HASHTAG# Also so lovely that cj anderson is being used against me as a gurley owner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# carson going down today could be for a while. Now people start dumping faab on hyde if he is unowned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i have malcom brown in the 18th and snell in the 15th with kamara lamar andrews. Now the bad news. WR1 boyd wr2 landry lol. Got reagor boykin stills renfrow on my bench. Also i took the malcom brown cuff cam akers in round 4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I hope biden picks her she will be a wonderful choice that will unite america forever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yes because it was his fault cuomo sent people with covid back into nursing homes instead of cutting a deal with motels to house covid patients for property tax relief. But yes all of it is trumps fault.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# where is the 54 yard te for the packers 4th te in your projections? And you call yourself an expert. What a joke you are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yes gavin newsom and other politicans go out and fucking crickets from you bill? So sad. Also do more politicial chatter on your show and less comedy. You are good at directing a conversation but your monologues are painfully unfunny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# in dk bestball fuller is always there for me in round 8 (well in my 2 dk bestball that i have done so far)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# before week 1 i dropped fant for herndon in a 100 dollar league. I cry about it every day. I never even gave fant a chance. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# a few weeks ago i hated not buying him on myffpc but a few weeks later i am glad he is not on my roster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# julio going to end with 13 dk points prob #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# and you are an expert how could you not predict this? Are yo even good at your job? Even God in Heaven right now is l ooking down and saying nope I did not see that one coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# davismattek is his username and i am not joking. I did a bestball with him about a month ago. He is friendly and will chat in the chat some.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# miles sanders can be the devonta freeman boston scott can be the atlanta tevin coleman and both investors can party like it is 2016.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# good thing i started minshew over him in replacement of cam #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If Eli gets to go in the hof so does matt ryan. I am not a falcons fan either i am fan of the redskins but it is not matt ryan fault he plays for a dumb organization that does not know how to draft o line or dline. Without matt ryan they are the crappy version of the browns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# all this sutton talk in 505 why no worries about his game logs with drew lock at his qb? he had 1 good game out of 5. most of his good games were with flacco. Is this not a concern? Metcalf was the pick for you imo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i have so much 7th round in bestball and regret not taking him in 6th in spots where he did not fall to me in round 7.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That really is the cherry on the top of this amazing promo. The look on hayes face I have to think was improvised. He is such an underrated commentator/interviewer from back then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# got an underdog bb team with metcalf claypool higgins juju diontae pittman ruined by olsen and herndon at TE #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# IF you think tonight was bad you should have seen the starless raw after mania raw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# imo murray needs a kamara injury to do anything of note. If you are a non kamara owner i would not bother with lat murray. Also do not forget about duke johnson as a bet against david johnson staying healthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I know its early but week 1 i feel your wr2 should be djax. He has been a week 1 killer past few years for tampa and eagles. May as well go for the trifecta. I think you so with your rb3 hunt and higbee in the flex week1. You could make a case for e sanders also.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# seriously i benched juju in a 12 team league today for michael gallup. I dare say juju is droppable in 10 team leagues. Maybe juju has 3 spike weeks ros but good luck guessing when they come. in yahoo dfs heshould not be priced at more than 10 dollars and i am not kidding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# your projections did not have him for a td. Shame on you mike. The nerve to not have the 5th texans wr who prob has not seen 50 snaps all year for a td. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# britney and rachel either would have been great replacements over danielle donato briones. I was talking about hayden being a former winner. I also rather have steve in there over ian to fill the former winner nerd quota.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# thanks to the nfl for the boring ass goff vs brady super bowl because they screwed the saints on that bull shit no pi call in the nfc title game a few years back. For the record i am not even a saints fan I am a fan of the redskins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# dont say such shit i got him in at rb with big ben diontae claypool so i need carson to get a 30 burger to advance on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# any time you can find the gm who drafted first round nfl bust for years you got to do it. His only good first rounder his last 5 years with the giants was odell and smart teams can find stud wrs rounds 2 thru 6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# absolutely disgusting he only gave away 200 turkeys. You would think the money he has made he could have handed out 205 turkeys. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yes but i rather go try and hunt for a guy in his mid 40s. I would give jamey chadwell the job in a new york second and give him 4 years. No matter who you bring in it is a 4 year mininum hire. I say chadwell if i got to make the decision and he would take the job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I better see a 4 rb start or you guys are such fish. Just grab laviska reagor lamb hurst with your 4 rb and coast to the championship. If you get first overall grab minshew early so you drink that 1850 dollar case of beer being offered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Crazy how many people do not understand when you draft you draft for upside and swing for the fence. For a 14 teamer I think he did great. Care to come join my 10 dollar auction superflex at 830 pm eastern? if so email me sylarisyourhero#USER#.com leaguesafe for payments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# if you look at matt harmon reception perception kupp can not beat press coverage (maybe because of his injury coming off the acl) so he can not be an outside wr. Also keep in mind rams have not extended kupp yet. Josh REynolds could be the darkhorse for 1000yards and 6 tds]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>