<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[it just reminds me of this time Joe Gittleman got a tour bus door for me.  is this why Asian women rarely marry rock stars?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yas like don't believe your doctor that hospitals are safe unless they're hospitals that Mark Hoppus is the chairman of.  There are real nice ones in Cincinnati and LA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why is it disgusting when people smoke though?  i naturally found aromatic cigars to be weird because when someone smokes them they say you never understand what is going on and all these blonde women were raped at a cuban party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i altogether stopped going when they said she was in creepers again doing that weird thing like stalking blonde women.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks is nothing more or less than friends who go to work who love each other.  Until we build teams to fight the caffeine neitzch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oh my God how sad Kathungphane's heathen knew me and I knew Shaun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[someone would admit to doing that but there is tons of things to admit to as i sit listening to her.  not to me did that thing happen entirely.  i thought it was her dad as usual looking for ways to wake me up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Checkout this super cool prize I won on Clawee - A Real Claw Machine. Watch the video!
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i always wondered if that noise were my mom fighting for her life.  i mean if we were the only two how are fumes not real??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[she doesn't hang out with anyone cool...naturally i was wondering if she had hard times socializing because i talked to her vietnamese friend who lived in golden hill and she told me that it's a johnny pandora.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[then someone got worse and i naturally wondered why it did that thing like when she bleaches her hair she starts doing this thing that girl does like says look right there what made you mad when i asked someone who sees straight through sweat and he told me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i ate vegan fudge and drank tea breakfast was toast but i got into smoothie bowls and chia seeds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes i kept telling the officer that the woman is hitting me and the officer didn't see anyone or admit that thing was a crisis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't really mess with april though she considered me a rock star and phoned for emergency help.  she got dressed as marilyn monroe one year saying that she was going to liberate japanese eskimos.  have you met her cousin from Richardson?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that's all i meant though that if someone went somewhere they can bring something back.  if i brought back vegetables someone naturally living within lieu of muslim women who is a protestant lutheran trans it just means they rarely understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[then you just start understanding that she lost that guy's kid in Texas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes like that guy made me want a marlboro light that someone understood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like the studious aspect of not complaining but he detected some odd mental disorder about food.  When I didn't eat in 1994 for 5 months my parents thought I was scared of food poisoning.  I don't eat terribly much when it gets cold out unless it's beef stew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it just makes more sense i am more loving than my own husband.  my bff and i sit around and talk about that thing and i kind of wondered why when i knew about the thirst trap they paid me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i did guess 11...certainly not 12.  mr. cute foot...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cause in an alcoholics form since ava saw an alcoholic when cubans open cabinets it's to show them naked photos of their mother since cuban guys can't stand blonde women.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[little kids just needed to understand if mark wanted to smoke in school he wanted too.  if i didn't want to get along with one of the teen moms at school i didn't have to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diva, Queen and Makeup extraordinaire RuPaul!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why didn't they both rape me their styles are the same that's what i see them doing but i can't understand how much male plasty they've gotten.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[they removed the :-X that was my hole is shut face but i'll take the shameful hole is shut face]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's the general style of people who listen to slipknot.  yes like jeannie but worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that's what anglophilia is though?  i think arabian woman like souhair are really loopy and crazy for saying their patients have PTSD when they're getting abused.  I never knew Jeannie had anglophilia though like one minute you're okay the next you're not.  like in a crisis?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[because she needs help saying anything to me at all but you kneow it's the influence of the mom that gets the daughter fucking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[giving birth in a luxury chair to someone you love is very normal.  i wonder where cailin was delivered i kept seeing blonde women smoking crack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes he didn't come up to me or anything like that i assumed he really needed affection because i was walking to the store one day and that old man came up to me and held my hand.  he was very casual and said he would be right back and i thought he meant he was scared of STDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's because my mother has never gone thorough birth, in asian women just give birth because they are able to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i figured roger could help april with her doing time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Herrera does not discriminate against the Jewish survivors of Normandy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tweeting too much my kid is on hold.  why would nathan give me tre cool's son to carry though?  it gets really confusing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm pretty sure my husband gave in to how sick my mind is and ended up sleeping with roger's daughter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when they couldn't figure out kyeoong's parkinson's disease the mother asked me to find french doctors.  a wabakanashita]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[jewish people never grow up anyway since sheena's cousin from the synagogue considers me the "new girl" that jewish guy dates an iraqi woman but her nose is busted open it could be jewish too maybe he just wants to make himself and his schnazz look good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i don't really wear designer things i am not sure what it's like to die for a vietnamese woman in gucci.  is it in the pedicure like it is for african women?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[probably from me ignoring her mother in law so bad.  if she's a mute i assume hearing her talk is just hearing a voice inside my head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sometimes i wonder if all of that state they're from is strictly online dating and needed to meet a phone sex operator in person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if that girl and Laura are friends still...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MGK flew out of John Glenn, may god bless the paparazzo's use of the airport lighting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is just talking about women in general not just because they're muslims.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[green hat guy obsession has turned into an obsession with sailor suit guy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you didn't see how it lit up my eyes with glow sticks that Adam knew Mark but I mist have just missed and loved him.  Adam even hangs out with that guy in that band.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that's so sad the entire town calls the pham's fobs.  like she started talking to high school students and thought she knew them.  in her religion is she really 15?  like at a rate that fits the mold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[joe king should act in movies is what i meant the guy is a theatrical actor where you'd never think twice about what kind of man it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes how they begin acting the same and we all laugh.  the big san antonio ghetto booty heard around the nation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[not normally would i eat birria but it's good in washington, the adobada sometimes runs all over the birria and they tinga the peppers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the mother of twins buys more for the boy than the girl is why and she said "their family" and I kept wondering what Connie was doing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i always have to pay attention to her response she doesn't say anything awful about him but you can kind of see she has an issue with him.  it just meant sometimes not all the time  unless she physically says she hates him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young homosexual men on the strip.  So many queens you'd think 702 was Britain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes i read a cue card and it was funny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes like my mother is a huge asian shinkansen wreck.  you don't want the kind of asian women who are shinkansens the virtuous ones are carnival cruises or viking cruiselines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i sued ashley's mother because it meant that ashley was half cherokee.  ashley is full blooded cherokee native american who had an unstable mother who would not provide housing for her kids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[making people laugh while at a urinal is standup comedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sometimes i think the pandemic is the apocalypse then i remembered the old biblical tale that when God lost his virginity fire was set to our utopia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[young love is just a game

a game of Russian Roulette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that's very sweet but my husband is only my husband in my bedroom we don't really engage in normal american things because he doesn't like when i drive with him so i do what i do in all relationships, hitchhike.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[rarely i'm usually just baking or drawing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[but yes just start starving people and locking them in rooms without food.  if they whine then whip them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm about to shovel the snow outside and make a natural pina colada.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nicole and i lived in a crackhouse with a reverend from zimbabwe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[then the person talks about wiping your ass with baby wipes and i began wondering why she said that thing.  i still recognize that the person in that thing is katie though.  like katie from a nice school.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i thought a nice office where most 18 year olds from the suburbs work.  she worked at a restaurant she was like Chinese but never talked with the local Chinese people which is weird.  Chinese people aren't Muslim is why when shit goes wrong with south asian muslims i sought China]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i can feel my ass getting fatter as i sit here on twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[jewish altogether is really bad.  trying to find something with kitty pepper in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[because how would a child that didn't have a dad even eat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[we are mean to that little girl though...because why doesn't she blend into the family?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you have to get the north face sandals though and argue with the jewish and japanese.  one says size 10 the other size 11.  if the smaller one fits you though Adam it means you don't eat enough.  Mark's feet do that too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sugar Cookie Latte is a genius for the anti-mochas.  Barista life is LIFE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that's so gross though i wonder who that is who asked me if i've seen that guy before i added my friend's dad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that first week you're home from having a baby and hubby doesn't understand the sexual pain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if a mom and dad posess the key instant slavery is he teaching us in nursing how to control the woman?  you can't control the rapid orange tree growth in texas where asian people go to push 9-11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the human league of people is a lot smarter than you think.  life is one giant smarty pants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'll take an onion bagel with chive cream cheese, smoked salmon, capers, and sun dried tomato.  this bagel means everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You didn't hear it right the first time, she is everything like cooks and makes herself at home and talks to us but she doesn't address that her kids are abusive does she even understand how to?  if my kid started abusing someone i would say something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ivy even eats the chiletas con dulce chamoy but doesn't with anyone.  wondering if neiko would like some.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually am on leave from Starbucks went back for a little bit while going to trigger point therapy.  so everything is fine but my right knee is thrashed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes i began laughing i wonder if she needs me to do that all the time for her before people wonder.  it was kind of interesting i said something for her then it means san diegans are right it's much better than a visual trip with her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's very creepy she has to eat so she doesn't go to concerts.  She never had the mom with the extra 10 for the weekend to dine out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes like when sheena looks at herself she can't figure out why she looks half japanese.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone tell me how I'm supposed to survive ancestry DNA test with my mom and dad.  chiletas for you chiletas for me chiletas con limon cuidado calliente azucar y lucas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes the internet is a Heathen as I restrict a heathen's profile because she hangs out with Kathungphane at something worse than TAO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[his mother isn't incredibly smart but life is a ton better.  now that i realize that name is a bad word]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes to wind it all over you mean.  what brings it in via the daughter though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i can't anymore it's never me in that room.  theoretically if someone held onto me i'd believe it but it was very hard for me to say that girl was me.  because it wasn't my husband cheated on me and told me to say it ain't so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i could wait until the end to find out what he did but when she gets the thought in her brain about who her parents are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sexual anxiety patients be like

"I'd rather be dressed than upset"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Adam and I poke our heads out of our M&amp;M shells and see the world together.  I'm being advised to travel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how funny that's just some random thing he told me about God being busy then I mind God and pray to Mary and he gets better.  What does he do that he's busy with other people.  He normally doesn't walk with anyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm so stressed about the pandemic i've eaten everything in my fridge and pantry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes it's kind of funny people talk about alpha males on twitter and this guy calls me on the phone and tells me it has to be that way that i pay him money because he has none.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i wasn't hiding jewish people i was hiding ava until the swiss were ready to meet her.  i sent her out to play all the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cherry Watermelon Gummy Lips...sealed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laughing at Adam from Big Rig...twas the night before fishing and all through the house the big blue gummy sharks were alert we were all drinking guinness draught.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all she wants is that thing and there isn't anyone who can understand how, while tricking people she was feeding them with her hands she couldn't get them to believe in edgy behavior.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes like I heard someone saying not to tell anyone where they're from and i began laughing they started fresh in Japanese because now Kyle is Filipino.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was at the mall and they opened up shop.  I walked into the container store wondering if they sell plastic urinal donation cups.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes he naturally told me all about this woman who had severe issues with vanity and trying to be humane and it ended up being she saw a way to finally be liked and it called her other dad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I learned this song and it goes like this

sheena. oh sheena.

bong queef'a

banana fana moe keesha

me my moe mischka

queefa!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the first photo is of her though yes that's cute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[april's feet are really big...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Asianality does to a white woman.  That time April and Jeannie were scissoring outside of Linh's wedding and Wendy joined.  Wendy's first lesbian experience was the eiffle tower!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[not exactly sick i realized there wasn't anyone on the phone at his house and wasn't at my house and the two called each other and we listened and it mildly made me wonder.  i deal with that thing everyday too though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[george michael would have been perfect for calvin klein underwear ads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[like that disease was found in someone and my bff and i liked the same guy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't seen her unless she's trying to make an appearance in my life, if I could remember her.  Don't really have any Arab relatives but my aunt's sister in law's from another marriages' son]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There wasn't any possible way the asian woman could tell me why i was meeting her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes he says very covertly that he's jewish by telling people he's italian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[barefoot in the park, resting my head on your chest under the summer sun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i didn't even add anyone i just look at my profile the way it is...when people from other schools do that thing i wonder why that thing is just a platform for people who went to school together i'm not sure how there is a way to do that thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hien is so sick of chemotherapy she looked for a way to send me in with her ID to take her place.  It's because in neurology after that Arabian woman thought I had a polarity complex I had a twin named Quoc Hong Chung.  Genocide is a cell degeneration discovered in Cambodia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Birria is better than the I need a Japanese translator if Kobe Don is a steak bown what is the bowl if it is pork because i ordered the katsu don and got ton katsu.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes even i posted a picture of my kid...and i don't really take pictures with her dad.  trying usually when i get the chance he is busy cleaning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm not sure she told me she had depression and i thought it was funny because my doctor knew what it is when someone is seasonal and gets victimized in the winter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lash extensions are a girl's best friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it smells like someone peed on everything.  i'm laughing on minute he's kissing that anglosaxan french woman the next he is cuddling with me.  is he serious like asian serious about dating or altogether in it to find out what love is?  i think he's asian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it just naturally just makes her sweat and makes her mad it's really nothing about what it is when she wishes her kids didn't exist to see if he would like her then she dropped a daughter word.  the man has a son.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My best friend from 8th grade apparently gave in and let me give Shakira to my husband and is now dating Kate Moss.  C talk.  Cuban talk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[asian muslims are really strict like catholic every dollar has to be accounted for to make sure that the vision is right to see the woman and the man.  i bought it for him but just realized she meant that she wants her japanese filipino kids even though she says she is japanese.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you see April tell her to call that number and leave a message with her name and that she's interested in the job.  it's for phone sex operating.  it will help her big toe after the manicurist made it bleed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[magic isn't a sign it means he's still studying why it does that.  i couldn't follow him very well he says really nasty things about people who do that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shaun's new boyfriend Adam maybe?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[we're just really loaded is what i meant...maybe she can gain fame in the circus for her shrinking feet fiasco.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[because one day i found out that swiss nurse hid a jewish woman in his mental ward and it came time i pay him for letting me travel to England and I was getting ready to go to his house to drop off money and realized that the jewish woman he hid was going to hold my hand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[to get into an MMB rave you have to talk to a french philosopher about witchhazel and successfully tone their man's skin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What am I going to do for Mark this Valentine's day?  Maybe I can fly in and we can go to Disneyland go on all the rides and don't even have to stand in line.  Teddy Bear guy wishes to meet Stella and the Prince for his birthday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes as always understanding he never let go of me then someone makes a confession that's her in the kitchen an i began wondering why she did that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i don't really look at it that way the person is western how can the person have issues?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[airlines need a sous chef for that in flight salmon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[asian people got involved and my mother was always wishing for a japanese filipino grand child.  they never told me to get the dress to get married i got a call from san diego that the mormon temple opened it's doors because of Josh.  My mom got me in the car and dropped me off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Name one thing you do to your starbucks red cup that you don't do to your lover?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[then does a three sixty and says she's my daughter and is a devout mormon and has 17 year old friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never really payed attention to them before I found out it's either or.  Or the entire family...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you don't have to belong to an episcopal church to eat ham for Easter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't mean to string you along, i meant to drag you...DUH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[imagine a heart of a guerilla saying YOU kind of like hien's sister telling me "you']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the scottish fold with pale eyes birthed ragdolls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine falling in love at Friday's only Robert Smith is a mozzarella stick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you know in mexican it just means we told Ryan's sister we like her but all secretly got together and started talking about her behavior of eating too much gum, not respecting mexican food, and farting in our faces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how i don't talk to people with my mom and dad and it makes it seem abnormal i greet i say hi moreso naturally interested in that girl whose best friend died in san diego]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Medicine ball from Starbucks today and mom emptied her wallet to me.  Why are Asian women so wealthy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*texan accentnn"...and a wishing you well to the homosexuals of texas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A husband is someone you can do anything with.  I just realized that guy with a son that I was dating was moreso something that happened because he had a question about Thai and I mentioned being together without reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the exchange student i lived with would wear my stuff she was a student on pot that fit the clothes of a 5th grader.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the embargo went to vietnam and there were yummy cubans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[she can't get meat from anywhere.  it's so sad she walks around like an adult and has the psychiatric periodontics of an 11 year old name Cindy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes Chris I trust you but Cincinnati issued a warning since that relationship was really high profile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[like real expressive lesbians...now i understand why God has issues with LGBTQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i kind of remember telling that girl when she thought she was a nurse just by being born filipino i hate her snobby attitude like she's vietnamese girl that goes to UCSD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nazis are that way, when i didn't have a way out of swiss takeover within the only thing pro-irish people do "work" you always have nazi parents.  all parents are nazis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marriage                                   Baking Cupcakes

              die trying to make it right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a family of all asian people and not one roger b horse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i made out with my husband for about 15 minutes as the window time for starbucks online ordering is 30-45 minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Y'all throw pumpkin spice over your shoulder and say."hail to all the blonde women in uggs"  *ahem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i could not build upon jpunk i had to build upon mexican then i found out morality and it was still intelligence and suave style.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes it's a 50 year old woman with wrinkles that talks to high school students and says she's 17.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark doesn't understand relationships at all, one day he brought this guy home who said that he had raped me before and i asked him why i couldn't see the person and began laughing he thought it meant his son could be my son because he had been to my house before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so to really do that to the mother take her breath away and speak to her in the sense if she can say it to say it with her...not an opinion of science if it is possible but to just understand baby's breathe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i never knew what that was i was kind of laughing the entire time.  really i have an opinion about tony's mother just naturally never say anything.  we're from different generations of time.  my opinion is that she's too sure when she's right that the opposing contender nails.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She believes she's being truthful when she didn't realize she is saying her way or the afghan highway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my god she's so ugly though i wonder if i have neiko's face wrong and if he's ugly too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes like he explained to me...but also i do kind of prefer red bull.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that's really odd the two guys are they queer?  someone asking me to help them with an espresso machine can comment on if he doesn't understand how to talk how he is talking, in finnish you talk about the statement towards mute women globally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dude hershyl's girlfriend is so jewish looking...hey though dude that kid he had is it theirs?  it looks just like her.  Like within the jewish community they date right?  they're not married and have a kid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i expected a huge blow and it is just some guy who at random met me and went along with me when really the power and glory of mark hoppus is when katie snuck on my bed and said they were having sex.  mark only sleeps with blonde women.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my mom and dad are both nazis because their general preference of how intelligent they like their conversation is hidden beneath having fun.  nazis are CIA intelligent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes let's help the mitchell's assist their kid into suicide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sometimes the doctor scares the crap out of me when he thinks seeing that way is haelthy, it sort of is but i lived with someone who pedicures toes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ava's room in kussumo was at something called a ski resort.  usually i just find a house and sleep in it houses are usually vacants when i go on vacation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that's news to me you could be mad at my mother, my mother never told me that the guy who followed her home from church had that issue with God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i remembered when they did figure out how to get along with veruca salt though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My husband is contrary to my belief that Valentine's Day is when our 1st grade daughter brings frosted heart cookies to her class.  I won't forget the sprinkles this time, Princess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm not sure what baby that is, miranda as a baby is usually sought after by asian women from thailand like quyen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i have a dyslexic jewish step sister that thinks blonde implies rich so she tried dying my hair black and did hers blonde not realizing bottled blondes are jewish.  bleach lightening!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i mean i hit in the back of that two seater car...is having fun i guess it just being the two of us but i didn't tell you two twins are separated from a store that has 3 businesses in one mall and i were going to find a way to sandwich myself between them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[about this time Roger's daughter stole 20 dollars from me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes it's very funny...asian people don't engage in incest and the guy introduces it to Laos and the Filipines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[but yes yes the entire world of people is Mark it's called Markopolis.  then I met a real person and began laughing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the rules of the mental hospital are what they are...alcohol makes you mental.  if you ask personal opinion someone would realistically speak with you but there is this white woman who celebrates the muslim culture and the muslim federal employment agency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so i just speak with a friend and begin laughing...it is a scary weird person it's not like people from church]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Except this one night her adopted daugher tried having sex with me wondering what I was hiding and didn't realize I was a female.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that's why it happened i think i started wondering if someone saw how our brains did that together.  best friends are the heart of kindness...for those things that people can't understand about God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes it's interesting to see hookers on crack...kindness to all but i'm not sure how she's going to pay for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes Mark sent me baby food and I was just feeding the kids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[instead of complaining i really understand it now.  still though why do people smoke crack.  dude we still have halloween candy.  it comes from unmindful Asian people.  I did understand it takes them forever to eat food they buy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wool is the earths natural itching powder.  but it's winter what can i say.  stay warm!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the idea that mom didn't understand to do something japanese and just spend and not care how much, instead i think what she did were bought the thing herself then had me handing someone money which makes it look like spending muslim asian money on that guys 39 kids is how i saw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes i remember it's this guy from the filipines who wondered if mark hoppus had a biggest fan and i began kind of wondering this thing oh well though i clicked remove not a big deal i see what happened.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kathungphane Videojeevski says she's Russian and you can't help but think Russian Orthadox Jewish when she comes to my house thinking it's her luxury cars new japanese cars and house.  Her twin sister loved my house and gave birth twice in it just to live here.  3000$ each way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes i knew he isn't sick but can't be sure of what he saw.  it would take a miracle to get the person to behave and actually act within means of showing the public of what happened.  sometimes people can it's called a prism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[she figured it out you just tell veruca salt about the person that is bothering you and they figure out how to get you back to your 100]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes some are in a world crisis of hunger he knew how to fix it and i kept wondering how world hunger is a crisis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i began laughing my work is letting me bring my cat with me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes i thought that was kourtney's cousin.  ava got routine waxing for 6 months now and wore the snow coat and looked back to herself.  like when she got waxed she looked like a model.  now she looks more like tom's daughter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it must mean it that muslim people aren't irritated by seeing.  because what does see too much see too little mean?  like he's trying to see like me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[vietnam's priorities for the catholic church is remain modest...you want someone to see you but not modesty on crack see you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[he did actually finally talk to me, chris holmes had to help me.  i mean that time he went into that room and had sex he thought i was with him and i never go in that room anymore and i had to really confess culturally if he tries that with any girl it's me.  sometimes i can't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so in lub so in lub...but where are we standing?  my eye is doing the game cube.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>