<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Please ask Modij and Nirmala Sitharaman to be realistic and think about the people who pay taxes and helping both of them draw their salary #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good the tax department has detected the black money. Now I dare #USER# to please raid Ambanis, both the brothers and Adani and Amit Shah Would be grateful to #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arre Bhai we all know MODI JI jaise economist ke samne sab fail he #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Modi is making India sweat so that India can shine like his face glows. He is giving India a Facial. Aap #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PAdma Award has been conferred on her for making illogical statements so that you and me can start talking about her instead of Chinese incursions. So if she is doing her job why would they revoke her Padma Award #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Can you answer why do Females like Pani Puri more than the males do? Always, wondered why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is Shivam Dube the youngest player in Dad's Army]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Please sing more but in private. Please do not post. Leave that to professionals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Devendra Bhai Why are you so Late, You should have had guts to do this at the time when you were the Chief Minister #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But Sir #USER# #USER# Modiji has stated that India will be USD 20-trillion economy in 2015. Why have you slashed the targets? Please see the link #URL# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must have left out something un intentionally This does not mean EVM's are faulty #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PM had to cancel the rally due to #HASHTAG# CM #USER# should give answer to the 700 odd people if not 7000 people waiting for the P M address #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul She has asked for only one word. Your tweets are encyclopedia on Marriage #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this is the reason Bajrang Dal and others are burning effigies of Santa Claus and attacking the churches and burning the religious texts #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you are desh drohi it should not be in World Record Books, instead, it should be in Limca Book of Records #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Translation Expert. We need people like him to govern us who can understand and translate English and Hindi #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# WAH MODIJI WAH #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expect a circus if you elect Jokers and animals #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No change sir Back to Square one. Now she has to reapply at NDTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We were searching for VIKAS but we found Shivaji Aurangazeb and Nehru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday was just a show off to public  that Govt Cares. Drama Team has started working over time #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The problem of short supply of vaccines is still not solved. I estimate it would ease by Aug 1 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Vowww Devendra Phadnavis looks so much of a farmer in this picture #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Khubsoorat Chehra Indeed!!! But why did he say that Khubsoorat chehra cannot be associated with Economics. Does he believe that good looking people are dumb? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Public ko Ch!@#$ya bana rahe hein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least Point No.1 has to be provided by #USER# gov or else its a useless government #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#  #USER# If govt cannot provide th correct deaths than it has no rights 2 demand taxes &amp; conduct raids #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Congratulations #USER# #HASHTAG# has Ended black money Shifted us to digital transactions Ended terrorism Ended prostitution Boosted tax collections Boosted world economy India is now a superpower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# By the way Has the DCGI released the third trial results of Covaxin. #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Rahul Dravid showing agression of a Fast Bowler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He works eighteen hours a day to ensure this ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contradictory tweet by her. Bhakts never think. Modiji thinks for them #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think on the vaccination certificate we should publish the petrol filling station guys picture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amit Shah is from RSS and they are braver than IAF. He can go to enemy country, count the dead bodies and then return back safely to India without being a POW in enemy country #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rafale papers got stolen, they did not scan and store it. Website Hacked cannot restore it because they did not back it up Good examples of #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ok we call it Wild Strain!!! but do we get any patients infected with Wild Strain any more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#à¤®à¥‹à¤¦à¥€_à¤‡à¤¸à¥à¤¤à¥€à¤«à¤¾_à¤¦à¥‹ But before doing that please announce a package for Bhakts and IT Cell #USER# because they will be out of Jobs and will lose their living #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# HE should have thought this before having rallies in Bihar and West Bengal and before allowing Kumbh melas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May be FIIs selling to fund UP elections. May be politician money was invested as FIIs money and now to fund the UP Election they are selling #HASHTAG# You never know with Cheap Chanakya on the helm #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# could be right in saying what she said i.e. BJP ke Burre din Aayenge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is due to the fact that the Gujaratis are always attracted by the US and US always shuns the Gujjus away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# thought today the whether is a bit cloudy due to bad AQI so he did a Surgical Strike]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Going by this logic a Prime Minister #USER# cannot tweet UPYOGI and biased stuff like that #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Uttar Pradesh Wallas? Reason why Mumbai is screwed up, its because of UP Wallas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please divide that GDP with Population you will get the Per Capita Income which will make India a poor third world country. Please explain this to our dearest Covidiod our Pradhan Sewak #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Jayant Agro interests me for long term Am I correct as per the charts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dont Fear Bro!!! Take a Dip !!! #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bhai you leave all this and read HANUMAN CHALISA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People attending Modi's rally are committing Suicide #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Modiji is very cute. Terrorists must be scared of him now #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you nuts. You don't recognize the significance of the name change? GDP rose 1% due to the name change. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Chaapluusi !!! Vaccine Researched by Oxford University of UK. Manufactured by Private company in India We have to give credit to #USER# and #USER# and not give any credit to #USER# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sir I nominate you as the Prime minister instead of #USER#  ji #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tum Chup hi Raho Uncle. Tumhara muh nahin gutter hey. #HASHTAG# The PM #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Madam Covishield has Efficacy of 70% Covaxin is 81% but it looks like Election Rallies have 100% Efficacy #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abki Baar Modi Sarkar . India still searching options of Narendra Modi in its huge population of 130 Crores. Even Chetan Bhagat will do a better job than Modi #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I am a Jain too. I am not hurt by what #USER# has said. But hurt by the fact and the act of Cowardice by the Jain boy who has to eat a Kathi Kabab on Ahmedabad street hiding himself. No guts to fight the society for what he likes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# By the way what happened to that PATANJALI wala Whatsapp KIMBHO or something like that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He can sue them u/s 138 of the negotiable instruments act and get double the amount #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kudos to Subramaniam Swamy #USER# for not including #USER#  name in the list]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dont want to hear from BHAKTS in response that she was doing a sting operation #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Give Credit where it is due, 2014 se Entertainment ki koi kami hone nahin dee KAKA ne. He has introduced so many great actors and actresses to the mainstream who keep on playing cameos and keep entertaining us #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adani should also be summoned like Twitter, Facebook officials were summoned for the posts of its users #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is because Rioters are governing UP and they are in opposition in Maharashtra. Hope you dumb Bhakt get the point #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sir Guruji had said we will be 20 trillion economy #URL# HERE IS THE PROOF #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live in Two Indias were PM addresses a massive gathering and in the evening chairs a meeting on threat from Omicron #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Laughable indeed #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember !!! Prime Minister is the boss !!! He can do anything, is that clear. Like aaj se 500 aur hazar ke note band kal se GST shuru. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Misreporting is the way India functions since ages. We do not have the accurate to point population figure. This #USER# govt has further worsened the Misreporting in India. We are misreporting everything from Economy to population to mortality to almost everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's a good counter thought to #USER# views]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear #USER# Please see BJP Leaders Wife is celebrating Valentines. Please take quick action CC #USER# #USER# Fyi #USER# #USER# #USER# Please make a cartoon on this #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Let's hope Banaras realises it's mistake and kicks him out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes they should apologies for hurling eggs on Naveen Patnaik #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# If they don't apologize then #USER# should be called Hooligan Party of Bharat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Saw you in the morning walking alongside water]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# For inventing the Vaccines and then manufacturing them for us and then administering them on us #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# Sarah Gilbert, Serum and HCW have done nothing #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Was it even required when the entire earlier and new pack is a deck full of Jokers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I learned long ago, never to wrestle with a pig. You get dirty, and besides, the pig likes it.

George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Since, as per the PM office Health is a state subject, can we have the permission for the  third shot i.e. booster shot in Maharastra. You can classify it as a paid shot. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kind Attention dear Bhakts Please do not use Cow Dung and Cow Urine #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Mr.Bobade Please pass the judgment after seeing this picture #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I think time has come for #USER# and its workers #USER# and #USER# and #USER# to start working hard on HINDUTVA or change tracks into something else, may be HINDUTVA is not working anymore #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Modi's student. Modi is the head master of such gimmicks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The state of Affairs of Gujarat are pathetic indeed #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope the history of #USER# does not repeat if   #à¤ªà¤¹à¤²à¤¾_à¤Ÿà¥€à¤•à¤¾_à¤®à¥‹à¤¦à¥€_à¤•à¥‹ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Name Change is ok but what about Fuel Prices #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He cannot become next FM. Current Qualification for FM in India are a) No knowledge of Economics b) No knowledge of Business inspite of this a lot of high headedness. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now Didi after Babul Supriyo and other leaders joining TMC after quitting BJP is saying #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Also wonder was #USER# sleeping when  he was the CM. Why didn't he raise all this with the police/cbi/ed/cid and other agencies to probe #USER#  I think Dev is trying to eat more than he could digest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And after getting elected the Lion did not give the shawl and told all the SHEEPS that Promise to give everyone a Shawl was a Chunavi Jumlaa #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter has not banned Free Speech They have banned Free spread of Lies Y r people like #USER# #USER#  #USER# are upset, could be next in line #USER#  #USER# Twitter has got guts. Imagine Airtel Blocking Modiji's Phone? Can it happen in India? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The current one is the mistake of Shri Atal Bihari Vajpayee the former Prime Minister of India]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# But what difference does it makes Dear Bhakts and Trolls. Lets see how correct and robust is investigation is    and whether it stands on its own in the courts Sameet you guys go to any extent fighting for useless things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No She is Union Minister Handling affairs of the insignificant Gandhi Family]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Living in the past glory. Always bragging that we were too great in the past. We were a golden sparrow in the past]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dear #USER# Please start talking about ACCHE DIN and show PC that you are not scared and you have 56 inch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Kumar Mangalam Birla and India should thank Mukesh Ambani and Indian Govt for the MESS in Telecom Sector. Mukesh and govt has shown the way how to kill jobs, decrease tax revenues, increase Bank NPA and kill an entire booming sector for personal gains #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paagal Aadmi, Like Shuking the oxygen via turbine and making oxygen from nulla #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Modi did research of ChAdOx1 Vaccine, Sarah Gilbert did not do. Modi is producing them in his factory &amp; not #USER# of #USER# Modi is the Vishwaguru &amp; distributing Vaccine globally at Cost &amp; not #USER# Does this make u happy Dumb Modi Bhakt #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Central Banks are the biggest Manipulators. They need to be shot down. They are against the Free Market Economy #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Woh toh Vibrator use karke #HASHTAG# hey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# She contracted Covid-19 ten days after taking the much acclaimed and tested by #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then what is Amit Shah's Number? 4 or 2 or zero or all to gether? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Inspite of so much Yoga they are unable to shed their weight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sir #USER#  Any updates on #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Spyware #USER# #USER# Not tagging Amit Shah because he is of no use]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW INDIA !! Gau Mata Playing Football #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arre tooo Driver hey ki Screwdriver #USER# Faltu Ghumate hi rehta hey #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Modiji where is the Mask?

Gomosa from Assam!!! Nurse administering the Vaccine from Pondichery!!!

Is the female standing behind is from West Bengal?

#USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just a few days back and You seem to be a Foolish Bhakt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Truly its Kalyug where #USER# A Monk needs to keep a revolver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# If Indian Rupee falls further say 1 USD equals 150, then soon India will boast of its 5 trillion economy with absolutely no value. The comparison of growth should be based on Per Capital Income #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After seeing the faces of the below four people, I am convinced that India is a land of Snake charmers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think #USER# and #USER# are well versed in reading this below. Its in Gujarati. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He has done so much today for commerce today by adding MAHARAJ great going #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is FM suffering from ADHD. Can't she see the trending topic #HASHTAG# and take action on it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We know the Bhakts are hutiya !!! There is nothing like Samjha hey kya!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Has he taken this decision all alone (Dictatorship) or collectively in the Cabinet Meeting (Democracy) #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Arnab was the one who gave the weather report to gobhiji before balakot #USER# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doubters would doubt and Haters would Hate. But with this Modiji has created History #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That too without peer reviewed phase 3 results. Ample proof that Modi Govt does not care at all. They are more interested in Drama #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# all world leaders attending summit for climate change and protecting environment have themselves polluted environment by reaching Glasgow by Air Planes #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maharashtra pays highest Income tax and gets least vaccines and the most pampered state Uttar Pradesh pays lowest income tax and gets most Vaccines. Shame on #USER# and #USER# for playing politics over health of people #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Imagine Modi alongwith his peacock jumping in the sea or imagine Modi and Amit shah jumping. Would be hilarious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But then why is #USER# importing it. You must respect #USER# flagging the shortcomings and desire for help and if possible help and you #USER#  #USER#()L# to stop poiltics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any Disclosure on the bad name generated in India for the project on Income Tax #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wah #USER# Amazing Insight between #USER# and Congress. We are blessed to have such union ministers Please make a note #USER# And bhakts please dont like this this is This has been stated since bhakts do not understand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FYI #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# MLA is a peoples representative and if a govt employee not working properly than this is people taking action #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She should go to the High court with same enthusiasm as she has gone to the Basket Ball Court]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But the Airport Contract of Jewar Airport will go to Adani, guaranteed #USER# do you agree #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Dada is Modi Stress free or Stressed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voww!!! Modiji, you deserve a Bharat Ratna for cancelling West Bengal Visit #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#HealthDept #USER#PHD #USER# Then For your benefit and if it solves India's problem of Covid-19 then Narendra Modi is #à¤­à¤¾à¤°à¤¤_à¤•à¤¾_à¤µà¥€à¤°_à¤ªà¥à¤¤à¥à¤°_à¤®à¥‹à¤¦à¥€ Happy now!!! But do remember Modi has fooled the nation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Modi is not wearing a Mask from so many months. Modi is a pioneer in ending all Covid Restrictions. What Modi does world follows #HASHTAG# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dwarikesh Looks likely to score a century in an year or two]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# After giving refund of USD 1 Billion dollars to Cairn #USER# govt should be shown in negative here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In between we had other very important tasks in hand like #HASHTAG# elections and #HASHTAG# Transaction of buying the #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# EVM Chor hey yeh log. These jokers have not been chosen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# can any one please tell both of them to light candles to fight Corona #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sameer Wankhede you are seizing very small quantities. You already missed the Mundra port seizure #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So can we conclude that both COVISHIELD and COVAXIN are unapproved doses #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then why dont they increase the Trollers remuneration from Rs.2/- per troll. Their remuneration is stuck at those  levels from quite some time #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Par aapne order karne mein bahut der kar di. UK USA Canada waale November mein order kar diya tha. Pehle aapne Vaccine purchase centralize kiya then In the month of May you decentralized. Very Very poor managment!!! Disappointed #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Then Arrest them, like #USER# govt arrested the people involved in 2G Scam and the way Vinod Rai issued an apology. #HASHTAG# #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake Govt, Fakeer Govt = MODI and YOGI Govt #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With love to #USER# #USER# #USER# and respected shri #USER# We know we are fools to buy whatever you utter. We are the Bhakt community. #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Do we have to pay for the proposed concert during a Traffic Jam #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then who will go to Galwan? Godi Media makes such a hue and cry about #USER# going on some personal visit, why is it silent on this #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yati Narsingh was born on 29th February, so he is definitely below 18 #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because when other countries were preordering vaccines #USER# govt and #USER# were sleeping or preparing for the Bihar and West Bengal and other elections.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# UP walas have screwed up my Mumbai. You guys go back to YOGI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There is such an important UP Elections is going on for this govt and in the middle of all this Why did PUTIN start this war]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bahut Der Kar di Huzoor Aate Aate. #USER# elected in 2014 and now its 2022. Was #USER# govt in deep sleep. All this is just to divert opinion. Nothing will come out. Everyone is hand in glove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He cancelled because third trial numbers are not released #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We should ask the Queen to renew the lease, since we are good tenants and we are paying rent on time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No wonder plastic surgery and internet existed in ancient times #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Funny is this govt. 
If anything goes right Modiji takes credit. 
Any question on Modi Govt, Rahul Gandhi has to Answer and 
Any shortcoming of the Modi Govt, Nehru is responsible
#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is called System Evolution. This is not because of Narendra Modi or any one else from this govt. or previous govt. Its like a just born does not know how to walk and after some time he learns to walk. So Stop being a foolish Andh Bhakt #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Modiji, please take action against Nirmala sithaRAAVAN. She has stopped being VOCAL FOR LOCAL. She is presenting a paperless budget instead of KHATTA BAHI #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#à¤°à¤¾à¤·à¥à¤Ÿà¥à¤°à¥€à¤¯_à¤ªà¤¶à¥_à¤—à¥Œ_à¤®à¤¾à¤¤à¤¾ the Rastrapita is a Bail (bull)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# peer reviewed research papers for Covaxin and Zy cov Stop fooling the nation #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Cunning would be the right word not intelligent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Bhai, All the work of Cooking Driving Secretary ship and Photography is done by him alone à¤¶à¤¿à¤µà¤¾ à¤—à¥‹à¤‚à¤¡. He is overworked, please hire a few more people you cannot be so cruel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes I have seen the dogs barking in rallies of BJP leaders in Bengal Shouting Didi O Didi #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this proves that LAATON KE BHOOT ( #USER# Govt) BAATON SE NAHIN MANTE #HASHTAG# by issuing circular right now #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This govt and ICMR needs to test their brains]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dear #USER# #USER# whether online will also continue or only offline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But there would be How many Calories in that Vaccine? #USER# Asking for the calories counters #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Apart from Modiji everything is bad in India - A Bhakt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May be the Vaccines are three dose Vaccines and not Two doses. So lets count only the people who are triple vaccinated as Fully Vaccinated and the Double Vaccinanted as partially vaccinated #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Please #USER# Please push both gujaratis out Please #USER# Please speak to #USER# Save the country please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Savio, dont ever never shift your loyalties to either #USER# or #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May be due to this ban of Non Veg Stalls in Gujarat on Main Roads, the side roads would become the Main Roads in the future, you never know #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But why were you sitting on this huge pile of refunds. Were you waiting for covid 19?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sir If the doctor has qualified through SC/ST quota?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Can't you read he is praising Modi and you don't like]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please also mention the greatest of all the economist who is heading the #USER# now None other than #USER# who supported the #HASHTAG# and poor fellow also had to justify by giving such silly excuses #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bang your head on a wall as Chaddiwala with no brains are ruling India #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For your learning #USER# Please share it with other Andh Bhakts #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They are more bothered  about Rahul Gandhi going abroad #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good Effort by #USER# in filing so many returns #HASHTAG#. You will be showered with choicest Abuse and expletives if you do not #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations #USER# I still remember your best innings. You scored 34 not out in our gully cricket match and we won the match. This was the turning point of your career and you are the BCCI Secretary now #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Indian People are proud because 5000 years ago we were very rich and were called Sone ki Chidiya. Nobody thinks what India is now. And Modi is exploiting this mentality by triggering the past all the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Vowww Devendra Phadnavis looks so much of a farmer in this picture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why has Kim Jong-un lost so much weight? Please update External Affairs Minister #USER# ðŸ˜€ðŸ˜€ðŸ˜€ðŸ˜€ðŸ˜€ðŸ˜ƒ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thank your stars You have not been arrested under sedition Modi Sarkar ki Jai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#à¤®à¥‹à¤¦à¥€_à¤œà¤¹à¤¾à¤‚_à¤¸à¤°à¥à¤µà¤¨à¤¾à¤¶_à¤µà¤¹à¤¾à¤‚ But Uttar Pradesh CM is #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two great economists are discussing. Please do not disturb #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Did the Singapore PM has said anything wrong? Why are we in a denial mode? #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# How can you expect sense in financial matters from a History graduate guided by Fake Degree holders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still you are sedating inspite of a chargesheet HA Ha #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking at the crowds in UP #USER# 's #USER# 's and #USER# 's Rallies, one thing is sure #USER# has not been able to give employment to the people of UP #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Country is supporting them since they have shown guts to screw up this govt. Dushman ka Dushman Dost hota hey #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FYI #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# He deserves Nobel Prize in Medicine or atleast Bharat Ratna #USER# Isn't it #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Note: These stunts r performed by trained professionals, U don't try #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's time Twitter asks through people of India to remove GOI #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is #USER# govt responsible for these things after 2014 or its #USER# Nehru's Mistake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is he the Official Camera man, who accompanies the PM ? If yes, than this guy is silently doing a great job. Giving credit where it is due]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oxygen Scam. THis is new kind of a scam #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If the economy is not doing good - Solution is to do another surgical strike #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Supreme court can stay the entire law passed by the parliament. High court cannot overrule a govt department. Strange things happening in New India. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those 4 hours are the only time when India Progresses. He should sleep more and let India progress #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No UP Model is best. Where people have to throw the dead bodies on the river banks #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now the Govt's Drama against #HASHTAG# is over. Its now turn of SitaRAAVAN to do drama over #HASHTAG# by Minister overriding CBDT and extending and get some brownie points #USER# If she does otherwise than we are sorry to have such a minister #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Everybody in the world has  been waiting for a lifetime for 30th February #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# For Mild to Moderate Symptoms #USER# should have Gaumutra if the symptoms are severe than Coronil will work #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This Gentlemen in the picture can twist the facts and numbers as per his whims and fancies, that is the reason people call him #HASHTAG#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>