<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Seeing as how one race is disproportionately targeted and KILLED WHILE UNARMED by another race, then I'd have to respectfully tell you that you're full of fucking shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But gay marriage ruins the family... #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My grandpa, WW2 Army Air Force, told us that a diagonal swastika was a "swastika for morons" ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think we need to talk.
You might want to sit down... ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# By his logic, they also didn't intend for the last 37 to become states, either.
What a fucking idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You literally just made yourself an example of "toxicity", genius.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# NOW you're worried about Russia? ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Those eyes...
Must...
Obey...
Buford... ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Um, ice cubes? Duh! ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# He could have said, "I'm going to be an asshole", "I'm going to act like a dick", but no, he has to say, "imma start beating ass".
Dude, don't defend that shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, that's not normal. I'm from Illinois, have lived in Longview, TX, so I can say that with confidence!! ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What a stupid question. Not that it matters, if we can't afford it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's not the hogs, it's the corporate greed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pete Davidson: genetics &amp; diet
Joe Rogan: hgh &amp; trt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Damn, that is *savage*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It takes about 15 minutes of exposure at -15Â°F for hypothermia to start setting in, FYI.
- former EMT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I would never actually eat this abomination.
I was being a 12-year-old. Re-read my previous tweet, with a Boston accent. ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think your current profile pic is very...
"Colorful" ðŸ˜â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Or kids, birds, etc... ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They don't care. They know she really didn't, but they *want* to believe that she did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# As an asthmatic, with chronic pain that raises my blood pressure to stroke levels, I cannot agree more. I'd literally die without it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# People can be freakin' weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Reminder for some:
Sober doesn't mean teetotaler, or not an alcoholic, it literally means "not affected by alcohol; not drunk" (M-W dictionary)
It's not exclusionary, or derogatory, it's complimentary. ðŸ˜‰ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Heterosexual white men, so underrepresented... nI mean, we're like, 25% of the population, and we're only featured in like 75% of media, and 65% in government. nI feel so marginalized... n#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I agree with your point, I really do...
But, "pubic sentiment" is the greatest typo in the history of autocorrect!! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because most bosses are colossal morons, who are horrifically unqualified, and only have their jobs due to cronyism or nepotism?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Have you tried a fan? A/C? ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The poisonings, window falls, and financial crimes were okay, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're in the USA, so yeah... ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I could stick spoons to my nose 35 years before the pandemic. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Okay then. ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I make mine do that, when I'm bored and fidgety ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# BREAKING: 
Mark Hamill continues to prove that he is a national treasure!! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Suicidal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Delete your account]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Megan Rapinoe has an Olympic Gold Metal.
You were born with a silver spoon in your mouth.
She will always be better than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hang in there, bro!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# All in fun! Everybody has their likes &amp; dislikes. I respect yours, just poking fun! ðŸ˜Š
Unless you're a Nickelback fan... ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mutant?? I'm a proud follower of my nanite overlords!! How dare they call me a mutant?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This dude need to go AWAY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You look like that guy in that t-shirt commercial, with his stretched-out neck... ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Most people: baby's head
Us: cat's head ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "I can't answer it, so nobody else can either" is such a Tucker thing to say...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# FFS, talk about good riddance to bad rubbish! 
Looking forward to you finding someone with a soul, so you can be as happy as you deserve!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Our 10-month-old Pomeranian, with our long-suffering 70-pound pit bull!! ðŸ˜„ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Smokers and drinkers are also NOT eligible for transplants, so... ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Funny thing is, half of those kids aren't "white" enough for Nazis. They'd have been selected, along with other "inferior races".
Freaking morons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "No link, just what I heard" is the most unnecessary part of that word vomit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My big brother was adopted. 2 of our 3 godsons are adopted. Hell, one of them lives with us! I've seen the effects, the questioning, the feelings of rejection and "otherness". That still doesn't mean that I understand. 
I sincerely hope you can find peace, you deserve it! ðŸ¤—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She's campaigning to be the biggest asshole in literature, and that's saying something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Does anyone have a birthday in February who wants to trade for a trip to the Bahamas? ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't care if someone calls me man, guy, boy, fella, mister, dude, etc.
But I'm not a fragile man-baby. ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Spice Girls ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Does she not realize that her face is already ON VIDEO??? ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's almost like... Propaganda. ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm a 44-year-old man, 6'1" &amp; 300#, yet when I see your sweet face, I want to squeal like a happy baby! ðŸ˜„â¤â¤â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm sorry, I thought this was the big cow? ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Knowing that he's laughing, if he's seeing this, instead of rage-tweeting, and my soul is healing. ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As a former EMT, I can tell you that the biggest difference with natural childbirth is PROLONGED AGONY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But he still can't name a single one, right? ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sit the absolute fuck down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Single women still have hope.
Married women want to share their suffering! ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My big brother, Troy, killed himself on 4/21/95. 
I can't imagine losing a child. Internet hugs! ðŸ˜¢ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't even touch my own godsons' heads (white or black) without their consent. 
If I saw someone just... Well, I try to put my white privilege to some good, when I can... ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Man, you guys are REALLY pushing this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ARE YOU SERIOUS RIGHT NOW???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My state, Illinois: 
Dick Durbin &amp; Tammy Duckworth
Thanks for playing! ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's like saying, "Guys who can ask for directions have the best dicks"
I mean, we'll never find an example, so why bother? ðŸ˜

*Most guys can't parallel park either, but that ruins the premise! ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I remember the first time I saw Michael Jordan dunk from the free throw line, 1988.
No exaggeration, if he flew, she SOARS. 
I'm 44, and I've never seen ANYONE do what she does. *G*O*A*T*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Your comment achieved ramming speed! ðŸ˜„ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That man is absolutely on fire!! Love him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Anyone who would unfollow for this is good riddance to bad rubbish.
If it helps, even the tiniest iota, then you do what you need. ðŸ˜¢â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is the dumbest headline in an extended series of dumb headlines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You're using a book of anecdotal folk tales as a scientific source. 
GTFO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's not like the Omicron variant replaced the others. Odds are, they're most likely infected with prior mutations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "What about the brown and black people??"
Is invariably the precursor to, 
"I don't have a racist bone in my body!" ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Since you're using a word that you obviously don't understand, you're just proving my point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Pretty sure she's the coolest VP ever!! ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think you meant "anti-mask demonstration", because surely you didn't mean to blatantly lie, right?-ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm so grateful for you for many things, not the least of which is that you use your platform to help normalize the people who are so often stigmatized... 
...like me. ðŸ˜Šâ¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Reminder: God supported abortion, even demanded genocide. They don't have much of a leg to stand on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, I think "your" great! ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tacos: soft
Eggs: hard
Music: METAL ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# JFC. Biohazard PPE protects the wearer from external contaminants.
Mask protects others from your droplets/aerosol contaminants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As in, canned meat? Or like, receiving an unsolicited email about hot singles in my area, printing it out, then eating it? ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I didn't say anything about the movies themselves, I said DC/WB shit the bed. 
I have every DCU movie on blu-ray and/or 4k. 
Aquaman and Wonder Woman were awesome, Shazam was great, the Baleman trilogy was great, and I even like a good chunk of MoS, BvS, and JL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I dig her dimples, her nail polish, and her fashion choices! ðŸ˜ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Star Wars Day!
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow, I wonder if there is some obscure, minor cause for that?
No, of course it's a choice. ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Right?? ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Word name for a Venezuelan Muslim... ðŸ¤”n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh, that's just wrong!! ðŸ˜®]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I believe I can safely assume that you aren't complaining about it, though...  ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You should write a caption for him, literally. 
"I can't come up with my own caption, so I asked my roommate to write one" ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Joe: "...so I said, 'Infrastructure? I hardly know her!" ðŸ˜„
Jill: "FFS, Joe..." ðŸ™„
ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I didn't realize that Manchin was Senate Majority Leader. I thought democrats had the majority? n#HASHTAG##HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't vote for the dynamic black woman, vote for the Old White GuyÂ©!!nShe's an elitist millionaire, worth just under $2M.nDavid Perdue is a blue-collar working-class millionaire, with a net worth of a modest $15M!nDON'T LET THE BLACK PEOPLE GET CONTROL!!!n#HASHTAG##HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because the mentats would burn out their brains, and thinking machines are banned under penalty of death.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why can't I just be fertilizer, like nature intended???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I believe the phrase is "mad dog"...
But that's insulting to mad dogs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Holy run-on sentence, Rep. Swalwell!!! ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do they have to still be alive after the 10 years? Because, I don't think any of them would survive that long, especially not TFG or Pillow Biter... ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# How can anyone believe a single word out of her mouth??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The used motorcycle market is going to get *flooded* ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've disagreed with you in a thing or two, but I have the utmost respect for your professionalism &amp; impartiality. 
The humor, though, is the icing on the cake! ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is the Way. ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pretty sure he was absent during law school, period. ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ah yes, all those blue collar workers with salaries near $200k... ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sounds about right for her. 
#HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 100 bulldozers wouldn't be enough. Those ships are MASSIVE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My answer is that I'm a white guy, but not one of THOSE white guys. I take no offense, because it's not aimed at me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm totally Ãœter, just hopping on top &amp; teabagging everyone... ðŸ˜ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah... ðŸ˜³ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Also, wash your hands after you touch your pets!! ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, tornados do go around &amp; around...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# On the contrary, I observed several times where minority patients didn't receive equal care (usually minor, but noticeable), and many of those times when the black nurses had to step in, volunteering to take on the patient, even if they were swamped. 2/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# For purchasing tickets, not for purposes of identification while traveling. Again, tickets don't have have gender listed on them. Neither do credit cards, social security cards, employee ID badges, bank statements, or power bills, either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What's the problem? All I see is a Great Clawed Meowhound. ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "I call him 'MISTER Potato Head'!!" ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# White supremacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When my dad died a month after my gf of 2 years dumped me, I didn't go and try to bomb government buildings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'll take "Aiding &amp; Abetting" for $500, Alex...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Siri, how do I show the world how sexist and ignorant I am?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# To be fair, he thinks 2nd-grade humor is "highbrow"... ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wow, the RATIO alone should tell you how much you need to reevaluate your life choices, McMeangirl. ðŸ–•ðŸ˜‘ðŸ–•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm actually cool with most of my exes. Most.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That's how I look when I'm around dogs ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wonder about the market for anti-Harris books... ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is the biggest scandal of all time, period! ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Whatever, freak. ðŸ˜ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That's what I'm saying! She looks a hell of a lot better than I did when I got dumped! ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It makes me uncomfortable to be called out, but that's because those ingrained attitudes/behaviors seem normal, comfortable.
Discomfort is necessary for change. I don't like it, but I need it.
Thank you for being gracious in explaining, btw. ðŸ˜‰ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I thought, "Pregolympics"?
Nah, that sounds like a pasta competition! ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ONE thing? I grew up in the country. 
- horses/cattle
- farm equipment
- asthma
- beesting allergies
- electric shocks
- gravity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're fucking sick. That's his grandson, you disgusting pervert.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm just ready for him to go meet his racist, misogynistic god.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What the actual FUCK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I know, I couldn't find a gif with the head spin!! ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I've met many Mexicans, IN Mexico, who were as pale as me, with red hair and freckles.
Willful ignorance is a helluva drug, man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I could see "Is he a stalker, or just devoted" being a feature article in Cosmo! ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There's not much "human" about human resources.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# TWO women?? We need to stand up for ourselves, we are being replaced! ðŸ™„n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am! It's not just contentment, or passion, or excitement, or stress, or any one thing. True happiness in marriage is the same as having a good life: a balanced bit of everything!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I was riding a bicycle, not looking around, and a cow got out of the pasture. Just standing there. This is pretty much what happened! ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is she talking about Tim Scott? ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Although it shouldn't be able to infect you, your can still carry &amp; transmit the virus, work is the reason that even fully vaxxed folks still need to wear masks. ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Even "Lars and the Real Girl" knew where to draw the line ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've been married almost 19 years, and I cannot stress enough how important communication &amp; honesty are. I (youngest of 4, strict father) learned to speak up, and she (only child, lenient parents) learned to listen. 
Anticipating your SO's needs should come MUCH later!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# People who are shocked at the ignorance in modern America, but saw what happened after 9/11: ðŸ™ˆðŸ™‰ðŸ™Š
Seriously, just one day after 9/11/01, I saw white people confront Indians, Filipinos, Hispanics, and even lighter-skinned Black people. Even for the Midwest, that was insane. ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# James "Jamie" was my 20-pound "dog", and he was a Good Boy. Seen here waiting for me to come home, per normal, after which he would follow me around "telling" me all about his day. â¤â¤â¤ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I love how many other humans have the same 12-year-old humor as I do! ðŸ˜„â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You've only been nominated once?? 
Pshaw! That's only one more time than me! ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Anything over 200 is typically less effective, wouldn't be surprised if your doc eventually tries something in combo with it, like venlafaxine (Effexor) for a "synergistic effect".
Hope you find the perfect dosage! Hugs!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Like, mayo between two slices of tomato?
Coz that seems messy... ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I was involved with a cheating manipulator, and while I still agree that friends should speak up, there's that line in "When A Man Loves A Woman":
"If she is bad, he can't see it/
She can do no wrong/
And turn his back on his best friend/
If he puts her down"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wife &amp; I both come from farm families, so we have indoor shoes/slippers. We don't ask guests to take their shoes off, mainly because we have a Pomeranian puppy who is STRONGLY resisting housetraining! ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What's #HASHTAG# ?
Oh, is #HASHTAG# trending yet? ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why? If people don't like your opinion, that's on them. For instance, the vast majority of "hummus" is just bean dip, and I will die on that hill!! ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow, I wish I could refuse to cooperate with a murder investigation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dead. And even then, there's always OzzFest... ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My wife's an RN. I've heard WAY worse! ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This idjit here... Never a mess in the house, never gets into anything, only doesn't like other big dogs. Great with our 2 Pekingese, marvelous with our Pomeranian puppy, and AMAZING with kids of all ages. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've been a computer geek since i was 6, when my dad brought home his new work computer, an IBM PC 5150. No HDD, a blazing-fast 4.77 MHz CPU, and a whopping 64kb memory. Oh, and DUAL 5.25" floppy drives!! Monochrome text monitor (grn/blk), later upgraded to a 16-bit CGA. 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She's already gone full Kayleigh McEnany. She just lies, and doesn't even care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Man, you just won't be happy until people aren't unnecessarily killed by other people with firearms, will you? Crazy liberals!! n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# See now, I would be DEAD within 30 seconds. ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...it has been known to occasionally flare up in middle-aged white men.nThere's no cure, so I have to do what I can: avoid FOX News, respect those who are different from me, etc.nAt least I can't get Black Man Mental Illness, that shit can be fatal. /2n#HASHTAG##HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nerds gonna come out of the woodwork for this! "ACTUALLY, they never said that line in the original series..." ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I could never imagine abandoning an animal! ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Demon puppy!! She's actually just holding a biscuit!! ðŸ˜„ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There's absolutely nothing sketchy about any of this. ðŸ˜‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, criticism of a foreign state is "anti-semitism"?? I missed where they said anything negative about American Jews. Surely they have, right? #HASHTAG# Celebrated to Vilified, Houseâ€™s Muslim Women Absorb Blows Over Israel #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# L-R: 
Callie, 11, Pekingese
Bella, 6mo, Pomeranian
Gracie, 8?, pittie mix
Wiggles, 11, Pekingese #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Oh, you poor thing. Don't try to be clever, you don't have the necessary brainpower.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I honestly thought "Hooked on Phonics" was a joke. Well, it was, but not like I thought! ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Seeing how many domestic abusers are instantly forgiven, I'm not hopeful. ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Last time I was in East St Louis, I got lost due to construction, stopped at a gas station, at night. Every single person in there was black.
I bought a Mt Dew, pack of smokes, and got directions. They were very nice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Gracie is a chonk, but deserves it. When she was seized, she only weighed EIGHTEEN POUNDS. 
Now, she gets the best of everything. 
I mean, her bed is a freaking sofa. ðŸ˜â¤ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's the worst false equivalency I've ever seen. Literally nothing in common. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Goldberg... sounds like a Jewish name. ðŸ¤” #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# "They have black employees, so they're not racist" is the dumbest fucking excuse. 
You also think plantation owners weren't racist, because they had black workers?
You make all white men look like fucking clowns.
Yes, you're a white guy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Welp, bye now!" ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ECMO machines are used in a last-ditch effort to keep COVID patients alive, when their lungs have completely failed.
These people are too stupid to try reasoning with. We need laws, mandates, and enforcement, or this pandemic will NEVER end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I was in industrial health &amp; safety, and have done education about the beginning of OSHA, including the MONUMENTAL pushback from around '67/'68 and onward. Used to shock people, how much they railed against basic safety requirements!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Preventing the spread, or preventing infection? VERY different.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I saw a Forbes article, comparing his pay to the President, military officials, and such.
Like, "why would a DOCTOR who has helped save MILLIONS of lives throughout his 50+ years of exemplary work make more than a politician???" JFC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Uh, that's why they're not being charged with 1st-degree murder? JFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, if we had an objective and impartial Supreme Court, they could interpret it, along with the rest of the Constitution; so, we're fucked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Maybe Biden should insult Ted's wife? That seems to win him over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, you did, when you questioned my openness to different comics companies. I'm an equal opportunity comics fan. I won't be disparaged like this. I'm not labelist! ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've had SO many friends &amp; family nervously come out to me, and my knee-jerk response is always, "Oh, cool! Are you seeing anyone?" 
The relieved look on their faces always warms my soul! 
If your family doesn't accept you, I do!!
#HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If nobody changes that to "SATAN", then I die a little inside. ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Just don't say anything about us white folks, though, or you'll get suspended! ðŸ˜³
I swear, the world has lost its freaking mind!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So, I will now be using "Don't be such a Britch!" on a regular basis... ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Stupid sexy Flanders"
"Mmm, doughnuts..."
"Shut up, Flanders!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Please, we all know that blonde Caucasians are the real victims here... n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow, nothing says "righteous" like threatening to kill someone for literally repeating someone else's statements. Such a relief that Trump pardoned this paragon of virtue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I believe a robo call is the new standard ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The vast majority of lawmakers who have negatively affected women's health-care affordable &amp; availability have historically been older white men. Not that younger men aren't involved, but there it is. ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Always knew you were a Looney Tune... ðŸ˜„ðŸ˜]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>