<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[That made me giggle, Just lately, I've become a Dolphin fan ðŸ˜‚â¤ï¸ðŸˆ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[there are so many I love, decided to stick with 3, who would you pick. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Count me in!! A while back I read a historical novel that took place in Italy during WWll, it was the one I recommended for your Mom;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I get so confused (imagine thatðŸ˜‚) but when we turn our clocks ahead I'll be 2 hours ahead of you right;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh good for him ... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This name sounds so familiar, wasn't he with the Cowboys at one time...... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thrash it and get a new one, am sure you have money growing out your ears ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤£(Oxyclean spray works pretty good but you have to catch it right away) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ’¯ one of my biggest pet peeves these days are commercials. They try to be so all inclusive that they look ridiculous. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's time for a new era and am so excited, more so than I thought I'd be ðŸ’œðŸˆðŸ’œ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eagle fans are nothing but class..... ;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# have you ever noticed, it's always the same people ðŸ˜¡Good morning ðŸ¥°â˜•ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I never worked as a waitress..  My first job was a checkout person at Snyder Drug, I ended up being nicely "let go" because my register was always off at night lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I've been there and it was a lot of fun.  Have no desire to go these days though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Karen, I have to take some deep breaths, and think about music, food and booksðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤£ðŸ˜‚ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Victor Hanson is a very smart man. As a preteen I was in love with anything about the Old West, in fact, I still am. Lonesome Dove is one of my favorite books and the TV series was awesome #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good morning Jeff, doesn't that movie look awesome ðŸŽ¶â˜•ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When we adopted a baby from El Salvador, I never gave it a thought he was Hispanic.  He made it to adulthood with only one little boy in 1st grade asking him why his arm was so brownðŸ¤£  Now days all bets are off, and I think society is worse off for itðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well said, I too love this president like no other ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm so sorry, that happened with my brother and I know how devastating it is. ðŸ™â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel your pain, our Walmart is cheaper than other stores but such a pitðŸ˜¡ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I read the book twice, watched the movie, I was obsessed #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I try my hardest and I know people have done same for me. ðŸ’• #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have a new TV with lots of bells and whistlesðŸ¤£ hope my son can find it for me #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning, I love days like that! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[absolutely and if I find out they love to read, bonus pointsðŸ˜‚ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love home made split pea with ham soup, not a huge winner at our house, but the cook always gets her own way ðŸ¥°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# that threw me for a minute.  Good morning MegðŸ¤£â¤ï¸ðŸ’œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm excited, I think we are on right path   I was a huge Zim fan though and wish him the best....I also like our QB (do I need to duck) lol #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning girl, I love a good laugh before I've even finished one cupðŸ¤£â˜•ï¸I hope you are feeling better #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[now we are getting somewhere.ðŸ˜‚  I think it needs a touch of purple here and there.  I can be boss lol #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning, I've heard the same rumors around here! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Peter, I always have to sit back and tell myself, life is pretty good;)  Thank you and hope you have a lovely day. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and to think I campaigned like crazy for George W (live and learn) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AP may have been talented but I'm not a fan;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone wondered what would happen if Rams won SB and he decided to stay, it would be a typical Viking thing ðŸ˜‚ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you spike your coffeeðŸ¥°One SB ring does not make you an instant HOF candidate.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think he will spend time with his parents, his kids and wife and just enjoy life #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning, I hope your coffee is delicious! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Football is entering a new era, and I hate changeðŸ¤£ heard on radio  we have had one of our coldest winters in years , so much for global warming ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see Johnny is working out, doing charity events, preparing for preseason workouts;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had such high hopes for #HASHTAG# but the more I read, the more I realize I was a poor judge of character, or he completely changed #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I forgot to tell you all how much better I'm sleeping now that Roger Stone is going to be put away for life ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I try not to think about what is happening to this country that I love, ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸ If anyone doesn't think Putin is enjoying all this attention they're nuts #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I have to do is look at the prices of everything and the empty shelves.  What a fool. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How cool is this.  Amazon was my friend, but priorities lol #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning, I hope you have a very blessed Sunday â¤ï¸ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi there, have come to the conclusion that some people aren't happy unless bitching about something #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to keep track of my friends betterðŸ’” If I lived closer would bring you some books, coffee and home made chicken noodle soup ðŸ’•â˜•ï¸ðŸ“š #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am sure if he loses his car keys or burns his bacon, he can blame white people ðŸ¤£ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOL, someone told me it was Jim Marshal, leave it to the Vikings;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good morningðŸ¥°â˜•ï¸, I bet there are a lot of players who don't follow their team's accounts. Gives us something to "mull" over though â¤ï¸ðŸˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may live in #HASHTAG# but Florida has a special place in my heart.  Also, I love this guy ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone knows I'm a huge Elvis and old school country fan,  but these guys also have my heart #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Roxy, I'm still eating Super Bowl snacks ðŸ¥°â˜•ï¸ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# when I have time to read I don't, when I am busy I want to read, go figure ðŸ¥°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Julie, I think E and I should go get a cup of coffee ðŸ¥°â¤ï¸â˜•ï¸ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so sick of it, he does everything ass half backward, same with Afghanistan. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have an idea Tom Hanks will bake an awesome Colonel.Parker #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my favorite image of Johnny, wish I had a poster;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and I'm sure everyone will be as pleasant as possible #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[am rather skinny,could probably wear Mick's pants, I'd just roll them up ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¥°ðŸ¤£ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it OK if I substitute Coffee for Wine, and books for pretty Shoes â¤ï¸ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You 2 would hate Minnesota, we will be the last, just wait ðŸ˜¡ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One year my son went on a cruise and stopped there.  He picked up a leather bookmark with my name on it, one of my prized possessionsðŸ¥° #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This looks right up my alley, Christmas present to self â¤ï¸ðŸ“š #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# it hurts me to watch, if I were the parents I'd have so many lawsuits filed they wouldn't know what hit them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chuck Berry got quite the induction, how can you not love it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is starting to drive me crazy.  What happened to letting kids read what they want.  Teachers and parents know what is age appropriate.  Whatever happened to Nancy Drew and the Hardy Boys;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Lincoln President Reagan President Kennedy President Obama President Carter President Biden I do have my favorites and least favorites ðŸ¤£ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe him too. I also don't think his Dad speaks for him either. Just one more TD would be so fun â¤ï¸ðŸˆ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right, you'd say "honey we are under a nuclear attack, be sure to grab the masks" People get crazier by the day ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is heart breakingðŸ˜­ had his whole life ahead of him #HASHTAG# As far as I know, not one major network has talked about it. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't know who I dislike more, Whoopi Goldberg or this fool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good morning Ruthie, my first social media chuckleðŸ¥°â˜•ï¸ðŸ¥°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have only been on a few minutes and already laughed out loudðŸ˜‚  Good morning. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember reading "Mommy Dearest" and what a nasty person she apparently was,she looks a little angry;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever had cold brew or iced coffee, I love it;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think it's a tie as to has better hair, Conway or George Jones;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope you have fun today, have an idea I won't be on social media much, quite a bit to get organizedðŸ’œðŸˆ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to decide what to make for supper tonight and am at a complete lossðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I personally think anyone who lived through the depression and both World Wars, would be ashamed to see all the whining some people do these days ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you, I'd like a cinnamon one with plain cream cheese ðŸ¥° #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My take away is it's okay to tear up State of Union speech but how dare you criticize anything that was said last night ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had to laugh, someone said they loved the work "myriad" - I don't think I've ever used it but am going to work on it ðŸ¥°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks, I always get same thing, large iced mint condition extra shot, creature of habit ðŸ¤£ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I once read someone had part of a garter snake in their bag of spinach and I haven't been able to even look at it since, ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kenny Chesney sells out NFL stadiums like no one's business, yet has never been entertainment for Super bowl.  Makes no sense.  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning, never going to happen #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In all seriousness, I think his friendship with everyone in the band has kept them all young;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I love summer lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She mouthed off about the Holocaust, caused a huge uproar. ABC suspended her for 2 weeks, I think she should have been canned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I take it you're on jury duty, hope you get a good one! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love all the pictures and articles about our former Presidents, especially President Lincoln. As long as I can remember, he has been my favorite â¤ï¸ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# and he had plenty of time to capitalize on his son's death, again.....ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it would be comical if it weren't so maddening.  have disliked presidents before but none like this one..... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Peter, I can either screw this week up royally, or have the best one yet ðŸ¥°â˜•ï¸Seriously, I hope life treats you good ðŸ’• #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# how anyone could find fault with this is beyond me!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are none  better than Kirk, and I stand behind this ðŸ’¯ðŸ’œðŸˆ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't been inside a theater for years, but I could change my mind;) ðŸ•ºâ¤ï¸ðŸŽ¶ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time a picture of Mr. Frank comes across my TL, I wish I could hug him ðŸ’”ðŸ™â¤ï¸ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I programmed it for my DVR as I want to save it and watch again some day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I drove a little VW for a time, my uncle Rudy who knew German cars always tuned it for me;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't have a WALL OF SHAME, however have a few games am not proud of, turned off and watched a Life Time Movie ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤£ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is so special.......Trump never did a thing #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations, you can't beat a good love story ðŸ¥° #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give me a break.   Crime is rampant everywhere and he knows it. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Roxy.  I received  book mail yesterday "Sisters of Night and Fog" by Erika Robuck, looks right up our alleyâ˜•ï¸â¤ï¸ðŸ“š #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone who doesn't follow me on #HASHTAG#, told me I was a fool if I watched #USER#, glad they set me straight on that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a book a while back about the S. S. St. Lewis ship, can't remember the title but it was heartbreaking... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back in the day I had the biggest purple crush on him ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¥° #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[but Hank Jr is still rocking and I love him;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it seems every day we take a step back, I go from being furious, to being sad, to saying the hell with it;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# if you hear anything, please let me know thanks!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rather lazy, friend stopped over, spaghetti sauce cooking, and  did a batch of reviews on #USER#  as I so appreciate them when I am looking for something....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is really cold and snow predicted for the weekend. I don't think we get much warmer than 15 for several days.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never thought I'd say this but beginning to feel same, he's an enigma, I wonder if he still has respect of people around the league......ðŸ’” #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Dad and I used to make so many trips to Florida together, have fun!!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than likely that huge stack of unread books by my bed will fall and break one of my legs ðŸ¤£ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She can apologize all she wants, I still think she is a fool. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're right, I'm confused , what's new;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am so happy for Kevin O'Connell. To win a SB ring and start a new job as head coach has to be thrilling. Welcome to the Land of 10,000 lakes ðŸ’œ(you will get a grace period, just not sure how long) ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤£ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good food, fun music, exchange some books and most of all laugh a lot;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning ðŸ¥°that first sip is pure heaven! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I too was being , twitter can be so hard for me #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I forget how important Rob Brezinski is to this team,ðŸ’œ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only sport I really invest myself in is football and I refuse to let them spoil it for me but I understand. I do think Karma will be a bitch for the NFLðŸ¤£ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading has always been my favorite escape (other than football), which means  I have no idea what's on TV these days ðŸ¥°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love him and Eddie Cochran, old rockabilly is so cool. ðŸ’•â¤ï¸ðŸŽ¶ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[am so sorry, I didn't realize you had been ill. Take care and nothing but positive energy going your way! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good for you, now the one in my bathroom will be off for six months ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤£ðŸ˜‚ðŸ•°ï¸ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same type of humor, am still gigglingðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤£Did you see the video of Stafford ignoring that gal who fell, wonder what is up with that.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For me it depends on the weatherðŸ˜‚  Love a cabin in the summer, a mansion in the winter #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope #HASHTAG# is enjoying the 107 degree temp in Goodyear, Arizona today, I bet that bologna is delicious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning, I love this,ðŸˆ it takes one to know one ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤£I still haven't had coffee, have to be careful about tweeting lol #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# if we go ice fishing can probably get by without a mask ðŸ˜‚I hate ice fishing with a passion lol #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did you see him when he was on DWTS.  He has quite the engaging personality;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Lady Laura Bush was so cute #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning, do people really let her get by with that.  I was floored..... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure this isn't going to cause any problems #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How could I have forgotten about this. ðŸ¥° Our humor is lacking these days! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# think we'll just get rain as we haven't had any this fall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Errands run, stopped at two stores to find things i needed, spent a fortune and not a tater tot in sight. ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes we could and have an idea there are some liberal ears that would ring ðŸ¥°No matter how old our kids get, it hurts when they are sick ðŸ™ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you, and here's hoping everyone is having a great start to their weekend. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this. If there were a picture of one of our presidents shooting a gun today, people would go off the rails ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care what the PC crowd says,Dr. Seuss was a genius. Just think of all the kids who have been entertained over the years, â¤ï¸ðŸ“š #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# best fashion advice I've had in weeks;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think it was Our Darkest Night by Jennifer Robson, it is one of my favorite books.  Your Mother is amazing â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I feel like pounding my head against a wall ðŸ¤£ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Karen, hope you have a good one! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crazy by Patsy Cline, one of my favorite female artists and one of my top 10 favorite songs ever. â¤ï¸ðŸŽ¶ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing I know for sure is we'll have meatballs ðŸ¥°  I also like week leading up to SB,lots of fun stories, etc #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's always had a chip on his shoulder or something, can't figure it out.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True story about #HASHTAG#   When she was born one of the nurses thought Frank was her first name and told her Dad he had a little boy.  He was confused as he thought they'd had a girl ðŸ¥°â¤ï¸ðŸ’”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benny Goodman but have no idea name of song #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I was a kid my Mom would always say "do you kids have books for the journey" we always did and nothing has changed ðŸ¥°â¤ï¸ðŸ“š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never fail to crack me upðŸ¥°Good morningâ˜•ï¸ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Library with big comfy chairs, big windows, and an espresso machine ðŸ¥°ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸â¤ï¸ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see Harry, Meghan and Stacy Abrams from Georgia have been nominated for #HASHTAG#. A person can't make up anything better than this ðŸ˜‚ #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For me. one of the best #HASHTAG# half times ever. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good morning and he had such fun dance moves!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning, I can't stand Camilla,ðŸ¥° but on saying that I'd love a piece of cake â¤ï¸â˜•ï¸â¤ï¸ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Karen, I'm under a winter storm watch so a good day to stay in and do nothing;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patsy was beautiful, I love her so. So many entertainers have lost their lives in plane crashes ðŸ’”ðŸ˜­ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We lived on the Blue Earth river, had some wild times, my brother got busted for a keg party and my friends and I would sit on the bank and smoke lol #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[or it makes me wonder if it is true, my head spins....our beat writers are as bad as network talking heads. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Roxy,  I hope you are enjoying The Three Sisters book â˜•ï¸ðŸ¥° #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I love it with original Bugles or Ruffle chips ðŸ¥°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I received an e mail for "healthy Super Bowl Snacks" they must not know me at all ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even if you disliked #HASHTAG# her fashion sense was spot on, she never failed to look stunning. ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't want to hear one more word from this #HASHTAG# about how much they care for children.  What is happening to the kids in Ukraine and on our border is unforgivable.  This could have been prevented and you can't  convince me otherwise ðŸ’”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She was beyond condescending, wouldn't even let him get a word in. She should be ashamed but highly doubt it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lines for Caribou usually aren't bad but the ones for Dunkin Donut are insane, I don't have the patience for that ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤£ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I loved the GOGO's "We Got the Beat" lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I turned on news and there are so many who would love to see us in another war. Also, please quit being condescending, most of us are smarter than you think ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you go to #USER# to order a book and they let you know you last purchased this particular book in July ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤£Thank goodness for technology lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If you are feeling lazy, Stouffer's makes one which isn't badðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning #USER# or 2 dogs is better yet;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I honestly have no idea and I thought I knew my presidents;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last thing I need is to have tweets in different languages, I struggle with English twitter ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Karen, -1 with a high of -1, lovely outside;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It goes without saying I need my family and friends in my life, but damn I love good food;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# they are so good!  I am also not ashamed to say I loved John Denver;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've composed so many tweets on how I feel about this "war" and deleted them all. Suffice it to say am more worried about the #HASHTAG# than I am Ukraine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember one player running wrong way for a TD, can't think of his name though ðŸˆ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As my Grandpa would say, he's a tall drink of water" ðŸ¥° #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many #HASHTAG# players I wish would write a book. I've read Fran's and Buds, I would love one by #USER# and #USER# bet they'd be bestsellers ðŸ’œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a firm believer and I don't think God cares what religion we areâœï¸ðŸ¥° #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I can't read this tiny print, is Kyler happy, sad, or just ho hum ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤£ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think about the Vikings being in the SB so oftenðŸ’œ In all honesty, if we ever got there, would probably be such a wreck I wouldn't be able to watch ðŸ¤£ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you know he and his wife Patty have been married almost 40 yrs, â¤ï¸I think he got married on his 40th birthday;) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and it's usually after I've enjoyed a great burgerðŸ¥°I hope you are having a good one! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another guy who loves war......ðŸ’” #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thanks, and I'm always amazed at how much she looks like her dad #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I doubt there is a family on earth where cancer hasn't reared it's ugly head. ðŸ’”Thank you for all the great music #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning peeps, I have no news, lead the most boring lifeðŸ˜‚ Have to go to store, though, as am still on a #HASHTAG# mission. Have a good oneâ¤ï¸â˜•ï¸ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's not to love, congratulations and I wish you years and years of happiness #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listened a couple times, now it's stuck in my head ðŸ¥° #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I make chili a lot during football season, walked in house, and the smell reminded me of Viking games ðŸ’œðŸˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love Betty Ford, took me a minute to figure out who was sitting by Pat Nixon #HASHTAG# ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸ #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>