<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I never have sex with anyone just in case I defend them later on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Heratage replacement. White genociders teache children of his native victims to identify with the heritage of the genocider. If this replacement is all they have, they will never be a threat to the genocider system. In fact, s/he can only validate it. Genocide of The Mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scariest people in our nation today are the organized coalition comprising establishment moderate liberals (neoliberalism), nationwide Urbanist agenda, corporate media, and big finance. They are actively trying to redesign our entire nation for top-down population management.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# By "freely developed" I can only take this to mean a self-regulating free market uninterfered with by the state, or state agencies as helpful handmaid to free market demand. If so, you are no leftist. Perhaps u confused over meaning of left wing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Racism necessary to capitalism - must necessarily find a criteria to profle those to exploit for profits of capitalists - but who this racism is gong to target is a contingency of history. This is why redressing particular racisms will fail to redress the problem of capitalism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Haggee is also the biggest Christian Zionist out there. Says Jews do not have to become Christian in order to be "Saved," which is big no no with a lot of Evangelicals. And has spoken as if Christians will be second class citizens in relation to Jewish folks, who will rule.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Back then the counterculture was all about the white male savior gunna lead us to "The Farm." See 1960s artifacts like "Hair," "Electric Kool-Aid Acid test" and "Easy Rider." all mysoginist womanizing hippies. Women were treated like second class. Manson Family extreme example.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Why are so full of assumptions? You assume building is something that must happen like an act of nature and opposing it is holding back the tide. Northbeach, Nob Hill, Russian Hill area as in photo has been a dense and beautiful classic American neighborhood. There is nowhere...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Demand" and "underbuild" are deceptive loaded term you use to smuggle in conclusion and conceal circular reasoning. What you mean by "demand" is rich white entitlement wants your house and neighborhood. Sollution: Tell them, "NO, YOU CAN'T." You naturalize "Demand" like it's...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I don't like doing this school book stuff, and slang is powerfull tool when highlighting a relevant aspect of a concept, but TheWatcher requires to be pinned down on his loose and incorrect use of terminology, especially since he's using it to harm poor folks and People of Color.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Republicans and Democrats have long formed adivision of labor for neoliberal colonialism. The Republicans' job is the "MAKE THE SLAVES," while it's the Democrats job to "MANAGE THE PLANTATION." Expect no help from the Democrat Party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And there are so many of these "memoirs" - just type into google search - obviously CIA subsidized if not ghost written.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ever hear Zizek in person? He obviously blew a lot of cocaine when younger - constant sinus snorting from coke-eaten sinus. But he's really into cola too. Always writes about the irony of drinking the uncola or eating chocolate flavored laxatives. Zizek on coke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That's just a waste of a tweet. You seem to be losing your temper, meltdown time. I'm getting to you. 😆😂🤣]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's right. The whole contrived narative about housing crisis is a fiction trumped up by real estate developers who only want the Benjamins. Plenty of housing avalable, unoccupied, right now. If any crisis, it's a gentrification crisis of rich whites displacing poor folks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# People around here put locks on their garbage cans. Bourgeoisie even greedy about trash.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ...optimum and should be fest alone. See though, real estate developers and their surrogates and functionaries already set their destructive sights on one of America's greatest neighborhoods. No one should be allowed to live somewhere just because they want to, just because...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-taxers are anti-vaxxers which will ultimately mean less anti-vaxers and more taxes in the future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face it, a fake CIA front communist organization would be more successful at communist cause than the CPUSA has been. Petty bourgeois CPUSA represents opportunists reactionary tendency, insulating itself from outside feedback leadership sees as threat to their personal positions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once while homeless in San Francisco eleven days I encountered a man who'd been victimized by a wolf pack at the very western edge of Golden Gate Park. The back of his khakis stained with blood where they gangraped him. He sat on a park bench sobbing. Why I kept weapond nearby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Finally, the first person I found who stands up for the Coalition. All these reactionary rightwingbats piling on Jennifer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They still won't allow Haz on rollercoasters. And he has to sit at the kids table during holidays. But compared to 10-year-old Timmy, Haz is a badass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That's it!!! That's how we need to do. No more mister nice sucker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# After utterly destroying all your arguments its dissapointing you sink to the level of disability-shaming, decompensating to infantilism: "your stupid," "I do good things, bet you don't. I'm better than you." Just makes your utter defeat sadder a more pathetic than it has to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RESPECTABILITY POLITICS: Affluent privililaged neoliberals display mask of white comfortable respectability (Discourse of white innocense), while perpetuating via their corporate media the "unrespectability" (Discourse of non-white guilt) of poor folks and poor POC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wisdom from the old man on the mountain. Sounds like an Alcoholics Anonomous meeting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# "Gentrification is a conspiracy theory." Libertarians also believe other people is a socialist plot. Gentrification, look up definition, is a fact. "Gentri- as in The Gentry, the aristocracy, elites. Get it. Gentrification is a fact that transformed San Francisco's histloric...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mean: Latinx and African American "characters in movie "represent" real Latinx and African and other POC real victims of US system worldwide. So little room Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Popular Evangelicalism also rallied in support of Adolph Hitler and Tird Reich, a primary constituency. Today Evangelicals whitewash this historical fact by focusing on exception of Dietrich Bonhoeffer, who would have been no friend to today's Evangelicals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Those "conservatives" who condemned prostitution, gambling, gayborhood economy, drugs etc. as sins yesterday will valorize them today, if they can find a way to make money off them. So much for Man-o-Stick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Tenderloin should be preserved as it is as a historic LGBTQ+ heritage site. Transgenders and queers, especially sex workers and POC not so welcome in white gay Castro or white lesbian Noe Valley, but made their own community in the TL. San Francisco's Stonewall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Do you have a fiends wishless on Amazon I can gift you a book present from?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# All these guys repeat the same tired scripted tropes about SF.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are definately a Karen if you bribed an ivy league college to admit Connor or Evan or whatever the f'ck Karen-esque name you gave your date-raping son.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleasure and traumatic horror are so closely linked they often overlap. We don't simply compensate psychologically for the horror of the Real, we seduce it and are seduced by it. We derive pleasure/jousance by refashioning it into the imaginary petit abjet a/object of desire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nice article. Wakan very unlike western notion of sacred, it seems to be all inlusive - even include devils if applied to Christianity - doesn't otherise or cast out of the family of being the way christianity casts out to non-being of hell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When there's a natural disaster elsewhere that leaves the population homeless we send in humanitarian aid as we should. Meanwhile there's homeless all around us, but far from offering humanitarian help, we don't even leave them in peace. Rather, we sweep them into the cemetary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Give what fulfils need, not what you are willing to give. Good socks and a good pair of shoes, and quality jacket tops list after a $100 bill. Packaging could also be useful: a backpack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instruments like the CIA, MI6, NSA etc. cannot exist in a representtive democracy. Government - all government - must be transparent to maintain legitimacy as the will of the represented. Can be no category of special exceptional power above the laws issued by the people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# By the way, why has everyone forgotten about the incest scandal at Hillsdale College, by the President and his adult daughter and resulting suicide of his son, given that Hillsdale has recently branded itself as the vanguard of religious-right wing revolution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CPUSA considers CPUSA private property of CPUSA Chair, Co-Chair, Co-Co-Chair, etc., etc. No one allowed to speak back to them, "cause it's their shit." CPUSA also asserting proprietary rights over proletariate revolution. Marx rolls in grave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't think the white gentrification bros can pile on you for this tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Good to hear, I spent last 20 years in SROs, rescue missions, and homeless on the sidewalk, I can tell you causality runs in opposite direction than personal moral failure narrative. Homelessness, or childhood history of family transiency, precedes substance abuse/mental illness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No names off top of head, but works on "restorative justice" and "harm reduction" theory, and even "critical race theory" may address this problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# THERE WAS BREAK AFTER JEWS STRONGLY SUPPORTED CIVIL RIGHTS MOVEMENT. AFRICAN AMERICANS FELT EXPLOITED BY SOME JEWS FOR THE ZIONIST CAUSE. WHEN NO LONGER USEFUL TO JEWISH INTERESTS, THEY WERE DISCARDED, AND JEW ORGANIZATIONS BECAME RIGHT WING ZIONIST WHO TREATED PALISTINIANS BADLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Keep sounding more and more like that leftist you claim to be. Stop talking about developers everytime like your getting orgasmically excited &amp; wet. "Messianic Capitalism" I coined it first! You must smell the scent of your property values going up with each evicted Black family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burning Man originally cool, a communal free-for-all. No license, no LTD, no $400 admissions for smething that belonged to everyone. Now Burning Man is owned by libertarians, and the magic has left. Right wingers keep thinking they can be cool simply if they get piercings &amp; tatts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intersectionality is like a venn diagram of three overlapping circles. While minority groups suffer distinct forms of oppression, there's space of shared suffering common to groups. Precisely in this overlapping space confusion and misplaced hostility between groups may occur.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you respond, you'll either dismiss me with usual PROPANE JANE dis or argue radicalism is not pragmatic politics and will just help Repubs win elections. Me: We don't want to "win" elections. We want to abolish the whole stinking party politics machine for real equality/justice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to understand the mind-disease infecting the USA today? Take a weekend and go on a reading binge of James Ellroy novels mixed with Ann Coulter books. That's it right there: the current American sicko Zeitgeist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Affluent white people honestly think the homeless are set pieces staged there to give their "urban experience" an authentic feel. I hate white tourists &amp; I'm white. Swedish and Norwegians the worst, they suffer from that brand of unselfaware racism from no exposure to POC before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Did you read that recent book I think titled "CARE REVOLUTION" or "CARE MANIFESTO"? Good read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The same strand running through almost all the bullying of homeless and the Coalition was this odd skepticism of nonprof motivations. The suspicion they are acting from hidden self-interest for personal gain, Which ironically is precisely what they hail about the "free market."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ...to build, and if you found some empty little lot sonmewhere this would just help to destroy quality of life. Developers would have to tear down classic landscape to do so, only to replace with some shitty Ruby Tuesdays or standardized condo. This SF neighborhood is at its...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...values-laden interpretation speaking on behalf of silent body - "sex" parts. Interpretation is everything godammit, so identity, sexuality are self-created choices driven by willing and desire. Free yourself to create, resist being created by latent rapists' interpretations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rich white criminals erase history of still unredressed crimes against Blacks, Latinx, and Native Americans by replacing them with imported wealthy elites from India and East Asia. NEXT: Rich white YIMBY accuses evicted Blacks and Latinx of being racist against Indian &amp; Asian 1%.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why you complaining Ken? It's your pro-development, import cheap labor to undercut US wages, pro-gentrification, union busting libertarian bros lobby thats bribing the politicians. That's your thing bruh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A CPUSA tweet spoken with all the voice of white middle class entitlement. It is "WE" who are the chosen, unquestionable, ones. Any who dare questions are the "other" who have no status. Anything they say is display of "gall" from the inferiors to the elect. Bourgeois elitism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Norman bates is to "MOTHER!" what Young Republicans are to Ann Coulter. They direct their mother-good little soldier complex at Coulter and she reciprocates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BEFORE YOU READ DON WINSLOW'S POLTWEETS, TAKE A LOOK AT HIS MIDDLE PERIOD NOVELS, IE. BEACH PATROL, DEATH AND LIFE OF BOBBY Z, ETC., IT'S ALL THE DISCOURSE OF WHITE MALE EXCEPTIONALISM, SO-CAL STYLE. F**K WHITE SANTA MONICA ZEN BEACHBUM SURFERS. MORE DELUSIONS OF THE MASTER RACE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It is actually the neoliberal gentrification project that wishes to remove poor people and poor people of color to the outlands and remake urban centers into boutique cities for white wealth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SF Examiner page 8, the usual neoliberal claptrap: "Affordable Housing Crisis". Predictable Examiner sollution: "Build!" by usual shills for outside real estate developers, directors of astroturf organizations. How bout we kick gentrifiers out. We have gentrifier crisis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Your single default thought function: "No, not me. You." That's precisely what I mean by "Echo chamber."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've seen so many poor people of color create something brilliant, but because they lack capital to develop and promote, vulture white capitalists (dare I speak it: often white Jewish capitalists) swoop in and steal the brilliance and claim credit for its creation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I once dreampt about Kripke's philosophy of language. In the dream I performed "rigid designation" by pointing at an object and making an atavistic gutteral groaning sound.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ...Let me ask you this, who has a right to your home, your neighborhood, you, your family your people; or wealthy financial royalists who've decided they want it so they can sale it to other rich white people. Will you submissively walk away grabbing your ankles as you go or...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...in spite of reality. Developers are capitalists. Narcissists oblivious to reality and indifferent to suffering caused to others. They construct imaginary bubble - the market - where everything obeys what they want like an equation. Social intervention, or revolution, needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if the fetus wants to be aborted. Never thought of that, huh? That's a game changer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Repeating sentence ironically displaying profound superiority. Responsiveness far beneath you. Dorm life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrified Tai Lee will scold me. (Secretly desire Tai Lee will scold me.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Why aren't the Jan 6 actors detained and hooded at Guantanamo Bay right now???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Narrative of 1960s: Rich white kids got together with poor whites and poor POC in the Haight, at Woodstock etc. But when 60s orgy was over, rich kids could afford to return to daddy's firm or to Yale, while poor kids were left behind on the streets, pockets empty, strung out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are fooling yourself if you think you do not live under a theocracy. Every government, by its nature, is a theocracy, sovereignty meaning Creator and divine Lawgiver. Since I believe I'm God I have no problem with this, beyond the fact another asshole is sitting on my throne.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They've actually attacked me as anti-immigrant and anti-asian racist for opposing YIMBY evictions of POC neighborhoods.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rich white people require an uneven playing field to compete with the superior POC. Uneven playing field is defacto affirmative action for rich white people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Resist phil. grad. urge to try philosophy-related humor: Juxtoposing high phil concepts to banal everyday experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, thank you. I got your books on my Amazon wishlist, soon as I get paid. I looked for Welsing a long time, until they reissued her book after her death. Got it at Markus books in Oakland. Gentrifiers evicted original Marcus books in SF. First Back Identity b store in US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you poor you doomed to loneliness. Can't afford to take care of yo lady and feel like a man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For white middle-class second-wave feminists the primary issue: female sexual liberation, sexuality prioritizing women's enjoyment. For poor women of color at same time primary issue was survival; not  increase of pleasure but removal of suffering. White-woman colonized feminism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...may actually fall into that common space of oppression shared by all minority groups, so that hostility toward a different minority speaking of it may be misplaced hostility. Especially given that rich racist oppressors will exploit civil rights of each group as a weapon...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SF Examiner reports Asian woman frightened more by hate crimes than covid. Asian women more likely to be victims of hate crimes: 62% of hate crimes reported by AAPI women and report 2.2 times more than AAPI men. Asian women face both violence against women plus racist hate-crimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are there so many neocon Jewish folks now. In the matter of like one generation Jewish people went from being Trotskyists to becoming Ayn Rand extremists. Enter through the door, but don't lock it behind you. We're cold out here and still trying to get inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# YES, IS THIS NOT THE SIGIL FOR LICIFER? AND ON YOUR WRIST, IS THIS NOT AN AMULET FOR PROTECTION?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thinning out the surplus labor via Covid, chemical pollution, unhealthy food, promoting narcotics, cigarettes, alcohol via media, evictions, homelessnes, slashed safety net, or just capitalism killing you directly via their enforcers: plain ol' killer cops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the great things about San Francisco is you can go to Chinatown on holidays and everything's still open when everywhere else is closed. See me sitting in Garden Bakery sipping coffee and munching rolls on Thanksgiving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's right, we've been saying this since it didn't work in NYC but YIMBY lobbyists for Big Developers refused to listen, until that is it was irrefutably proven by vetted scientific scholarship. Now they can no longer deny the facts. They've, however, moved on to other tactics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In today's Evangelical mega-church, the minister has an agent and publicist. He uses his pastoral salary to support himself while authoring books and producing media series - church members never meeting him personally - the profits of which he retains as a private entrepeneur.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes I understand. You're just pointing this out. I thought you were trying to make some sort of argument. Thank you for taking time to respond.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Try good ol' grilled cheese sandwhich made with cheddar and texas toast bread.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not "Checks and Balances," more like "Blocks and privilages."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Who's "we"? So you hold a position in some kind of gentrification-agenda driven organization that bullies communities even beyond San Francisco. You're an actual agent actively gaming the democratic system. The right wing libertarian conspiracy reveals itself,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Point of avant garde theory - particularly current French philosophers - is that it's at odds with "common sense," and seeks to dismantle it, so we may think and act new possibilities; not privately - they are no personal therapeutic theories - but collectively, structurally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# But you are YIMBY pro-free market Log Cabin Democrat. You should praise their financial success. They are capitalist success stories. Are you criticising them because they mirror your own free market values? Condemning yourself there bro.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# For us majority who suffer from your amoral decisions from a soft comfortable position this is not an issue of proper etiquette, it's harsh reality of survival.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# YIMBYs all say they're left wing. Part of the script. Then they defacto support gentrification despite what they say, bacause you still do not understand demand for gentrified-targeted areas will only grow with building more houses. Test: If you are left wing, then you must...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They are a little boost to already well-heeled members of minority demographics to do well in the free market.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Classist and racist voices on Twitter. And others who have no voice 'cause of poverty, gentrification racism. Segregationist Twitter's not your constituency. The people from (originally) the Tenderloin are, including those who are homeless and in underground economy to survive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# How is it you support Chesa, criticize the SFPD, and support squatters while simultaneously promoting urbanist gentrification, which necessarily entails removal of poor Black and Brown folks? No cognitive dissonance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[repeatedly disproved, as only causing increased onslought of gentrifiers, booming prices, and ethnic removal of POC neighborhoods. SF does not suffer housing shortage. We have plenty of housing for us that also sustains healthy quality of life. We suffer from rich...cont]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...But say that the "sellout" behavior of Zionists and the wealthy gay man also oppresses some Black people. Say Zionists discriminate against Ethiopian Jews in Israel or most of the homeless removed happen to be African American. Can she justifiably criticize each as "sellouts?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You are socialist comrade I assume, do you have a critique of the Marcuse-type New Left philosophy of the 1960s?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People confuse tweeting with feigned overconfidence and aggressive Trump-like personal attacks with being factually right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Show us now what you can do as a writer on Twitter. Ready-made audience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I USED TO GET DON WINSLOW CONFUSED WITH WILLEFORD BECAUSE THEIR "MYSTERY" NOVELS WERE NEXT TO EACH OTHER ON THE SHELF AT GREEN APPLE. CHARLES WILLEFORD IS A SUPERIOR WRITER. "COCKFIGHTER" IS A MODERN MASTERPIECE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is old white man tradition. They burned some of the Native Americans out too,before stealing their land.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yuo know, that book published by Nation of Islam about secret history between Jews and slaves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truth Speaker and prison novelist Donald Goines was assassinated in 1974 by PO PO for writing the Kenyatta novels, about a Panther-like group of Black revolutionaries who fought back against police corruption and racist violence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I wish you would catch up with the stage of the debate. You're like ten years behind. The facts are in, not an issue of opinion. YIMBYs now accept proven fact old supply &amp; demand factors don't work - that new housing in gentro-targeted cities only increases demand, increases...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Orwellian calling the cage of capitalism freedom. Ayn Rand crazy sociopath bitch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Porn seemed funner, the girls happier, enjoying themselves, back then compared to today when it's justs so grim and unpleasant to watch.  Not everyone of course, but not the image propagated by abolitionist feminists. I'm a sex-positive feminist like goddess Hartley.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global neoliberal imperialism's operated by division of labor within ruling race/class itself. In local terms this division's between conservative Republicans and liberal Democrats. While the conservative Repubs make the slaves of empire, the liberal Dems manage the plantation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At some point a higher legal authority has to bring London Breed to justice for her crimes against humanity or else law in California is a farce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# SWERFs are just part of libertarian PR rebranding-image makeover campaign, from stodgy old rich white guys to "cool," young hipster types sporting tatts and piercings, saying, "Yeah, hey bro, everything's legal now, 'cause money has consumer right to victimizing others."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They turn normal values on their head, "greed is good", etc. They becoming more and more hateful, leading to something truly frightening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If your hourly employee spoke like this about his job he's immediately be fired.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Found it,follow you on Amazon. Wish I could make the distinction between rich white people and poor whites, who have suffered too from white power structure, although certainly not as much. but who am I to say this to Africans. People like me have no one, niether whites nor POC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CPUSA hoodies on post-Christmas sale for $13.95 until Jan 1st. Minor defects do not effect wear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This requires radicalization group sessions in which the individual is awakened to his position within structural exploitation, ie. the personal is political, with reference to intersectionality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Capitalism is fundamentally sexually repressive especially of women. The repression is structural and therefore not visible to many who haven't learned to reason critically/reflectively. Market demands sexual coersion/repression. Sex-positive=anti-capitalist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Overthrow the court by stacking it with political operators and you overthrow the rule of law, and America. The S Court is fomenting another civil war.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You and the financial elite will be banning people from doing so, because in criminal capitalist society, those with most capital possess unequal power to evict those with less, even to transform entire communities into boutique neighborhoods. You know very well your grifting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Mybe they think a police issue 9mm injection is the only cure for covid, at least for POC. What happened to defund the police? They invest more to fight homeless people than they do to fight covid, but maybe we talked about this befory. Twitter affects my memory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One example of effective method for vanguard group formation: Members separate by deployment to deep wilderness for two months where they must rely on one another for survival. conditions harden members while creating vanguard solidarity and readies for independent  group action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is some new YIMBY evil: "Minority signaling" in order to ethnic remove historic minority neighborhoods for rich white grentrification that will raise their property values. And force-building new highrises that will bring more rich white techies, and outprice poor working...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Rich whites importing 1% from India and East Asia to attack US People of Color who have long history of oppression here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In any condition we find ourselves, whether covid crisis or something else, the wealthy will always be enriched, because they are the only delivery system of whatever good is needed at the time. Only way to change this is to restructure society into nationalized delivery system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeff Spinoli anounced new head of CDC. First line of business: "Order pizza dude. I got the munchies"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Rich white YIMBY tactic: Erase Native Americans, Blacks, and Latinx with long history of racist oppression by replacing them with 1% from India &amp; EastAsia. Makes it easier to ethnic cleanse their neighborhoods for gentrification while denying accusations of racism. Not nativism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Underground economy and "street living" in SF's Tenderloin is a way of life - not chosen, but resorted to for survival. It was chosen for these folks by the Mayor, Chamber of Commerce, and outside real estate developers who evicted and deprived them of mainstream employment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Isn't his the genuine materialism without Empiricist  or Marxian prejudices?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...for our own good. Deomocracy and equality are out of date artifacts anyway. Think Daniel sounding the citywide alarm everymorning for mandatory calisthenics,  because managers think this a swell idea. Daniel I recomend for your edification Horkheimer &amp; Adorno.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sexual freedom for everyone, which means freedom from coercion, structural or individual. My kind of feminism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If people are so bad then why let them run a government of "We The People," or be free to pursue business enterprise? They are contradictory in their logic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fascinating how all the projects created and survived after the 1960s counterculture were coopted by a white professional managerial class that now operates them accorting to a gains/losses logic, spending donations on on red carpet benifits for the society page set.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All these white wing snowflakes insulated from reality by the gated safespace burbs move to the big boy city and get all traumatized seeing homeless people and drug addicts. Welcome to the world trust fund. Time to grow up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be consistant the anti-tax capitalist and his Republican flacks should also be anti-capitalist tax. The employee stands in relation to the capitalist in precisely the same way the capitalist stands in relation to the government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...to meet fans &amp; sign autographs, and some assplay with lucky fan in 1994's BUTMAN'S INFERNO, from Evil Angel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...many gay people died of AIDS - because they had too much sex...This taught them that gaysex is bad. The gays who were left realized the importance of stable,monogomous relationships and began to agitate for marriage and the 1,000+ benifits it would bring." -Yasmin Nair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Great to hear you're pro funding legit housing for the homeless and other social welfare services Ken. But you really should be up front with Twittersphere from go about any libertarian/urbanist-gentrification/real estate developer lobyist affiliation or position you may hold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# SWers a libertarian hipster fad among some blase privilaged white girls. It's already jumped the shark. If you're genuinly pro-erotic enjoyment you'd abolish the "for pay" part and promote economic equality so everyone could equally enjoy the erotic, not just Wall Street bros.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# "SUPPLY/DEMAND": The God of the rightwingbats. Demand speaks with the authority of the Almighty and we must obey His command by fullfilling the Supply. Biden is the High Priest of this religion of the free market.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sounds similar to Gurdjieff &amp; 4th Way psychology.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "Left" is at war with itself. While rich white progressives who controll the Left's direction prioritize "transgressing norms," ie. spending their ill-gotten loot on decriminalized drugs, sex trafficking, gambling etc., poor people &amp; POC struggle to stop the suffering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One virus, two systems: contrasting approaches in socialist China and capitalist United States #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanted to respond to 2 SWerfs threw a gang of libertarian talking points at me. Strange how libertarianism and high-end white sex workers go together. Reminds me majority of direct messages I get break into two types: Prostitutes &amp; investment sales both wanting my money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I gather: UC Berkeley trained upper-middle/upper class professional, $900,000 home owner in SF. You are not like the rest of us. You want gentrification to raise property value. By the way, dropping you have an "immigrant Vietnamese" wife just reinforces we know you're racist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nationalize all real estate/form government agency to realocate decent and humane living conditions for everyone. Nationalize supermarkets and all food distribution so everyone has healthy and sufficient food. Nationalize all utilities and WiFi and pc resources, so everyone...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The question is, why of all feminists would publishing industry give her such huge book deals? She is early 1990s reaction against feminism, attempt to take revolutionary impulse out of feminism and incorporate it into comodity capitalism. Feminist Rush Limbaugh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Great movie from director of Parasyte and Host, good TV series. Rediculous premise, but made plausible by excellent execution. Weakness of TV show is male lead, a rather lackluster actor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Love Jennifer Cohn. One of my heroes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Left was great during the 1890s to WWII period; bohemians, Shanghai, Lost Generation/Jazz Age, PWP, Bonus Army, IWW, 1930s Berlin. My God, thoughts of Progressivism today are so depressing. I was born out of time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...removal via YIMBY-gentrification policies written by YIMBY lobbyists; enforced by Governor Newsom and Senator Wiener, and executed locally by Big Real Estate surrogate the San Francisco Planning Commission/Planning Department. YIMBY-gentrification lobbyists bybass...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...Element." Benji cites a different law having nothing to do with current state mandated 80,000 density housing, wanting to identify for the reader ethnic removal policy with meaningless policy giving symbolic nod to minorities, because readers are too stupid to see they are...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Capitalists tax their employees, witholding from their paychecks lion's share of the value they created and calling this "capital." Then the free market hypocrits complain about being taxed by WE THE PEOPLE. Why do libertarians hate America so much?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another (this gets old) SF Examiner gentrification flack, Benji Schneider. You'd think just for the sake of escaping monotony, Examiner would put a couple counter voices in their rag once in awhile. 2 Benji errors of the top: Gov. Reagan evicted mentally ill from institutional...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YIMBYs have no shame or self awareness: They are actually using our argument against their "Build more housing will solve all evils" argument as precisely the reason YIMBY position should be embraced. Facts finally forced them to concede more housing doesn't in fact lower...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Americans love this arse hole. Get all teary-eyed listening to his old sentemental lying speeches.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Now right wing YIMBYs attacking allies of Native Americans, Blacks and Latinx who oppose ethnic removal of their historic neighborhoods by privilaged gentrifiers as nativist racists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ground's cold and wet. It will penetrate to the bone during the night, be sure to lay down some kinda insulation between you and the ground. Perhaps a flattened cardboard box. You will wake up soaked anyway due to Pacific Ocean spitting on you. Better drink a lotta alcohol first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ...increases rent exponentially, and increases evictions of poor working class, mostly POC, neighborhoods. Demonstrated by scientific vetted research; YIMBYs have accepted this and moved on to new tactics trying to explain old assumption doesn't work by arguing miniscule...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer service employees should recieve hazardous duty pay on top of normal wages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right they have created a whole seperate industry of phone banks, Twitter banks, fake orgs. newspapers, events, etc. all to manufcturing public opinion and create an astoturfed narrative serving interests of elites, with choreographed character assassinations of critics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ...details like raise in costs of materials for constructing new houses, and labor etc. Again, check with YIMBY home office and thy will update you so you don't keep arguing from ten years ago and embarrassing yourself. Just trying to help you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Unless a tv series shows a character dismembered, they're still alive. Even if dismembered they may still be alive. Why I didn't like KRYPTON, no one ever died even when they died. "It was my clone."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Let's keep to facts, not the little elves in your mind whispering happy thoughts. Capitalism is indifferent to suffering it inflicts, just read a history book of the 19th Century. Leftists, i.e. marxists, agitated for state regulation, to stop capitalism from destroying the poor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem with Twitter: Most times it's lowest common denominator - social maladjusted cases, libertarians, hipsters, YIMBYs, teens trying to get daddy's attention, MAGA types, etc. - doing the tweeting. They think it's a GAME of upmanship, destroying its potential for change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Why accept we must all subjugate ourselves to will of the rich? What's wrong with you? I thought we lived in the "land of the free" where there are no serfs. You must either be one of the rich or a coward on his knees. I say, "HANG THE THE NEW ROYALISTS," as did my forefathers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most f'd up demo in US is desperately poor whites. Everyone hating on us. PWP(privilaged White People) exploit and deprive us, and hate us. Minorities blame us because we white. We got nobody to have our backs. We want to revolt, minorities say "no". We waNt wealth, PWP say, "no"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# City/Urban Planning Departments function in partnership with private Enterprise &amp; it's lobbyists Chambers of Commerce &amp; Merchants Associations to engineer communities against the will of WE THE PEOPLE, and are therefore illegal and illegitimate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...neighborhoods left in SF. I picked up a propaganda tract from the hate group SF Examiner on my way here. Front page, neoliberal flacks, and gilded whites, Lincoln "Moderate Menace" Mitchell, C.W. "Neo-colonialist" Nevius, and Benji "Hate Schtick peddler" Schneider with their..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And descent men, like your boyfriend and myself, get labelled bad because of acts of other male bad actors and general rape culture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[..."re-tenementing, turning The City into a crowded, airless, garenless, architectureless, charmless, mostly viewless location," cherry-picking the one numbskull who doesn't represent the reason for anti-gentrification-evictions, anti-YIMBY opposition. YIMBYism is bought...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What about the safety of the evicted and made homeless by your pro-gentrification policies. Sellout.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libertarians believe reality is a socialist conspiracy."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one seriously believes in the Christophile God anymore. If they did, then they'd hold the King James Bible as both their political constitution and economic policy. Even the US religious right don't want this, prefering the polytheistic &amp; Luciferian US Constitution instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Has this guy drunk the neoliberal  cult Kool aid or what? He can't tell the difference between NY and Kentucky? Check out the blank gaze and mindless smile of his icon. He thinks we're all the same underneath the surface: White men.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump trying to reinvent himself. His tired old tactic of defying expectations that he's responsible for people having. Now he's pro-vaxx, pro-China, and critical of Jan. 6 supporters. He's revving up for a new season of Trump Whitehouse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Libertarians endgame is to do away with the nationstate except as some cultural artifact like the British royal family, and turn America into one giant flea market free-for-all. So much for patriotism, right guys?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bukowski greatest fiction writer of 20th Century. Horrible misogynist however. Causes confusion like your dad didn't show up for the big game like he promised. I feel abused by Bukowski yet I can't help myself but love him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I actually looked like this as a kid in the 1970s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# They got us bickering while we should be united against the true villain: Imperialism. Western Intelligence agencies do spend millions to divide their victims.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dream society: Authoritarian feminist communism. Bourgeois delinquent reactionary types: fake intelectuals (Ann Coulter, Tucker Carlson), capitalists, party politics opportunists, criminal class enablers all sent to labor farms to learn healthy manual work and reeducation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking Dead: The zombies devour last four seasons that suck so hard, and new production team breathes fresh life back into series.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We do not live in Dem run city. We live in a "moderate Democrat" run city, and moderate Democrat here is a euphamism for defacto Republican. We have problems not because of progressive responses but because neoliberal conservative policies run and destroy our city.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think about it a sec, the covid virus might be the Rapture the born again Christophiles are always preaching about. Born agains' more likely to be anti-vaxers, so more likely to be raptured outa here by it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The SF Board of Supervisors needs power to backup mandates with penalties if Mayor disobeys her legal requirements. Instead, homeless shelters became incubators for covid, infection rate like 100% in some. Sidewalks filled up with desperate homeless. Meanwhile Breed living large.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Less cutsy ha ha. more serious engagement against rich white racists, ethnic removal, gentrification. economic equality, support Puerto Rico against tourist gentrification, support Native Americans against continuing "soft" genocide, abolition of prisons and sex traficking.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Narative framing San Francisco by libertarian-YIMBY machine it's "a left-wing, dystopian hell"(SF Exam. Oct. 3) needs fixing, i.e. Mayor's "state of emergency." Of course, "dystopian hell" is code for People of Color, particularly poor working class ones in way of gentrification.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's not forget the original YIMBY gentrifiers. "Housing shortage" was a bitch for white people back in the day, So the first YIMBYs were forced to gentrify Native Americans out and onto the reservation. Little has changed today, as YIMBYs still removing POC off their land.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Self-appointed white bro language police.  Why you hate "black" so much? Black folks use and want "Black" to be used in reference to them. It's mighty white of you to see "black" as so bad as needing errasure. Sounds like you want to rehabilitate minorities into white people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're a Fundamentalist Christian, believing in the innate depravity of fallen man, then why on earth would you make the self-interest of this fallen nature the bases of your political constitution and economic system, thereby proposing the problem as the sollution?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Take Breed and her enablers into custody, transfer to the Hague and charge them with crimes against humanity for their slow genocidal policies toward San Francisco's homeless humans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Forget about market rate, "below market," and so called "affordibale housing" refers to subsidized housing for people making six figures, or to us regular folkes: the well heeled. not for those on hourly wage or people on social security. Even subsidies that should go to the...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# C'mon drink like a real Bolshevik. Drink vodka.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everything we've made, we've made from fossil fuels: energy, food, medicine, and consumer goods. The world has been organized to burn. -  DR. Rupa Marya, INFLAMED: Deep Medicine and the Anatomy of Injustice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish rich white YIMBYs trying to raise personal property values via gentrification would stop exploiting images of minorities as face of ad campaign, given they are engaged in ethnic cleansing evictions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Get your ass back in the cardio kickboxing class dammit!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't get it. In grade school we all start out wanting to be the "good guys" and fight the "bad guys." They read us the same childrens stories with moral lessons, we cheer good, boo bad. Then "boom" adulthood, and there are so many evil mf'rs. Whend'd this change happen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christy Canyon feasts on Jenteal pressed facefirst against wall in movie "Comeback."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# "Progressivism" originated during the Enlightenment with the aspiration humanist reason could solve social evils. The "Progressive Era": Late 19th/early 20th centuries: "left-leaning" social reform/improvement issues focussed: Temperance, Suffrage, Abolish child labor.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>