<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[the mission begins now. block all hexagon pfps. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[imagine ironically bringing up the fake concept of "agism" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you have a gear in your name so i assume you're just being secretive as usual

the fact you're mocking lolicons in the first place while using ironic terminology like "troglodyte" and "leftist" shows #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes, ban them from the internet. that majorally causes the "trauma" they claim to get looking up their favorite things and then seeing stuff they don't like to blame it on the adults. not to mention existential depression and addiction. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tfw defending pedophilia causes you to think fiction is cope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sometimes i worry how unprofessional i or my account looks when verified or professional accounts follow me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why tf does twitter keep doing this to me

everytime i dig through followers it just makes them disappear for whatever fuckig reason, as if some sort of security measure #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["waaaaa waaa i hate smoltubers and lolicons they're pedos" -OP #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# jokes aside, i wouldn't disrespect scott's religion by doing things to his characters that he wouldn't approve off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a large issue that hurts me is that i've been seeing a few "idol" friends of mine liking tweets of antis/fancops mocking proship/profic accounts i follow such as #USER#. i get a unnerved feeling seeing someone like a tweet trying to completely misarticulate a tweet- (1/3)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# idk if following them back is really a good idea though.

i had a stress meltdown because of a pro-child molester that harassed me, and was also approached by a old pedophile user from before, who hates lolicons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[he called himself "jesus" as a means of larping judge hearings and admitted to molesting his mom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# the thing here is ironically obligatory because he's part of a clique of unironic pedophiles who retweet lolicon but slam lolicons who rightfully out them and call them outnnthey don't like that normal non-pedophilic lolicons aren't the same as them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[well fuck you, rapists don't get free passes #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S-shosho had bad dream last night.. *coooo..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how do you be "sexually attracted to the features of children" dude.

petit women exist. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-belly stuffing/water belly inflation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you shouldn't be paying jack shit for that. 

no wonder anyone who has sexual attraction to non consenting individuals always has the lowest lives #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[she insulted/ostracized loli tubers/smoltubers. and pulled shit about lolicons. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# if only i could transfer everything from my copy of lbp3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THEY'RE STILL DOING DBFZ DLC WHAT THE FUCK????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# pedos use fiction that they seek interest in because they want to scapegoat the law.. but they'll eventually get tired of it.

no, nobody else who are non-pedos that consume the fiction are that. watch what you spit out without regarding that CSA survivors cope with such media.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[discord was full of creepy groomed kids who acted like horny zombies making ships and kids as young as 12 being there (when they shouldn't be for gods sake) and amor even siding with a groomer. 

i can't do much, but what the community can start doing is gatekeeping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[segregation and the act of child rape are two different things #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# that's a water bed worth cuddling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# &gt;demon girl

again...... you need help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is too good already, we need more games like this

no, not like fortnite, that fucking sucks #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[whenever i'm in my friend's Curious cat profiles, i try to think of the fairest or funniest things to say

9/10 i'm too afraid to say the things because i swear it won't work out

as one has stated, i'm super awkward. â˜¹ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why do minor stans have the worst profile layouts and tweets #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i'm pretty sure the reason they bring that up is because of the nsfw accounts who follow 17+ accs out of cluelessness or the adults who have to discipline the kids because of them bitching like complete babies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lolicon isn't pedophilia. the artform is unbroadly seen as obscene on a moral stance, and conflated between the realms of fantasy and reality.

many argue on multiple stances-
"IT'S LITERALLY A CHILD"-what child? are they real?
"THEYR'E ATTRACTED TO CHILDLIKE BOD-" petit women. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tell that to the majority of the CSA survivor community. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[assuming all e-dating goes bad/wrong is cringe #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# "literal child porn" you're basically saying children consent to porn even though they can't stop saying that lmfao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[which one of you ordered the pizza with chocolate sprinkles and clam sauce? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this isn't really about rape and moreso pedophiles, who seem to really want to justify their attraction as "normal and healthy" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the application of electric currents or heavy pressure i looked around the room at the numerous inventions eloquent testimony of a tireless ingenuity "Sir, it is lamentable that mass agricultural development is [not] speeded by fuller use of your marvelous mechanisms Would it not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# you've been shown you aren't mature enough to handle outside online spaces that don't focus on nesscitant safety/ the necessity of safety for "children".
by bitching about adult content you've lead yourself astray to concequences of your actions.

this ain't no playground cowboy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[pain 

too much pain

must soothe with ladies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# idk how some of my old friends decided to like this tweet so uh

listen dude, nobody in the thread has a attraction to children or is defending it.
the tweet is mocking DBZ virgins for getting mad at artist for drawing porn of fictional characters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you can't actually be saying this with a etika-clause pfp #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i think we're going to need clarification on how 2006 planet classifications are "wrong". #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["blah blah hate on pedophiles is bad blah pedophiles deserve love"nndid you hear about that one dude with pedophilia who hated it and wanted to chemically castrate himself #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 5$ lefty:
-close-range stand
-has the ability to decapitate any person by biting them
-can turn into goo
-will disable for 10 hours if the user is given 5$
-has a 90% chance to summon a clone of markiplier that only laughs for 10 mins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the autistic urge to buy all 4 power rangers pudgy pig figures from Hasbro lighting collection, bandai retro, classic retro, and funko pop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[those people obviously don't know better, because that's how they get more marginalized by moral cuckolds.

taking offense to fictional material doesn't solve anything. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# this is hypocrisy lmfao

"child sexual attraction is acceptable"

"don't be hornyposting if you're a minor!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Lolisho is illegal"

Then these people pull the first thing that comes up #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Literally how did he not see that i was replying to a pedophile against their fallacies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# &gt;be me
&gt;first app i ever chose
&gt;not know that topic-strict communities exist
&gt;go to smash amino
&gt;the mods are confusingly unreasonable and toxic
&gt;community has bot and rule issues
&gt;banned for speaking up against a scam poll made  by a jackass user and the leader himself
&gt;regret. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["friends"

you have 0 followers and all you've been doing since account creation is starting virtue signal over a fucking demon girl with big tits who happens to still be "biologically 14-16"

nobody is laughing at anybody except you. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[saying this to the arkansas dude i used to follow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-those really sexy size differences where the guy is a pratical smol boy and the girl is like

6ft or so with a giant pair of tits and thiccness as much as a bowl of oatmeal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[from what i solely identified, people who moral crusade against transgressive media (particularly anime lolis/shotas) have seemingly only of 3 arguements: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[every time someone casually drops the most overtly offensive racist xenophobic tweets because of the fiction japan makes, i lose 9 braincells #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[t-tya heehe... shosho don't have to worry about beiing issue for other grown ups.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[no children should be allowed in your vicinity for god help they're told you're a pro-pedophile #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2020: "lolicons are pedophiles!"n"but being sexually attracted to real children is a-okay!"nn2022: "anime is for pedophiles! and i'm a pedo who likes anime!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# they just brought up a 4chan "study" from some autiscuck who "reads too much loli" claiming artists who draw loli are pedophiles, and showing a picture of some lolicon media with a hidden message or some shit.nni'm tired of this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-growth/inflation sounds: gurgle... creakkk.. groan.... stretchh... grrrgrg....pshh....pft.... etc etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# god help them if they think their autism led them to make this conclusion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# it isnnit was a fucking troll pedo from 2020 who ratioed me in a poll when i encountered themnnalso the same person that said to me "lolicons are pedophiles!" but yet admitted to being one themselves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# huh... looks interesting. what are you developing it on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# they're really scared of you bcs you're a horny 32 year old with fetishes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# no offense roxx, but tbf, i've been noticing you've been following alot of ironic pedophiles and larping pedos for seemingly no good reason. i wouldn't follow said users simply because they share ideals or you're trying to understand them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You can't be saying this with a kid sasuke pfp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# h-how bottom heavy exactly?* kya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# huh....

i guess we're getting warner land instead of disneyland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[fun fact: most people who mock and or berrate lolicons are projecting pedophiles 99.9% (ex.) of the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i'm pretty sure newgrounds is adults only.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["you see good sir, not every pedophile is a pedophile, there are child molesters, and child exploiters, and those who photograph CSEM. those aren't pedophiles.nnow listen as i proceed to longfully list off why molesting and sexualizing kids is perfectly acceptable and legal." #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 10/10 legs

needs more thigh thicc though imo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["invalid"

the only one invalid here is you dude, who thinks that because i'm disapproving of your sick mental condition that you think i'm "invalid" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# weird for them to groom children and animals then bring up religion and purity and then bring up ageplay.

like.. i think the entirety of the ageplay community (includes actual CSA victims) would not want to associate with some creepy pedo dog fucking lady one bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# oh yea, the dolls being called loli is misinformative misuse of complicated foriegn terminology. knowing how it was used when a article was made on a dutch pedophile creating baby sex dolls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[user is autistic but has a bunch of bullshit on her carrd lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nobody except genuine predators and morons trace actual children from real life

EX- that one predatory lesbian/transfem artist who traced someone's baby for diaperfur art]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-by a deer. 
bulma flashed her naked vagina and tits at roshi.
so on. 

like, jesus christ. both anti-lolicons/anti-r34 and dbz virgins are so fucking dumb. i can't imagine coming up with the blandest tweets using serious terms to call out a innocent person. please stop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt;looks like adult, is underage, is "adult"

bullshit #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# okay then that means people who play gta are violent murderersnnand furries are zoophiles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# off topic here but i'm sorry about something recent that has been going on regarding your change to a 18+ acc and the thing with the trans stuff. 

i don't think you're in the wrong here at all, you're innocent.

you're a wonderful wonderful artist pup-chan, don't forget it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i bet playstation removed it for their regulations lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# miitopia is good 

i'm not doing KSA just yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i however don't trust the claims of any "non offenders" who are questionably open about their attraction and wish to glorify it on the web. that's what vito is trying to pull here basically, as he watched cuties and praised it. 
those are just pedophiles wishing to be punched.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the proper viewpoint i wish for pedophiles to look towards is not seeking acceptance online. it worsens the condition. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# the thing that bothers me is how these types of shamers exist because:
1. they were specifically abused using the material, leading them to believe it's seriously negative, and that they should despise it without understanding
2. they were groomed to despise it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[asian artist: draws literally something

twitter:
OMG THIS PERSON DREW *PEDOPHILIA*/*ZOOPHILIA/*GORE*/"*CHILD PORN*"/*MLM FETISHIZATION*/*LESBIAN ERASURE*/*BAD THING* CANC3L THEM #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm not a kid anymore so kids aren't the prime interest in me anymore. i can't have minors meddling in my business as such. (2/2**)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# they think anime depictions being different from real life "makes no sense"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "durr.. white racism isn't possible becuz they invented it.. durrr..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["TWITTER IS 13+, WHICH MEANS IT'S FOR KIDS! AND I DON'T CARE ABOUT MY STUPID PARENTS NOT GIVING A GOOD WATCH OVER ME SO I CASUALLY FIND PORN TO COMPLAIN ABOUT! I GOT SEVERELY TRAUMATIZED WAAAAAA"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 3. mystery song (god glitcher)
2. bugged
1. triple trouble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "she's still a child"

WHAT FUCKING CHILD HAS BODY CHANGING SUPERPOWERS AND IS A DEMON DUDE

STOP BEING FUCKING SCHIZOPHRENIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tldr- survivors shaming other survivors for how they cope says alot about the shamer than the victim coping innocently lmao. they could be "psuedo-groomed" to shame someone if they happen to use something they were abused with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me: i love tiddies and big girlsnnthem: *rants on about political sides while arguing in favor of child molesters and CSEM while "mocking" lolicons in the worst possible way*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[honestly. this whole generation has been a mistake. i ironically want it to be back to the time evangelicals called everything "satantic" instead of moral crusaders calling everything "pedophilic".

this is giving me such bad stress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# muta probably is too pussy to admit his fallacies/conflicting opinions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# the tweet about necrophilia was him comparing non-consent not mattering between a dead actress and a child.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[twitter is suspending your accounts because you violate their policies dumb fuck #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i missed when disney didn't overtly steal every Ip they could get their hands on and weren't too stingy of copyright.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[???????????????

you literally called me a trog in one of your ad hominem tweets you dumbfuck #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that's basically the emphasis of the qrt you made to that DBZ artist

it's not really "saying shit" if you complained about how they were basically wasted talent because they drew porn of pan (which most of us don't give a shit about) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you've checked in within my Carrd bio, or know me best.. just please bear with me that this B-day marks my final time with being negatively infantalized. i no longer will have to suffer the title i've hated for so many years. 
for those who trust me, it's your choice to stay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3. whilist somewhat true, i'd digress. pedophiles do have a heavy reputation of breaking on their promises, and will tend to heavily act on urges. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["DUHHH BUT IF SOMEONE LIKES A FICT CHARACTER THAT KID IT BAD AND ILLEGAL!"

Cool. lets see what happens when later they ban violent video games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# already seeing a contradiction here...

people have common rape fantasies, but it's not a sign they approve of or endorse/desire rape irl. 

you literally said GTA doesn't cause violence... but then proceed to say fiction in a sexual sense of taboo is bad and "will lead to irl".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# this is bringing up "cartoon pedophilia"... which is apparently "movies and shows featuring pedophiles".... not japanese loli...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[he literally deleted the tweets and privated

lol #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[they also called the US a "human rights country" or something lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[women literally made some of the most notorious anime girl designs

a fucking woman created bayonetta #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boob. Butt. Thigh. Hip. Tall. The perfect girl combination.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# it's not real lmao 

i don't even live in the UK aka Unus kuckold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "half-breed men dni"nnyea that's kinda really discriminative towards mixed race people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[north korea is suprisingly more painfully ironic than the films made around them. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i suggest you back out of the whole "lolicons are pedos" con booth before the con jacks your career.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# like.. it's okay to find fictional taboo stuff gross and what not... but you can't go saying senseless things without knowing that people who have had a history of trauma will use such dark fiction to cope.

take this image: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[jojo- jotaro
jobro- Ceasar
antagonist- dio
arc- bohemian rhapsody (stone ocean)
outfit- jotaro part 3
stand ability- bohemian rhapsody
stand design- bohemian rhapsody
fight- bohemian rhapsody
opening- part 1 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you have to be the most kind of fucking stupid to blackwash someone's pfp as a own]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[to sound like it's bad when the art in question is of a fucking anime character. the art even had to be from a artist who was dogpiled by a bunch of virgin dbz fans who hated that he drew pan porn. like... dbz literally had multiple scenes like that. pan got her tits sucked-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# a majority of the genshin character ages are unexplained and or unknown. many cope shit to age check or guess that the loli characters like klee are 8-10 years old. 
they even claim venti (who is a god of thousands of years) is still physically underage as well as traveler.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# oh yea those scripted moments in lego games where you can manipulate where they play with the wrong characters

just like how i had steven spielberg and mr. DNA running with the survivor group in lego jurassic park's story  mode]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the problem is that you'd rather bitch about anime girls being "molested" than real kids being abused says alot about you. putting drawings before real human beings simply because "BUT THEY're NormALIZING Child ABuse" is not valid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yall ever played the PR samurai game: rangers together samurai forever? childhood memories man..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FINALLY I CAN ACCESS DISCORD NSFW CHANNELS NOW

it's not even my b-day yet but whoop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# they're basically saying when it doesn't have age gap or loli it's bad

but how they're making the point is ironic because they're not calling it "lolicon", they're a real pedophile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ah??

did you fix a virus issue or something??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ugh.. i had to fucking block that chizu guy finally. got tired of him trying to use ambiguity, 4-chan, and ubran dictionary to prove his point. 

whether he gets banned or not, i hope to never see  him again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# that would be a perfect size f--ffor you
i agree

kya,.. need big girlsss...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7. largely centered by seeing someone/(or my gf really) in a massive bodily state. they tower over me, their plump large body looming over my smallness. then i'm gently played with, cuddled, snuggled, pampered. basically be dommed softly by a huge girl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# affor. trans moot has been judged by others bf and has large issues being able to talk with someone who isn't transphobic and is able to actually help her :(. i really want to help her but can't do as much, and would love if she got the help she needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "duhhh mastodon won't ban me! they're DEcENtralizeD"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[people misgendered omocat and they don't know toby literally made homestruck albums about incest lmfao #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hot take: all pedophiles should be chemically castrated and banned from the internet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the fbi isn't going to help your crybaby vitrtue signal dumbass #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# weird how this specifically joins them to hate monger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[probably my most favorite episode of the entire DSQ series was "pet peeve". i loved the mutant dino-pets, and it was something i probably watched alot for the plot points and jokes. ironically enough i don't know how the "hey good looking" line didn't become a meme somehow. (4/?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# this would mean that pedophiles and child molesters aren't technically too different lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# so this is basically the "all gays are pedos" monger but in reverse.nnwhat a bunch of clowns them antis are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# well the anti just went up and said "twitter is the only place where you'll see people defend their attractions to children" and the thing in question is a fancop mocking account making fun of DBZ virgins for getting mad at a dbz artist having drawn pan porn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Idk how you came up with "support pedophilia" but you really don't need to be on the internet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what shosho wishes for:
*1k followers
*more mutuals that have huge boobs/thighs/booties/bellies
*more mutuals that are tall (pref. female)
*to be shorter
*oneechan mutuals
*mommy mutuals
*attention]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[again, the "trauma" kids get from seeing stuff they aren't supposed to is chalked up to bad parenting, the same reason kids become aggressive and abnormal from excessive gaming or mature games. 

it's not the fault of those who provide the services, it's themselves, and parenting #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i hate flat chests 
i hate flat chests 
i hate flat chests 
i hate flat chests 
i hate flat chests 
i hate flat chests 
i hate flat chests 
i hate flat chests 
i hate flat chests #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# PS- if you want some junk in the trunk, i'd advise looking at weight gain remedies, specifically ones for gaining fat in the specific places. and granted, ones that do say it won't give belly fat and such. those exist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me when my gf finally comes get me and takes me to her place after i'm done with school and my parents leave her to care for me

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[can somebody pls report him so that weird fucking blackwashed pfp of gregory from fnaf sb goes away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. okay, cool, i have a trans gf, but the issue here is pedophiles glorificating their condition online instead of seeking to aim their behavior towards treatmentnn2. idk man i'd be scared knowing there are pedophiles in my neighborhood that'd want to fuck men3. THEN HELP THEM. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i've been manhassled by at least 4 fucking pedophilic incels who can't get bitches because they want kidsnnwhy did god create these fucking excuses of shit sacksnnwhy are they pedophiles. why pedophiles.nnno more. this needs to be cracked down on.nadd a feature to report pedos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[fictional "children" look nothing like nor are "children".nnyou're implying as if anyone who consumes fiction with such are pedophiles. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[well i'mma go to sleep now guys

i have tried my new grooming kit you may have seen before, it works pretty well. shaved my tummy and arms. 

goodnight now, boob night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# seems so, bcs peach and daisy are nude at the end]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[going to bed guys gn

promote me to others so they can find shosho ig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i can link a thread where a shitload of people rallying lolicon turned out to be complete demons themselves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9. (skipped the last one because it's too vague)nok, because they're begging to be abused by both molesters and acting pedophiles. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. and?????? unless you're not underage i don't think i'd approve that. not to mention that being normal attracted but defending pedophiles is not okay.nn2. and???? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# amor, the founder of the fungang and bob and bosip mod was exposed as abusing his team into overworking, and acted innapropriately with minors. he even drew porn of some of his friends characters (the friends were minors) without permission.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-soft dominant older girls, the ones that have huge tits and thicc bodies and use it to seduce smaller guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[fancops excuses are straight up trash too-

&gt;they thrown in memes that make no sense or were contradicted
&gt;google searches OOCT in 3 seconds
&gt;a "lawfirm" site from california that has no idea how the US constitution works
&gt;logical fallacies

 stop crying like a bitch. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[someone get me the sauce on this Thumbnail

please

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# that's not a Pokemon! that's a Gðšð² lð®ð¢ð ð¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# bruh

imagine making a blocklist but not blocking the people in question]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[fuck you , nobody in the autistic community owns you #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in conclusion: pedophiles fucking suck. children cannot consent to sexual relationships. fuck off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# LOOK MA IM BECOMING A (ÃŸÄ¯ÄŸ ÅŸÄ§0Å¥) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["evil" tf2 be like:
-trolldiers are the undermined player stereotype instead of F2P
-demoknights are hated
-F2Ps are showered with free unusuals because "they're in poverty"
-hacker bots exist but suck ass instead of terrorizing players, only using soft mic-spam
-medics suck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-heavily seductive sounding female voices, particularly ones that are high pitched.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is coming from someone who is "autistic" and reads too much "loli" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# dw i'm sure pope didn't care enough to get genocide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm autistic and can understand most jokes well #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you left a long hiatus since having been banned and creeping away to some obscure twitter bootleg before coming back and now decide to change methods of owning to claiming big lolicon figures came out as pedophiles secretly (according to you, a pedophile who says lolis are pedos)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[very great art and artstyle, very nice and sweet, but i have a hadr time connecting knowing i was only temporarily mutuals before a follow clearing. i miss being mutuals. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# oh shit we're doing a anti-pax rebellion now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my oneesan friend is apparently REALLY eager to try and get super thicc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As for KFDP, well.... it's way more closer to a sentai KO fever dream than DSQ. 
unlike DSQ, which had mutant teens who could turn into dinosaurs, KFDP featured a group of mutant dinosaurs that survived extinction, and turned into humanoids. it's basically fucking TMNT. (7/?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# we've reach peak official shitposting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[where the fuck are all these pro-pedos coming from crawling out of the depths of dark twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# i mean, rex technically still got in somehow. i'm still glad for that. in the final smash, intro, victory, and taunts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i don't think even anyone knows what the fuck "PTHC" is nor wants to care about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# ching chong is from the chinesennooga booga is from the european aboriginals and africansnntacos chimichangoes is from the southern mexicans and Spaniards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[even now this still fucking sounds like fire #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt;"borderline"
nope lol

you literally mentioned having a little partner #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i have friends

just not enough

bold of you to immediately assume that #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[kapwing finally fucking added the ability login/sign up using email as opposed to facebook and google, now my newest videos shouldn't have that dastardly watermark in there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt;"animated characters can consent duur hurr" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# tbf the ratio of dominant alpha males to submissive males is underrated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nobody puts urban slang on wikipedia #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# that's just the canon age of the characters, but it's arbitrary to reality. 

jack to lolis, hate on practically the same thing from a shonen anime, defend real CSEM
kind of sad hypocrisy for a neckbeard if you ask me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# how are you blocked by a majority of the most shittiest accounts on this site including rando gimmicks/stan accs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# sure, she's not a complete midget, but she still has developmental issues. 

i literally saw a (Chigago P.D.?) episode where this dude had a girlfriend of age who had psuedo-dwarfism. he was assaulted by mistake for taking her for a walk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so uh that dude in the picture has multiple pro-map tags so yea, please block them

nevermind the weird fake flags #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GODAMMIT I WANTED TO BUY THE DOOM SLAYER MII COSTUME BUT I WAS SHORT 1 CENT

CURSE YOU TAXES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i bet the fucking map community ironically supports and celebrates this #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt;"canonically underage"

&gt;ralsei isn't even human nor real #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# does this dude even know he's the hypocrite lol?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[but you literally said anime is for pedophilesnnso you contradicted yourself #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[none of the artists who draw lolicon are drawing "children", they're drawing depictions of humans resembling young individuals.nnthey're not pedophiles dumbfuck. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[still reminiscing back to phisnom (creator of fnaf +) being abliest because he thinks mentally disabled people "shouldn't be on the internet" and blocks them for following him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just a fyi guys i'm not going to sleep if i'm yawing it's way early for that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm obligated to say that pedophiles saying they "wouldn't ever offend or harm a child" is massive cope if they're literally romantically/sexually attracted to them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the "evidence" you provide is not only invalid and irrelevant, but completely out of the question. you're not making anything easier for yourself. #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>