<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Next Covid strain could kill many more, warn scientists ahead of England restrictions ending. Demands grow for government science chiefs to reveal evidence backing move to lift last protective measures #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Santa never looked so good ðŸ˜€. Happy Xmas and a great new year. Stay safe and well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When I have my Elite Series 2 / Xbox Series X controller (probably any) plugged in via USB as I always do. It SHOULD NOT to go to sleep or at least give the option. Chatting for 5 mins to buddies only to find you have to wake up a cabled controller is wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ahh well, Thanks for the update, but I will never know RIP #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You should put on a mask bud. KOTOR was allways on PC &amp; Xbox. Games that have history on PlayStation are being honoured by Xbox and will stay on PlayStation. Hence you still have Minecraft. So its different. I was agreeing that games should be multiplat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Much has been made about .. Oh wait your name is John snow because you know nothing. Those games are cross gen not next get... gods what a waist of review. Thanks for reminding me why I stopped watching Click. A gold fish would have given more in-depth info. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did you see the windows phone in the black widow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There is no problem, otherwise than followers of TC games don't want a Battle Roy as the next TC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's been happening on xbox for ages, those who play on xbox play on console those who play on PC play on pc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Assides from multi monitor support, new store, android apps, HDR / auto HDR, direct storage. True there are some things that get changed I don't like. I can't run win 11 and don't know when I will get to, but we are safe to run Windows 10 till 2025, but you are just wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ahhh but that's the thing .. timed exclusive it be lols]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# RIP the best of both possible worlds, apologies for the right wing dumber and dumest mad harder conspiracy believer take over of the UK. Have a happy Xmas and New year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We need it, and no I don't mean football either..sigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Even on PC power user can't boost, that would be a hacker. If devs want to redo old games &amp; boost fps / graphics then xbox are happy for them to, and some devs gave. But what xbox dose is independent of devs and dose not touch their code. So all you devs feel free to up update.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Whatever I allways boycott all PC games on my #HASHTAG# that go to #HASHTAG# but not #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Also getting FPS boost and Automatic HDR, playing Sniper Elite 4 boosted to 60 FPS is amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think any single parent should be apriciated for how hard they have to work, i don't think pitty comes into it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But that's so proconsumer.. How yucky, why can't I pay even more if I want to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Just got one for the arival of my #HASHTAG# on the 10th, its so good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thanks to everyone that work on and around Halo.. you guys knocked the pvp out of the park ... please deliver on a amazing story for the pve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Jordan I love your work, but what is with Comedy Central banning the UK now? #USER# Keep up the good shows even if I cant easily follow it all. So long free press!! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sorry that the #HASHTAG# let the #HASHTAG# down, but we are not all bat shit crazy in the UK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Officially who gives a toss, please find some news to earn your money and subs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# But your an expert and experts are no longer valid #HASHTAG#.. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 8 TB, and how about a docking station to take 1TB, 2TB, 4TB and 8TB drives in any combination]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So you can by a xbsx or xbss, or a ps5 or a ps5 no dvd. Not seen ps prices yet but ps5 is not likely to math xbss. Xbss give the cash short ot those who don't care about 4k an entry point to play games on next gen console more powerful than Xbox One X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They get more exclusivity by not being able to use it I guess!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep, It's my first day back at work in London today, I am not looking forward to sharing London with all those anti vaccination loons who protested over the weekend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hmm I sense a Terry Pratchett quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Xbox have you covered.. plug and play lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I don't mind him talking ps, but I don't tag ps guys when talking xbox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hahahahah saw bones I think. Buddy I don't jump into playstation threads and trash them, just go home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh well, thanks for info. That's fracks me than. Will never get it then. Have a good weekend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So I can't play a single player game on xbox?.... well that is 100% untrue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hahahahahahaha.. ohh that hurts .. hahahahajahaha ...oh my sides hurt... hahahahaha .. she .. you do know what an independent developer is? You have a point over streaming, NO ONE KNOWS what the game is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# untill they brake .. good thing you have the space for all those consols as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's Great how about bring all of the benefits you bring to iOS/Android user to Windows Phone 10 users #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well, happy to know date/price, yet sad it leaked before PS leaked. You guys obviously prepared so much but only to have it drop early. For those short on cash, thanks for #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG#. All said &amp; done I am still stoked and prepared to pre order #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You can have both if you want and can afford it, even a PC, but I play on #HASHTAG# with my beauty of a #HASHTAG#SeriesX ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sorry but I actually have games to play vs arguing with trolls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Bin in tomany parties with people ranting about "lagit not fair" .. if your in a game that makes you feel target ... then just don't be there. It is after all said and done the sole purpose of the other team to frack you up.. hence pvp. Play a game that leaver you feeling good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Founder for that game .. never had a PC good enough to play it lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hmm Windows phone .. sigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Buddy are you being funny or high? Sovereignty had nothing to do with this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You are correct Xbox didn't make Psychonauts 2. They bought Double Fine. Giving them time and money to perfect the game. Hence play station gets a PS4 version, Xbox sets a Xbox Series S/X version. Funny how this works eh? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤§]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sorry to hear that, losing a loved one is hard, my Mum passed away not that long ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hmm good for crapgamer then lol... so why have a dislike button?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Got both .. who needs 5g lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That looks eraser head levels of wrong lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ahh yes, I see it was highlighted using inverted commers lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Any show that kills of characters for no good narrative reason other than shock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's irrational but so is Brexit, calling the moon fake and being an anti vaccination muppet.. but that dose not stop them ðŸ˜€.. stand up for your jokes ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Multi cultural..elf, dwarfs,  humans, or so etc lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Your supposed to be a pc player according to profile. All those games are going to PC and Xbox you big fake pony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Really don't give a hoot about final fantasy any version. You PlayStation bots keep on trying to create wars when in only exist in your black lil heart. Try playing games, you will have less time to grief.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# So once we leave the EU we can then unshackle our selves from the tyranny of the UK government]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# HP baked beans on toast is the king of food]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Looking at your profile you are a PC and PlayStation playing where I am a PC and Xbox player, I assume that is why you hate Xbox so much. But that is no excuse for you childish foul mouthed insults. I dont talked to infants. learn to talk with out insulting or lose. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No I have not, why would I? The actual not fake reviews  did not say burning. You have a crap load of data being transferred the power has to go someplace. In a doc the data would be distributed. You would know of raid arrays, those drives dont burn down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# True, but just imagine having a machine that supports it lol .. some day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# How???????. Granted if one was to cut open the skulls children then place a mask around the brain ðŸ§ , I do agree that would be detrimental to learning and life. But do explain with science, I would be fascinated?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When you write for "The world's leading games industry website." I do have something to tell you. The Xbox Series S is more balanced and viable than than the last Gen Xbox One X and the Xbox Series X is the most powerful box for the Next gen. What is your malfunction?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Warframes main game is not space combat but inter ship combat is exciting, No Man's Sky is all about space ships but they fly and look like potatoes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Speak to the cult leader of apple, it's in his hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And if this is related to the engin used in Fable.. oh wow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Firefox is so good it had low adoption.. Wow that must be so good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# what a surprise, I never saw that coming lol, still its all good within the sales model.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Wow that's a lot of money" thank brexit madnes the UK won't be getting any of that, few we really dodged the bullet on that one. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hmm looks kinda familiar lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When I mentioned you did not need makeup, I was not critical of you having it on or using it. I Was saying you were amazing with or with out. Well tou have blocked me know. I truly wish you a good and happy life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's really not though. You have self-control. If you don't then don't play PVP as it will be unhealthy for you. If you find the game so bad just go play something else. Go play something you love. Either way, it's no excuse for "unsporting" bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Both are agents of discord, both are untrustworthy, both are traitors to the country they were/are heads of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Already do use N95 masks .. but do you think I will step foot in a place that let's FAKE can't put on mask nut jobs breath their particals all over the place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# LAMO you three are a killing joke to the world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# WOW so far I count 12 notifications for #HASHTAG# pre orders, no one could accuse you of hating #HASHTAG#. But hey I am sure you will POST EVERY SINGLE #HASHTAG# notification for #HASHTAG# and #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# as well wont you?  Wake me up in time for #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am deciding between the Most Powerful Console of the next Generation and the Best Value for money. Sorry PlayStation you lose on both counts, Xbox Series X all the Way #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Covid-19 symptoms raise new questions #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#19 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, or at least a special sub set of good rolls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Buddy, don't you want to hang on for the Xbox Fridge S ðŸ˜€ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# if you build thing A to match thing B, them thing A should match or exceed thing B. Because of RDNA 2, next gen SSD, and more in Xbox Series X, you can not build a PC below the price of an Xbox Series X that comes even close to matching the performance of a Series X. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# omg if chromecast don't come to uk i will die #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tried to love it.. It's not a trash game. But it feels like gears but not as good. Maybe it will be better after demo but so far it's not as good as the adverts, and nothing loop like destiny 2 like so many said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good and valid for more than #HASHTAG#, also #HASHTAG# and others but they won't be listening. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Available on pc, I guess Microsoft did not pull an apple on that one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 great reasons to vote ukip - because you know they value free speech and because .. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# LAMO and LABULSHEEET, if you spent $500 on a PC with better hardware than an Xbox Series X then you are either 1) using stolen kit 2) from the future 3) lying #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#SeriesX #HASHTAG#SeriesS #HASHTAG#GamesPass #HASHTAG#GameStudios]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Played both stalkers on PC.. can't wait for this. It had tones of weapons,  hope this is the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Happy Xmas and New year to your family and all the teams at xbox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I see you point, when it crash it can serve up an advert for the closest amberlance chancer. I cant see anything wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Her kind are an embarrassment to journalists and humanity in general]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I see your point, but this started on the merits of running windows as a VM on Mac. Simples run windows :-). But I do see your complications.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I expect Bill Gates's corp backed army is tapping into his phone and will be abducting him soon but will have left fake evidence that it was litle grey men lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# what.... No calls for extending support for windows 95.. Why not!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's so obviously a flat earth. Give all the flat earthers a free ticket into space #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think getting WB games would be good for Xbox and PC, but as much as a feel a new jerk reaction of sticking it to PlayStation, I agree it would be healthy to keep it Multi Platform. Though there could still be some new IP made be them that was just Xbox Series X and PC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Backwards compatibility on Xbox Series X lets let play Splinter Cell  (XB), Splinter Cell Pandora Tomorrow (XB), Splinter Cell Conviction (XB360), Splinter Cell Chaos Theory (XB), Splinter Cell Blacklist (XB360), Splinter Cell Double Agent (XB360), Splinter Cell Double Agent (XB)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I said "The difference is integration between Windows OS or the lack of it in the case of ios and android." you said "It is a matter of integration not os. Add on cloud services and the story is easier.". For consumer Windows Phone was a one stop integration android &amp; ios is not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because we get to have a blue passport lol. Sad world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Your going to be beautiful with long or short in any colour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What ever is daging you down, I hope you get past it soon x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Like .00000001 chance of winning but still sucks I can't lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# But individual countries can not talk as the EU, hence the reason for EU minister's, most, etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# An end to nurfing, a stable ever expanding game, that let's you play as you want to .. kinda like you promised us all those years back. Please for the love of the speaker keep pvp and pve sand box seppeate and even potentially block some things from pvp but allow in pve. ..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hmm you know all that weight you lost..... ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hey Jim, was it hard to predict when you would open preorders, or did you just flat out lie to your self and the world LAMO. Will be happy with my #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# so that's talking "nasty"? I guess words like piffle, sugar &amp; drat are the foulest swear words he knows #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dumb trolls will be dumb lol trolls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Chris that's harsh towards #USER#, as say this is #HASHTAG# we are talking about. Given the way he and his swamp buddies don't wear masks and encourage mass meeting it's quite possible he has it. But he is quite capable of lying about this for sympathy for votes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Anti-lockdown protesters are are dangerous to themselves and the human population in general.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Its a snow day in Kent, but working from home so no excuse to bos for being snowed in lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Funny how all you ps guys where ready to preorder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wow .. how strange ðŸ¤”.. you sure your not a droid lol .. seriously had my second last week .. anti vaccination not please go land on the moon lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't think it's ugly, kinda like it. .. can't run it on my laptop lol, going to be while before I can get a laptop to run it. Interesting change of stance that win 10 could be run on lots of old kit, but Windows will force a lot ot people and organisations to buy new kit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hey #USER# thanks for spreading Fear And Disinformation... your did a brilliant job at stoking up the hate towards #HASHTAG#.  I don't place a value on that kind of click bait. It would have taken 6 mins for you to research the story. So unfollowed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hmm its amazing how much bad will still exists for xbox, granted its been a bit of a shit show, but the 3rd parties will be there, and the first parties will come. God forbid anything delays spider man cause that will be sure to be given free pass lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Year... after they franked over all the theird party face plate designers, wasn't that nice of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Also Ryan that review is contrary to what you have said on your xbox show. #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# would be nice if everything was ready. for me even without halo the speed benefit for all the games I have will be enough. We have yet to have confirmation on what is or not going to be dropping. Not panicked, the ps trolls will be busy no matter how many 1st party we had.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# LOL,  dream on.. Your work horse pc still needs a next gen ssd, Velocity Architecture, RDNA 2.. you and your budget PC can stay on the shelf in PC best buy lol #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hmm exploded, yet its melted inwards .. must come from bizarreo world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Very true but I would have plug and play over not being "proprietary". Xbox have already said they will open up to more providers so Xbox Series S/X owners will see the benerfit of plug and play plus cheaper storage and not having to find that screwdriver or lose the screw ðŸ™„ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ohh great #HASHTAG# and yet they killed Starwars 1313 #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Ahh you are one of those. It's OK, the moon is fake, there are no stars,  the earth is flat/hollow/.., dinosaur bones are fake, so many other grand truths you can believe in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You can not slap in the SSD because you cant get it yet for PC. You just admitted the X is optimized and that you ant match it. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, just block them, if they keep going for last word. It's better for your sanity ðŸ‘ðŸ™‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Shocked.. And there me wondering why all the far and ultra far right support it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Haha that way better than anything Spitting Image, or Drop the dead donkey could do, your satire and self mockery are on spot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So.... I can still get guns in Walmart? Because as a life long gamer mostly on Xbox One These days I keep hearing the xbox telling me to go slaughter people and a need a family safe place to by guns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohhh been a while since the no mans sky hype train, good to have ir back #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hey #HASHTAG# best in class at promoting #HASHTAG# or better known now as #HASHTAG# for multiple games games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Chill and relax, haters will get their own rewards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Big single players games that last 10-15 hours are by definition NOT BIG.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because 1) sonny would block it 2) NFT are  con .. good day ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The driver on my #HASHTAG# will be ready and available and run better than #HASHTAG#, but we thank them for the prolonged #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Give that man a stage show, he should have a live stand up comedy gig.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Its still a problem for #USER# and the #USER# eg #HASHTAG# book #HASHTAG# and his anti Gypsy stance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# OK Chris, not going to hammer you on this. Have a good day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Show this to a flat earthers,  they have wanted proof of Australia for years #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Cheaters are bad yes, but so are quiters, you are making it harder for the rest of the team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hmm happy to use and prefer Edge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Agreed, but they are loosing players. I seriously have no one left to play with from everyone I know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "I think anyone who had a PS4 is better off buying a Series X now, especially if they're into older games." and newer current gen and new gen games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Take your time, fill it with friends if possible, take as.long as you need.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No personally rate ES6 above GOW2, but if PlayStation makes multi plat evening then I am ok for xbox making multi plat everything .. in the mean time waiting for snow in hell .. anyway who the heck will listen to me ðŸ˜€ #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sadly been down that rabit hole and the other side of preorder cancelled. They can go farm PlayStation for all its worth. Not giving they my Xbox support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# In my ignorance I assumed they would spread the skilled players, but in practice that did not happen for most games]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# cyclists using pedestrian walk ways and blocking up train carriages ... No there are no problems with prats on bikes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I guess the big take away is that you don't get it. The other thing is you could read all the dev blogs see how it benefits them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We are in a tech privileged age.. nvidia rtx and big navi from and will power next gen pc, the rdna in xbsx is at least as powerful as the rtx 1030, and that cad is $500 just for the card.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Buddy where is my Radioshack TRS 80 version lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# " You must be 18 or over to enter, and based in the U.S. to be eligible for shipping." USA only .. so that's a hard pass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# WOW that's shockingly good the value , I can get a weaker the #HASHTAG# for the same price as the stronger #HASHTAG# , If I am only getting one .. oh yes Xbox Series X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Xbox One X to Xbox Series X, run through set via xbox app, once that was done unplugged USB drive from Xbox One X, and plugged into Xbox Series X, all done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Granted.. that would be a lil to big]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# False, you are iether a trump supporter or a bot, any one doubtful of this need only reed through your time line #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nope... its their own fake news ... best is not to try and apply logic to anti vax/masters... they defy logic ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Both .. at different times.. also coco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Peasants and Pheasants.. All can be hunted in the right season, it's seams like the time is now! HEM, HEM, CHIZ. CHIZ #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good idea, in fact they should get to smoke till they drop dead from cancer #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And PC and is a ps timed exclusive so will come to xbox as well .. thanks for the toxic #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I said nothing but the current state of the once somewhat sain conservative party, that has gone so far to the right that Margaret Thatcher and Winston Churchill would not be recognise it. You can back padel in false shame but you did attack and insult first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It dose not bother me if they develop a new bisexual or gas character I would support that. But I don't like when established characters or altered. But if this is superman's sun then it's fair game. If you don't like it then don't read it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# colteastwood #URL#, Zalker 87 #URL#, Rand al Thor 19 #URL#, Double-Barrel Gaming #URL#, XboxEra #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So he specifically mentioned PS5 because that's where the hype is at, not the facts, so he is not so much a tech reporter as opinion blogger. Probably not worth checking out #USER# unless you want unbiased info on things he loves then. Its not first time they dished on xbox.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Wow, you have so much faith in your tribe yet hold them to such a low bar. This was a made out to be a big thing and PS5 exclusive at announcement. If PS had giving him a PS5 it would only be good PR for your PS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If you think they won't put games where the market is then good luck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I think this is brilliant news, #HASHTAG# is giving the UK the entire USA as a test lab to see if our vaccine is lethal or safe, and who said there was no us/uk special relationship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So your a doctor (fake) telling us we should not trust what doctors say 
.hmmm .. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's a parody account... mute or block its up to you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It's really a bad idea to ever engaged with trolls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# LMAO have a MASSIVE catalogue on Xbox One X. In regards to combat its not to rave over. But mainly I wont support #HASHTAG# anti #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# use of Spiderman when they dont own the IP. Dev said if we want to play Spiderman play on PS, hard pass. So no loss on my side LMAO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hmm but If you plan or can only play solo you won't be in coop, so you won't need to unlock those coop things.. just a thought. If that's all your missing I am not sure at this point how big a thing it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I dont expect Spiderman ever will, not unless PlayStation stops paying. I lived that destiny &amp; PlayStation exclusives. The game can just live with out my wallet, I will give my financial support to games that dont disrespect my platform or force me to play else where for content.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# use :P or on windows find charnap.exe and search for character U+061F, or just use or]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Even if they did not not win they should be in in, frankly they would win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh well MS is dead shame they are doing so well in general then #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# On the train from Orpington to London Bridge now, 14 in carriage, 4 masked plus me, 5 half masks, and the rest are mouth breathers. Oh happy joy! Dude just got on the carriage, no mask but hey at least he had expensive ear pods, that's what matters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I hope so, getting rid of the #HASHTAG# poster baby #HASHTAG# would to a lot to stop the far right in the #HASHTAG# and #HASHTAG#. But I have my concerns about this going wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello Jason #USER# good day to you. A question, can something be done re Elite Series 2 controllers. The amount of my friends including my self who have "stick drift" is concerning considering the price. Have a good day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Well for one it won't be $79.99 LAMO, as for runner better they will have time for optimization we will see. Either we won't be paying for better graphics LANO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I guess he realy did end up making the world a safer place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No, but it's still installed, I stopped only because I am waiting for the Xbox Series X update... please be quick with that ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# In case people think I am dumping on #USER# in general. From a general tech perspective I have a lot a respect for him. But he dose often give the a perfect imitation of a windows 10, Microsoft &amp; Xbox hater. It would be more impressive if he treated tech more even-handed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not happening on my Xbox Series X plus LG CX 48]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Take your time, losing a loved one hurts, losing my farther and later my mother was simply the deapest pain and reality rip. If you need to he alone the be alone, when your ready to talk to family and friends it will help. It will pass but its OK to cry! Hugs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well in the UK you let them ride on pavements, and let them cycle on the wrong side of the road, but hey they can do anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Still a mesmerising film, with great music,  story and effects.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Honestly.. really miss that ðŸ˜ªðŸ˜€ did you get anything?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nahhh .. they will sell xbox division to PlayStation #HASHTAG# ðŸ˜€ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# allways been in favour of salary transparency. Any one with the same skill sets &amp; same experience &amp; training should be on the same salary. If management enforces an environment where transparency is not allowed you can bet they pay as little as possible...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hi James, sadly my laptop is to old.. it dose look nice though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Never had people to play it with but will stand with you to say its a Good game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I am no fan of the Tories, but as he is in charge of TLF he could do more #URL# If I was a Police office with direction to enforce the law I could  easily see enough to charge 20+ cyclists/scooters per day for being on pavement plus other offences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# on behalf of #HASHTAG# thank you for concern over financial returns, but there are more #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# out there than #HASHTAG# &amp; Xboxs Combined so feel pretty strong about it being Windows PC &amp; Xbox exclusive. They also hope you enjoy running on MS servers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# the Register telling lies about Microsoft.. How unusual]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So what are you doing about all the cycles, scooters, and other non combustion vehicles being riden on pavements by adults? Assizes from health and safety you don't know if they are just antisocial or a ride by mugger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Maybe because it dose not brake any single part of the game play.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Please #USER# stop talking facts and practicalities, they have no place in a post Donald Trump, Boris Johnson, Nigel Farage, Domic Cummings new world disorder ðŸ˜„. FYI you make a good point ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Errr what F. So dose he think he will live that long? Maybe he is getting alian DNA treatment from that doctor lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Tories are wasting Â£120m on a Brexit festival, let's spend it on recovery instead #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>