<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[When Irish clowns defeated orange Toronto cops #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Travel update for families as EU changes rules of children travelling abroad #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Edwin Poots fails in bid to become DUP South Down candidate #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shocking moment ‘footie fans’ clash in Glasgow as cops launch probe #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two men arrested after seizure of firearms, silencers and heroin in Tallaght #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six arrested after investigation into robberies targeting Asian women in San Jose #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Ice Age’ franchise tries spin-off with possum brothers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sarah Palin Spotted Dining Out in NYC Again, 2 Days After Positive COVID Test #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘No one will accept a Westminster cover-up’ says SNP as Met denies report delay #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Images emerge of $143 million stealth fighter crashing into the sea #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michigan High School Students Participating In Safe Driving Campaign #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gay’s 30-yard FG Lifts Rams Over Brady, Buccaneers 30-27 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live Updates: Nor’Easter Set to Pummel East Coast #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Nod Triggers Tennessee MAGA Carpetbagger Fight #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID Omicron News: Millions of routine vaccinations have been missed amid the Covid-19 pandemic #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kansas man traveled to D.C. to kill ‘Antichrist’ Biden: report #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Montana Curbs Wolf Hunt After 23 From Yellowstone Are Killed #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MLA REPORT: Building back better starts in the legislature – Saanich News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Asian slur yelled at basketball game between Bolingbrook, Joliet West high schools #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin says West ignoring Russia’s security concerns #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guide for public on reasons for sentences published by body for State’s judges #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cost of buying some Chicago properties drops under new ordinance #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police searching for missing siblings from Gage Park #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FDNY Reminds New Yorkers To Use Space Heaters Safely As Temperatures Dip #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five arrested after illegal guns found Friday night #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul McElroy is penalty king to complete remarkable Ballymena comeback #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gardai investigate alleged sexual assaults on teenage girls in Sligo #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the price of gas keeps going up in most provinces | CBC News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biracial American opera singer Maria Ewing dies aged 71  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Biden to move US troops in ‘near term’ to Eastern Europe over Ukraine crisis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Virginia governor shows dog’s ‘heinie,’ tells Bette Midler to kiss it during televised address #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York says it will prioritize non-White people in distributing low supply of COVID-19 treatments #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Austin tenants without gas, hot water, heat for a month #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful nor’easter slams East Coast bringing heavy snow and strong winds to millions #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘I don’t fall into male or female’: AFLW player Tori Groves-Little on coming out as non-binary #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About 40% of January 2022 COVID-19 deaths in B.C. tied to long-term care outbreaks | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flying start to this year’s Big Garden Birdwatch survey #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7th Annual Philadelphia Polar Plunge Event Begins At Citizens Bank Park #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadine Dorries faces squealing lefties: HENRY DEEDES watches Culture Sec shredding the licence fee #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’re cleaning mirrors all wrong – get rid of those pesky streaks in 3 steps #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ukrainian schools train for bomb alerts #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kayleigh McEnany: ‘I don’t say this lightly, there is a war on cops’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Northwestern Medicine Launches Nation’s First Urology Clinic Targeted Toward Needs Of Gay And Bisexual Men #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Oakland County Priest Pleads Guilty In Sex Abuse Cases, Sentenced Up To 15 Years #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silicon Valley unemployment drops, on par with rates before pandemic #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jason Van Dyke Expected To Be Transferred To Illinois Today Ahead Of February Released Date #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neil Young praises Amazon Music days after removing catalogue from rival Spotify #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[York charity’s appeal to help refugees raises £500 in just 24-hours #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TikTok’s most famous trainspotter visits Welsh railway #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five members of Team Canada delegation in COVID-19 protocol ahead of Beijing Olympics – Vernon Morning Star #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘No way back’ for PM if he misled parliament over parties at No 10 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gardai to consider possible probe into Kerry mental health service failings #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Risky and significant’: Canadian capital braces for trucker protests #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jack Harrison believes Leeds can emerge from their injury crisis stronger #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homeless Encampment Sweeps Begin Near SoFi Stadium Ahead Of Super Bowl #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | While Indigenous and Black people are killed for speaking up, white supremacists get a free pass in Canada. Just look at the convoy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sooke School District seeking funds for seismic upgrades – Victoria News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jammu and Kashmir: Police Officer Shot Dead by Terrorists in Anantnag District #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maritimes awaits wrath of latest winter blast | CBC News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No bail for man accused of shooting at CPD officer during Loop traffic stop #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celtic vs Dundee Utd: Live Stream, TV Channel, kick-off time and team news #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recap: Eagles chat with Jimmy Kempski #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philadelphia Will Lift Snow Emergency At 5 P.M. On Saturday #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the pandemic’s unequal toll on people of color underlines U.S. health inequities – and why solving them is so critical #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pedestrian struck in Saanich crosswalk after driver failed to stop – Victoria News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MSNBC’s Reid: Republicans Using ‘Hitler’ Tactics to Exploit ‘White Grievance and Rage’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taliban, Western officials meet in Oslo to discuss Afghanistan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesting truckers and supporters converge on Parliament Hill #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[49ers Fans Look to Make Noise, Boost Team at NFC Championship Game #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report says Tom Brady, who lost two Super Bowls to Giants but won six others, is retiring – but that’s disputed | amNewYork #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[City Snow Plow Truck Crashes Into Vehicle In The Loop #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man United youngster Savage added to FIFA 22 for first time in latest update #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: Gov. Hochul updates New Yorkers on COVID-19 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lottery ticket worth $421 million sold at Woodland Hills gas station #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strip Clubs in Dallas Push Back on City Council, Closing Time at Center of Lawsuit #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dog lured to safety with Cheetos, now named ‘Cheeto,’ soon up for adoption #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aussie rival Max Purcell does Nick Kyrgios dirty before Open final #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dallas’ Vogel Alcove Breaking Cycle Of Poverty Through What Looks Like Playtime #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parties beg Italy’s 80-year-old president to stay in office #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emotional Ash Barty triumphs in Australian Open #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayer and Prostitutes: Redeeming Love Tackles Faith-Based Romance – LA Weekly #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Brady is reportedly retiring after saying football is taking a toll on his body and relationships #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regina charity looking to build 6 duplexes for low-income single mothers – Regina | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Brothers And Big Sisters Of Texas Is Looking For Volunteers To Mentor Young Boys #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lydia Ko takes back outright lead after third round of Gainbridge LPGA #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three Mpumalanga men in court for demanding a share of R2m from an NPO | News24 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘SP Adopted Model of Destruction, Development Only in Graveyard’: Adityanath #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Ku Klux Klan Hall In Fort Worth Being Turned Into ‘Arts And Community Healing’ Space #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rail line in southeast L.A. County approved as leaders seek to speed up construction #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UN rights chief: Reparations needed for people of African descent #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mitaa Group Moves Ahead On Redevelopment of Shriners Hospital #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Braid: Premier Kenney stakes his leadership survival on ‘Open for Spring’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italian Lawmakers Say They Have Agreed to Re-Elect Sergio Mattarella as President #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police retrieve loose horse and stolen vehicle in busy night #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Juve Zakaria claim made as Villa strive for Bentancur deal #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diego Verdaguer, Mexican-Argentine singer-songwriter, dead from COVID at 70 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honduras: Chaos in congress as politicians brawl over election of new president #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Covid-19 pandemic approaches 2-year mark, experts weigh in on the future of restaurants #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman wrongly suspected of killing an entire family speaks out #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethereum Bullish Signal: Number Of Holders With 1 ETH Touches New ATH #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Litter Boxes for Students Who Identify as Furries? Not So, Says School Official #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State grant to help fund Riverside homeless project #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tribal eviction plan pits Native American authority vs. civil rights #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Prioritizing Antiviral Pills for ‘Non-White’ People #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emmerdale fans gobsmacked at David’s epic hair transformation as he returns #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland boss Andy Farrell not worried by lack of club games ahead of Six Nations #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dusty Can Of Bamboo Shoots In Back Of Cabinet Last Remaining Trace Of Woman’s Withered Cooking Ambitions #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Punjab elections: Navjot Singh Sidhu declares assets worth Rs 44.63 cr #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghanistan’s Taliban have started their first talks in Europe since takeover #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Borders care home celebrated Rabbie Burns in true Scottish style – Deadline News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politicians must stop blaming unemployment on foreigners, says Amnesty International #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghan women’s rights activist ‘hopeful’ after talks with Taliban delegation in Norway #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 injured in Pittsburgh bridge collapse; Human chain formed to help rescue people from bus | LIVE #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barty outplays Collins to win maiden Australian Open title #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deputy who mentored young officers is gunned down during traffic stop, Texas cops say #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Energy provider warns of potential power cuts, ahead of Storm Malik, which ‘will bring strong winds across Scotland’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dad who killed kids in murder-suicide named #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful winter storm slams into eastern US #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents in Iowa are suing a school over a video that shows a white student pretending to execute another student wearing blackface #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wounded Warrior Project 5K raises money to help injured veterans ‘Carry Forward’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[List Of States Reopening Schools, Colleges From February 1 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. Ron Johnson Is Betting On Conspiracy Theories For Reelection #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women’s Ashes Test match, day three: Australia v England – live! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Diego Unified approves redistricting map meant to increase racial minorities’ representation #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omicron infections have peaked nationally, Canada’s top doctor says | CBC News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keith Cradle aims to teach kids: Black people camp and hike, too #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All iPhone users can shut down spammers with this robocall blocking trick #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many Super Bowls has Tom Brady won? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Zealand premier Jacinda Ardern isolates after coronavirus contact #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joni Mitchell joining Neil Young in protest over Spotify #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valley Fair Mall Plan to Charge for Parking Draws Employees’ Ire #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge approves agreement to destroy gun used by Kyle Rittenhouse #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gayle King signs new deal with CBS, spurning interest from CNN #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covid: UK records 89,176 cases and 277 deaths in latest daily figures #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are travel credit cards worth it? Absolutely. Here are the best cards to get | CNN Underscored #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jokic logs 6th triple-double in January to top Pels #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘He absolutely will do it’: Why Putin seems poised to attack Ukraine – after one of surest signs yet #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID In Minnesota: 43 Deaths, Including 1 Inmate Fatality, Reported Friday #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LETTER: Seniors should have access to COVID rapid tests – Victoria News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greater Manchester to be hit by high winds from Storm Malik #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World heavyweight champion Tyson Fury will take on Dillian Whyte in $59 million blockbuster #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. researcher shows how Syrian refugees settling in Vancouver adapt #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 deaths, 2,137 new cases of COVID-19 in B.C. Friday – Victoria News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive — Mike Cernovich: Attempts to ‘Hoax the Country into War’ Are Failing, ‘Nobody Cares’ About Ukraine #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covid-19: Prime Minister Jacinda Ardern in self-isolation, identified as close contact of Covid case #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heavy snow, high winds threaten U.S. East Coast, thousands of flights cancelled | CBC News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moorpark boys soccer finds spark, scores four goals in second half to beat Royal #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video Ice sparkles on Long Island’s Great South Bay #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women with endometriosis forced to seek ‘unaffordable’ private care #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tucker Carlson Says ‘Conservatives Have Remained Calm And Nonviolent, Thank God’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blackhawks C Jonathan Toews sidelined by concussion #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exercise could help broken bones heal faster – here’s how #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Garraway slammed for being unable to say Good Morning Britain guest’s name #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A call for kindness – Vernon Morning Star #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joni Mitchell joins Neil Young in pulling music from Spotify over ‘lies’ | CBC News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH | Gauteng hospital bids farewell to doctor who helped women with fibroids become moms | News24 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexit ‘certainly diminished’ UK’s global influence, ex Finnish PM claims ‘No question’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young Humpback Whale Freed From Mooring Line, Buoy Off Maui #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TIMELINE: Nor’easter Dumping More Than A Foot Of Snow On Long Island &amp; Jersey Shore; Up To 8 Inches On NYC #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stavanger-studenten Khatireh (23) flyktet fra Afghanistan: – Fikk sjokk da jeg så at Taliban var i Norge #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Russian invasion of Ukraine would reverberate around the world #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three ways to improve the uptake of COVID vaccines by ethnic minority groups in the UK #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MISSING: Valentina Cruz, 14, And Luis Cruz, 12, Of Gage Park #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man held over alleged racial abuse of TV pundit Ashley Cole at FA Cup tie #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[N.Y. nurses allegedly made $1.5M selling fake COVID-19 vaccination cards – National | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highlands council taking deeper dive into survey data before local area plan moves forward – Victoria News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McDonald's Happy Meal earns nod for 'most memorable fast food' #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sichuan, Cantonese, Shanghai: where to eat regionally this Lunar New Year #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laos makes big meth bust as UN warns of security breakdown #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Novak Djokovic: a poster boy for anti-vaxxers? | The Week UK #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reason Liverpool aren’t playing this weekend and next Premier League fixture #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer In Contract To Sell Malibu Assemblage With $51.5M ask #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the archives: The Space Shuttle Challenger exploded 36 years ago today #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former MLA Anna Lo on online abuse that forced her out of politics: ‘Trolls posted sex images of Asian women, linking brothels with me’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samantha Schwartz, Accused Of Hiding South Shore Plaza Shooting Suspect, Held On $20,000 Bail #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Best Redhead OnlyFans (Top Only Fans Red Heads)  – LA Weekly #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thai province declares emergency as oil slick hits beach #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TUNE IN: Live Irish music to celebrate St. Brigid’s Day on Tuesday! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-CEO of medical imaging companies sentenced to prison in $250 million fraud scheme #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow blankets the region, dumping a foot onto Shore towns in N.J. and Del. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Irishmen carry a dead man to post office to collect his pension #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Houston recycling co. creates JV with Honeywell, to expand local facility #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TODAY IN HISTORY: Designer creates one of the world’s most popular toys by accident #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gas Prices Rise In New Jersey, Around Nation Amid High Oil Prices #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selfridges launches its Valentine’s day gift collection – Shop the best deals #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cambridge graduate recalls clothes being cut off by officers after intervening in a stop and search #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scots dog owner’s frantic bid to find pet taken by couple after he escaped home #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massachusetts Reports 7,181 New COVID Cases, 65 Additional Deaths #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philadelphia Weather: More Than A Foot Of Snow Expected For Jersey Shore As Nor’easter Approaches #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More culturally-appropriate help needed for struggling families, charity says #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Abbotsford hotel to offer ‘complex care’ spaces for homeless people – Abbotsford News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nor’easter Triggers Blizzard Warning In Suffolk County, As New York Braces For Widespread Snowfall #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Priorities have changed for Bulls guard Zach LaVine this season #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taliban, Western officials hold landmark talks on food crisis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adams to NYPD’s 35,000 Cops: ‘I’m Here for You … New Yorkers Are Here for You’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manchester United transfer news LIVE #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little-known law could land forgetful dog owners with £500 fine #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photos: Nor’easter Leaves Many Trudging, Biking, &amp; Skiing Across Snowy NYC Landscape #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Brady assistant said to be job hunting — fueling retirement rumors #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Storm Malik: students have narrow escape as tree crashes down on their house #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>