<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Pinkwashing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Thanks for saving me the time. Changed my mind. Nas is doing a fine job of making you look like an idiot all by himself, so listen to him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Venezuela is a horrific police state with dreadful torture. Why do you obsess about #HASHTAG# where every single person has a roof over their head and UN aid? #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Appalling and ludicrous #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# rants from Algeria's government no less.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Vile race hatred and lies. 
Every Jew, every Israeli feels sad when an innocent Palestinian or Israeli child dies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I'm Jewish so it's hardly bleeding surprising is it? It would be presumptuous &amp; Patronising gaslighting to speak for any other victimised minority. In your book is it some sort of crime to recognise racism and fight the fuckers who perpetrate it, or is it just Jews you Patronise?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The report was too early in #HASHTAG#'s reign- released before his #HASHTAG# lickspittles had spawned and occupied #HASHTAG#, like a cuckoo sneaks into a nest and murders the genuine occupants by throwing them to their death, so genuine socialists were pushed out by national socialists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Appalling Turkish #HASHTAG# need investigation by ICC #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Definite marriage material. You struck gold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Minute Warning #USER#.
It's nearly 6 hrs after the #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# ceasefire went into effect. You can correct your website now.
In joke: Yesterday #HASHTAG# took a full 6 hours to state #HASHTAG# had bombed desperately-needed relief aid going into #HASHTAG#, so blaming Israel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# 
Question: What do these numbers represent?

5  3  5  2  5  3  3  3  3  3 = 35

Answer below
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Time #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# 
The number of goals our 1st team has scored in the last 10 games, home &amp; away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Absolutely. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Last few. Thanks for all your work! Kol hakavod #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Because they're #HASHTAG# fake #HASHTAG# campaigners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Please tell me who this man is. 
I want to visit the USA and educate him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes: "follow the money". 
It needs #HASHTAG# financial support to terrorist groups to end too, and UNRWA's perpetuation of the conflict by, incredibly, increasing the number of #HASHTAG# refugees daily, instead of reducing it, as happens with every other refugee problem ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#'s govt. duped innocent Iranians into investing in the stock market, concealing information from investors.
It crashed, leaving many people in poverty.
Snivelling silence from #USER# because #HASHTAG# was bribed £20,000 by the regime to spout propaganda #HASHTAG#Protests #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This may explain why it is in dire financial straits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gigantic mushrooms 
Mushroom henge
I recognise #HASHTAG# of Lewis Carroll fame.
Can you name any others?
Any edible?
#HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ROFL You are pathetic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ROFL.
You're a Racist idiot.
I spent my youth fighting racist skinheads targeting innocent blacks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# yes! #USER# does it regularly and he loses his deposit every single time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Goodbye to tokenist #HASHTAG# scum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# In war, defence, especially one you have prepared for, and on home turf, is much easier than attack. Long line of logistics, unfamiliarity with terrain etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I'm having a conversation mate, please don't interrupt thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Background on the situation in:
India 
Pakistan
Bangladesh 
Sri Lanka
Nepal
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In exactly the same way that dozens of African states, liberated from Western imperialism and colonialism, are posting a flag that didn’t exist when your great grandparents were alive.
Happy to answer all sensible questions on Zionist decolonisation of our historic homeland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# ROFL
Or do you really believe that, cos it's utterly stupid childishness ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# soldiers putting their lives on the line to defend #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# starves #HASHTAG# farmers. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Re my account about treatment of Jews by Muslims was right? 
Sorry 280 chars is often insufficient. Jews have generally fared better under Muslims than Christians, but that sets an incredibly low bar.
Obviously I know of the Law of Return and it has nothing to do with property]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That's a very close-up photo. Kudos to whomever took that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Oh no it doesn't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Mazeltov! 

Now he is in a much better form of captivity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Looked like a few 1000 to me. Amazing considering the high level of racist intimidation Jews face in Britain at the moment. 
(Thank God Corbyn was trounced at the election. He would have sanctioned all this racism)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My thoughts: Israel Says 'No Problem' bombing Russian S-400 Missiles To Iran When UN Embargo Expires"

Putin will forever be grateful of Obama &amp; Biden for their highly flawed 2015 nuclear deal with #HASHTAG#'s regime. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# covered up #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Explain why you feel that (and then why on earth I should take you seriously); then you can ask  why Jews have loyalty to Israel? Did that thought cross your mind perhaps? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Omg
Iran will give these to terrorist groups]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to see #USER# #USER# charity donations going to a good cause.
Poverty-ridden, penniless #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# miraculously find a drone to film their motorbikes, machine guns and fast cars.

#HASHTAG#sLiesMatter #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's a bot with a Jewish name so that was antisemitic of you (joke) #HASHTAG# etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# SOS - Saved Our Season! #URL#
Deep joy - love Jamie Carragher laughing his head off in the background!
#HASHTAG#wonderland 
 #HASHTAG#Becker #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Where do you live kid?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Wow. She has 
Nerves of steel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! A pipeline to stop Iran threatening world oil supplies in Straits of Hormuz, lower pollution (no ships burning vast amounts of fuel to sail all the way to Suez), cheap fuel. What's not to like? I prefer renewable energy, but I'll take any eco gain. 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ROFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# At Abu Simbel, an Egyptian World Heritage site, the tour guide described how a Pharaoh's army there suffered a truly catastrophic defeat by Ethiopians.
Fearing loss of his throne, he declared it a wondrous victory.
Arabs have done this for 1000s of years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He's not wearing a mask]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Absolutely
Exploitation of unpaid workers and tax evasion is perfectly acceptable, as long as you write virtue-signalling slogans for gullible idiots]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# When there's a terrorist attack in Pakistan, do you go round "Paki-bashing"?
Do you excuse people who go round murdering Muslims outside mosques?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, not even a murmur of disbelief from the crowd, they simply believe ludicrous, obscene #HASHTAG# nonsense (not that 13 Jews in the BBC should be a problem anyway).
It's like watching a National Front rally from the 1970s.
I am persuading my family to make aliya to Israel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You were conned by a fake anti-racist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Medals go to Lapid as horse trader extraordinaire for even attempting to fit 8 round pegs into square holes.
I suspect, up his sleeve, he has an offer for a religious party to join his gov. People only vote for them as they're almost g'teed a seat in gov &amp; subsidies for yeshivot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ROFL You just made that shit up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't seem to turn on mike, but shukran aleef. Why do you think many Muslims believe Jews are a threat as there is no evidence for it. Is it an ego issue perhaps?
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# People call left-leaning people who care about social justice issues “woke lefties” like it’s a bad thing, because they are frequently tokenist, fake anti-racists, who worship disgusting tyrants who murder, rape and torture people - as long as they spout anti-imperialist claptrap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# in #HASHTAG# reveals its entire membership list. They even have members abroad! Imagine working for a company in the West yet belonging to a foreign political party from a dictatorship.
#HASHTAG#Movement #HASHTAG# 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. Muhammad - "Peace be upon him" 
2. Tweets furiously about #HASHTAG#  
#HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG#TheProphetOfPeace 
#HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG#Cartoon   
So illiterate, they don't even know it should be #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First #HASHTAG# ambassador to #HASHTAG# arriving to present credentials to #HASHTAG#i President Rivlin
#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There may even be #HASHTAG# there too, and us #HASHTAG#, we don't understand #HASHTAG# - gospel according to St Jeremy (Woody Allen, Seinfeld, Mel Brooks, Marx Brothers, Joan Rivers, Lenny Bruce, Larry David, Sammy Davis Jnr, Richard Prior - joke, just checking if you're still reading)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She's c.27k followers who live in an echo chamber.  For many, it'll be the first time they ever hear the Zionist view. A fine opportunity to convert them. Any with an open mind will see sense. Those without are no use to us #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Perhaps this:
TWITTER must DELETE any ANTISEMITIC tweet breaking IHRA Antisemitism guidelines within 2 hrs of being alerted.
Simple, Measurable, Verifiable
#HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG#
also
TWITTER BAN all ANTISEMITIC accounts tweeting racism &gt; than 2x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cheers mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Trust me mate - it's very, very helpful. 
Maybe not to you, but in the galut, yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think they may mean facts like Beduin are not Palestinian and conveniently ignoring their history and racist, patronising and cluelessly lumping them together with Palestinian communities in the West Bank, when they live in the Negev, shows an appalling lack of basic knowledge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thanks for supporting the #HASHTAG# festival of #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG#??
#HASHTAG# of 10s of 1000s of helpless black African refugees completely ignored by "#HASHTAG#" campaigners #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# etc.
WHY?
Because #HASHTAG# more than every other, much more legitimate, need. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# In kicking #HASHTAG# out, he has the full support of members of the #HASHTAG# who are genuine anti-racists too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL#
#URL#
#HASHTAG# kids play &amp; sing with #HASHTAG# soldiers
#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ht #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hizballah -
First they blew up Beirut Marines
Then they blew up Beirut port

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I didn't know #HASHTAG# is part of the vernacular in #HASHTAG#! Can I invite you, #HASHTAG# &amp; a gay friend for tea at the House of Commons? You can hang him from a crane- you'll feel so at home (#HASHTAG#). Seriously, who wrote the tweet for you? Are some of your best speechwriters Jewish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cornwall?
Deeply thick as well as deeply #HASHTAG# 
There are probably more fingers on your left hand than Jews in Cornwall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# *checks notes*...is fine with treatment of #HASHTAG# genocidal #HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG#LiesMatter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# leaders finally act like normal human beings
#URL#

#HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG#LivesMatter #HASHTAG#sLivesMatter #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 main reasons for world support: 
1. The #HASHTAG# exposed the #HASHTAG# narrative as fraudulent / anti-peace 
2. Blatant #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# - firing rockets from civilian homes - at civilian homes
3. Much lower death toll than previous #HASHTAG# war 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL#
Absolutely love this - a paean to #HASHTAG#, with a tiny bit of criticism cleverly thrown in, so it doesn't look like it was written by a PR person.
A huge thanks to Michael Edwards for all he has done for the #HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Please. This is how we deal with serfs and foreigners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Also
Occupied West Bank 
Liberated West Bank 

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The #HASHTAG#
1. Indulges in fact-free trope.
2. Squeals that he's a victim "paralysed in fear of speaking up for Palestinians".
3. Self-contradiction and fraudulent #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes. We also need to promote our legitimate rights, use the language of human rights and debunk fraudulent Palestinian claims.
Just because Israel clawed its way to being strong enough doesn't reduce our legitimacy one iota.
The far-left has an obsession with the weak being right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# banned from Estonia
#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please help, I can't keep up!
#HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# opening embassies in #HASHTAG#! 
#HASHTAG# #USER# #USER# #USER#
#USER#
#USER#
#USER#
#USER#
#USER#
#USER#
#USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL#
Jews tell jokes about God.
Christians tell jokes about God.
When Muslims tell jokes about God, the world will be a much more peaceful place.
#USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not sure this is wise at all.
Even ostensibly clever people believe all manner of ludicrous stupidity. 
Marjorie Taylor Greene, US senator, for example
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To all genuine #HASHTAG# campaigners worldwide -demonstrate outside #HASHTAG# offices, against its #HASHTAG#, tokenist, faked report on #HASHTAG# in #HASHTAG#.
#HASHTAG# lets murderous, vile, obscene regimes get off scott-free. 
#URL#
#HASHTAG#Lies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An especially warm welcome to my new followers from n#HASHTAG# (a #HASHTAG#) n#HASHTAG# (a #HASHTAG#) nplus the usual suspects, I mean #HASHTAG#, from #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# etcn#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The Nazi Party started years before the Wall Street crash and was a direct result of the chaos of the post-war Weimar Republic and the (justifiable but) swingeing terms imposed on Germany after WW1 by the victors.
You're either completely thick or deluded.Try reading a book on it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Palestinians" have been making Unspeakably stupid decisions since 1948. 
The first one was leaving Israel. 
Part of the reason Israel is constantly winning on Palestine, is because Palestinian leaders make - Unspeakably stupid decisions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For 70yrs, the Soviet Union (Russia) harrassed, imprisoned &amp; sent Jews to Siberian labour camps for teaching Hebrew. In the '60s Jews launched a campaign to stop it, that became a worldwide phenomenon. We won!
Christians WAKE UP! You are far stronger &amp; 50x more numerous than Jews #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Old Jewish joke

What is a nudnik? 
A nudnik is an idiot. 
What is a PhDnik. 
A PhDnik is an idiot with a PhD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a great man, such a good man. 
Sadly, he has passed on, but happily, he passed on much wisdom and understanding too.
Rabbi, Lord, Doctor of Philosophy Jonathan Sacks.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is this parody?
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Have you read 1984? 
It's where the term 'Orwellian' comes from.
A Jew who supports a racist and affects to be MASSIVELY offended at "the politicised use of antisemitism" is a victim of Stockholm Syndrome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China literally sterilises #HASHTAG# women
Turkey ethnically cleanses Kurdish #HASHTAG#s
Egypt expelled #HASHTAG# from their homes to destroy #HASHTAG# tunnels
Complete silence
#HASHTAG# defends itself from #HASHTAG#
Mass demonstrations
Deeply #HASHTAG#
Fake #HASHTAG# campaigners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It really looks terribly deprived &amp; poverty-struck. #HASHTAG# nWhat does it say about you, that you ignore the appalling, endemic poverty &amp; food banks across Britain to focus on a tiny group of the 1.5 billion #HASHTAG# in the world. It couldn't be that you're obsessed could it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't work hard. Work smart!
Self-identify as a #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#. You'll get:
your own chalet, swimming pool AND licence to commit #HASHTAG#.
Pretend you're a victim!
Gullible folk across the world will donate #USER#
#HASHTAG#LiesMatter #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A Jew who cannot spell antisemitism
ROFL
You're as Jewish as a pork pie luv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Kol hakavod for all your work.
Whatever you think of him, he's been prosecuted for assault frequently &amp; is, rightly or wrongly, strongly associated with the far right, so isn't a suitable ally &amp; this can undermine us. Pl don't use him, or discuss it with me 
please. Thanks! Sorry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The obsession with #HASHTAG# 2 years after he failed is because genuine anti-racists hate f*cking pathetic lying, obessive Virtue Signallers.
Massive numbers of clueless young, gullible people got conned by the #HASHTAG# and their parents, the adults, got scared of the Pied Piper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ROFL. What would opposing look like?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What?
Vegan too??
How dangerous are you??
;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You may have missed that #HASHTAG# also sold a kid to Wolves who's never played a #HASHTAG# game for £9m (13.5m with add ons). £32m for Jota, &lt;10% downpayment, looks like decent biz to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thanks for providing news in 
English , v useful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thank you for your #HASHTAG# but also for your profound love of religious Jews. That must be hard to balance in a tiny brain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am honoured to welcome you to Tel Aviv to begin your historic job as #HASHTAG#’s first Ambassador to #HASHTAG#!
"Next year in Jerusalem", as we Jews have said for 2000 years.
Shalom and thank you for spreading peace throughout the Middle East]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# At a Jewish ceremony in Liverpool for communal service in the 1970s, Golda's biography had just come out. She was so loved that as the awards were given, it turned out that every prize was her book.
Each donor had independently
bought it. It was funny. I guess you had to be there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yusuf, an #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# who bravely served in the #HASHTAG# (#HASHTAG# Defence Force), describes how a #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# baby's life was saved. #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So infiltrated or escaped?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# False

Israelis are liberating land 

Everyone needs to support this in the 21st century.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Go &amp; look on my timeline for the racist antisemitic statement from the leader of the breakaway Republic of Donetsk. Jews are not White, no amount of your patronising need to impose your definition will make it so.What other oppressed minority do you impose your own definition on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Three years ago you stood in #HASHTAG# and watched #HASHTAG# soldiers shoot 100s of #HASHTAG# in lynch mobs. Some died. Others lost infected limbs in crowded hospitals short on medical supplies as #HASHTAG# spent £10s of millions on tunnels. Another awful human toll, and nothing changed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# LOL. Bee Gees. Saturday Night Fever. 
Seeing the contrast between the hedonistic lyrics and the clothes in this video made me think of Studio 54:
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Mohamed, the Eurovision Song Contest beckons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# putsch.
Who will do it?
Hopefully someone with a heart
#URL#
#HASHTAG#WarCrimes #HASHTAG#sWar #HASHTAG#WarCriminal #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Now #HASHTAG#Resists 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#HASHTAG#nWar #HASHTAG#HASHTAG#War #HASHTAG#War #HASHTAG#Conflict #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You've gone very quiet, which is a shame. 
Maybe #USER# who says she's "very bright" can prove she is, instead of, y'know, just saying it.
The brightest people ask questions, the fools among us spout slogans.
Ask any sensible question you like on #HASHTAG#/#HASHTAG#- I'll answer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Moroccan official: #HASHTAG# have been telling us unacceptable lies for 60 years. 
In 1967, #HASHTAG# liberated the #HASHTAG# from illegal Jordanian occupation.
Palestinians duped us about their "rights". 
We're sick of being conned.
The #HASHTAG# deserves #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Pack of lies. #HASHTAG# leaders refused vaccines so they can con gullible #HASHTAG# like you that they have none. They even rejected #HASHTAG# aid from the UAE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You are a #HASHTAG# gaslighting piece of shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who supports illegal #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG#?

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# 

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 14/ 
In response, an independent Jewish spokesperson said: 
“You sound exactly like Corbyn - and he was lambasted for his frauduence and racist antisemitism by the Equality and Human Rights Commission. In other words, you're condemnation is fake”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which campaign group castigated installing a disabled elevator at a sacred religious tomb as a "war crime"?
#URL#
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#UAE #HASHTAG#UAEDeal #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#
A great player who gave his heart for #HASHTAG#.
He also had a hilarious long-running TV series with #HASHTAG# &amp; England icon #HASHTAG#.
I often thought they were drunk when they were filming it (!) 
#URL#
#URL#
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like saying 
"In 1994, there was a shooting in a Hebron mosque. A man was beaten to death. 29 other people died" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Help #HASHTAG# now! nIn conditions unheard-of in the starving Third World these poor "#HASHTAG#" suffer horribly from obscene levels of #HASHTAG# &amp; are doubtless dying from heart disease from doze bastud #HASHTAG# (and before any of you #HASHTAG# pricks RT this- it is #HASHTAG#!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL#
In the first two days of Operation Guardian of the Walls, most of the dead were terrorist operatives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I can see that you love putting things in simple terms.
Are you able discuss your tweet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I hate #HASHTAG# for his #HASHTAG# and wilful gullibility.

The #HASHTAG# cause is based on woeful lies, hatred and fakery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If you repeat a lie, does it help you believe it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Disgusting #HASHTAG# parents' Child Abuse - sending innocent little children to violent riots, so the idiot media can film them and clueless idiots can believe them.   
#HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, #HASHTAG# pocketed £20,000 in bribes for appearances on Iranian State TV as the regime was shooting Muslim protesters dead on the street.
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Thanks for the excellent publicity #USER#! 
You have kindly catapulted the guy to worldwide fame and we know whom people are more likely to believe - a TV station run by an #HASHTAG# tyrant, or a young #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# kid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You have NO proof whatever.
Genuine Fact: A #HASHTAG# couple rushes to hospital. Their small daughter got a bone caught in her throat. A doctor luckily is there, dislodges the bone and saves her life. The father, mother and the doctor are overwhelmed.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# LOL. 
Actually, I'm just getting over it, despite a triple jab - it was pounding headache, bad fever, rasping sore throat, so bad I could not speak at times, extreme listlessness and exhaustion, plus aches and shooting pain, intolerance to bright light: v unpleasant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# y’all stole the name palestinian and claimed it as your own. 
er, 'stay in your lane' kid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incredible 77 wins in his first 100 #HASHTAG# games, Trent Alexander-Arnold. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Gonna lose lots of followers with this .. but here goes.nI demand the right to have my own #HASHTAG# version! n"Kill two women with one stone"n"Be the guinea"n"Beat a dead Jew / Christian / Yazidi" (delete as applicable) n"Bring home the" n"Cut the vagina by the clitoris" n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This requires a complaint. #USER# should be made to correct any bias, distortion and lies.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is a sick warped society #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The only people who celebrate when #HASHTAG# women and children are bombed is #HASHTAG#, because they place them there as human shields to fool #HASHTAG# like you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# There seems to be a flag missing from her tweet.
Gosh, I wonder which one?
Do you think we were born yesterday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The only reason #HASHTAG# have not just 1, but 3 universities, is because #HASHTAG# built them, Israel paid for them and Israel turned a bunch of illiterates into the best-educated Arabs in the #HASHTAG#. 
You're an appalling liar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL#
#HASHTAG# finally. 70 years of murder, lies &amp; fraudulence, now #HASHTAG# lies are being exposed
#URL# #HASHTAG# #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A disgrace to Britain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Not a Nakba denialist, but knowing it's a colossal con - 100% self-inflicted: an attempted genocide of indigenous Jews by Muslim immigrants.
Israel deported some Arabs (they hadn't hijacked the term Palestinian then, it actually meant Zionist Jew!) 
Please listen &amp; learn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# organisations-
They betray #HASHTAG# don't they 
#USER# #USER#dispatches #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#NY #USER# 
#HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG# 
#USER# #USER# 
#HASHTAG# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ROFL
You shift the goalposts, ludicrously demanding I cover "state sponsored illegal cyber activities" that I've no clue on, but say I "shift the goalposts".
I offer repeatedly to debunk #HASHTAG#, you say I'm not backing it up. 
You have comprehension issues. Last chance son]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Seeing it another way; a #HASHTAG# (pretending to be anti-racist) is endorsing a #HASHTAG# festival about triumphing over attempted racist genocide, so the joke's on her (&amp; IfNotNow) even though neither appears to realise the #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# B) Israelis think they’re smarter than everyone, but British Jews are smarter ;)
A) Do suggest ways to build normal relations with KSA
C) Looking for the help of Palestinian leaders for normalization with KSA. Really? Interesting.
D) Desperate to live in peace in rejected region.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# plunder every genuine cause and suffering on the planet to obsessively demand attention, like little children; so self-centred that they cannot conceive of the fact that there are other people in the world apart from them. 
Me ME ME! 
Unbelievably egocentric #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I’m also a big fan of green things &amp; natural stuff, used herbalists for 50 yrs, and consider/ed McDonalds the "anti-Christ" - it's better now, but still worse than most restaurant food and sustains highly-destructive farming methods. V. little is wrong in moderation, of course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's not just obsessive tokenism and Anti-semitism it's completely stupid and clueless. Ask me why.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I like what he said.
Any genuine woke person would support and defend Israel as morally superior and fight for the only pluralist, free, equal society in the Middle East. 
It's all about the narrative.
Fact-free, demonising slogans about Israel are simplistic Soviet-era nonsense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really, really, really like this HSBC initiative to help people with no fixed address get a bank account.
No idea if there's a hashtag, so I'll create one
#HASHTAG#
Kudos to #USER#.
Well done. A mitzvah (good deed)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nonsense. 
Most of those who die in Gaza are armed racist terrorists. The pic is fake. Idf does not use phosphorus as a weapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# child abuses #HASHTAG# children 

Teaching little boys to fire rockets at civilians

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5G Antennae "Public Consultation" bypassing Planning Permission to erect millions of Antennae/masts on PRIVATE PROPERTY-your roof/garden: you won't be able to do a thing.
It's likely to put off the average person so pl. have a go.
Deadline 11.45pm, 14 June
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# demand separate prayer site for Jews.

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

Jeer and throw rocks at devout worshippers. 
Shameless vile yobs 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[land, a bare plot of sand by the sea. You are forced to buy it at outrageous prices, but nurture it into a beautiful paradise. 
It turns out your neighbours are racist redneck, KKK members, who lynch your family regularly and proudly proclaim that they will throw you into the sea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sounds like a v powerful / large bomb if several floors collapsed (?).
Size matters, and the larger the bomb the greater the risk of detection. Plus a physical object is far more difficult to conceal than a   cyber one which can lurk for yrs undetected. Leaving a bomb is v risky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They look terribly well-fed (and clothed) for #HASHTAG#. Like #HASHTAG#, I'm delighted that £billions of charity aid goes to such a deserving cause, instead of the millions of #HASHTAG# starving in #HASHTAG#, Yazidi women raped &amp; murdered in #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# victims in Indonesia #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where is this?
Like Oil-rich Dubai 
RT Prison Camp Gaza #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# An excellent first move. 
Do you know what concrete steps they now intend to take?
Explain it to students/staff?
Prepare guidelines for the Student Union/lecturers?
Explain to both what is antisemitic, what is legitimate.
They may need your guidance on what to do.
#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# arrested by police.
#USER#, #USER# completely silent!
They are corrupt, fake #HASHTAG# campaigners.
#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# 
#HASHTAG#LivesMatter #HASHTAG#s #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's v. annoying as I love #HASHTAG# and haven't touched it since their #HASHTAG# hypocritical boycott of #HASHTAG#.
 
Open letter to franchisees:

In the US, you can sue for anything.

Class action sue #USER# for loss of profits.

Peace, Love and .. Racist Boycotts 

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Guilty before innocent
The #HASHTAG# mantra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Thanks (I think) to #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# and other left wing #HASHTAG# for their contribution to #HASHTAG#.nAnd he said Jews have no #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I see you wrote "Israel" instead of "the Zionist entity." (probably because your tweet would have been incomprehensible otherwise). Anyway, it must have been hard for you, well done. It's difficult to treat people like human beings when you've been hateful &amp; #HASHTAG# for so long]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# the way some people are angry is really telling:
it tells more about them than anything else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He fights #HASHTAG# not #HASHTAG#, so no. You?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A baby Palestinian girl screams in agony after being taken to a riot by her child-abuser parents, so racist scum like you can pretend it's Israeli forces fault.
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Flat out lies.

If your cause is genuine, you have no need to lie.

The #HASHTAG# cause is a colossal con

Fake flag
Fake refugees
Fake cause]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# regime- #HASHTAG# on a huge scale.
However, as #HASHTAG# found out, fake likes on #HASHTAG# will feed your ego, but won't win you an election.
He was trounced. 
#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The notorious murderer and fraudster, Arafat* was invited to speak to the United Nations &amp; declared the sole representative of the Palestinian people.
You're either a liar or misinformed. 
You wrote clueless, fact-free, nonsense.
* He was born in Egypt &amp; isn't even "Palestinian"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You are #HASHTAG# sexist filth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# another sickening gaslighter for you to expel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do postmen occupy your house when they deliver mail?
Are you completely thick or something?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[fao #USER#.
#HASHTAG# - they demand concessions, then lambast you behind your back #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL#
FIVE Cups in ONE year.
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL#
I look forward to a time when
- #HASHTAG# have lost so much support that they drop their fraudulent cause
- We're secure enough to not feel a need to run Israel support groups across the world and get on with life in #HASHTAG#. #HASHTAG# is free]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Name any other conflict in human history,
where the party that began the war,
lost the war,
demands absolutely everything,
but refuses to talk,
murders anyone who does!
Even defines talking to the enemy as "normalisation".
#HASHTAG#: like dealing with 2-year old brats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I really don't think thanks are in order. They disseminated obvious nonsense, received an immediate barrage of emails correcting it, but left a blatant lie up for 6 hrs, misleading millions of viewers. It claims to provide up to the minute news. It has lost all credibility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it just me who finds it easier to remember the name of the lead guitarist from Slade - 50 years ago - but can't remember what I did yesterday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If he's one of the #HASHTAG# families, give that man an Oscar. Fantastic acting.
What a fraud.
The families lived rent-free for decades, now they fool gullible idiots that they're victims.
They occupied stolen land.
60 yrs of injustice, 60 yrs of robbery, finally evicted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Perhaps you're not old enough to recall 1967, or have forgotten?
East Jerusalem is liberated territory. Liberated from illegal Jordanian occupation.
It was re-unified, like Berlin was re-unified from Soviet occupation in 1990.
This is fact.
The int'l community will agree in time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's because he is still hated by all genuine anti-racists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You have failed to answer the questions, so are using childish diversions - please demonstrate some credibility or withdraw your insulting #HASHTAG# claims.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG#

Fake Keys - Fake Cause - Fake News

Fake #HASHTAG# 

#HASHTAG# - conning well-meaning people and #HASHTAG# for the last 70 years. Stealing from genuine causes for decades.

Stop funding #HASHTAG# 

#HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Demanding her sacking, abusing her (I assume) genuine concerns, &amp; her disagreeing with you, by accusing her of "hatred" of a minority is:- obscene, Orwellian, outrageous harassment, blatant intimidation and flagrant bullying: hiding behind "Transphobia" is no excuse. Shame on you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# If you're not part of the solution you're part of the problem.
Look it up. You'll see many examples. Eg He accused anti-racist Jewish students of being agents of a foreign power. A racist offensive age-old antisemitic trope that should make any genuine anti-racist puke. Not you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reveal the true number of genuine #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#! 
#HASHTAG#s dupe the world, monopolise media attention thus stealing aid from desperate, starving, penniless #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# and Burmese refugees.
Stop the #USER# fraud. #HASHTAG# cover up.
Create a #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You are so lucky. Liverpool is the best place in the world mate. You could (soon I hope) go and watch #HASHTAG# play football at #HASHTAG# every fortnight
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Israeli settlements are perfectly legitimate and justified. 
The apartheid slander is a vicious lie.
Please do not parrot nonsense you have heard and ask sensible questions. I will answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Dear #USER#, perhaps you could also realise that #HASHTAG# is not a state, never was a state, its people are a fictitious invention, and #HASHTAG# violations are being carried out in its name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yes! I suggest we look from the #HASHTAG# side.
Eternal lies for caring, horribly gullible folk.
You're the one who needs to STOP spouting &amp; start listening.
There's lots more where this came from
Ask sensible qns on the topic, I'll answer
#HASHTAG# 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sanctions help deprive Damascus of resources, if it had more resources, it would spend more on barrel-bombing civilians - that would be popular and contribute to social stability, in Alawite areas at least. WTF is Int'l Crisis Group doing paying you to be an Advisor? #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In #HASHTAG#, you savages chop hands off thieves.
In #HASHTAG# they escort them back to the parents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Truth is more powerful than anything, which is why, after &lt; 24hrs, #HASHTAG# withdrew baseless slurs abt #HASHTAG#: 
Sari Bashi, Consultant, Human Rights Watch:
"We are not saying Israel is an apartheid state"
I've debunked all your lies, you will be blocked if you continue]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>