<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Tories endorsing a creationist?! I'll get my cod piece.ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because the media presented him as the best. Because when money is threatened; it resorts to #HASHTAG# which is its real face. Because the media says: "Its extraordinary times which no PM has faced; and people parrot it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Aye..I was being . Good luck for today Nipper! ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm afraid that's a forgone conclusion now.
Ps. In all the furore, everyone's forgotten about the guy who invaded the pitch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "... a third-party that handles our database"- that'll be a rogue "ex- mossad" agent then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ...and only that dysfunctional political/media class, by its lone voice; amplifies that dysfunctionality. Has the whiff of tragic demise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The imminent deterioration of #HASHTAG#'s ability to import and the so-called: "free press"- deflect, by turning it into trivia. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Who benefits by pathetic sanctions? 
Boris might be a liability to us. But him and his party, are an asset to Putin. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ' woke left' and 'cease to exist' is like 'I'll kill myself if you leave me''- emotional blackmail #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If proof was needed, of an intelligent being. What better example could you have, than ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The young generation should start their own party.
That would put the frighten the political classes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I remember years ago, that there was an outcry because #HASHTAG# passed a directive that allowed the #HASHTAG# to do exactly the same thing that the #HASHTAG# are now trying cover up. curtain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Feels like the Fall of Baghdad and Chemical Ali territory.
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Set adrift on memory bliss of you.."- the establishment trying to remain relevant in the 21century, by living in the past.
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think #HASHTAG# by business, is their tactic, to off set against better pay, as promised by a "benefits of Brexit" Tory gov't, who voted against it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Guess someone got up on the wrong side of bed this morning?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I remember there used to be a variety act who did exactly that. Can't remember their name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Theresa Villiers stands up and asks a question, in creaky voice, reminiscent of one who has the "flu". #HASHTAG#ãƒ¼19uk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hancock at the dispatch box: "...these allegations are untrue"- don't think Cummings would do this without the evidence. Which would imply he's lying at this very moment, at the dispatch box.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Haste ye back! Don't slam the door as you leave."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is Boris a British liabilty?
The answer to both lies in who benefits from weak sanctions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The hereditary line to #HASHTAG# Cameron Boris Brexit Indy Conservative &amp; Unionist...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mogg uses contradiction to lead you astray. The oppo of genius is stupidity. The incongruity gives it away as his statement is incompatible with the facts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I've saw a lot of ppl criticise the delay in #HASHTAG# 
I think wait, let things deteriorate and then strike:
"Hence the saying: if you know the enemy and know yourself, our victory will not stand in doubt".- knowing is seeing and boy are we seeing this #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "Biting the hand that feeds you." Cash for access. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Boris &amp; his ilk, Jacob, Grant and Dom; are just well-off louts, 'the boys'.
What you see in every high street on a Friday night.
They are not better than any of the lads! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There's our #HASHTAG# comparing himself to #HASHTAG#
Keep taking the "tablets"- BoJo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analogue employee of 'govt provider', pondering on the beneficial good' of a British Broadband Corporation digital provider? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# is a systemic risk and is leading to systems failure. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dark Lord comments on face coverings. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "the spirit is willing but the flesh is weak"- my sonðŸ˜„ðŸ˜„ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A PM using a tax avoidance vehicle, as a get out of jail card. 'The First Lord Of The Treasury'- #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a cake of a country comprised of; a xenophobic, insular, little englander Conservative sponge and a creationist, darwin-denying, insular DUP.
Welcome to Conservative&amp;Unionism #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Horizontal climbing? That's a new one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It allows Watson to play the victimhood card...as if?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That's excessive force #USER# 
Ps. A police officer saying: "look at the fcukin state of you!"- is no way to conduct an arrest.
It's obvious, he has alcohol/mental health issues. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I can't get over how much the West now resembles the old USSR. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That defies logic, it's a warped image of reality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The lack of self awareness in these ppl is hard to believe, those days are gone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "For the love of money is the root of all evil".
Love of; being operative words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In this day and age, they usually survive the calls to resign; but not in this case. Raab's lack judgement, urgency and empathy, makes this different and should end in a diffirent outcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Like an ever diminishing echo; to an ever diminishing demographic, in an ever diminishing circulation. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's pasokification right there. The route to disaster. #USER# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Surkov edifice of, black is white, up is down, warping reality; with the help of tory/tame media.
After 2 years, this facade of lies is begining to buckle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, does that mean if you dont vote labour; you wont be classed as antisemitic? #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I remember the day when the PM was feted for not following the rules. To break the rules and not resign, is the very epitome of what was once seen as an asset, especially when it came to "Get Brexit Done"!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah...true. Haha!
That album, with it's original sleeve, is worth more money.
 More than a those poor souls will be paid. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If interest rates rise and mortgage rates rise? Then some or all of the rise, would be placed on the tenant- depending on the discretion of the landlord.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I once heard that the reason you feel tired after a meal, is because blood is taken from the brain to help digest food in the stomach and thats the reason you feel drowsy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I can't get over how quick the authoritarian language has come into play: "a national plan".
"...patriotic party." #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We've went from a worker's paradise to a billionaire$s paradise; because of a lack of bargaining power through union neuterization. We know the side Mandelson trumpets. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I hear Sir Edward Leigh is a big believer?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "PC laptops giveaway...we'll be giving one winner"?
So, thats one laptop then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Invoke the law to stifle indy. Invoke the law to absolve yourself: "the law's an ass!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Strongmen require subservient media. Seems to be the pattern now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# ðŸŽ¶Fletcher memorial, home for the incurable, tyrants and kings...is everyone in?ðŸŽ¶
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't want be governed by a #HASHTAG# fit for the 17th century.
I want live in one thats fit for the 21st century.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Its like a drug cartel raid, except its countries and elites making all the money. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "...and Dougie sees a straight red!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Â£37 billion "thats very patchy"- dnt ever listen to tories spouting: "value for money"- ever again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I think thats what the movie Ghost Writer was about. Although, in the movie, it was his wife who was the 'asset'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# "post-shame"? That's a fcukin cracker! Centrists don't do PS. For him to come out with that, shows that he accepts no guilt. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Brilliant! The "intersection" between personality/disorder, one muses...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Where "customers" can enjoy the benefits of a 63% tax rate. If that was you, you'd be moving your money ofshore. My mistake! You've already done that. Head of #USER# has a history of tax 'minimalisation'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I remeber reading that; disassociation is the coping mechanism used, when dealing with traumatic events.  A reflex action, that tries to protect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Pasok...the party promised to resolve...That promise proved false."
The similarity with "manifesto pledges"- going the same way, would indicate yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's just the idea, that the west thinks it can contain China, it can't, it's too late. I mean't no offence. Ps. An interesting side note. Nostradamus predicted "the rise of the yellow race."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think there's parallels between this and the Munich Olympics and Jesse Owens.
When the world #HASHTAG# up, to #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Doesn't look like Dom's "resetting" his phone anytime soon?
Unlike "Dodgy Dave's" mucker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Luv the welcome mat, quite fitting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A Tory government, world renowned for its disrespect for the law. One could say "world beating; embarking on legal action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This puts to an end to a ref after we sort out covid. Westminister will, as you say, employ disruption tactics on #USER# which should now hasten a ref.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I like the idea we're descended from the apes. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it just white faces, or is it early days still? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Here we go! Male, stale and pale. Vote winner!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If the boot was on the other foot i.e Corbyn?
It would be a diffirent refrain, more like a dirge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It seems, the only way to remain wealthy, is to do down the poor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ""They could appear to themselves each day, on colour tv, to make sure they're still real. Its the only connection they feel! "Fletcher Memorial Home For Incurable Tyrants and Kings"- is everyone in?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Closing down News of the World, is akin to tying up loose ends, like Ruby with Oswald.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# charismatic leader
ineffectual minister's
enrich cronies
use tax havens
loot the state
russian template #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think Labour are doing a News of the World because of the Forde report. Which has done to them, what phone hacking did to NoW as a way out.
Just a thought.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Capitalism discards the mask and shows its true face when threatened- fascism.
This is the result; because all those that benefit from the old order; will do anything to maintain it, including ommission.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maybe another police force should be brought in, to investigate, both the Met and #HASHTAG# ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Get knowledge my son and with all your knowledge get understanding and with all your understanding get wisdom. Wisdom is the principle thing!"- King Solomon's Proverbs. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What does it say about "being a role model for society"- when you are a tax dodger?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Whats telling about that.
Is, I have yet to see a rebuttal of this from anyone, never mind the leader!  #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Deep bore sample drilling by scientists in the Arctic. 
Then they they analyze it: carbon, methane.
It's a record of Earth's atmosphere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Vote Tory, receive scraps from the table.
Vote Labour, receive a wee bit more sraps from said tables
Militant tendencies in full flow, from the militant right. 
Welcome back to the 80's!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The quality that Raynor possesses, is the ability- in a media sense- to be relatable to working ppl. That's what is lacking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We've went from "Up the workers!"
To "Fcuk the workers!"
"I'm alright Jack!"
"Greed is good."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "...world war 1 style convalescing" #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "the ends justify the means"- The Prince. 
Required reading for the right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# An example of a "virtuous circle"- and it works! The way to go. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The generation below, are screaming out for #HASHTAG# and the greens teaming-up with the snp, is such an example for a greener #HASHTAG# Which makes you and Johnson an irrelevance and a boost for the greens in #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's some political choice facing voters at the next general election: Captain Sensible or Captain Insensible?
No change, in an age of #HASHTAG#
Ps. What is it with tories and pigs?!
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How apt, cos it feels like "the slough of despond" at the moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A once dominant super power, reduced to pleading: "Rise and Fall..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There's the lack of natural justice right there.
"Their grasp extends their reach."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The whole establishment, media, politics, are so 20th century, hanging on to power. 20 years and a younger tide will wash them away. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The same thing happened to Brandon Lee on the film set of The Crow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have a theory that 'Political Correctness' PC. Was a contributing factor in the #HASHTAG# decision. It suppressed feelings, now being vented and capitalised by the right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the same person who is infamous for never giving a straight answer, to a straight question.ðŸ˜… #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He's not worried. Dark money will pay for the damages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The University of Oxford: Revoke Professor Richard Dawkins Emeritus Status at The University of Oxford - Sign the Petition! #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A story about basic income, behind a paywall. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What better way to teach emergent AI technology; than to train it to recognise young faces; so it can apply it to everyone else. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To use extremes as a defence. Is a big fat lie in itself. #HASHTAG#ðŸ˜œ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "The descendants of those enobled by William the Conqueror still control...wealth and power in Britain."  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The PM, Home Sec and a majority of Tory mp's, condoned, CONDONED!! That behaviour and fueled it, until it blew up in their faces. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pay, conditions and holidays, that hark back to the socialist 70's.
The only place that hasn't changed. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maybe the new, needs a vessel to be born in? Like a new party? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Right Honourable/County Court Judgement"- just doesn't sit well. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The reason why we keep putting incapables, in office. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It'll be some laugh to read George Osbornes' pontifications on the subject, in the Standard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Boris and his ilk, used to burn fifty quid's infront of beggars. 
Havin a laugh at our expense #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mogg and his ilk, strikes one as a latter day Knights Templar: "white is right"- and all that shite.
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That'll add a few thousand votes to the tories.
Ps. Is Chris Leslie chasing Boris for the debt? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There's plenty of oxygen on mars; but not, on earth. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think, maybe, some ppl have picked up the wrong end of the stick? He's using the Gove argument, to highlight Gove's stupidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# ...don't forget a dysfunctional media culture as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's amazing! Divorced from the real world. Blair pontificates on what ordinary people want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A healthy #HASHTAG# should be able to shed light, on the dark corridors of #HASHTAG# 
"Power corrupts and absolute power corrupts, absolutely."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Its a balance between how much the tax payer can sustain and tendering out to ease that burden. If I read my Streeting correctly? Its mixed messaging: 'trying to be all things, to all men."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I can see #HASHTAG# going down a storm! In places like #HASHTAG# and the #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nah...Beagle crashed into Mars cos the metrics were fcuked up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think to increase viewership, they should have topless presenters. It works in Russia, or is that Italy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# hijacked and being sacrificed by a technocratic elite, as a vehicle, in a power struggle, with strongman authoritarianism and the voter prefers the latter.
"Time to go..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sir Christopher Chope, that champion of the anti-establishment- go figure?!
Lying is like breathing tp that mob. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A political system where  the main parties support corporate welfare at the expense of social welfare. Leading eventually, to the unravelling of the social fabric: Scrooge Neoliberalism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If govt's project violence; it filters down to their population.
Its called: "Leading by example". #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# May does a speech, mentioning how #HASHTAG# shames #HASHTAG#. But sells British cluster bombs to an equally loethsome regime?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah...I just mean't the possibilty of intensity in the future; which I realise is a guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There's the dilemma. Can you trust the LD's not to prop up a lying gov't?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If Greens show it can be done in #HASHTAG# . 
Then it could boulster support for Greens in #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There's where the hate began. Polluting the public with bile and hatred and the corrupt capture of our corrupt political class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think the tories will be a spent force within 10 years. There voter base will have passed on. Their propaganda media will have diminished because of that declining readership and it explains why #HASHTAG# have lurched to the right, as its the same clientele. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Remember now, when you appear on politics live and your asked if it's appropriate language?
Just remind them that it's the content that's more important, not the language.  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Hiding money in tax havens, has lot to do with how we've ended up with failed democracies and authoritarian leaders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It would seem to show you who their 'target voters' are, as Maddison said, tories.
Expect more of this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I can't get over how, the West has become the beligerent bad guys of the #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The absurdity of so-called "moderates" trying make the #HASHTAG# smear stick, whilst it's unravelling before our very eyes, is the height of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nothing says dying, like 40 ppl tuning in to your event and its called 'Progress'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# causes ice sheet to melt. Which inturn affects the weather. "Icebergs" are part of the ice sheet. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Its a subconscious uncoupling. Conservative&amp;Unionism no more. NI: "thrown to the wolves".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ...and what do scots do, when there's no one to serve them at home? It's joined up thinking like this, that's led to the state we're in, now. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Imagine if others followed suit, in a sign of #HASHTAG# ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Whatever grey, tepid, trickle of an opposition...can muster."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like : "the white heat of technology"- has moved over to the blue side?
Ofcourse; it remains to be seen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Does that mean all his descendants are "bastards" since they married in a 'church' he set up? Oh...the !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There is a better way to manage economies: "community wealth-building" and govt's seem powerless to stop this; unless they legislate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think the Eton Boys have ran their course- politically. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# To be reactive instead of proactive, is I think, what will finally bring this government down. #HASHTAG#  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I believe it! Johnson does govern unwisely. Look at the state of the country, it proves it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Divine Right Of Kings precludes any sovereign being subject, to any law. Its an argument against barabarism, putting all power into the hands of one individual. A flawed concept, as history shows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its one rule for them and another for the rest of us. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Its so much than a clanger.
Bozo, has just handed #HASHTAG# on a plate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It never rains but it pours.
A frost in the political air.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "Haw...haw! That Dobber's in the lead! Haw...haw!
Interpreting for the neds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Puts paid to the myth: if your rich, you must be highly intelligent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's shocking! The BBC's setting portrays him as weak, almost like a victim. It's brilliant propaganda from the Tories, for the Tories! 
They need Campbell's help. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "We're nearly there with the letters."
Expect the platitudes to intensify.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Luv how the streets are so clean, litter free. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They toy with the idea of small scale tactical nukes on the battlefield; and end up escalating to the horrific reality of MAD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Just heard Beckett, because of his suspension, has lost his place on the NEC. A lost vote for the left. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This press conf feels like a preempt because of inaction, of whats coming down the line; and is more about saving the pm's back, than ours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Your party is doing a better job than the SNP could ever have dreamed of. The party of the Union, destroying the Union.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Institutionally racist and not fit for purpose in the 21st century- SFA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm still waiting for one journalist to ask Patel or Johnson if they still believe taking the knee is gesture politcs? Maybe it will pop up at #HASHTAG# ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# All our institutions should be based on this model: free to everyone, benefit to everyone and everyone benefits back to renew and replenish for future gens. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You are now approaching, in football parlance: "squeaky bum time"- a phrase coined by Sir Alex Ferguson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a fact, that the brain weighs 1300cl.
Or to put it another way; a 1.3Litre engine. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Imagine running 100 metres in 1/3 gravity; high/low jump. The Olympics would be unreal. #HASHTAG# World Records]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# From Nuneaton to Norfolk: "Great British Railway".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You would be a mug, to buy now, in the hope of hedging against a higher price in the future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Bozo plays the fool, except, when in the mileu of historical settings, as thats where he sees himself. As his dimeanour shows. Its a weak point for him, to be challenged in these settings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe the phrase is: "Pot calling kettle black", and this one's a corker! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So let me get this straight. A leader who hasn't the "confidence of the commons"; or her own party! Won't step down until there's a leader who has?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Takes airbrushing to a new art form.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You could turn up at the voting booth pissed and say you left your ID at the nightclub? That would count? Wouldn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You say 'graduated'.
Bill Browder says 'timid'.
You allow leeway and by extension benefit of the doubt.
Browder has no qualms.
You're an outlier. Which makes you am apologist. An appeaser.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There's what: "levelling up"- really looks like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# a technocratic lash out! Afterall, Angie was never a part.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "the road ahead is paved with good intentions."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's that a device lauded for it's expression of democracy, referanda.Has resulted inthe "Goodbye democracy,"quote. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Design used to effect behaviour- brilliant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's tax avoiding U2. Selling their wares, aided by the tax paying, licence fee- payers, state broadcaster #USER#. Giving them a little helping hand. PS. 'Feed The World'.ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "25% of #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# are corrupt".
"...re-phrase that."
Ok! 75% of #HASHTAG# don't take russian bribes." #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We had our shot at the title and fcuked-up.
Time to move over and give the new improved generation their chance; as we are now obsolete.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Even our wars are out of fcukin' date!
"The Land That Time Forgot." #HASHTAG# ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In hindsight, you get the feeling Putin seeing the Afghanistan withdrawal as confirmation of his success in destabilizing the West. Presumed- incorrectly; that now was the time to strike; but understimated Europe.
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# His gov't produced a report not long ago, that exonerated the UK of racism. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There's lots of sub routes in the article, leading you to pieces by other writers too, on the subject.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Let that narcissistic rage vent free! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Its brilliant they got too greedy, couldn't help themselves!
"...hard earned tax payer's money"- and stashing it in tax havens to avoid paying tax?! #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I believe that nurse is from #HASHTAG# ? Which means, she prob would have been deported? But its deffo now, after those comments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The gov't intend to lower standards.
They say one and do the other: "chorinated chicken".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's like a metaphor for her impending demise as PM. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Johnson was advising the exact opposite at the start of this pandemic, restrictions; but now it's being seen as a futile gesture to continue, honestly?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A Curly coup d'etat: "Luck is what happens when opportunity meets preparation." #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think we're seeing the unravelling of New Labour's policies, when in there pomp? I also think that "political correctness"- played a part in Brexit? New Labour being undone by their own policies from the past. It might explain the reason they've went from pomp, to insignifance?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>