<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER#
I hope you know this guy who is standing next to you and your husband is a #HASHTAG# , #HASHTAG# ,racist . #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please take my survey :  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cast aways...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here,the minister of the right wing #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# government of #HASHTAG# and admirer of Hitler ,Nazis and the military junta calls all  non europeans #HASHTAG# ...n#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# n#USER# all ok ?..#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Remember Mengele's claims were  "scientific" back then ,supported by many"scientists" ,like the ex nazi von brown.
People have every reason to be hesitant/suspicious ofbig pharma,stop pretending all scientists(with vested interests)hold the "truth".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# gets what it asked for by voting for #HASHTAG# mafianProblem is we didnt vote for him but we still will bear the consequences (#HASHTAG# )of their stupiditynThank you very much Brazil..#HASHTAG#  #HASHTAG# if we dont have our own idiot fascists.n#HASHTAG# kills.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Some vultures are trying to make the mask a "fashion statement" in order to make profits,at a time when there are millions around the world who can not afford a normal face mask.
It s capitalist #HASHTAG# in all its "glory"....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A week ago Erdogan was sending 10.000 Turkish soldiers as "mercenaries" to keep the "peace"
The Taliban also heard him and got the "signal" from islamist Turkey, that they have nothing to stop them since Turks are the same like taliban,also Qatar  was harboring the Taliban leader]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# At the same time the Greek right wing government and the media that serve the propaganda of the right wing mafia (new democracy/Mitsotakis ) are hiding the facts and pretend that nothing happened..
Greece is in the hands of a corrupt populist right wing gang of fraudsters&amp;thieves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just don't bomb others joe...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# BS. There are no peaceful religions.
All religions kill.
So wake up and stop this idiotic excuse.
All religious idiots are fanatics who are ready to kill for their gods.
So give us a break and give peace and logic a chance...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# this 17year old bastard deserves to be beaten to death.
He is now protected by the same murderous police racists who let him live and walk away.
Actually, Americans should realise the old saying, good Nazi is only the dead Nazi.
And there's a lot of them nazis in USA today...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worldwide rise in femicides,our society is racist and sexist and has no willingness to change.
There is nothing left to talk abt.
It s time for action.
The "helpers" of patriarchy need to start paying for their crimes. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor #USER# cant decide...Migrants,refugees,illegal immigrants,..reporting for humans (by humans(?)#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# in disguise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wishful thinking
Europe,a continent full with racists,greedy vultures and lots of police to keep the poor under control.
European right wing uses #HASHTAG# as a scarecrow for the racist "average"Europeans.
Europeans have to confront their own racism first.
Is not going to happen. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I ve stood for 5 minutes in a fast-food just next to charing cross station, trying to order a chocolate milkshake.
The cashier(pretended?)didnt understand my pronounciation of "chocolate", which i tried in English,French,Spanish,Greek with no success.
(Racism comes in many forms)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Its not his fault that (right wing) Greeks have fish-like memory and get him reelected again and again...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Indeed! hello from the other side of the pond.
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once a greedy b#USER# ,always a greedy b#USER#.
#HASHTAG# ,not for his jokes,for his greedy bastardy nature.
He always ewas like this,but he was hiding it (or not -for those who were actually looking) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ðŸ˜‚ Which simulation is he influencing?....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Total stupidity. 
As if the deadly challenges humanity faces (climate change  for example) will wait for everyone to catch up wt calculus....
The system doesn't need any more smart, they need "subjects",the more ignorant the better...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# (and Die)..

#Î–ÎµÎ¹ÏƒÏ„ÎµÎ¤Î¿Î½ÎœÏ…Î¸Î¿ÎœÎ±Ï‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This deserves a report for threatening violence against people.
You fanatic moron.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The German government must stop covering up for #HASHTAG#.
The #HASHTAG# state of #HASHTAG# must be stopped
No matter how many Turks live in Germany,and how scared of refugees some citizens r,u must stand for European values/defend yr allies(Greece,Cyprus),not profits of companies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# spot on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# now i got your drift!...:):)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry mr. Pfizer but no thank you.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In #HASHTAG#, under the orders of the new government, #HASHTAG# assists islamist dictator #HASHTAG# by attacking anti-capitalist music bands' gathering.
Is this #HASHTAG#?
Is this any different from #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#?
Is this the European Union you want?

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Hypocrisy part 2..
The only ones worrying about freedom of speech are the neoliberal neonazis and the terrorist right.
No,nazis don't have rights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# hello , and thank you for videos!
I wonder if you have a take on this Methuselah star .
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# when they burn you alive ,i hope you still say they are alright with you..

Idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# but of course not all jews are the same.....#HASHTAG#..:(.#HASHTAG#  #HASHTAG# is after all just a fascist state,consisting of racists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Never mind Greece's democracy, you and your New Democracy friends managed to step on it (and our necks).
Fake "progressive",you tricked lots of people who trusted you back in 2015,and helped the right wing fascists come to power.
now u play the revolutionary
Stupid little man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# also closed the channel (in Greece at least)
Also #HASHTAG#'s swan lake is now banned ..
Democracy, 1984 George Orwell style...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet #HASHTAG# has an answer ...#HASHTAG#..:(:(  #HASHTAG# .#HASHTAG# .#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Look mommy,no humans !"...
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Naughty Michele Bachmann, "God's Iron Rod" is probably her sexual fantasy....

As for the "christian" message of peace,i can only ask : Why is she not behind bars already? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call the 25th (amendment) on the 45th potus .
Get rid of  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Keep walking,nothing to see here....
Normal paranoid anticommunist US behaviour of the cold war era (which lives on today,in the republican pit of shaite)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Not "autocratic", Terrorist movement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are the "ukranians" that the "west" supports...
#HASHTAG# flying the NATO flag and the Nazi svastika .
In Europe ,in 2022.

#HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While in USA,the country that unleashed the racist"war on drugs" stupidity,they are selling it legally (&amp; tax it),in the backward allied countries people still suffer the consequences.
Policemen,Judges,lawyers,prison guards &amp; other parasites r using these laws to feed on society. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Does this "Love" include sex?
Bcs Turkey and NATO are fcking us big time,since we first joined.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Î ÏÎ¿Ï†Î·Ï„Î¹ÎºÎ¿Î¹ ÏƒÏ„Î¹Ï‡Î¿Î¹:

This morning I woke up in a curfew
O God, I was a prisoner, too.
Could not recognize the faces standing over me
They were all dressed in uniforms of brutality.
How many rivers do we have to cross,
Before we can talk to the boss?
All that we got, it seems..1/2&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trump supports terrorist erdogan.
Trump supports terrorism.
You support terrorism.
So shut t fck up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#  : Because i am an idiot and i dont know what you are talking about,but i am the president ,so i can say whatever stupidity i want.

#HASHTAG#....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# once a Goebbels always a Goebbels..
#ÎÎ”_Î§Î¿Ï…Î½Ï„Î±]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Greek right wing government decided to go full nazi...
Torturing prisoners is sooo "European Values" - like...
Isnt it #USER# ?
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# are violated by the New Democracy Mitsotakis party. 
But you already know that,you helped him become prime minister. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Surely you heard about the Greek Junta asking to shut down twitter in Greece because they think the name "social media" comes from socialism
#HASHTAG# Mitsotakis Mafia wants to silence anyone who defends human rights and democracy.
What are you going to do #USER# ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# were always known for their ethos and humane nature ...#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course they do.
Any other option than an occupying mercenary force is better. even theocracy.(and i m saying that,the antitheist)....
Women's rights are important but its more important to stay alive and not get bombed by drones or mad  cowboys who are out to kill for leisure #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# noone but almost everyone..
You cant avoid the international ridicule for allowing the backward priests to do whatever they want (and it is the opposite of the scientific advice).
The right wing government that gave religion a boost in order to manipulate people,it now backfires.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You see,Ukraine is full of the kind the west likes,nazi scum .
I ve yet to meet an ex communist country citizen who is not fanaticly pro-right wing(aka pro- nazi)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# in the US though, not in France..its kind of funny #HASHTAG# .Racism is endemic there,so .....Its not just a muslim problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# a bit earlier.
US sealed its fate when they accepted the result of the  00 elections despite the evidence of fraud(voting machines tampered with)and made potus a useless hypocritical "christian"(Bush jr.)who was in the service of the defense industry wt his gang of vultures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2.. we have lost
We must have really paid the cost
Burnin' and a-lootin' tonight
(Say we gonna burn and loot)
Burnin' and a-lootin' tonight
(One more thing)
Burnin' all pollution tonight
Burnin' all illusion tonight
Oh, stop them
Give me the food and let me grow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# These morons think they are the "space force" ,and want to arrest "lefties" and "anarchists"(everyone who is not racist/fascist supporter of trump)....
Just like ISIS arrested/killed everyone who wasnt a terrorist...
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You are supporting terrorism,racism and nazism.
You are supporting criminals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We don't need  a "father" ,mr whatever.

Go to your next banking job through the revolving doors and leave us alone.
Political fraudsters,EU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Get the nazis out of my TL...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# stop spreading stupid conspiracy theories abt a place you cant find on a map even if we told you where to look,you moron .
directed energy weapon my ass. At least watch some more videos to see how stupid your claims are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I cant wait to hear your thoughts on #HASHTAG# and the murderous response of  your "golden man" Nursultan Nazarbayev to the demonstrations of the Kazakh people against him and his Stalin-like dictatorship....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Well ,the world still owes us for the pi (Ï€)..:):)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# In all military parades th "special forces" are demonstrating their equipment.
Egyptians obviously dont have the money to buy the diving suits for their "special forces",so they do the next best thing...:):)
All dictatorships have such parades.Turkey,Egypt,Pakistan,India,et al.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[" You cant talk to a man
with a shotgun in his hand "

#HASHTAG#  
#HASHTAG# 

(#HASHTAG# Ï„Î¿ "blues")]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If you were in the 0.1% who die,you d say different 
Lockdown saves lives till the "system" realizes that only by investing in public health  it can start functioning again. 
So,stop passing responsibility to the victims.
War vs free health care and social benefits is the problem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Read the tweet first ,then maybe delete your -full with right wing stupidity-response.

Noone said anything abt CO2,the prediction is abt PM25 particles,and you dear "expert doctor" have the right to be self destructive,unless you re hurting the rest of us too.
So ,shut t fck up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER# welcomed #HASHTAG#'s #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# Europe's enemy &amp; #USER# "ally" who "weaponizes" #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# &amp; threatens to invade Greece &amp;Cyprus ,ethnicly cleansing Kurdish areas ,etc #HASHTAG# ...nice!#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# ,he believed he can fly,i believe he will die (in prison)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# done!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Seems fundamendalist Islamism sells well in erdogan's turkey...
Otherwise he d be long gone...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# eveyone kisses it,and gets wet from the greek stuff in his other hand.
Lots of droplets around,and the priest doesnt wear a mask in a closed space,which should be punishable as they punish citizens for not wearing it on busses or in cafes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I ll give you constructive.
religious people are psychopaths who believe in imaginary things/gods ..
how s that for constructive?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Can i quote you on that?...:):)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cc #USER# #USER# #USER#  countries with normal governments should learn from Mitsotakis how to impose restrictions on your citizens while you violate every sense of decency,by dining with your friends on the balcony of an island you visited in order to"check the vaccines" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 26000 deaths,at least half of them could have been avoided if the criminal gang of New Democracy and #HASHTAG# had reinforced the NHS of Greece, instead of giving 6 billion euro handouts to his crony capitalist friends and relatives.
You hypocritical bastard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If in order for few to get high we destroy earth's resources and environment ,maybe weed is not such a bad deal after all.
I  dont want to go to space(physically),but i m all for smoking the whole weed supply of USA.
I fancy my chances fr survival are better than on bezos's dick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The trip back to the 80s UK put a smile on my face.:)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Attack of stupidity from an idiot is what this is.
Who still believes the Putin's bitch.?( i tell you who,stupid people)

Trump can go fck himself and stop spreading misinformation

Just stay away vultures,noone needs your stupidity and war loving idiocy. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The coronavirus is mutating. Now what? 

(Now we are doomed...- not really but we all need to take care-wear masks-wash hands-social distance yrself )
#URL# Î¼Î­ÏƒÏ‰ #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# ?
 Done!:):):) #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Say hello to your friend the murderous saudi prince ....
Hypocritical pos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The well-being of the citizens depends on the number of police cars( right-wing neoliberal "ideology")
Who cares if people die in hospitals?
The right wing gov has stolen enough to be able to pay for its family members private hospitalisation. The rest of us can go die in a ditch #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# A brilliant double today!
#HASHTAG# and #HASHTAG# thanking #HASHTAG# 
A big bravo to all drivers and personnel for standing up against racism !
the best F1 GP start of all times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If I only knew that's all I needed to do in order to marry you before the covid travel bans, I d have emigrated to the US  and applied for citizenship   ..:):)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Please get me out of here too!......

Demo-#HASHTAG# ,#HASHTAG# style ..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once a barbaric thief,always a barbaric thief. 
#HASHTAG# is the thief in the Eastern Mediterranean and the M. East.

USA and NATO want to have ally near Russia (oh the communist danger!),and thus turn a blind eye to all the Turkish threats vs Greece.

Hypocrisy helped Hitler too..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This was a very accurate description of the propaganda used in Greece too,against the left. The right wing government has now in it at least 3 neonazis, lovers of n Hitler, who openly and repeatedly have said antisemitic things.
Thank you for this video]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What i hear is that the ukranian nazis emptied the hospital long time ago and installed defensive weapons in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck dog eaters #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And he is a typical chicken shit nazi,he deleted his account.

.#HASHTAG# under #HASHTAG# and the rightwing fraudsters of New Democracy(that has nothing new in it,only old fascists) ,has turned into a banana republic.
Corruption rules,violent crime is up,the poor get poorer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[60 million racists,fascists,selfish violent hypocrites,religious fanatics(as dangerous as ISIS &amp; Al Qaeda put together)who like #HASHTAG#,are too many to hope to change them/country
It s like if u d try to change nazis in the 2nd WW
U wouldnt.
Humanity did something else back then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes,it's my twin brother..ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real thing. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please Romania,Send us a Prime Minister too! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# So 2 doses arent enough?
And how long after the 2nd you can have the 3rd?
And why noone told us that before hand?
After the 3rd will you be calling for a 4th?
After the 4th?

oh yes the data says so.
bs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#'s non-fascist,non-racist citizens should go out and vote out the republican cancer.
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What this has to do with political views ?
Only nazis would say such stupidity.
and judging by the flag you are one of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes for sure,they risked their lives for Trump in order to bring down Trump.
Wow!

Your brain is a big brain,we know...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I m sure he doesnt have a gun pointed to his head while saying this shit....#HASHTAG##HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# is a #HASHTAG# and the "west"  is responsible for it exactly as it was for the Jewish #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# So it was fine for the police racist murderous bastards to let him walk around armed like a terrorist (if t photo is prior t the shooting).
People must fight back ,fascists are armed and dangerous ,and they should get what they are asking for
(exactly what t nazis got in 2nd WW.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# warnings were out since a long time ago..
Seriously.
#HASHTAG# - Mass Destruction (Live) - Passing The Baton #URL# Î¼Î­ÏƒÏ‰ #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Someone behind me said :
"You should wish him to have a horrible painful life".
But i m not this kind of person to wish bad things for full of complexes of inferiority miserable "right wing",neoliberal #HASHTAG#  who got a chance to spit their poison outside their caves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2..
Its one thing to want to know how stars work,and  another to hope that u will find another earth-like home fr t self-destructive humanity &amp; move those who "worth" it to live on t moon while earth &amp; t rest of us burn.

Instead of moon missions how about "food missions"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The northern europeans dont understand humanism.Only blackmail (like Erdogan does).

For now they are backing the Turkish aggression vs Greece,and demand from Greece to keep these people in cages,without any help.
Fck EU. I dont want to be this kind of "European". #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is working hard to help Turkey ,instead of siding with it's allies.
There is no more European Union.
Only hypocritical backstabbing Germany,Spain,and others who are ready to sacrifice Greece and Cyrpus.
Shameful leaders,ready to bow in front of the caliph Erdogan. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# not that new.
I remember back in the 70s you could make your own painting in fairs and playgrounds,for a few drachmas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER#  ,#USER# and all "European values" proponents , in #HASHTAG#  violations of #HASHTAG# r taking place by the right wing #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# ,who is trying to install with #HASHTAG# a neoliberal racist junta.
Why are you silent?
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good. Actually, brilliant.
All terrorists should get punished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dubai ,The shit-iest place on earth.
50+ degrees ,lots of sweat smell covered with perfume that costs 2000$ a gram and lots of robe wearing perverts who pretend to be religious and have slaves.Slaves that usually end up raped/beaten by their "owners".A fake place for fake humans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #HASHTAG# (and i bet #HASHTAG# too) ðŸ—ðŸ– who learned how to write very recently....
Fast and furious w.nker.
Find a girlfriend (i know, impossible for ðŸ’© like you, who would go out wt a stupid sexist?) and tell her that to get the response you deserve ... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hey dw have a look whatz happening in Greece with the nazi right wing government of #HASHTAG# and the mafia New Democracy. 
#Ï€Î¿Î½Î±Ï‰ 
European  values my behind..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Next time you need surgery ask your doctors to not wear a mask,you ll be fine....#HASHTAG#

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smells like democracy .....#HASHTAG# style #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# They have profit targets to meet......
Natural immunity thanks to omicron saved the day..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Are you sure I am the one who is under the rock?
One sided information is not information,its propaganda. Are you doing that?
If not i dont understand your reaction.
Have a nice peaceful day .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They were ready to pop the bubbly as soon as their coup attempt had come to fruition....
A mafia party.
All these "people" should immediately get arrested for this coup attempt and put on trial like the traitors that they are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We will repay you for your sacrifice in the long run! :):)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The right wing in Greece must (and will ) die.
Unless people decided to be self destructive and vote for the right wing mafia (again).
oh wait,they knew Mitsotakis and New Democracy history back in 2019 ,but they wanted to "punish" Syriza.
So fck the "people".
They asked for this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Check out the latest video from John Oliver abt misinformation and big tech....
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# 
1035mb !! pressure is not common for Greece.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daily new confirmed COVID-19 cases per million people #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG# of a #HASHTAG# under the rule of right wing New Democracy party and Mitsotakis the leader of the right wing mafia. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# more uninformed than the person who calls the chaos created by Mitsotakis a "well managed crisis"?

ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤¦â€â™‚ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is a defensive alliance said the Secretary General, Stoltenberg...
Hmm.....
How do people believe ghis crap?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lets be clear.If #HASHTAG# goes we ll have few more million #HASHTAG# slaughtered/or turn refugees,so #HASHTAG# can help #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG#.nice!#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nazis asking for help from a "lesser " race?...
Ts ts ts... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The people of Europe should have hanged all those criminals,and their offspring that today poses a threat to our lives.
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That would be animal cruelty.
what have the pigs done to you ,to want to feed them such crap?...:)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swing states seem to not swing after all....
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# working overtime for your sponsors again?? n#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# Respecting democracy and the will of the people #HASHTAG# your cup of tea,greedy gang of Lilliputian "conservative" humanoids (not that democrats are any better)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# law prof./judges/police would say lies to remain useful to society.Hope doctors wouldnt...high hopes.#HASHTAG# legalise it,dont critise it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You should visit Greece and listen to our PM #HASHTAG# ,he exemplifies lying to the parliament and the people. 
All right-wing fraudsters have the same attitude: Carefree stealing of public funds and lies abt everything.Even during a pandemic(or a war for that matter).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Vietnam, a job half done...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# .
Time for this world to start killing nazis ,before we have a sequel to the 2nd WW... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Ok,we get it, Germans hope that he will topple Putin and he will return the favours to his western helpers...

noone buys the "human rights"story any more.
Stop messing wt other countries,you "democrats".
Buy the Russian gas and give lies a rest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Similar thing happens in Greece doctor.
With the added bonus of paying off ALL national Media/reporters-only in name,propagandists of the right wing 
Right wing governments proved they are dangerous for humanity.
those of us who have lived under dictatorships already knew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no nazis in Ukraine, only racists...
Fck Ukraine, Russia and NATO. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A Russian interference maybe?...ðŸ™„ðŸ˜‡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If i had more followers,it would mean more people can get fast decisions from informed and educated people:)your loss world.:)#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# report]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Food and water consumption during infection. 
Do not take paracetamole or similar to lower fever.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Isnt Venezuela the country with the biggest oil reserves in S.America?
Why would they need Iranian oil? Oh wait ,is it bcs USA is stealing their resources?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you wouldn't sit for a photo op with #HASHTAG# would you?

So that you know,it is the #HASHTAG# that your wife hugs in this photo.
You ve been used to white wash a corrupt ,racist ,fascist government.
The kind you dont want for your own country. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I m a "typical vax hesitant" but  i always read the side-effects to make sure i m taking the right drugs.:)
I always check t leaflets
I live in a remote area,dont have social interactions,so i m hesitant bcs it seems the vax is riskier for me.
If i had to work/meet ppl i d do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# , the most dangerous  enemies of Afghan people are not the Taliban.
(thats not to say the Taliban are good)
Lowkey on Afghanistan: "Good Riddance to the War on Terror" #URL# Î¼Î­ÏƒÏ‰ #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And i thought its t #HASHTAG# .
It isnt. It is the religious hypocrites,everywhere.
And #HASHTAG# leads the way for the #HASHTAG# .
Back to the middle ages, the era that the Americans are comfortable to live in, since they didnt evolve like the rest of humanity did. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "#HASHTAG# Scholars" = Perverts,backward illiterate paedophiles and rapists.

No sorry ,not any more,this will not fly,you dont get to name the terrorists "scholars".
#HASHTAG# keeps humanity in the dark ages.
Get rid of your stupid religions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# correlation is not causation ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kosovars are asking for a war it seems... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# blocked brains block truth.
whats new with you racist subhumans?
Just accept the fact that you have a racist society that doesnt count black lives ,just say you would like to  feel superior since you are such a worthless PoS,be at least brave enough to admit that bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Poland is not a democracy,only in paper.
In practice the government is a nazi friendly group of corrupt criminals,who by the way are used by USA to insert the alt right BS into europe.

Good nazi is only the dead nazi.Still applies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You, "Pseudo-Marxist" you....:):)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Public opinion says stop the warmongering you lackies of the USA. 
Stop the propaganda and the lies that push towards our elimination 
"Media" as in propaganda machine of the defense inductry vultures.
You must pay for this.
Bastards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "unknown" as in criminal nazi right wing New Democracy(aka Golden Dawn),known to the police(some say they are policemen in plain clothes).

The fascists have a free pass to attack anyone who reports truths or speaks against the Mitsotakis government and their criminal acts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# in #HASHTAG# assisted by USA . #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Hopefully you made sure to include and expose all the racist policies and the terrible conditions for immigrants in Greece, the racism that is "hidden" in the psyche of the "average" Greek who thinks he is better than everyone else,especially if their skin is darker than his own]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# retweet if you are a hypocritical fascist/racist coward who hides behind such idiotic slogans .....
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This explains why only violent nazi-like perverts apply for police jobs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is the next USA president.
The world tonight is breathing a bit more calmly than what it has for the last 4 years..
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Get me a ticket for a spacecraft, i m off to live in the "other" earth. How worst can it be ?
What,poisonous gasses.high temperatures,cyclones of ice/fire? 
I ll be fine,i m trained on earth....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The NYT say differently,quoting experts.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And today in Greece, a 63 year old woman collapsed and died after 30 minutes of receiving the AstraZeneca,and of course the media is playing it down, pharma have enormous advertising powers...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sure,count on the mafia sidekick to do what is legal,logical and decent....
After all he hasnt shown any signs of being disreputable and a puppy of Trump.
Pence is a representative of the "Christian values" hypocrites/perverts,who wipe their behind with t constitution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes,but what about the antifa?..ðŸ˜‡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# made America Albania ...
He should end his days in a cell .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# .gov.gr.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The next #HASHTAG# of the hypocrites is #HASHTAG# .
There is no way USA,UK,China &amp; Russia will allow the people of Kazakhstan to choose a democratic course for their country.
#HASHTAG#(aka #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# companies) have invested there.
we all know what happens in such cases]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Big up Giannis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# the democratic tolerant response of the #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# of #HASHTAG#...#HASHTAG#...#HASHTAG# care to comment of your ally?#HASHTAG# do you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# indeed.they fcked this chance they had.
now the only hope (in the future,the very distant future) is AOC ...
but till then , there might not be a USA as we know it..
I predict a war,a civil war,a bloody civil war.
But i ve been wrong before...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cut the crap,and stop talking abt both sides as if nazis exist in other than the right.
watch this and realise you are normalising the racists and the neonazis .
They are the only ones who threaten with violence.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How it is to remain like a teen who revolts against those who tried to help you evolve...
#HASHTAG#
Enough already with the backward,self destructive,maintaining the oppression that became "natural" or religious idiots.
Evolve for fck sake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Should be illegal. Do you have some specific school/teacher in mind?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It contradicts every sense of decency .

It appeals to perverts, paedophiles and ugly mfckrs who otherwise wouldnt get laid with anything other than their goats..

The same reason why rape of boys is usual in arab countries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah sure,when pigs start growing on trees,USA will suspend military sales to Turkey...
The defence industry is making the US external policy,and they want sales.
And under Trump there is no way US will stop his friend Erdogan.
Even if he attacks Greece i m afraid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So...#USER# promotes nazism.
Nothing new here...
right ?
#USER#Support is (probably) full with hateful right wing "keyboard terrorists"and racists who like such tweets, is the only explanation i can give. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Famous last words of Hitler before his end..
Where can he go man?
 Usa used him and like they always do,left him alone when sht hit the fan.
NATO is to blame for all this. The NATO 2008 declaration of",Georgia and Ukraine "will" join NATO.",while Russia drew the line in the sand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Is Turkey one of those who hold the"values" while occupying Cyprus&amp;threatens Greece?
NATO is a useless for the european citizens organisation that lives on our taxes&amp;looks after the US interests.
They will let us die if war breaks out
NATO &amp; Putin,different sides of the same coin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Spanish goals send the Croatians home.Deservingly so.
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# For the 2nd pro i d be holding a small basket...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 
Reporters who dare criticise the mafia Greek gov are getting arrested,citizens are getting tortured in police stations/on the streets,but #HASHTAG# will appear as a guest of the dictator Mitsotakis in the 200 year aniversary of t Greek revolution.
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Very fitting send off for the luxury prostitute.
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Like Sadam eh?
Same bullshit to justify the war against peace.
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Fantastic opportunity for the secretary general to spill his lies abt the NATO participation in the pandemic response uncontested,and show his continued support for the terrorist Erdogan of Turkey without anyone confronting him with the facts...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# standing with the #HASHTAG# .
Its not a first,they did the same with ISIS,Taliban ,now with Turkey.
They use religious fanaticism to control their masses.

Feed your people first(so they dont eat u alive).
Also have a shower,you stink as bad as your "prophet's" corpse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# IN Trump's America? 
Even outside Trump's USA noone is safe with Trump's gang .
You better do something this November or else we are all doomed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["After US "Democracy*" what?".

The title of a new book I ve started writing 4 years ago(2016),and still cant find a way to finish chapter one...
#HASHTAG# 
#HASHTAG#-ism will be with us for a long time in the future.

*a constitutional republic is not necessarily a democracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Turkish people!
Lets kill each other for the interests and profits of the big multinational oil companies!
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# 
The nationalist dumb asses on both countries want to kill themselves for the oil that will destroy the planet&amp;kill us all.
Which side are you on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ÎšÎ±Î¸Î±ÏÎ¼Î±Ï„Î±_ÎÎ” .
enough said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You probably confuse him with the ISIS faces in their propaganda videos.
He has the "typical" terrorist face.
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We will bury you"

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Are you nuts?
Why send people to their suffering?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is result of keeping the black community convinced they must be christians,religious and faithful.#HASHTAG# saved the slaves too #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i hope this helps..:)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["fight off" left wing.
This is what the status quo planned,to use the activists/left wing citizens in order to remain in control.
I hope Biden doesnt betray the hopes of millions for the profits of the few. It will be the end of the democratic party,and a win for Trump 2024 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My basque friends Kiko,Ibon and David will be smilling  today!
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Of course you are talking out of your behind when you say plan.
The only plan that the right wing,full with racists,peadophiles and nazis is to exploit the people who are in need.
It does the same with the Greek citizens too!.
Lies,lies and lies.
But your racism can not be hidden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ðŸ‘ðŸ‘ðŸ’ª power !]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>