<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not defending racism. It's abominable to blame Asian Americans for COVID. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The fucking #HASHTAG# is that so many (often "#HASHTAG#) parrot the buzz phrase "Science is real" yet are the first to deny biological #HASHTAG# differences.nnHumans are so fucking stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# ..... men's genitals are mutilated too: circumcision isn't even recommended by medical experts, yet (WOMEN) will often say: "eew, cut that off!" Wow, imagine a man saying that about women's bodies!
Re: ur murder stat - What's 2 x 52 weeks? 104? What's the population of Germany?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yup.

Good to know. It's something at least.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well answer this question then:

Are you saying an injustice isn't worthy of concern, if there's a more "widespread" one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Also: homicide is RARE. It's .00005% of the U.S. population, yearly.

Men/women do not murder anyone regularly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Self-awareness is NOT their strong suit. See this screenshot of an ostensible "#HASHTAG#" using a #HASHTAG# "joke" to slam "#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#" who reject #HASHTAG#. And these "pro woman" activists do this all the time.nnAnyone w/ a brain can spot the #HASHTAG# of his joke: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yup. It's a huge elephant in the room. I don't hear women today clamoring to pay for dates. 
-Yet, they expect to be treated "equal" to men? That's equality: pay for dates! It's that simple.

It's that simple.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# men are awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I just made 50 feminists cry when I presented similar stats a few days ago: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Ur so eager to point out men's toxic behavior, so I'm pointing out women's toxic behavior.

Can you handle it? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So society can say horrible things about women, &amp; women should just take it too, then?

Doesn't feminism hate all kinds of sexism against women - including simply rhetoric?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Shaming all men isn't the solution - it just creates more problems e.g. it fucks up the good men, ironically. It has to be more nuanced than that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Uh.... I literally did not say women commit "as many crimes as men". That's on you. I was pointing out that women do destructive things in different ways than men.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Oh I know - I meant to point out the double standard / hypocrisy of Feminists' stance against saying "not all men".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# 
Having a penis is awesome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Example: people will defend someone they love, even if their loved one is wrong/guilty.

Why? Feelings.

NOT TRUTH. Get it?

Same thing w/ this "believe women" bullshit. Enjoy your feelings!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#Women #USER# We can try. But count me out on the shaming/blaming tactic.

Witness: Catholicism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yep. That's why I often bring up women's flaws - not to put them down, but to balance out all the fixation on men's flaws &amp; counter the narrative that women are "perfect" LOL!
It's damaging to everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah, the abuse one is a big one - cuz it's so UNKNOWN to the public!

So when I bring up female domestic abuse, it's not saying "Women are bad!" at all. 

Also: it's just FACTS. Facts are facts. No lie, no agenda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Over 90% of Fortune 500 companies are run by men. Does that mean over 90% of men will run a Fortune 500 company?

You are doing what's called a FALSE EQUIVALENCY. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ALL presidents have been men too... so by your logic (The majority of a DISTINCT minority in the general population) = we must believe that every man is potentially a PRESIDENT!

Whoo hoo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Women crying about things that happen on TV.. it's not even real!!

I just flipped your "argument" against you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He's a fucking moron.

I can't stand this generation. WTF went wrong? We're all a bunch of fucking saps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Just cuz u keep saying that doesn't make it true.

You literally purported that if some injustice isn't as widespread as another, it doesn't warrant my concern.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same thing w/ women and men!

We don't have to shame boys/men who haven't done anything today, to "empower" women! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's funny that we live in a world that LOVE to protect women, yet we say that it's a world that DOESN'T protect women?nn#HASHTAG#?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# THAT's why women are always fawning over sensitive, considerate, nice guys, instead of bad boys who treat them like crap! &lt;=======#HASHTAG#!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally with you, Phil. 

Fuck. And not EVERY man oppresses women, so there you go! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is a quote from a book about masculinity: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is my cell phone #HASHTAG# volume so loud? Pretty sure my neighbor upstairs can fucking hear it. Shit. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Exactly. 100% of U.S. Presidents have been men. Does that mean 100% of U.S. men will become President?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Have you actually looked up murder statistics?
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Being a victim is a HUGE privilege feminists can't live without.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's useless. I hate talking to strangers, but when I sneeze - NOW I have to?
It's hostile; I shouldn't have to talk to strangers.

No one should.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that my worst feature is hidden (MY #HASHTAG#!), I get more looks from ppl when I go out. #HASHTAG# 

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No response? Big surprise!

Gotta pretend radfem's aren't mentally deranged morons.

Open secret.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yep, our if the woman outearns a man, the man needs to "step up &amp; match her" - if he wants to be marriage material!

WTF happened to "feminism", which was supposed to end traditional gender roles, then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Let me illustrate it for u:nPerson: "I'm a #HASHTAG#! I'm against #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# stereotypes for #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG#!"nMan says something they don't like.nPerson: "CRYBABY! MAN UP! You're a GIRL!"nnLiterally. This happens EVERYDAY, online. It's called #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a former #HASHTAG# buff? Who gives AF about the #HASHTAG#.

It's not about merit anymore, if ever. LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Seriously... why is no one countering the feminist lie with this??????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I don't know a single woman today who defers to her bf/husband/father of her children. It's a myth. Sure it happens, but it's not the norm in the western world. WOMEN have power in all their relationships. 

U can't use the past to punish innocent people today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# YEP. 

Murder rates are literally .00005% of the U.S. population, yearly!

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's the added complication with the fight against "toxic masculinity". That's on THEM, not the men or boys.

If u claim to be against it, &amp; u make a (dick joke), you are ... TWICE as bad, cuz you claimed to be against that very thing &amp; now ur guilty of it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# True. It's also why men tend to be more innovative. They take risks. Some are dumb, some are not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations, u just made people hate "#HASHTAG#/ #HASHTAG#" even more. #HASHTAG#, much? #USER#, #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#women #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG#: The women who actively #HASHTAG# (men AND women) in the name of "#HASHTAG#" r merely making a case for MORE #HASHTAG#, cuz they are so clearly making themselves completely monstrous, i.e. condemnable by sane human beings!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Also the reason why I think ppl are capable of sheer simplicity. Seriously: "sticking up for men = hating women"?

How simple is that? It's more complex to say "you can stick up for men AND support women's rights.."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# She had a baby so to gain sympathy from the court. How TACKY! She didn't "accidentally" get pregnant via IN VITRO. Her lawyer prolly put her up to it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's like saying black ppl who are murdered by other black ppl don't matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I've also tweeted this analogy to you:

When AIDS first arrived, it was mostly gay men who were infected. Did that mean ALL/MOST gay me were infected?

NO! Again: false equivalencies are DANGEROUS and SPREAD LIES!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Really? There's a female teacher in the news every week who preyed on an underage student.

Wanna go full tilt into statistics? Such as the racial break down of that?

Your bias is showing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mind game: I pointed out the blatant error you made &amp; now you pretend like I was wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I visited Salem, MA - home of the infamous witch trials. Tour guides emphasized: don't judge a whole group of ppl based on a few bad ones, like Muslims..
UH, LIKE MEN????!!! 

History repeats. How can no one not see this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yes, look up voter stats! They're the LARGEST VOTING BLOC! Which means: Politicians HAVE TO pander to women! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So many "woke" women turn homophobic, when they wanna hurt men.nnLOL. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I always "joke": If ppl are so "complex" why do we think so simple - e.g. the #HASHTAG# debate. It's so simplistic: "Man bad, woman good". There's NO complexity (i.e. gray area) at all in that WIDESPREAD ideology.

No complexity. Humans can be simple.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm talking about antagonizing tens of millions of men because of the actions of .00005% of them annually.

You think that sounds fair?

It's a false equivalency. It's disproportionate slander.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# To make an analogy: If u have a choice between an easy day at work or a hard day at work, what would u choose? Uh, most ppl would choose the easy one!

It's human nature to want things to be simple &amp; easy! 

Ppl are so ashamed to admit the "S" word about themselves! LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# People: "Women are oppressed!"nAlso People: "I'd rather help women than help men."nn#HASHTAG# ???????????????????????????????????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# All this talk about political correctness in our zeitgeist, yet MILLIONS of women buy the book, "fifty shades of grey", wherein a woman submits to a dominant man... LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's what needs to happen: civil discourse between "polarities". We don't have to be enemies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# What's your point? If she wants to stay and fight, that's her choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She implies that MISANDRY is men's own fault cuz they created society, then gets mad when I give examples of WOMEN displaying MISANDRY of their own volition today. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They didn't believe a woman when she accused JOE BIDEN of sexual assault.

Proof that "believe women" was just an excuse to skewer men they disliked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yup. People CLAIM to "help/address" men's issues, but they NEVER put their money where their mouth is.

It's a RUISE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I had one feminist admit she had no statistics.

I fucking swear, feminists are certifiably INSANE #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The yearly murder rate in the U.S. is literally .00005% of the population!

You're 2-3 times more likely to die in a car accident, just as likely to die of the FLU, and TWICE as likely to catch HIV than be murdered!

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The term causes more confusion, animosity, &amp; hate than anything else.

I wish ppl would just realize that.

Also: It's not working! If something's not working, stop. Gawd, people!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Women suffer MORE consequences? When women commit violent crimes/crimes (which is often deemed "Toxic Masculinity"), she's far more likely to get a SHORTER sentence than a man for the SAME crime!

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# *I meant to say: Why ELSE is (that book) so popular.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Rock star, fuck. It's the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think someone is "conservative", do yourself a favor and ASK YOURSELF if you're a conservative.

In my experience, conservative people ACCUSE OTHERS of being conservative.

Like, CONSTANTLY. It's a thing. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yep. It's like saying: If you're not a Republican, you're a Democrat.

No, I'm not Republican, but that doesn't mean I agree w/ 100% of what Democrats do.

Stop being so BINARY!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Here's gibberish from a feminist: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Fyi, I will NEVER stop calling out feminists for their hypocrisy: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm an alien. I.e. borderline autistic, so "fitting in"? Isn't a priority for me, for better or worse. LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ladies &amp; Gents, here's a "#HASHTAG#": Shaming a #HASHTAG# for "hurting". Isn't #HASHTAG# against traditional gender roles, i.e. shaming men for hurting? Literally. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do ppl label each other if they think humans are so "complex"?

LOL. Why am I the only person who calls this out?

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But you do talk about my sex life.

Why are you so interested? Again: do u like it when men tell women "you need to get laid"?

I'm guessing u don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a MALE did this, everyone would be like: "LOCK HIM UP!!!"
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#Women #USER# I don't wholly subscribe to any ideology but my own (lest others judge me based on certain political groups). The irony about these #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# who think they're "#HASHTAG#" is they treat women w/ kiddie gloves—cuz they think they're FRAGILE. Get it? #HASHTAG#. I'm more #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But ppl also use feminism to justify hating men. Like this "radfem": #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So it wouldn't be considered sexism, supremacy, and oppression if it were "happy husband, happy life"?????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Thanks for all the likes, folks! Glad to see not everyone is blind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# This is so funny. Sure, men may be the vast majority of offenders when it comes to violent crime but the portion of the total population of men who are violent criminals is small. 

What is your point?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# YES! Stop telling men "you're murderers and rapists".

Cuz... most men are not. Yes, we should be able to FUCKING SAY THAT. Telling all men they're murderers/rapists hasn't solved anything, has it? So that technique can fucking DIE.

That's the next revolution, assholes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perez regrets what he said about Britney. Who cares? We all say things when we didn't know better at the time. It's called life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Do you think the worst feminists represent all feminists?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yup.

Feminists: "We HELP men!"
I bring up a men's issue.
Feminists: "SHUT UP!!!! I DON'T F---king CARE ABOUT MEN!!!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Feminists ARE the new chauvinists who exhibit "toxic masculinity" by their OWN definition: they never admit weakness or flaw, &amp; expect absolute deference from everyone.

I've rarely if EVER heard a feminist say: "Yes, I can make mistakes. I'm not perfect."

Seriously. Can they?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# So we should protect women, but not gay people?

Just slam them w/ homophobic slurs? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yep, they constantly reference the PAST "injustices" to justify complaining in the PRESENT - where those injustices don't even exist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Cuz the elephant in the room is: men AND women favor women more.

Look at our immediate social circles. I always knew this! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# ^ This means that ppl who claim to be woke (YOU!) cannot be trusted.

BURN.

Welcome to the real world, honey. That's my gift to you, as someone older and wiser.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's more complicated than this: there are factors such as  appearance, race, gender, etc that determine how ppl/the world treats u. It doesn't have to color your life, but it's still true. Sometimes you can't deny the ugliness of this world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The stats speak for themselves.

Enjoy your emotions though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I always say: WOMEN have most of the power in relationships/families. I don't any woman who defers to her bf/husband/father of her kids. Do u? Not in the western world! Power isn't just a job title, public glory, or a salary. And this women's power? It's PERVASIVE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I've said that a million times: these so-called "feminists" r the FIRST to use (#HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG#-enforcing) terms like "#HASHTAG# up" or question a man's sexuality/manliness.nnThe fucking #HASHTAG#!!!!!!!!! !!!!!!!!! They're so fucking stupid! They can't even see it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emotions are more powerful than facts, for some people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# In my own life, men &amp; women seem to get along (unless I'm missing some undercurrent of hostility lol!).

Again: it's the shrill vocal minority that is driving this antagonistic narrative. And it causes damage cuz BOYS internalize all that misandry! (I did, as a kid!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It was completely relevant: women dodging responsibility for the same things men do...

Get your head checked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I always say this: who runs families? Or perhaps more "taboo": who has power in romantic heterosexual relationships?

Come on. It's often WOMEN.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Honey, you're 2-3 times more likely to die in a car accident and just as likely to die from the flu. Do u know anyone whose died from any of those? I haven't. 

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Again: sidestepping. U haven't acknowledged the stat that women are beaten by female partners MORE than male partners. You aren't helping women by ignoring this issue. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'll stop when we get rid of the trope "Yes, Dear" and "Happy wife, Happy life" - both which imply deference to women, i.e. INEQUALITY.

#USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And why does he think he can speak for all men and say "it's not insulting"???

I think it's insulting. There you go. And so do other people, a la your linked source.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# .00005% of men is not a big number. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep. Who wants to be a politician or CEO? It's INTENSE work that consumes lives. To borrow a cliche: (it has little) Work/Life balance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# men are often more logical, than emotional, compared to women. That's why.
Yes, there are exceptions!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#Women #USER# U know who is guilty of toxic masculinity? FEMINISTS &amp; their DICK JOKES, and their "jokes" about killing men.

I got one to delete hers. I f--king called her out on her toxic masculinity. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's just common sense? Why would you oppress a new group, in the name of stopping oppression??

... it's just common sense. But people are too BITTER.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If u wanna go even further.. there are "gender roles" in the animal kingdom!
Not saying that justifies EVERY trope in the human world (&amp; we can never deviate from these roles), but just saying... some of it just NATURE, not... an "evil male construction".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wow, I didn't know how it was in that part of the world (the effects of "feminism"). #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#Women The very people who claim to be against gender roles are the first to slam men w/ macho tropes like "man up", "man tears", etc.. So ironic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And I have tons of gay people in my family. They will attest: gay people are often cruelest to EACH OTHER.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# cuz people have such a visceral aversion to helping men/boys. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Why did the media down-play his allegations?

Why didn't they scream in the name of female victims everywhere? (again, "WOMEN DON'T LIE!!!!")

Explain that. LOL

The stench of convenience is overpowering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Re: the article's question about why there aren't more women politicians -

It's a very specialized skill. It requires sacrificing work/life balance. MOST people (men included!) don't wanna do that. I don't!

A (SMALL) group of men gravitate towards jobs like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Me: How about not scolding &amp; berating men when they do something "wrong".nThem: I'm NOT GONNA CODDLE MEN!!!!!nnThey treat men w/ the very "TOXIC MASCULINE" traits they purport to be against: stoic, hard, &amp; insensitive! nn#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah, women never lie...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# An evil person I knew was completely stupid, cuz he was a narcissist &amp; too terrified to court truth that opposed his ego. Yet he was evil. 

So it's possible to be stupid AND evil - if you're a narcissist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And as u prolly know, wives often inherit their husband's fortune cuz women tend to live longer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ppl don't even notice their bias against men, like this. It's so ingrained. They're so uncomfortable showing compassion to men - while preaching how "woke"/against gender tropes they are. The IRONY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So you will be the new oppressor. Congratulations on that title! Enjoy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# female privilege is being able to blame everything on men cuz "they were in charge", so you have no accountability for anything you do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER#, as a public figure who poses as an authority in your line of work - you completely UNDO your credibility when u "defend" something you failed to even RESEARCH first. At least READ her tweet before you rush to defend her, you twit. 
#USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Ur "approach" causes more damage than helps men's probs = antagonizing ALL of them for the actions of a SIGNIFICANT minority of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# 
Our ancestors created modern society.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup, me too. Women draw our compassion: they're smaller, softer, and more "vulnerable" looking. It's biologically programmed in us to be nicer to women. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If u decide to un-follow me, I beg you: tell me why.
LOL
I truly am grossly interested, against all better judgment!

HAHAHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if u believe in #HASHTAG#, y is it ok to BASH #HASHTAG# (but not #HASHTAG#)? Hint: That's NOT equality.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# 
#USER#

#USER#

#USER#women

 #HASHTAG# 
#USER#

 #HASHTAG#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You literally think individuals don't have any influence.

You're gonna negate every historical figure that had influence then, cuz "individuals" don't matter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# yup.

Also: "Believe women!" - without any TANGIBLE evidence!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You are literally saying: "People can touch each other without permission, if they're not physically harming each other."

LOL!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, boys are brainwashed &amp; conditioned to believe they're disposable, immoral, &amp; inferior for their interest in sex. 

Girls are held up as pure, clean paragons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Toxic Femininity = letting emotions overrule logic.

It's a women's trope to be overly emotional, &amp; it's destructive. Hence: Toxic Femininity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social anxiety is a SERIOUS problem; shouldn't it override the "politeness" of saying "Bless you", which is quite frankly, useless against a sneeze anyway? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# agreed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If u have a problem with the stats, take it with the CDC, not me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The story had holes in it from the beginning, regardless of political affiliation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hm? Me. I came up with it lol. No offense to women. It's just the female equivalent of bad male stereotypes.

Both the masculine AND feminine approach have drawbacks, as well as strengths. We need both, to complement each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# But yeah: there's a lot of power in being a victim. That's the #HASHTAG#; it's the lifeblood of being a "feminist". They use that to their advantage; without it, they'd have nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Also: what percentage of the population is that???

It's not even 1%! 

It's shockingly LOW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Don't become a lawyer. You just guessed my race with no evidence.

Nice representation for women everywhere... LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# And your infantile emoji's in your last tweet are so much better?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I'm gonna screenshot myself lol. 

I tweeted this recently: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# U think women don't intervene on men's matters? Telling them how to think and behave? Putting an end to "male only" spaces, while promoting "female only" spaces. 

U think wives don't have power over their husbands?
Where does the term "Yes, Dear" come from after all?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You threw gay men under the bus, &amp; feminists claim to be best friends w/ the LGBTQ community.

I knew feminists hated gay MEN.

What a *** you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No. Cuz these ppl know the old term is DEAD.

I want equality too. But I hate what feminism has become.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# toxic femininity: letting emotions overrule truth &amp; logic.

I'm coining the term here lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Cultural indoctrination.

People are mindless sheep. I will say that til I'm blue in the face. I DO NOT idealize people. We aren't that smart.

An elite is smart. The rest of humanity are SHEEP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Seriously. U wanna control someone? Judge them. Disapprove of what they're doing, even if it's the most BANAL thing.

This gets under people's skin.

It's a cowardly way to "dominate" someone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# So she'd be fine if people mocked International Women's Day?

LOL #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Omg, you're dumb. I already told you: "feminists" use this as an excuse to hate on men, when only .000005% of men are guilty of commiting this crime!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ppl "joke" about how low maintenance #HASHTAG# are, then turn around &amp; accuse them of hogging up resources/destroying the #HASHTAG# w/ their "greedy" ways... Which one is it? You can't accuse men of OPPOSITE things!

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#Women You sound like a man placating a feminist, hahaha.. #HASHTAG# nnbtw, that's exactly how you get ppl to shut up about important issues: make them feel sheepish for giving af.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I agree w/ you both. It's devolved into the most shallow, superficial, commercial shell of its former self.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If men earn more than #HASHTAG#, it's a problem. If #HASHTAG# earn LESS than women, it's a problem.nnYes, it's so "hard" to be a woman, and so "easy" to be a man!nn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#ism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# B-- please. It's cuz feminists contradict themselves constantly out of hypocrisy and lies. Check out this one who says "it's ok to hit men": #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# This is over your head but I must educate u.

Here's an example of stereotyping: It's mostly GAY MEN who have HIV. But just cuz they're the MAJORITY of HIV cases doesn't mean most of them have it! And they don't deserve to be stereotyped for it. Get it?

Don't stereotype. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If humans are so complex, why do they put each other in boxes so readily? That's not complex. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retweeting forever.  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# 
#USER#

#USER#

#USER#women

 #HASHTAG# 
#USER#

 #HASHTAG#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yep. I had a self-avowed #HASHTAG# ADMIT she doesn't have statistics!!

It was fucking HILARIOUS! And I'm sure she's not the only one.

Feminist = BONKERS. Seriously! They're mentally disabled idiots. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I literally just tweeted this:
People: I'm not good at competition or physical strength, so I'm declaring it "toxic masculinity". #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# 
We aren't as easily offended.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The #HASHTAG# is: YOU must think #HASHTAG# r "quiet &amp; deferential" if u think they hold no influence on society &amp; culture.nI don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i keep saying this #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ppl: Men need to stop buying into #HASHTAG# tropes.nAlso ppl: Ew, I'm not gonna date a #HASHTAG# man. That's not manly.nn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#ism #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The #HASHTAG# of "#HASHTAG#" using gender tropes like "MAN UP". (which they do!)nnThey have no self-awareness about their own #HASHTAG# mindsets.nnThat's why no one likes them. Not cuz we're against #HASHTAG#, but cuz we're against... psychotic #HASHTAG#?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ugh, really? People are so stupidly blind to their own misandry. And often, they claim to be "enlightened" and "woke" for fuck's sake. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's why I don't trust human judgment! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've had both a charmed life &amp; a hard life, &amp; honestly? The former doesn't justify the latter.
Life is hard. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 100% true.

Worst part is: society lets this hypocrisy rule. We're afraid to call ppl out on this, cuz they've shamed us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Society: Mental health is so important!

Also society: We can say "kill all men"! It doesn't hurt men, mentally.

..... shit's gonna hit the fan someday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Often, the very ppl who claim to "fight for men/boys" are the first to BALK when someone dares say: "Maybe you should treat them w/ more consideration."nSome even respond with: "Man up! Crybaby!" w/o realizing the #HASHTAG# - they're supposed to b "feminists" AGAINST #HASHTAG# roles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The other side of the coin is when they complain about not getting any attention from anyone, lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And every one of those coffee shop feminists' eyes glaze over when you attempt to talk about actual men's issues.

They're all talk, no action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good! We need more of that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why stop there? British and Chinese cultures are considered more "stoic" and "reserved".

Should we consider their cultures "harmful" cuz they're not more "open" and "expressive" w/ their emotions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# yup... they've no self awareness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "Men are expendable". 
-So all humans are not equal after all?

He might wanna tell the woke movement this. It undermines everything they (allege) to be fighting for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#Women Feminists are never nutty: #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep. Just like one woman doesn't speak for all women either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# When someone said women's oppression was more important than men's cuz it was "more pervasive", I asked:

Should racism against Asians be prioritized as less important than racism against black people, since the latter is "more pervasive"?

No response, of course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The people in charge are pitting us against each other. It's a common tactic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# this is why no one takes feminists seriously.

It's not cuz we don't believe the "radical notion that women are people". It's that we believe the RADICAL NOTION that women are ACCOUNTABLE too - and you don't!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "#HASHTAG#" is comparable to a dictatorship now: an ideology we can't even question. People literally say: "#HASHTAG# r useless / #HASHTAG# r perfect"—with almost no #HASHTAG#. Even if it's hyperbole, it's dangerous rhetoric that seeps into the conscience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You think there are more (incels) than there are men who SUPPORT women?

Where's your proof?

If I walk outside, I'll bump into an incel? They're so plenty??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Saying (all) "men are the problem" also CREATES more problems, cuz you dismiss millions of great men out there.

That's what today's "advocates" don't realize. THEY are part of the problem!!1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Also: the majority of a minority does not equal the majority of another group.
All U.S. presidents have been men. Does that men all U.S. men will become president?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# ^This doesn't even make sense, u idiot. Ur just trying to twist like a pretzel to make women into victims yet again. LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# U advocates love to stress the most tangible (physical) evidence against men, but when a woman makes allegations, suddenly:  u don't care about tangible evidence. It's "BELIEVE WOMEN!" @ all costs.
Cuz ur so emotional &amp; subjective, u wanna herald women as heroes &amp; men as villains #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Or they grew up without a father]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# hahaha love it.

But no: smart people are plagued by the burdens of truth in this world. Dumb ppl are oblivious - ignorance is bliss. You can't just count on them to walk into traffic, ha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# To be fair, there are extremists among MRA's i.e. they post anti-women things all the time on my Facebook.
There are extremists in every group. I'm not knocking MRA's. I will fight for men's rights 'til I die!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# SCIENTIFICALLY PROVEN that men support women instead of each other!!

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone is crazy, stupid, &amp; fucked up - regardless of gender, race, sexuality.

All humans are terrible. LOL #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Uh... I see women uplifting each other all the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "greedily dominated"? That's simplistic. Maybe some jobs appeal more to certain demographics.

Do women want to pick up garbage, work in sewers, and put out fires??

Why aren't they complaining about finding jobs in those fields?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>