<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bullshit, and even THEN, you refused to acknowledge the full context of what your dead-eyed temple priest says from his pedestal.nnThis is not a formal conversation and it never was, but the way you comport yourself in refusing to educate will win you no sympathy or support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "We can start with what I dont mean. I dont mean taking innocent women at gunpoint and handing them over to useless men..."nnThanks for clarifying Jordan! Maybe you should speak clearly so that people don't get the wrong idea when you say incels deserve "enforced monogamy."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# He sells self-help books dude, like he's not even a novel or interesting conman like Alex Jones and his slobbering ads for fluoride-free toothpaste. He's just selling The Secret for Men.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's funny seeing actual economists calling NFTs a bubble that will inevitably experience massive collapse and NFT guys like "yeah I'll just get out before that" like my dude... Get out now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# A major issue is that as older conservatives die, get sick, and lose power, younger conservatives become more isolated, lose mentorship that provides opportunity in politics, and become more prone to fascist radicalization.

The self-victimization complex on the right...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I know various hospitals and services can't keep up with linen washing/exchange because of gowns and curtains, excess garbage, excess electricity consumption, short-staffing... The next five years are going to be a serious strain on medical infrastructure and budget.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're shocked and disappointed that someone who is clearly brilliant *and* accomplished would turn to podcasts and platforms that no reputable doctor would ever appear on because he knows he'll never be questioned by someone with medical experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Listen if you don't know how to perform an invasive surgery to cut this very common infection out of your newborn's chest using your teeth, you don't DESERVE to be a mother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# 

You cool with a self-styled - albeit comically inept - nazi being on your side?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Socialism in what country and when?

Imo a lot of the "corruption" that people associate with the rise of communism in the early/mid-20th century is stuff that was even worse under monarchism and feudalism.

If you think Stalin was paranoid, read up on some Tsars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have more sympathy for Elon Musk more than most after learning more about what a tyrant his father is, the horrific bullying he endured in grade school (he required reconstructive surgery), and that he's actually been pretty consistent in vocally hating apartheid.

However...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Do you think Musk adequately pays or credits the people that work at Tesla, SpaceX, or whatever company he farts out?

Like you wanna suck his filthy ass for being a genius, prove he is a genius and not just a guy who consistently makes the world worse for people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Would say it's less of an Arrival and more of a departure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I will always support people who kick the fuck out of fascists who have historically executed, imprisoned, and tortured people like me because of our identities and our disabilities.

You pretending these things are in any way alike is revolting and a wilful denial of history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Oh Christ not Jimmy dore don't make me watch Jimmy dore, what's the study he's citing, what is the direct source]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If kids feel guilty because they and their families are continuously benefiting from rape and murder that's been happening for hundreds of years then sure, but I don't know how kids reading about reconstruction are going to think "I literally did this"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# 1. Could you achieve a quorum of 75%?

2. Could you achieve turnout of at least 75% of voting age population?

3. Are there going to be registration issues like there are in the US?

Because the past referendums have not met those standards, turnout is far lower than acceptable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah, the absence of a maternal figure is really common as well, Trump's mom had an emergency hysterectomy that left her physically frail and mentally unwell when he was 3, and most of his life she was in and out of institutions and Trump attached to his father, Fred Trump Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Have you ever heard the origins of police departments across America?

It's kind of shocking how many originated as slave patrols, union breakers, and native American hunters.

If you would like a podcast series that's well-sourced, look up Behind the Police by Robert Evans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Rowling has said that "superfans" obsessively point out minor continuity errors in her books but when you bring up the list of errors there are major errors and flaws in basically every chapter, several of which have been edited for later reprints.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I'm not rich, what I am is concerned about mass, preventable human death because people are angry or frustrated and can't employ well-warranted caution when planning to reopen. This is bad and has been bad but what you're suggesting would make things significantly worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Could I discuss a specific example of an group from within an institution addressing the racism of its foundation?

This is an open letter from professional/academic Jungian psychotherapists on Jung's views on "Africans" and how it affects the practice of Jungian psychotherapy...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Mhm yeah and places with low vaccination rates are doing worse, which is why America, Brazil, and India are leading the world in both cases and deaths.

Cases admitted to ICUs worldwide are overwhelmingly unvaccinated people. This isn't rocket science.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The code of Hammurabi for example is SUPER concerned with grain production, land-leasing, and punishment of agriculture labourers. Fascinating read tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is going to happen in Ontario for sure, our cases are still rising daily and we've gone into some real weak "restrictions" and I fully believe it's because they know the conservative provincial government and all the con mayors would throw an apocalyptic tantrum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There's so much very interesting Soviet-era folklore, like people think a lot of it was propaganda when really folklorists in the Soviet Union had to fight to be recognized as workers but were eventually a treasured part of Soviet culture and got to travel across Russia learning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# R Palme Dutte said that "fascism is capitalism in decay."

When control of institutions is seized by individuals learning previously elite-only rules, mechanics, and languages, fascists revert to logic that they know they can enforce: Might Makes Right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Iirc it's something like 0.1% of Bitcoin holders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Jung is a prominent contemporary example, since the late 80s increasing attention has been drawn to the fact that he believed black people had "primitive" intellects and psyches, culminating in open letters from Jungian groups acknowledging this and cautioning psychotherapists...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He was refusing to use preferred pronouns for his students, one complained to faculty, it escalated until there were small on-campus protests, and he turned it into "I am being CANCELLED despite being such a beloved academic!"

He was seriously disliked by several colleagues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ok now do the holders of the other trillion in student debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think what bugs me most is when people are like "I'm such a nerd I love Marvel" and it's like "me too but please doctor can you operate on my son" and they're like "no can do he's wearing a Batman shirt and I literally just said I'm a marvel nerd."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Well for some identities that claim victimhood it certainly is weak association, but for identities that have experienced consistent and explicit oppression or alienation from self-determination, it becomes a strong rallying point. I don't think it's outrageous to say that...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "We're leaving it up because it's important Libertarians feel comfortable talking the realities of current bigotry in America."nnYou're leaving it up because you're selfish racists and pretending to eat crow lets you continue saying this to your dumbfuck adherents who agree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I would say that's up to indigenous people to decide, like it was when they came up with the term "two-spirit."nnYou can hold this view on the historicity of indigenous attitudes toward gender, but that doesn't stop indigenous people from deciding what is right for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# For me the wildest part is that they brought her to a guy that was like "Ah, I speak Portuguese and recognize this as Portuguese!"

Bro she was not speaking Portuguese lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Also the actress who plays Renee, the autistic girl, is actually a non-speaking autistic person named Madison Bandy. She demonstrates that non-verbal autistic people can still be given a voice, both literally and metaphorically, through positive portrayals and consultations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Marxist goal of destroying childhood innocence"nnThese guys know that Marx was fighting against child labour while children were literally working in factories, right? Or is this them calling Democrats pedophile socialists because you can just say anything now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah the trade unions should have adequate bargaining power regarding industrial standards and maintenance, they're the ones that know what they're doing, and state specialists should be on rotation to avoid consolidation of power in the industries. Isn't that how we got Lysenko?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Can you shut the fuck up, you've already proven yourself the kind of self-victimizing piece of shit that believes this is anything like the Holocaust.

Anyways woops looks like kids are getting hospitalized, I hope you're a happy little special boy now!

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Why are you so entrenched in your beliefs that you're chanting them at me like an incantation to banish unwelcome spirits? What is driving you to very comfortably reassert these slogans? What has made your outlook so dour in the face of imminent reopening?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Because I love my kids and think they're funny and enjoy sharing that joy with people?

Jesus what fucked you up and made you so jaded dude.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Actually far less black people and significantly more East and Southeast Asian people. Tolkien criticized South African apartheid in letters to his son, but also said in other letters that orcs were intended to look like the "least lovely Mongol-types."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You still haven't provided counter evidence, you are entirely putting the onus on me to provide evidence, which I have at several points demonstrating Peterson's open association with conservative organizations and individuals. Not just "agreeing" on points, but AS A SPEAKER.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# So you don't think that coronavirus has killed nearly a million people in the us? Or you think people should chill because doctors initially predicted more or?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yes, or provided evidence that this is a conspiracy to destabilize and destroy the gentiles instead of Jewish people hiring each other, which is just nepotism and happens in literally every industry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I agree, at a certain point you can't keep seeing the same people at the protests you support and say "we aren't like them at all, though, they don't represent us!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I don't know why people are disagreeing, that's in NYC and they passed a vaccine mandate on the 27th of September. These guys probably already got fired. Lots of people got let go because they refused to get vaccinated. It's a problem in areas with high concentrations of this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Mitt Romney forcibly cut a classmates hair because he thought it looked gay.

Mitt Romney pretended to be a cop to pull over classmates in college.

Mitt Romney tied his dog to the roof of his car and drove for hours.

The dudes a fucking asshole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Hm interesting tell me more about these libertarians who are not racist, I've never met them #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Like I don't particularly care for Mencia's style of comedy and of course the plagiarism was blatant but like that was the end of the dudes career, his show was cancelled, his roles dried up, he went back to being a touring comic. It was brutal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Before his final exams. It's unclear why he dropped out, but by his accounts, he couldn't afford tuition.

I always wonder what he would have done if he had stayed in school.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And yes many Germans actively participated in race riots, pogroms, murder... But not the majority. The majority was content with "out of sight, out of mind." They were fine with chasing Jews out of Germany, proudly declaring themselves Judenfrei, but most could never have...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I was definitely someone who thought the choice between Hilldawg and Trump was a lose-lose situation but I was genuinely surprised when she bombed and lost.

Anybody who said they voted Trump for econ purposes was lying or duped. Sadly a lot of people were truly conned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I actually looked into this and I think that the right has over-blown what is a legitimate exaggeration.

The main issue I've seen is that the 6509 number is too high, but the official number from the TRC - confirmed deaths - is 4118.

A discrepancy of 2000 is notable but...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If guilt is what prevents them from enslaving people, forcibly converting them, and committing genocide then yes, yeah, absolutely.

I would say that feeling guilty is less bad than all of those things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Nobody thinks Florida is evil, it's just a southern state governed by a colossal dunce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes if you change the metrics and variables you can argue anything, but the metrics and variables as they exist in contemporary society are pretty clearly defined by years of segregation along racial, gender, and class-based lines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It is kind of funny that you're lecturing me on how Canadians cannot understand US history (my ancestors were shipped down to Louisiana but whatever) while simultaneously lecturing me on prejudice.nnSee I might "prejudge" Libertarians, but they always prove me right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The noble savage myth is about ascribing a set of values to all indigenous people, not discussing the ways in which their cultures were oppressed and eliminated by colonization and advocating for indigenous self-determination.nnI don't know about the US but in Canada...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Do you think the only people who this will affect are unvaccinated people, and you think that there's a government plot to do soft reopens and closes for some reason? What's the reason?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He said he was "forgotten by god" and that the way to prevent murderous incel attacks was "enforced monogamy."

If you want more criticisms of him from academics, this is a big one from the guy that got him the job at UofT

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I work at the hospital in support and everybody is so burnt out in different ways. Paramedics are seeing a lot of really sad stuff out there. My understanding is that the convoy has delayed hospital transport on a few occasions so far, but i can't confirm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Two spirit is a modern term intended to reflect, replace, and reclaim concepts of non-binary genders in varying native groups that have historical and anthropological basis.nnIt's a contemporary shorthand that is hotly debated even within indigenous LGBT circles, but...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And you listen to sources who have documented the Holocaust extensively through primary archival sources, like The Auschwitz memorial, and you call out fascist grifters like Classically James or whatever when they try to levy claims of fascism against people likely to be victims?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Some weird anarchist just told me Hitler was Jewish, Marx was a Nazi, called me a tankie, and then suggested I was stupid because I only did four years of university before dropping out.

That's not why I'm stupid, I'm stupid because I smoke a lot of weed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I had to reread this because I thought this was just a picture of Molly Shannon, biopic when???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You can find other libertarian parties comments on this by googling but here's one as an example. They even acknowledge a racial component to the murder, very rare for libertarians tbh but also popular thought has turned a lot in the past 10 yearsnn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I don't think that anybody is really talking about mass deportation seriously, 4.5 million is about 10% of the population and would devastate infrastructure. However, Apartheid only ended in 1994 and there is still an imbalance in power held by Afrikaners over black Africans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I can't find any free info beyond abstracts, but a psychotherapist named Farhad Dalal studied Jung's writings and released articles discussing how his colonialist views effect his work. Recently Dalal's work inspired an open letter from a British group of psychotherapists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Theft should be punished by lawyers and judges, not by dogs. If somebody steals $50 or a bike or even a car, and a cop siccs a dog on them, how is that a proportionate response to the crime?nnHow much does dog training cost? Medical expenses? Extra court costs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Imo whitewashing in progressive circles is usually a reaction from more centrist groups to make radical action more appealing. No better example than MLK being diluted down to "I have a dream" and "content of character."

As the gay rights movement gained political momentum...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I see what you're saying but also "great products" is a bit of a stretch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It's not like there were a lot of venues for white people and black people to discuss or debate on equal footing. Gay bars were some of the more neutral grounds where people of different races could commiserate on shared oppression, but there's still evidence of ample racism...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This happened at an "anti-vaxx" rally in Ottawa as well alongside several serious injuries and assaults and a soup kitchen robbery. I think anti-vaxxers really need to examine their relationship to white nationalists and white supremacists, it's startlingly noticeable. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# For sure! Like what happened with Makhno was frankly pretty shit all around! And honestly imo fuck that dude! But also there was a reason he joined with the Soviets several times, and there was a reason they accepted his help. And I think in general contemporary anarchists...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Any resource with ample numbers or high sustainability would be considered "free," even though in theory it's limitless.

If you don't believe we live in a positive-sum environment re: food, housing, wealth, access to education or healthcare, then you need to expand on why...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't bubblegrunge just that one Olivia Rodrigo song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You try being occupied by America after they drop nuclear bombs on two of your cities!

But seriously, America did a lot of this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think Mao's China is super fascinating, especially Mao's desire to improve conditions for rural people based in his own experience growing up in the countryside. I'm not a Maoist, but I find him a lot more approachable than Soviet authors who can be cold and paranoid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The Irish who lived alongside black people as designated non-whites in the 19th century. As Irish people were assimilated into white government as law enforcement, Irish people who remained within black neighbourhoods experienced increased rates of police violence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Libertarians actually resoundingly denounced the murder of Philando Castile, specifically pointing out that he followed gun laws to the letter. I don't have issues with that I have issues with them blaming "government" instead of white supremacy that is enforced by their ideology]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's wild because people are saying "oh who cares omicron is milder" when 1. Like you said we don't know that just yet and 2. People are still being hospitalized for delta.

Hospitals are bracing for an influx of hospitalizations after the holidays. Hopefully it's for nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're telling me the head of government who increased military expenditure by 43% while drastically reducing social spending is telling you that "government is bad actually!"  and your response is "this guy is a genius"

Jesus that's bleak 

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You won't catch me defending Mencia, he's terrible, but I do think it's interesting that Rogan got his first big viral break destroying a man's career over plagiarism (one of the only major cancellations for it too) and spends good chunks of time complaining about cancel culture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The result of individual racism, but the result of an institution or system teaching students to treat black people and white people differently when there's no evidence supporting that difference in treatment.nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I haven't read much post-2000 Avengers tho! They may have changed it, he is one of those characters they keep digging back up for various reasons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Interesting because even the libertarian party of New Hampshire issued a retraction saying it came across as racist and then nuked the tweet but I guess a bunch of dumb white guys with a child's understanding of history are the experts on what is and isn't racism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# BRPD police budget is well over $100 million btw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There is something profoundly ghoulish about a diet app co-opting "cognitive behavioural therapy" in what I feel is a blatant attempt to appeal to people who've struggled with anxiety and depression and may have positive associations with that therapy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# This is not a conclusion and this is still being debated by a variety of psychotherapists, Jungian and otherwise, but the consensus is that issues with Jung's view on black people mean that Jungian Psychotherapy may not have the desired outcome on black patients.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This lady in the lunch room has been talking on her phone for about 30 minutes straight.

I don't mean she's been on the phone I mean she literally hasn't stopped talking for like 30 minutes, she is audibly winded from how much she is talking.

I'm mostly impressed by the stamina]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That's so much worse than what it sounds like]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I was curious so I looked a little into this and I can't find a primary source readily available.

The main source for this quote is a man named Nathaniel Weyl who was briefly a member of CPUSA in the 30s before becoming an avowed conservative and anti-communist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Right and anybody being like "this is questionable" gets "WHY ARE YOU DEFEBDING NANCY REAGAN" and it's like, I'm not, I'm just saying we should be attacking her for the war on drugs, killing Rock Hudson, pissing away who knows how much taxpayer money on her personal psychic...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We truly are living in a golden age of capitalism, look at how average income per capita stagnated for about 50 thousand years before skyrocketing by 1000% in 2010]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Define it closer to genderfluidity or non-binary genders, and I've talked with indigenous people who say it's not a part of their cultural identity at all and that those people are crazy.nnImo what really matters is that it's indigenous people who define it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The more you learn about Stalin's life, the horrific circumstances in which he lived and the awful things that happened, the more it makes sense that he was not particularly well-adjusted and Lenin didn't have faith in him as the leader of the USSR.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Why do you feel like you need to shame someone for doing something for ten seconds that hurts literally no one, gives updates to friends and family, and keeps things light in a stressful situation?

How is you insisting that she is wrong and you are right *not* narcissism?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She literally posted a video whining about losing a sponsorship, we all know she's going to keep making money off you sad dorks, but this is conspostingLs and a con posted her L.

Big brain genius.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# He inspired Hercules but wasn't actually Hercules (because Marvel's Hercules is a separate character who actually is) and while I don't think it's clear that he *is* Gilgamesh, he does confirm it was his name in Walt Simonson and John Buscema's Avengers (#HASHTAG#, 1989) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the most difficult challenges in confronting violence against children is how often it is linked with poverty.

Poverty, as a stressor that affects the entirety of one's life, leads to fractured relationships in families and communities, less focus and ability to...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah if there's one thing bubbles are known for, it's growing indefinitely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I will disagree because I think that Terrace House is the crowning achievement of reality TV and I think it's largely a response to reality TV that pits people against each other in a contest by not having competitive aspects and encouraging positive interactions and cooperation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The first two frames are from his chat with Paglia right? I watched the whole thing, at one point he says lesbians are more physically violent because of "penis envy" and suggests that women miss being conquered and raped like in the olden days. Paglia nods her head dipshittily.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life would have been quite different.

In some ways, I know it would have been better. I would have been better.

But it was not, and tomorrow I turn 30 with a smile on my face and more love than I knew I was capable of holding in my heart.

Na Zdrovie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# How unexpected, a nazi denying the Holocaust???1?1?1???

God it's abundantly clear now why you're the master race, jeez, hey those kids at the elementary school won't stand a chance against an intellect like yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We should hate libertarians because they're racist and selfish, not because they accidentally took the correct stance on drug legislation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If a guy steals a car and then runs away, and response is to sicc a dog on someone who might be a teenager joy-riding, I don't see that as proportionate at all, and as we see in the racial disparity of victims, I would call that racial profiling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I say specifically spanking because many more kids are killed by their parents' abuse in different methods, but "spanking" is seen as one of the slighter, more accepted corporal punishments.

But worst case scenario, you compress a child's spine and kill them. Nobody means to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# 1. Nothing to do with the discussion at hand

2. I'm sure you are just a bundle of love and acceptance

3. I'm literally trying to explain an idea from a neoclassical economist to someone who linked me to a child's NatGeo page on scarcity. You can help or shut up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Why? What is the breakdown of reasons? One study suggests that gay and bisexual men are significantly more likely to attempt suicide, especially early in life. Suicide amongst Inuit people is ten times higher than the rest of the population.nnIt's not just a male problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's -30 out and 9pm why would I be outside, this is the time we both have dedicated to being obnoxious fucks on twitter, I'm just pedantic while you're dismissive.

I have kids, what's your excuse for being in this late on a Friday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And I am SO sorry for being casual in my parlance, Master First Approximation, I should have treated a superior like you with proper courtesy and respect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Also can't forget the Nemoidians, the inscrutable and shrewd industrialists with the slant eyes that Lucas confirmed spoke in voices he based off of East Asian people's accents at a panel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yes it's very hard to maintain all aspects of culture through genocide, war, and assimilation over a few hundred years. But how contemporary indigenous people attempt to relate to pre-colonial gender expression is up to them. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Like again libertarians are comfortable bickering about whether you make $7 or $10 but threaten the billion dollar lifestyle of an exploitative owner and oh no no no, you have VIOLATED THE NAP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's kind of wild how the first book sets up Jake's decision to fight the Yeerks by showing that his brother is controlled by one, and then the last book has Rachel turn into a grizzly bear and tear the shit out of Tom while he's a snake before getting killed herself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Like I'm just saying I wouldn't bring my kids anywhere near Ted Cruz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sure yeah Stalin *was* paranoid, anti-Semitic, drunk from 1945 onward (don't blame him tho)

Prior to that, Nicholas II sent millions to death in failed wars, oversaw state-funded pogroms against Jews, and rural areas (like Georgia) experienced constant hardship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Sure yeah, people who are closer related, however distantly, are more likely to have the same blood type or other properties or traits. And mixed race people exist. It doesn't make them form a hivemind bro, lay off the science fiction late at night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Friends living downtown are saying that despite having access to porta-potties they're just shitting in snowbanks along Metcalfe and Elgin. Cops are saying they're peaceful but I've seen at least three separate reports of assault from drunk guys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# FDR called the internment camps "concentration camps" at several recorded points. The Nazis didn't begin implementing mass death programs until 1942 (the first gas chamber was used in 43), but by that point millions had already died in the prisons, as intended.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saw a well-moisturized British guy.

Aloe Guvna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I mentioned elsewhere I've met indigenous people who enjoy the term and feel it reflects them accurately, and I've spoken with indigenous people who reject the term altogether.nnI didn't realize it was a point of contention with conservatives but I guess I'm not surprised.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah but you don't know how many videos about Krav Maga they've watched on YouTube.

Not even counting compilations of cool martial arts moves that probably include some capoeira spins that would tip their legs right out of their sockets if they tried.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I don't think he did since he employed broad economic changes that massively decreased the capacity for poor people to gain any form of assistance, which further disenfranchised them and established the contemporary republican stance of fear-mongering against social programs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right, he was a supporter of Nazism until some point in the 30s and adjusted some of his work on Jews. But not all of it!

Here's a full rundown of his relationship with nazi Germany and his views on "the Jewish psychology,"

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You are effectively just reinforcing a status quo that has demonstrably failed women and minorities in securing them gainful employment based on their accomplishments.nnThat's not equality. Libertarians are not committed to equality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I've talked to a few indigenous people about this and it really varies from individual to individual and band to band. I've met some FN people who identify as such and kind of like your sayin, believe it's taking roles outside of gender norms, I've met indigenous people who...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Ultimately, we don't really know much about these early humans beyond what we can glimpse from samples, and how much were learning often leaves more questions than answers.

Cool article about very early human culture and how little we know.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think people tend to forget that Holocaust denial originated within Nazi Germany and was so effective that nobody really knew the extent of the concentration camps until the Soviets liberated Auschwitz.

Hitler is said to have made jokes pretending he wasn't aware of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I studied Maus in university and something you may not be aware of if you've only read the first volume is that Art Spiegelman reflects on his decision to use animals in the second volume and talks about how it probably wasn't a great idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I think the common thread between you guys who are all freaking out at a young mother is that you don't know what RSV is, how common it is, or how severity presents.

I've said it before and I'll say it again, baby is not on oxygen, baby is just being observed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Personally I would just change my name like most Germans named Hitler did after WWII, maybe change it to something that shows I am opposed to Nazism, like Carl Communist or Mike Jewsarecool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Maybe Ted Cruz but that's as low as the bar gets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you told me about a global pandemic, and you told me about how many lives would be lost, I might have approached the world differently.

If you told me how repeatedly disillusioned and confused I would be, I might have tried to kill myself on the spot instead of in three years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Who is a dishonest individual that has no interest in discussion or coming to a conclusion that approximates the truth, it is you.

I have bent over backwards finding a wide variety of sources for this conversation, and you have provided nothing, consistently misunderstanding me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She just hung up and took the deepest breath, I'm really amazed, that was astonishing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Dean Thomas, the only explicitly black character other than Shacklebolt, doesn't have a father.

The very Irish Seamus Finnigan is constantly exploding things.

Cho Chang's name, and being placed in ravenclaw.

Turns out Voldemort's snake is a Chinese woman for some reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Marie Antoinette was sold into marriage in a foreign country when she was a child, was never particularly bright, and after her arrest was forced to watch aristocratic "revolutionaries" get her son drunk to the point of vomiting and then abuse him until he died.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've been reading some capitalist "classical liberal" literature in my spare time and all the people who drop shit like "Read Sowell/Mises/Smith" bother me on another level now because I know they're just watching pragerU videos that name drop these douchebags]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Black people maintaining distrust and resentment against American police or government is simulacra or loose association. For indigenous people with gripes against the church, there are living survivors still seeking legal compensation for the abuse endured. These aren't abstract]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah it's a complicated issue in Canada because of our history as a mixed French/Irish-Catholic and English-Prot country.nnBut enough Irish Catholics fucked up Nazis for the Brits that they kind of owed em and it was pretty easy to get people to hate the French.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# One time as a teenager I was very upset at a friend who wrote shitty, goofy poems for another friend who had died. My gf at the time saw how angry I was and asked my why I believed I had the right to dictate her grief, and whether or not my anger was producing any benefit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# So you're claiming you're a doctor and then saying that a non-peer reviewed "study" conducted on Facebook has merit as a statistically sound source.

Are you studying at DeVry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's the only time you see pan-left solidarity, Marxists and MLs and anarchists and MLMs and Trots and the one unironic Posadist and even the ones not worth mentioning are all holding hands under a rainbow like "fuck libertarians"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I don't think leftists are worried about being "replaced" as much as "placed in concentration camps" and I'm pretty sure CRT just wants to teach US history in public school, and I don't want to get into how you're conflating ideologies and academic/public education concepts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "whoever flew this flag is personally responsible"

No dude everybody who saw the nazi and Confederate flags and didn't immediately stomp the fuckers into paste is complicit. The cops who didn't arrest those flying hate symbols are complicit. You aren't wriggling out of this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Are you suggesting the FBI is incapable of doing anything racist?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Both of Marx' parents were Jewish by birth, his father was a rabbi, his grandfathers were both rabbis, and he was and still is often criticized for being a Jew by white supremacists.

Jews are not exclusively a religious order, especially at the time that Marx lived.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One of the sadder things I learned moving away from online ML culture and into reading beyond the popular theory is that Lenin really did not like the term "Leninism," but Stalin pushed it and made it part of the canon of communist history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Can I see your sources for those claims, because those are wild claims bro and I have *never* heard an indigenous person say that about the concept of two-spirit, even if they dislike the term and are generally pretty socially conservative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Like certainly some groups had looser systems of government than others but the largest American indigenous groups had distinct systems of government ranging from pluralistic democracies made up of clans to religious monarchies ruled by kings and a theological class of priests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# With Alzheimer's to advocate for themselves if they weren't capable of it, but they're still deserving of advocacy from someone who is capable.

This is why we have lawyers and advocacy organizations that try to have self-representation but are often reliant on Good Samaritans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Who didn't much feel like going to war for England (understandably!) Hesitance to defend their historical oppressors was interpreted by English Prot Canada as open support for Hitler. As WWII went on, more Catholics went overseas and also more Catholics became involved...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Lenin wrote that imperialism was the highest state of capitalism, and Dutte wrote that fascism was capitalism in decay. So you could see colonialism as the expansion of a thriving capitalist state and fascism as the consolidation of power in a struggling capitalist state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A lot of them genuinely don't see or expect the throughline between anti-mandate, anti-vaxx, and right-wing populism. I would hope supporters would be shocked seeing multiple swastikas, Confederate flags, but apparently not enough to stop them from setting up and hanging around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# "they're saying the exact same thing as you, and nobody liked it, we pretty much all agreed that shit was terrible, so don't do it."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a feeling that she is the most capable of the family. She is brilliant, skilled, cunning, and the family acknowledges this. She is the apple of everyone's eye. Both families adore her.

The only reason she is stuck in the shit and piss is because she was born there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# lol you're definitely over-estimating how good line cook positions get based on training and experience bro, I know people with 20 years and degrees making ~$20 an hour.

But sure sure "percentiles" yes yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is a description of the actions Colonel Ustra took against women accused of being "communists" or "guerillas." Many were just workers or related to other suspected communists. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I already defined it in the first tweet bro, keep up.

I'm on to subcategories of scarcity, namely artificial scarcity which is the most important kind when we are discussing zero-sum and positive-sum economics.

Who are you, I'm lecturing the nazi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I understand what he's trying to say, that birthing has become a for-profit industry with unnecessary procedures pushed by docs, but home births are still medical procedures and you still need a professional (midwife, doula, DOGOBGYN) there to make sure everything goes well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The majority of political prisoners in the USSR in the 30s were not Nazis, they were kulaks.

Stalin was *extremely* paranoid by the 40s (understandable) and plenty of people ended up in the gulag who didn't belong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Well I disagree with the direction they're coming from and where they believe we're at in the "civil war" but I feel it's clear that tensions are escalating between progressives and reactionaries. I don't think the level of violence is unpreventable but it's not getting better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Always struck me as bizarre that the Catholic school boards tend to have more advanced curriculums on sex ed and world religions than standard stream public schools but I guess the trade off is you gotta wear the uniforms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "but snowboarding can be dangerous so let's give him a TBI."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I'm watching China's efforts to sell state-sponsored and regulated NFTs after their crypto ban. If their market is stabilized I would imagine the west would consider making changes to legislation to follow suit and limit fraudulent or illegal interactions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Air Farce was a core part of my childhood and Tom Green is a comedian that every gross teenage boy thinks is *the funniest*. He has his own brand of milk beer you can buy at the LCBO. It's okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# And they believe that additions diminish the efforts they made initially. Strong arguments against that are the whitewashing of early LGBT movements, racism that continues within LGBT circles, disproportionately high rates of violence against trans people and people of colour...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In the meantime shouldn't we arrest the person who kidnapped 110 people and stranded them on a desert island.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# This is the introductory abstract to a 110 page study that contains *a lot* of nuance around defining what "minor and youth" sex trafficking is.

They define any minor that participates in commercial sex as the victim of a crime.

Not to mention "trafficking" seems to be done...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking the keys from his driver to bring his kid to the hospital as Ki-taek watched his bludgeoned son carried off and held his dying daughter in his arms, I thought that would be a breaking moment for him, but it wasn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is, my friends who work graveyard and live downtown are basically being tortured with sleep deprivation by these assholes, it's non-stop honking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Business. Jordan listens to his daughter because that's what you do as a father, but then does something you don't do as a doctor (even as a psychologist) and puts forward a claim that "superbugs" are ravaging hospitals and ergo hospitals kill more people than they save.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["ppl have a choice whether to see friends &amp; family this Christmas."

I'm going to be working at the hospital on Christmas with patients who cannot see their friends and families. Who are terrified that this wave of COVID will be the one that gets them. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wish I had a kid named Gordon but my wife said no]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We're a sweet baby rays family]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# One of the reasons the Nazis found support in India was because a lot of Indians were like "You hate the British? Say no more, well sign right up."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Crushing small business increases unemployment, not a good thing. "Destroying the middle class" doesn't tell me how you define middle class tbh. inflation is not a good thing for a government's re-election chances. consolidate wealth... How? To what end?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You know how there are people who are pretty sure they had mild or asymptomatic covid once or twice before testing?

I'm positive I've had multiple mild or asymptomatic breakdowns the past few years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Filing a false police report, especially with the intent of causing distress or emotional/physical/financial harm to an individual is a serious crime.

Because nothing actually happened I don't think a suit is necessary or desired but covering bases is a good idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Why do you keep saying that? Were not "preparing" for anything, were in the midst of dealing with it *right now* and it kind of sounds like you just want to drop restrictions and throw care to the wind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Well, Serena Williams, as one of the richest female athletes in the world, had enough money to fire her doctor and hire a new one.nnI don't believe most Americans have that option, and this doesn't exclusively affect rich black people, as demonstrated in the studies provided.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I lean Marxist so I don't really disagree, I just don't really understand people being like "you're literally an anarchist dummy" when they're saying something that I think is in line with Marxist doctrine too. The state has to go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obviously we know that the bulk of death threats come from the right wing (since most of the actual murders do too), but wow this is a interesting breakdown of threats sent the past few years and the legality of saying someone should be murdered or raped. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Online white supremacists reference Dragonball Z all of the time because they're children, it's way less common today than it was back on 4chan in the early 2000s, but you still hear shit like this or "concealing your power level" here and there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So someone says they don't like a comedian you do and your response is to belittle them for being autistic?

Even if you think this was a needlessly mean tweet, I don't think this is a great way to go about vocalizing that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Rogan's been coming under scrutiny for peddling misinformation by medical doctors lately, personally I don't think it's a good idea for him to have a disgraced psychology professor come on and spread further misinformation because his daughter wants to sell a diet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm pretty sure you're just making super broad generalizations about tens of millions of people so that you can justify the rape, slavery, and child murder that has led to the complete destruction of who knows how many unique cultures across half of the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Now I don't think we'll agree re: private sphere and it's late so I'm due for a hard medication shift so I don't want to get into a discussion on capitalism, but I actually really do agree that public policy needs to look at elevation of basic welfare...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am not a reality TV person, I actually really dislike reality tv because it's either needlessly combative or people ham up their interactions, so I am not an expert, I just think Terrace House is good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I think the Clinton's are the worst culprits of propagating "progressive" racism in America. Hillary coined the term "super-predators" and Biden/Bill passed the 94 crime bill which saw large, disproportionate increases in incarceration of black people, but I don't believe ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solzhenitsyn, a notable anti-communist and staunch supporter of Putin, advocated for Ukraine to rejoin Russia after the fall of the Soviet Union.

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm sure this would be a lot more effective if you threw in some animated hand gestures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I have *repeatedly* said "provide full context" and rather than doing so, you are implying I'm dishonest, saying I'm too lazy to source, saying I don't understand or that I'm projecting.

*Provide the full context or shut the fuck up.*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bro I'm dying this guy is going in on Pete Buttigieg for being Maltese like how racist do you have to be to look at Pete Buttigieg and think dudes not whiter than the driven snow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't eat meat beyond fish but I've killed a lot of rats in my time working in kitchens and basements, and I've always had cats to keep mice in check.

It doesn't feel good, but these are pests that can cause disease, destruction of goods, and even death in serious cases.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Contemporary "queer" culture you've mentioned.nnLike it is explicitly meant to apply to indigenous people who don't feel comfortable with Eurocentric definitions of gender and sexuality and want a term to distinguish themselves from non-native gender and sexuality concepts.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>