<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why appalling comments and not just comments or his opinion now. just more crazed stirring by the standard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Joel you are clearly scum, promoting hate and abuse. Just another Remoaner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# Now happy to pollute children. They are a danger to the UK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Oh, so it's ok to touch memorials. Great just what we need. You are supposed to be a Cllr. There was no need to touch or be near a memorial to get the message across.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wow, an apology that actually, worryingly seems honest, from an MP. There might actually be hope for #USER# ðŸ™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#
A vote for Labour is a vote for a nasty, antisemitic, terrorist supporting Marxist who hates Britain and has nothing but contempt for the people of this country - lying to them and thinking he can play them for fools.
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# See the usual #USER# #HASHTAG#  haters are out in force trying to condem a possible extended future trade deal, all using equipment engineered by Jews. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hi is the ticket machine at #HASHTAG# working today. Or what time are staff on duty so I can collect tickets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Even the Garden of England #HASHTAG# has #HASHTAG# Jew hatred through its communist veins. Trying to abuse #USER# for speaking up. #USER# The party of hate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You clearly have not seen it for years as you forgot to mention Australia. Oh it's just the Jews you don't want taking part.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Leave cannot ever win. Our Government will fraudulently effect the next result.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# Hated by everyone around them, doing nothing for alleged Palestinians except for treating them with contempt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Love itðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Absolute scum, in any religion. Attacking young children causing head and neck injuries. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You and #USER# wanted to murder the whistle blower on Sunday. Oh I get it, it's not ok to whistle blow that you and your party #USER# Hate Jews.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# More Jew hating from #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We are told incessantly that #HASHTAG#  is embargoed and can't get basic supplies like toothpaste or tires.  But apparently they can get all the rockets they want.  The disconnect irks me. They are Terrorists #HASHTAG# are the real problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I love Labour cultists who have no Idea about some of the original members and leaders. #HASHTAG# That hating Jews is the new Labour history for the party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Or the front bench is the worst opposition in history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Unfortunately as usual #HASHTAG# make promises we can't afford. Not quite on the scale of unicorns for students this time, but promising rural bus services, especially when standing on a tram, was pushing it, even for the great leader on this occasion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER#  Just another usual Jew hater from Novara on #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thank you, for getting their first. #HASHTAG# The party of hypocrites, just keeps on self destucting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The underlying Jew hatred, has to stay, it wouldn't be right for Labour to be nice anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The results were released last week by accident.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# She lied to her constituency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# He's a nasty shit, always arrogant and unhelpful. As the saying goes, "dancing on his grave, singing hallelujah"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But you don't speculate look at your history. If u spent as much time screaming @ China for killing Tibetans things might change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Your a Russian. WTF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#  So it looks like its a new #HASHTAG# for #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# airports hints the Prime Minister. âœˆâœˆâœˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# He has. Turns out you fell for the lie before checking the story prick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Bit like when Bercow redecorated at Â£8k a roll of paper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The #HASHTAG# have always, always lied to get a vote. #HASHTAG# was the favourite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# think it's ok to #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# voter's. They want an #HASHTAG# for those that voted leave. Sick, Scum. The state of this country, it's clear #HASHTAG# are In the gutter. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# More lies. This country will die if #USER# are elected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Clearly another day for you &amp; #HASHTAG#  hating Jews, but you keep denying any relationship. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently voting #HASHTAG#  was a vote by the young for the next generation of young. Why are the marches and meetings always full of the elderly. We had a choice, we made a choice. #HASHTAG#
Time for change. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sky would prefer the Terrorist Hamas leadership]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# clearly free listening is now a crime in your world if you are a Jew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's about Jews, #HASHTAG# don't care what happens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Provoked by #HASHTAG# hate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# James only wants to hear impartial, gammon remoaners, what a shock ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Thank you. First rule, look after this country and all its residents before giving to others. Not all Jews support Israel but all support its existence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#  A lying undemocratic disgrace. You are why MPs are no longer trusted and becoming hated by the public. It's clear MP's are completely deceitful. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Perhaps #HASHTAG# could take a very urgent look at the #HASHTAG# The daily tailbacks &amp; Pollution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fake, woke, lowlifes with nothing better to do, don't agree with majority of the public. The prat, is a professional moaner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hi is the standalone machine at Longfield station working today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Leaked out to channel 4 first. Sounds dodgy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Only listening to what some people want. I thought this guy wasn't a fan of Jews Maybe you should take a look at his older tweets &amp; Facebook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So far Galloway, Griffin and the K Klan have shown support of #HASHTAG# being #HASHTAG# Labour and it's friends really hate jews for some reason this week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tony, it bloody took you long enough mate. No excuse, should have been a  year ago. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Usual prat making an excuse for losing over 18% of a vote. The Labour leadership are scum, killing the party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The woke brigade have lost again today. The CoOp did a Ben &amp; Jerry's and got screwed, now this. The country needs to stop giving into a pathetic minority.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Gotta love a bit of local Jew hatred.  Maybe they rent an Air b n B apartment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# just keep giving. It's another day to celebrate hating Jews. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Owen Jones ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ The far left have generated a world of hate. At some point Owens abuse was going to boil over and bite him back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh so it's ok to not promote a green world when it's Jews #USER# That's a wonderful idea, racist energy. You haven't got a clue, just showing your true colours. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Brighton, has one off the largest LGBT communities in Europe, The non democratic, apartheid Middle East would murder everyone of them. That's what you get, voting for Corbyn and the New Labour Cult.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ brilliant. Those pesky Germans have such a sense of humour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Femi you love attacking, you were particularly hurtful to David Cameron and his family. You need to apologise or be punished to the extreme.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It's quite clear on the dark web that remain MPs are inline for serious disturbance to property and life, it's clear the left Brexiteers are itching for a war on remain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# After Rocket fired from Gaza destroyed a home injuring children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's another Â£160million pounds of our money wasted on these lowlifes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The New Party of Hate, now with added, "we hate each other. Gilly, leave it out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# This is vile. Threats of #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# to a female. If this is true, surely the Police and #USER# need to act urgently. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, that threat after the vote didn't come to fruition and nothing proves it will when leaving. The world economy fluctuates on a lot less than the UK leaving the EU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The #HASHTAG# 10 minutes earlier hundreds of these leaflets were handed out. It's just about Jews, but don't tell anyone ðŸ˜‰ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Race baiting again. You are clearly becoming responsible for hate. Your own constituents are waking up to your lack of support locally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# it's official, it's dead. Pranks, that's the reason for watching Harry hill. This is just crap, with added bullying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Whorephopic. What are you talking about. Wow, grow up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Liverpool and Terrorists don't normally mix. Oh it's #USER# Just another day hating Jews.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Apparently it was a Mossad plot, but they ran out of shoes ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You sold 65% of the NHS off last time under PFI contracts. #HASHTAG# Lying again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well said. Get rid of the terrorists Hamas, then sit down. Whilst the left make millionaires out of Hamas, the people will suffer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh dear how sad. The usual we are remain you are wrong website. Slagging of the same Gammon that , keep the country moving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A Councillor, wow you are dangerously stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# As a group of companies that's the move we made 4 years ago. Much nicer helping local charities around the UK and at our European and middle East sites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Where are all the female and child refugees]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 90 million leaflets we're distributed. The majority of those who voted, voted leave, by over a million. It's clear as day. A choice was made, but you cannot stop crying over it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Why is #HASHTAG# deciding the outcome of the nation. He's an odious little traitor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hi why does the number 03000 583 527 ring out after 13 rings. How can we get through please about a child benefit question.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Starting to look like it never happened.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What a fool you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Unfortunately I'm early but this happens for the 06:22 to London Vic every day Especially from the offside car park entrance. No signs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Deutsche bank has around $40tn in derivative contracts. In context the UK national debt is $2tn. When Deutsche goes bankrupt, (it's happening) they must be absorbed by other banks The problem is that the global banking system itself cannot absorb that much debtðŸ’¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sorry about the Jews, breathing and interfering in #HASHTAG# being the worst opposition in living memory. Don't let a bit of care, stop you supporting the worst leadership since Michael Foots government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He should Go to prison, it's gone on long enough. How can #USER# support this prolific drink driver.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The #HASHTAG# have always hated Jews, why change now. Ffs they supported nazi germany, so it's old school for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Some were climbed on, to place placards. The face of one memorial covered. Ultimately there was no need for this, just purely disrespectful. There are better ways to raise your disapproval without touching memorials.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Grow up. Your timeline is covered in hate VB and lies. Just another hater.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Just another terrorist supporter. They never mention the complete blockade by Egypt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But they are happy to march on Synagogues. The Leadership #HASHTAG# has to prove he's not an antisemite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hopefully no, unless you support under age sex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good to see it's not just Russia impacting on world politics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 112 #HASHTAG# politicians gone since the old fool #USER# came to power. Labour are not the party of the people, they treat everyone with contempt, enjoying a drug fuelled, lying lifestyle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Now that's #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Terrorist supporting, Murderous scum. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If you vote for the current #HASHTAG# party you risk death to any civilian of any belief, colour or persuasion as #HASHTAG# and this cult are a risk to all our security and can never be trusted with friends like this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# Jews can relate to that ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Bits it's ok, she and the rest of #HASHTAG# Just hate #HASHTAG# What about the outstanding investigations or her views on whites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Seriously we have always had thousands homeless and destitute in the UK. Social media brings it to the table, the 70s were terrible under labour. They all only care about themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# I love #HASHTAG# picked onion but it's like feeding time at the zoo #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A Pakistani talking about land grab and murder. Your a moron, do some homework. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Wow #USER# some kind of perverted, harassment going on in your head. Very dangerous statement, "Look into". It's not 1939  nazi Germany yet Neil. I think the police need to put you on a watch list. #USER# what is going on? #USER# you clearly agree it's ok to target her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Everyone hates #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Who elected #HASHTAG# to go to the EU to get us to remain. What is she saying behind our backs. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Non of it should be Halal. It's cruel and a pointless requirement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Guess She will receive death threats from the #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #HASHTAG# surrendered and #HASHTAG# lost 2 wars. The #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# is doomed to failure. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# Armed #HASHTAG# have building cordoned off,  possible suspects inside]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What a fantastic advertising idea. As usual spark a reaction, job done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Will he #USER#  visit his and #USER# paymasters in Iran and watch gay men get hanged or just the live streaming! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Driven to his daughters house get it get it! oh i give up. #HASHTAG# a whole new programme for ITV2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Guaranteed to get off. I will give you my account details and bet you. This animal is Teflon coated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# anti democratic lowlifes fail again. Stop wasting Court time #HASHTAG# it's time to change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Spot on. The Hitler youth cultists are blind to how crap he is, even the young voters found him out with his lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# diversity, not in action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's take news and been retracted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# usual scum on street &amp; on #HASHTAG#  usual chav scum #USER#  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The religion of hate. Even during a joyous occasion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# On the grounds of you cant read a sign in 2 different languages or tell the time you silly woman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There are thousands of #HASHTAG# private #HASHTAG#  CV ticket cases causing more problems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Corbyn is to busy getting his Cult to hunt down Jews or to send abuse to anyone who doesn't agree with anything he says. Look at the abuse your getting for speaking up. The mob will be attacking you and your family forever now. #HASHTAG# Now #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Under siege from Egypt as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Great news. Finally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# As usual the flag of hate towards Jew's is on show. The normal rent a crowd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Why, when we're you last in a room full off political people and a smirking gatecrasher entered. If the prime minister had been there, the lady could have been shot first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just another day, just another #HASHTAG# #USER# Jew hater. When will this party care about the people of the UK, more than it does about about abusing and hating Jews #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The page feeds are being put on here. It's horrendous. Religion asside, it's an amazing piece of architecture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Your kidding, it's a Jew hate lovin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# account #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Just another Terrorist supporter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# During August I said on 9 occasions, Labour leadership really do hate jews either that or they are being #HASHTAG# hourly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So the train I normally get 05:58 from #HASHTAG# is already 6 mins late &amp; now makes 4 extra stops. #HASHTAG# r crap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well as it existed in 1963, that's a bit of a shock. Covered in1966, 73 and 77, they did not quite "make it"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Your time line is full of hate and harrssment towards Emily and others with a lovely  spread  of clear anti-Semitic quote's. Your the type destroying Labour for normal Humans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We didn't get the onslaught you promised us this week, why should we believe it will happen. Unless it's an excuse for #HASHTAG# to ruin more days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covid 19 Why don't civil service or Council offices have to use the Track and Trace app for visitors or staff. Surely all those worker's and visitors are spreading the virus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is David, David doesn't think #HASHTAG# is black enough to play some black part's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Who are you. A forgotten liar, just another wannabe. Gone &amp; forgotten Lib dems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If #USER# has his way, the cult will be attacking you later. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# just want to waste another Â£160million on a general election. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Where's #USER# He's great at set ups.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why, the government, press and us are afraid to say anything. A religion where a book tells you in the sword verses to kill is what's wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He's taken enough cash for supporting them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Your lies sent an apparent innocent man to prison, what else did you lie about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# How can you just throw in the word genocide. You are an apologist for Terrorist supporting scum. You see, it's all bs. Stop Hamas, you will have freedom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Great to see the Jew hating momentum on TV. Well done unbiased BBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Her hatred of jews &amp; Israel is clear. Along with #HASHTAG#. They never complain about China's genocide of Tibet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# All Jews were banished from 3/4 of the middle east. Get real. They are under the control of Â£multimillionaire Terrorists. #HASHTAG# are the problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Apparently so. How dare you. If you're far right apparently I can also call you a racist ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That's the Tweet stream of the year, right there. Ant &amp; Dec stand aside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Parts of Europe are dead, America is self destructing. #HASHTAG# allegedly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# So obsessed with a nominal amount of Jews, that they no longer care about the people of #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# but are happy to take #HASHTAG# subs &amp; live a champagne socialists life.
#USER# don't care about the Uk #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You cannot use a car, keep up with the detail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# say's Muslims need protection ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The contempt for their own staff, is just the start of the hate, that would engross this nation should Labour get elected in the next 10 years. We have to remove the Left wing extremism before letting this dangerous megalomaniac &amp; his sexual partner near No10.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's in your name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stop kidding yourself you are being endorsed by

1. Former BNP leader Nick Griffin
2. Former Ku Klux Klan chief David Duke
3. The Neo-Nazi Daily Stormer 
4. The White supremacist Occidental Observer

Guess you  forgot that in your tweets ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Did you really tweet this at some point in your life? That's awful, surely you don't think like that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The same Muslim carrying a Machete.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Unfortunately the poor sods #USER# will likely lose theirs trying to save this CV selfish idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A sexist political group. Oh yeah, because that's what we need. FFS stop this absolute BS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Jew hatred is strong in this cultist #HASHTAG# Another day another lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# 1000s of #HASHTAG# Jew haters were pushing for a boycott using Twitter.  It still failed, because no one in their right mind support Hamas terrorist scum pretending to support Arabs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Me at family weddings, oh the shame I bring ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# 24000 airmiles travelled. He's a liar. It's all about the money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 50000 balloons on the beach, thousands of cannisters #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Typically lying Jew hater.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have just mentioned on another post. Italy will crash in 9 months The Euro will collapse with Germany covering Â£320billion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This New Labour will destroy this country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So not only am I not allowed to look at woman, they are now shoveling it into my face. They wonder why men are confused. To be honest, even most women are probably confused by this what appears to be self abuse. The World has gone mad. That's before we get all Transgender ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# A party of hate now. Wow a danger to the UK in every way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Because Diane Abbott's a rocket scientist. Get real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Both rubbish clubs. Just by your players direct from South America and cut out the rip off Spanish French German Italian etc etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Just another week of abusing Jews on the pretence of supporting Palestinians. Forgetting the actual problems the UK has. #HASHTAG# clearly hate everything about the UK except London.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# who is responsible for bridge over railway line #HASHTAG# kent Cleaning, repairs structual damage nothing for 16 months]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are not enough #HASHTAG# to help #USER# win a vote. It's simple, Labour are happy for Jew's to be abused, they don't matter. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# uncovered. The Cult hate Jews, who knew! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Police to investigate 147 postal votes, from 5 care homes, after allegations of 98% total Labour vote, from previously split voter's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# supporters don't care, they just want Jews murdered. For them it's collateral damage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sorry you are wrong. 11 December 2015 they had a plan. The Unions hoped it would not effect Jobs ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG# hate Jews. It's a clear party policy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So there you have it. African nations don't want your money, your help, your caring thoughts, unless, you are black. 
If you are white, stop giving to any charity that might think they are helping, they're not, apparently. Fair enough, thanks for clarifying that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloody dodgy TPT She past it. Ian for boss #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It was always set for this week you prick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# beat you to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stop attacking a democratic country. It's a simple choice on a Friday afternoon, if you do, you die. The Arab and Muslim world really don't care, if they did they would attack Israel harder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# promoting violence and hate, whilst abusing their own residents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Shouldn't she and #USER# actually concentrate on stopping the abuse, investigating the issues. It's pure communism, white washing the problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We grow 600million tomatoes per year in Kent in pollytunnels. Next year a billion. Mainly sold to Italy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They want us to Remain. They are liars to democracy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# Libdems being slaughtered for lying and changing their minds. #USER# lying on behalf of #HASHTAG# This Parliament has failed #USER# If Labour are confident call a #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No she is Catholic as was her mother. Her missing father was allegedly Jewish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Taking Jobs from real actor's. So selfish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Just another #HASHTAG# for Labour supporters to abuse Jews. The Cultists won't be happy until the yellow stars are being worn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#  is their candidate. #HASHTAG# Labour style. Your just as bad in hating a group of people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's the Tower Hamlets Postal voting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Surely if they were racist or homophobic he would have been arrested and charged.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Year 5779 in the #HASHTAG# house. Today, again, #USER# continued hating #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>