<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Actually atheists are not weak, they have bigger balls than Christians, we're not scared of hell! You are! :) #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vive la France!! :P 
“#USER#: The Record Of The Year goes to Daft Punk for “Get Lucky” ft. Pharrell and Nile Rodgers #HASHTAG#”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday, December 28th: Everywhere in America Playstations and Xbox go back online while brains go back offline.

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darn, how good is this track!? =&gt; Gimme All Your Love - Alabama Shakes 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Greed is dung of the devil!" - Some man sitting on a golden throne asking his congregation to give 10% of their income to an invisible god.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I would like people to appreciate science in the same way they appreciate the arts. #HASHTAG# has a timeless quality to it."
Richard Dawkins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science, 1 - God, 0! =&gt; New antibiotic teixobactin kills drug-resistant superbugs #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hippie's eyes are truly following you, it's a miracle! Hallelujah amen!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nice! Better than the street cats who fuck under my bedroom windows. Nothing more blood curling at 3 am than that weird moaning! :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are the official summer outfit for Norwegian cops. Yep, America you still got a long way to go! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Pope tweets...through computer and the web, both created by atheists  #URL# n#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They probably were hoping for a Super Bowl...of food. :(nnHomeless couple wins trip to Super Bowl XLV #URL#”n#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# nn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HIV strain came from gorillas #URL#
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thanks, can u be my drug lord?? lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just heard Suicide Blonde from INXS, it just hit me; was Hutchence talking about himself? Or was it just a bad ironic coincidence?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Me too. I noticed my chai-decaf frappucino melts a little bit faster now when I'm sitting on the patio, it's ugly out there! :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's bitchin'! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This touchdown is for you Jesus!!!
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men nudity Vs. women nudity.

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Baseless denial? Like when u claim prayers work but still millions of children die of starvation in Somalia?? #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I have cancer. But the good news is, I've got my cheekbones back!" 
David Bowie to Gary Oldman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["POOF!!" - Famous sound witnesses heard when Jesus got resuscitated! -]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Gates ( #HASHTAG# ) says The world is better than ever #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's sad to see a grown man worship some deity like you're doing. So what, Spiderman wasn't enough when you grew up??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Star Wars is no different than religion. Fans forget that fan comes from fanaticism. No different than Christianity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump loves Putin. 

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do I get a cake??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh yeah, too bad the giant Marilyn left PS, I woulda loved to see it toppled on its back so I could climb on her tits! :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# True. Or like "off" is a TV channel. Like not collecting stamps is a hobby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last great run by a Bronco.

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Telling me that God blesses me has no effect on me. None. It's like telling you May the Green Lantern bless you! It's stupid!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only in LA! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christians make up 78% of American prisons. Atheists? 0.07%

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think there's ever been or will ever be anything as good as Fargo season 2 on American TV. Finally a show for adult sans capes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best album of the year goes to a #HASHTAG# member! 
Xenu would be so proud, well done Beck, your thetans must be all over the place!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you notice it's #HASHTAG# but never #HASHTAG#. Poor crocodiles are so misunderstood. And they love kids too. They're so chewy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I never understood why black people are so religious when the bible clearly states that it supports slavery. n#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So refreshing to hear Beyonce (notorious bible thumper) say "TEAR MY CHERRY OUT!"  on her song! Hope she gets it torn real good!
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Let's hope they all get abducted by drug cartels!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How shocked I am to see that this is coming from Fox News. :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Trump's promises are as worthless as a degree from Trump University!" - Mitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a sweet lovable town!

“#USER#: Los Angeles gun buyback nets 817 weapons. #URL#”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opting Out of Coastal Madness to Live a Low-Overhead Life 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rooftop drinking with sunset all ovah Hollywood! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In English: "Hi, we're the 72 virgins!!"  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pat Robertson: 'Atheists are jealous of our happiness and want to make us miserable!" #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# 
mixed with a lil bit of 
#HASHTAG#

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ha ha! Hey my great grandma died at 102 year old &amp; she had 1 to 2 glass of wine a day so it must not be all that bad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget the American Dream, here's the Danish Dream!
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mimosas at the Saguaro in the desert. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lucky you! Up here in Hollyweird it's ghetto birds non stop in the sky for the last hour. I feel like I'm in Baghdad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Mother Teresa, a profane marriage between tawdry hype &amp; medieval superstition, a media superstar who was a fraud." Christopher Hitchens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Uh wait?! Didn't your lovely Reagan pass amnesty before? So what? Are you just against it because our President is black?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The church is so forgiving!nn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vatican lashes out at gay couples #URL#” #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'll pick hell. I just love the heat! :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The fact that u didn't even make the connection with Alan Turing means u didn't even know of him, you're clearly uneducated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I hear you. I hate Cher too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Well I think we should have the right to carry grenades &amp; flame throwers! It's my FUCKIN right!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Soon enough they'll want to meet Xenu in person! :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok so now I'm extremely liberal but I don't know if I'd wear this in public! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How funny I just drove by.  Very trippy, hopefully it stays that way as an art piece!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Humans require 13.2 gallons of water each day to meet needs.The average American was estimated to use about 98 gallons per day."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# U're clearly have super short memory. Read the first tweet u sent me. Then u said u NEVER read the bible, so now u have? lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I love crepes! I'm craving escargots lately &amp; all my friends here are like "Ewww!" LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't get back people sometimes, why are you looting WHERE YOU LIVE!? What? There's no rich republican areas around you?
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hate to tell U but if you believe California will fall in the ocean, It's like saying Jesus is coming back!
Equally moronic! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No life didn't come from my asshole, thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guimauve Thrones (doubt anyone gets this joke) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Takes a lot of wrongdoing to climb up the ladder. See exhibit A, Donald Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surprised? =&gt; Bible Belt leads the nation in consumption of gay porn 
#URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody votes in LA. Let me guess why? Because the city is so corrupted your vote won't change a thing? See exhibit A: =&gt; Eric Garcetti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was it all part of God's plan if he didn't lift a finger?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus is Dog! Read the bible!

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really lost my twitter mojo, haven't tweeted in ages. Not even sure why, just happened overnight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'd say I think Irreversible is probably the most disturbing thing I've seen in screen. Also High Tension &amp; Inside were out there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# As a Euro I can tell you America glamorizes violence to the "UTMOST" and it is a very....violent country!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's beautiful. I'm in the desert. Check out these desert beauties. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad when in this economy they can only afford one ball. Where is U2 when you need them?? Let's start a benefit concert!
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad they're making a doc about how much of an asshole Steve Jobs was. Don't worship false idols! #URL#
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#atic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember the last black female Pope?? 

Yeah me neither!

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know it's wrong but I laughed so hard at this... =&gt; 
Free sex 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's so convenient for skeptics, their motto is "let's not take side &amp; have an opinion, it's just too scary!" lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully Kelly Clarkson is pregnant with a good song.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Remember when Jesus pulled out all his weapons of seductions?? What a night 'twas! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This nation cannot accept that a white woman would rather be black, I find it ironic! However it's okay for Brucey to want a vulva?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate it when Jesus rides dinosaurs in my house! LOL

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irony: 
When #HASHTAG# have no African American winners yet Oprah could buy the Dolby theater and...everyone in it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have a library card? A smart phone? Download hoopla. Voila! Unlimited free music! Stream it to your car radio even. Me likey!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For laughs read the comments of the deluded christians! lol =&gt; Canadian scientists raise fish to walk on land 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because religious belief is a delusion, does "sincerely holding a religious belief" mean you're crazy?

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# results at present time is 28 to 24. Collective IQ results 0 to 0. Back to you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow night we're doing the Walking Dead maze at Universal Studios. It looks scarier than the lame TV show! 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So that's what happens when you feed the christian trolls like #USER# 

Please don't feed the trolls! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Imagine no religion! Nothing 2 kill or die 4" - 
Man plays "Imagine" on piano in front of Le Bataclan after tragedy
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This survey confirms what we know is the common sense of people in UK that whether u are religious or not has little to do with morality!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manny Pacquiao seems to not have read his Bible well. Defacing your body (aka tattoos) will send you straight to hell! 
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm sure you can't wait for Sunday so you can drink the blood &amp; eat the flesh of a 2,000 year old zombie! Sounds so exciting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EARTHQUAKE!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In AT&amp;T bills you always get up to like $10 in hidden fees &amp; surreal taxes. In Straighttalk it's like...60 cents lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I tried to put my iPad for sale on Craigslist &amp; all the replies are asking me if I want to buy Viagra or a young Russian wife!?? Uh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even Priests are donating blood and we all know they're not....celibate!nn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alright! Well that was fun. I always love those nice long enriching convos with good loving Christians. My favorite! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to Dark Harbor, wish me luck!! Looking forward to see the "so called" haunted indoor pool of the Queen Mary ;P 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 95%? Does that mean that if the earthquake doesn't strike then u're really really seriously bad at predicting earthquakes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You forgot Christians. How many people have they killed thru history. And oppressed? And raped? And tortured? And etc...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nancy Reagan was into astrology so much it will definitely prevent her from going to heaven. Sky Daddy hates that shit!

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Historians recently discovered that the whole quote actually was "Jesus Loves You...in Victoria's Secret!" Hallelujah Amen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So random all these people who drew crosses with their feces on their foreheads today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh I agree. I hate stereotypes &amp; clichés and rioting is not helping. It's making them worse!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I love it. I'm at my favorite spot, Beacon Hill. Plenty of grass to lay down on and watch the mountains!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hilarious! I always wait for the Jehovah announcement at the end of her games, tis' a great drinking game!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It bothers me to see the #HASHTAG# , because death is reality &amp; praying is fantasy! Religion is the root of most violent acts!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tHe TwEeteR Haz cHaNNgeD aGaIN!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Funny was just downloading the track as I was reading this. Love her stuff. Also got  the Penguin Prison track]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny, it's up my street! =&gt;
Dumb Starbucks' stupid mystery: Who's behind the faux coffee front in Los Feliz?
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just bumped into Mrs Claus! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Same here. Have been yoga since I've been 16 after a car accident damaged my back. I take it without the spiritual bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So you say, I thought God's creation (the body) was a beautiful thing, why not show it?  #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What people call #HASHTAG# is simply an acceptable term for their ignorance." Stanley Kubrick
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ha but u're a skeptic. That clearly means that...a part of you isn't "sure". I'm n hardcore atheist, I don't believe. At all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Movie franchise yes but when it comes to being worshipped like that it's no different than Scientology to me. My opinion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# True. It's not Paris yet where u can see giant nipples and dicks on billboards in the street but...we're getting there. :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That awkward moment when USA's first presidents were all atheists.n#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facts about life and death...it doesn't matter if you pray, people still die!

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drinking game: take a shot each time you recognize a cameo in #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They're breeding when truly they are the poster children for abortion commercials. Oops,did I say something wrong?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done Twitter. My account was locked for saying that...praying didn't cure pneumonia! Cough...

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm going to start wearing a cow around my neck. After all they are sacred in India! #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# =&gt;n“#USER#: bloody #HASHTAG#,.. you are going to have to start paying me for my services! costs alot of time to educate you know!”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mild morning humor. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes it IS hard to quit meat, i m not a big meat eater, maybe once or twice a week that's it. Couple burgers a year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So since even after I offered u to unfollow you're still rambling I will help you and block! I'm all about helping out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's about time we get a temple where we can kneel & not pray. #HASHTAG# =&gt;nnAtheists to erect Temple of 'worship'  #URL#”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The saddest part is people do buy the movie tickets. The dumbing down is scary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7/11?Check. Dairy Queen?Check. Gas station?Check. Mexican church?Check, check, check. You are at an intersection in the San Fernando valley!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He had a wooden leg with a little door in it. Inside the door were marijuana cigarets." J. Fante - Ask the Dust]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So funny me too, same phobia. Don't mind snakes though but the more legs the scarier. Hence spiders. :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Atheists...because we can handle the truth!

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chuck Norris hates atheists but...famous Atheist Bruce Lee kicked his ass!

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rooftop drinking in Hollywood. Maybe because 87 degree in March??

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NY is sweeping snow. In LA the FBI is doing a gang sweep. See? Sweeping means different things depending on which coast you are!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The burning bush!

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you find Jesus? Because if you didn't he's behind the couch, look!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the first time I'm out of town when a quake hits. Lovin' it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shia LaBiotch retired? From what? Transformers? Let me tell my 5 year old niece, she'll be SO pissed! :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'll find the piece for you later. It's something about NYers writing books set in LA. In LA Times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Charles Manson can marry in jail in America and no one is offended?

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The science that backs up your faith? LOL Which one?? #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I agree. The Interview is so stupid. There's only 1 slight gag in the...trailer. Probably the only one in the whole movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow cue in those bad Dead or Alive jokes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just saw something incredibly funny at the gym but can't post the video on Twitter? Why? You can't post videos on here anymore??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, looks like God is giving all the money to the atheists! They make up the richest people on earth! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That guy is super cool, mellow and talks to everyone, just walks all around LA in the Jesus outfit! Priceless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Question with boldness even the existence of a God." Thomas Jefferson 

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Placebo effect, just like for #HASHTAG# =&gt;
Two magic words make regular coffee taste better, study finds #URL# 
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I feel so bad for you. It's so sad to perpetuate life destroying myths like Jesus &amp; God! Shame on you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you feel raped by the Bible? Atheism can help u shed these old silly beliefs.
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't you think Muslims are better off than Christians? They get 72 virgins when they go to heaven?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You sound like you're the one needing help. Again I don't play video games &amp; u hit me up, I didn't come to u "out of the blue"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sure. Obviously you were there. Do you believe in Thor? Poseidon? Cause they were there before Sky Daddy! #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why would god heal you? Why you &amp; not the millions of kids  dying of hunger, cancer, AIDS etc.. ? #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So odd to see all the towers I worked in crumble! =&gt;
Final San Andreas trailer will make u fear earthquake forever
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But since U can't prove that God IS good or even exists. There is zero proof but U saying U "know" or it's in the "Bible"!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fifty Shades Dumber would be more appropriate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But atheism is the reason you're on a computer now &amp; on the web, they were both invented by hardcore atheists! Ironic?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not surprised Trump is so popular, when so many Americans rather watch brain splattered on the Walking Dead than pick up a freaken book!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worshipping at the altar of fitness. I might sacrifice my freshly bought sneakers! Abdo-Amen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Black on Black crime is the first cause of death of African Americans (see exhibit A: Chicago) but I guess that's ok with America!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is it worse than ISIS? I'm scared to open the link! :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We agree. We wants to see less of you. A lot less! Go to Jesus already!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christians, stop using computers and the web, both created by atheists!n#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm reading Mockingbird now actually. Had never read it so I figure I should.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Atheists, please stop oppressing Christians' religious freedom!nn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# School?? What is school? :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# belief isn't a choice?? It's forced onto influenceable kids with threats of sin &amp; hell!! Are you out of your mind??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I am at #HASHTAG# !

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sarah Silverman is visited by Jesus 
#URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2014, in a galaxy far away:
"Hey Smorg come take a look at this! Humans are pardoning a bird! Ha ha ha ha!"

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now you know what is fucking annoying?? Michael Keaton chewing gum like a maniac on every frame of his mug. 

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Jesus truly never was that handsome. I'm thinking Dave Matthews! #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# As I always say...don't dish it out if you can't take it! ;) You picked WeakSquare as a handle and...it fits!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know, somethin' about a country that will only accept straight blood to go into gay bodies! nn#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 'Twas not the devil but She-Devil! :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Edward Snowden’s Privacy Tips: “Get Rid Of Dropbox,” Avoid Facebook And Google  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Like I tweeted many times before, I saw a 7 year old girl attacked for no reason by a pit bull (on a leash) in a park in Paris!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama is scared of going on Bill Maher's show because he knows he won't be able to hold his atheism inside the closet much longer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# God made fish so polluted by mercury to make "Fish Fridays" more interesting! #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Promising cancer therapy treatment: Vitamin C (via #USER#) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's about to get really cold in LA at 62 degrees. Body not equipped for survival, should we call FEMA already for emergency sweaters?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I played "count the black people" during Jurassic World. 20,000 attendees in the park and only...one black person! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw #HASHTAG# where the scientist is a very hot and thin white woman. Wow I didn't see this coming!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But why don't we mention Thor in the Pledge of Allegiance?? He existed too and predated your God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kiss-ins, Die-ins. Any fuck-ins??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Atheist teens are far less likely to care what the “cool kids” think, than their religious peers." 2010, Duke University survey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Stop imbecile! It's a radiator!"
#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# movie looks about as dumb as...I dunno, can't find anything dumber. It will be a hit in America though, because duhh bro uhh OMG!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why is it that ONLY religious people can't write "Atheist" properly?? It's revealing! n #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#'s #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YaAawn, Twello!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>