<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm honestly convinced that things are going to get a whole lot worse before they get better in the US.nnNote that this is not accelerationism. I don't want this to happen. But I think the democrats have brought us to the point that it's completely inevitable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They were purporting to expose "Woke Misogyny" lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is frankly offensive to claim that JK Rowling is the UK's greatest female author of the last 100 years, considering that you're claiming that she's better than Agatha Christie with that statement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, the FF XIV PLD class quests are downright boring in comparison to the DRK ones, huh?

I saw the twist in the PLD one coming a mile off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think they used to do a bunch of Zelda remixes I liked, IIRC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why establishment democrats are the enemy.

Even when republicans are bad, they blame socialism.

Democrats do more to make sure that republicans remain in power than Republicans do. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I will happily admit that some of this phenomenon exists on 'the left', especially among unironic establishment democrat supporters, but my point is that it's not at all symmetrical.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I didn't like FF7 original. I think it's the most overrated game in the entire series. Hated the narrative.

FF7R not only made me reconsider, it changed my mind. The story just needed a little room to stretch and some good writers to flesh it out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Also, you know, having every right wing position under the sun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's projection. He literally runs a site that makes money off of right wing culture war outrage and clickbait in anime and gaming spaces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Montichagne would definitely spend the entire meeting laughing at everyone else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny how it's always white guys who use racial slurs who get upset about people saying "cracker" online.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aaand here is a creepy gay TERF ally not realizing that this exact same argument was used against homosexual men regarding serial murderers and pedophiles, happily going along with spreading the same lie and fake statistics about trans people.nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The problem with HFCS isn't that it 'causes fat people'. It's that it makes less healthy and gain weight and is associated with all sorts of bad health outcomes. Stress is also a risk factor for that too. These things are all connected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matthew Parris just last week called for genocide against Roma people, one of the nazis' other targets for genocide.nnMatthew Parris is a quisling, and a nazi himself, just trying to harm other LGBTQ people by supporting the far-right's campaign of hate against trans people. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Are you going to go all conspiracy theorist on us and suggest it's a "false flag" with zero evidence? Like trans people would try to get their supporters injured to damage "GCs" like you fascists don't damage yourselves already?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmao, whenever you call out one of those gay male "GC" allies on their homophobia, they invariably trot out the Milo Yiannopoulos defense. "I can't be a homophobe, I'm gay, you idiot!']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marx's ideas have pervaded philosophy, especially political and social philosophy, since they were published, basically.

A huge amount of all political philosophy since Marx has either been trying to expound on Marx or trying to oppose Marx.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't support LGBTQ people, you're a social conservative. It's that simple. I don't really care how many other "left" positions you have, especially not economic ones. 

It's a litmus test that has never failed for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, doing Twilight Sparkle dirty here. This is not what they mean when they talk about Fllanderization. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right is responsible for the current form of the FCC and the enforcement of Obscenity Laws, meant to control what can or can't be shown on TV and Radio. 

The right was responsible for the Comics Code Authority and the Satanic Panic and anti-D&amp;D stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He has some very bad takes but I don't think this particular tweet is one of them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# So you don't understand what white privilege is. 

Even in this case, this person still has white privilege because they won't be targeted for their race in the way a black person would. 

They're not privileged in an economic way though. Try again, my dude. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# People like Adam get real mad when LGBTQ people stand up for themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Because they're forcing other people to take that risk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an actual Web3 should be: Democratization of Platform Creation, Usage of Cloud tech to Empower Individuals, Actual decentralization and re-fragmenting of online social spaces, open-source sharing &amp; federation of platforms, Respect for what you can make]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stop using us gays as a prop for you hating racial minorities, you absolute ghoul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Reporting harassment doesn't work on this platform, and even if it did, that doesn't make it not harassment in the first place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They spun it into a war against women, LGBTQ people, racial minorities, and anyone who supports progressive politics in games and game journalism, and claimed it was about "ethics" while being completely unethical and supporting big corporations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# This is just like "just say homosexual, straight is offensive".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I ever get to the level of sending out Twitter polls to my followers to "prove" I am right in a petty internet argument, please cancel me immediately. Just end my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Here is what you said. You literally accused me of engaging in cult behavior for taking it personally when someone smears a group I belong to. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah. I mean if you read the VN there's a LOT of material about humans needing someone that they can push their sins and blame onto in order to break the cycle of violence and hatred.

The Jesus parallels are obvious, though the reason for the necessity is different.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Also, we actually like sex and don't have any shame in admitting it. 

I'll be honest, a furry going OwO what's this is not even on the same SCALE as cringy as normies thirstposting in the replies to some woman's selfies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# For #USER#'s benefit, Hasidim are the really orthodox jews that you see caricatures in popular culture about. Often dress a particular way, including hats, etc. There is a strong cultural center for them in New York.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This character just came out like a week ago so it can't be from this game. Haha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It could also just stay the same, is my real fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That said, I still like Samurai because I like how 'busy' it is. I like the fact that we have an absolutely monstrous oGCD that we can use, and they made a lot of QoL changes to make it a lot nicer. Much of your damage is still caught up in your iaijutsu but it's smoother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah. I had the weird explosion launcher, which is nice for normal enemies where a burst of damage is helpful but when you're constantly dodging, it's not a good weapon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I -am- an LGBTQ person. I also don't believe you, considering that anti-woke means anti-LGBTQ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pronouns are political now, according to conservatives, lol. 

Nice to see these people admit they're not, and never were, left #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The show and the games themselves imply that many, if not most, Pokemon are intelligent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're a hate group who hates gays, lesbians, and trans people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I like to think the snobby Gridanians are in the minority.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't want to make it about ME disagreeing with YOU but rather, disagreeing with the opinion. 

Genuinely not trying to be an asshole here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I could have sworn I saw screenshots from his discord or something from a long time ago where he said some transphobic stuff, but I'm not familiar enough with the situation to actually dig them up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The developers of Celeste being pro-LGBTQ and making a really brutally hard platformer really broke the brains of gamer chuds, didn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# So like here is the deal. I agree that fatness is not synonymous with unhealthiness. 100%

Some branches of the medical industry have been captured by the weight-loss industry and that has led to ridiculous excesses of what is called unhealthy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always love shit like this because it reveals they have zero ideology. 

"America is the greatest country ever and capitalism is the only way that science can progress, communism is evil and makes every stupid ...

But also...the commies beat us to the moon, actually." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I've been told that maggots and grubs actually taste really good if you can get over the yuck factor. They're mostly fat so they're like little butter/tallow bombs basically.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...Is nobody familiar with the rhetorical tactic of the Reductio ad Absurdum?

The thing where you take a statement and apply it to a situation the speaker didn't intend, to create a trivially ridiculous conclusion, therefore showing the original statement is bad or false?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He gains mindshare and liking the game is normalized.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to head this off would have been for the democrats to show a bit of spine. But it's far, far too late for that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on, the game's text literally states she's an alternate-dimension version of Ratchet.

(Yes I know other alternate-dimension versions of people are a bit different in other ways, but hush)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No wonder holocaust denial is so common in America. nnJust to note, if you include LGBTQ people, Roma people, and other "degenerates " the Holocaust is more like 15 million people. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Basically a lot of people want to define "RPG" in video games by narrative elements and I think that generally misses the mark, because it defines most JRPGs, especially older ones, out of the category of RPG.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# People like this guy support segregation anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nobody is like "I would have voted for Hillary if only she had gotten more of the delegates in the democratic primary."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If you're on Primal I'd be happy to craft stuff for you, given most of the mats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# LMFAO. Okay nazi boy. Keep on trying to insist that antisemitic stereotypes are not a thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Was ns in the case of bike lanes the idea that bike lanes will lead to better health is dumb. That's not why you make bike lanes. If that's your reasoning for it, it's doomed to fail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# My overall position is that I support body positivity, and emphasize the fact that people have trouble doing all the "right" things to take care of their bodies under this environment where we have to give half our waking hours or more to "getting by"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call me a doomer if you want. I'm just looking at reality. The question is, what to do about that reality?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I simply cannot believe someone with a brain would actually try to make the argument that the average person would draw a distinction here because Harris dropped the charges after the victim complied with her blackmail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# My objection is that not everything that can be framed as trying to combat the prevalence of "fatness" in America falls under that category.

I will stand by the examples of pushing against added HFCS and prevalence of unhealthy convenience foods as things that are "good"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hahaha. That's the gamergate loser who wrote that "gamer's bill of rights". Do you remember that shit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I agree that framing bike lanes of all things as an anti-obesity measure is stupid. It won't work for that.  I agree.

My issue is that what they said could apply to something like "stop funding the corn lobby in America so hfcs doesn't end up in all our convenience foods"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The issue isn't things like "Obesity is a public health issue so we should start looking into cutting corn subsidies so we can get rid of the HFCS in people's food."

It's "Obesity is a public health issue so individuals should do [laundry list of weight loss quackery]."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# WoW does have some hits. Honestly they did a great job with the Vrykul and the Vulpera for instance. I liked Helya a lot. 

Just...sometimes the decisions are mystifying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Lmao what. internment was a right wing policy. Lefties at the time opposed it. nnFascism is also right wing and supported by Christians. Try again, dude.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The funny thing is that the anti-cancel-culture brigade was always the side that wanted to limit others' expression. They are mad that other people could criticize their "betters"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maybe politics matter for some of us and we are tired of being told that we are destroying the party for wanting human rights, or a healthcare system every other developed country in the world has.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# See I'm exactly the opposite but I think it's because I don't think Dzemael Darkhold is too bad, especially as a Squadron Command mission.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Except you doubled down on another thing you were just as wrong about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Most people I've seen say that are like in response to me dunking on some ridiculous post telling me it's bait and therefore I shouldn't laugh at it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But yeah, I'll be honest, I'm going overboard. I'm going for absolutely insane melds by overmelding X's into my first overmeld slot. I have all my clothes pentamelded, I'm now doing the stretch goal of doing my tools.

It's honestly not that bad if you just overmeld IX's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw this while hanging out in a remote spot in FF XIV between dungeons.

The journey of a thousand miles, beginning with a single step right here. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No. People can be unintentionally racist. Racism is about intentionally or unintentionally treating people of different races in disparate ways, which disadvantages one of the group, especially when combined systems that give that behavior power to affect others' lives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Literally all of this is made up. I personally guarantee nobody ever said that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow I'm finally making a dent in leveling up all of the combat classes in FF XIV. It's quite a process though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tony's fans totally showing that they're not right wing apologists for bigots here. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I like you man but you gotta give me some more credit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Antifa supporters don't support terrorism. Antifa are heroes, nazi boy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# And I don't think any less of him for it. I don't think him being fat was something that needed to be fixed for the sake of it. I was more just worried that he would develop health problems quickly and wished we could do something about THAT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep. They never know what postmodernism even means.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyway, BRB, time to go gyre and gimble in the wabe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They're not all at my place. I just go to their places and feed them and such.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think my favorite part was that he claimed someone saying "I hope you get painful kidney stones" to him was an example of leftists being violent.nnAll the while he is furiously jacking off to the idea of people he dislikes being tortured for eternity in hell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Hell I even agree that there is an anti-fat eugenics program, even if it's possibly not "intentional." Mostly in the form of blaming fat people for their health problems to justify saddling them with an even more onerous share of medical costs than the already crazy norm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The shitty Gamers(tm) are usually cryptobros.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Sorry but if someone donates money to anti-LGBTQ causes and politicians, that doesn't get canceled out by donating money to good causes as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Because many people like you guys have insisted that I'm not actually queer and just pretending for clout.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note also the similarity here with anti-porn "feminists" / "radfems".nnAnti-porn feminism has -always- been an attempt to hide reactionary right-wing politics under the guise of feminism. It was never left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I agree about Frank Five followers, which is why I'm trying to get better about doing that myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sad thing is that before he started drawing MAGA furries and waving other red flags I was generally like "Well more power to him. If he can get paid thousands of dollars a commission, he's living the dream."nnAnd then he starts in on being a chud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also been preparing meat in sous vide bags so I can just toss them in the machine and have them be done easily.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I traditionally get a honeybaked ham at xmas and at easter. I wish I could justify the cost of just keeping them around all the time. One food I could never get tired of eating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Is that the actual distinction? I honestly think that's not that great a distinction TBH.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh and he is a creepy man claiming that women can't rape. 

Red flag. People like #USER# should not be around women.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Basic Instinct is necessary to do that. Even with that, though, it's hard to do many synced without a lot of the more advanced spells.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think, at best, he cries all the way to the bank about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# LMFAO, that won't matter when hundreds of people decide they want his stuff, creep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lmfao, let me guess, you believe the left thinks that all white people intentionally oppress racial minorities and are therefore bad, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That never happened. You're just lying to justify your hatred of trans people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dudes who follow far-right domestic terrorists probably shouldn't try to tell actual lefties about who is left wing or not. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd think that someone who has "genderqueer" or "trans" in their bio might stop and pause and think about it when a bunch of Nazi troll accounts dedicated to harassing and mocking LGBTQ people are liking their post en masse. nnBut nope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I got the impression most Bernie people didn't like Warren and vice versa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was always the goal of the moral panic about "Critical Race Theory"nnIt's all about banning books that teach inconvenient truths and silencing racial minorities. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah I post that sort of "bait" but I genuinely believe what I say about pineapple on pizza and sandwich taxonomy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The entire problem with fatphobia is regarding fatness as an individual problem and a moral failing on the individual for being fat.

Treating fatness as a SYSTEMIC problem that is caused by capitalism making it profitable to shovel garbage down people's throats is not fatphobia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# But like...just for example, I've lived with someone who weighs 400 pounds and I used to be getting close to 300 myself. 

And im SURE that my old roommate's weight was unhealthy. He thought it was too. But he hadn't had any luck losing weight. It's probably endocrine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I just don't understand the impulse to absolutely refuse to give an inch of ground on the idea that being "fat" might have health risks.

We all have health risk factors and many of them are much more voluntary than fatness is. Smoking and drinking are high up the list.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And also not all things in the genre of "JRPG" would them be Japanese, but I suppose we kind have that issue already even now so I shouldn't complain a out that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maybe I might just start back up doing this if the hate raid situation gets more under control on Twitch, but considering my stalkers, I'm not sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I consider "dieting" in the category of "weight loss industry quackery" as a general rule. 

There ARE cases when dieting is warranted but it's rare. 

So I agree with you here. 

Weight loss needs to come about as a consequence of more-or-less permanent lifestyle changes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ex-cop and gun nut seems to indicate fash to me but sometimes you get ex-military ex-cop lefties. But this is not a good impression to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A...are these Bicolor Gemstones from FF XIV? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wrong. You are lying. This bill bans conversion therapy for all LGBTQ people. You want to continue to torture gay people to be straight. You are a disgusting, murderous monster who wants to torture gay men, lesbian women, and trans people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The most clear was when he did a whole fear mongering segment about "gypsies" coming to America and how we needed to stop them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah but wasn't there still debate about when it should be for a long time after?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah. I didn't go in trying to fight. I went in trying to have a constructive conversation with other people on the left.

Unfortunately that was not to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah. Your ideological allies placed the razor blades.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The only person who is projecting is you. There is no way to heal or restore peace without accountability. 

You think accountability is 'pettiness'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# LMAO, so socialism is privatizing public utilities? I think you have no idea what socialism is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What people don't often understand is that the entire online right is fascist or outright Nazi nowadays. There are no "moderates" in the sphere of right wing thought leaders anymore.

Tucker Carlson goes on TV every night with Nazi shit and it's normalized.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people have never heard of furries and I am wheezing.

Wait till you find out that some people sexualize moogles. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good job supporting the patriarchy and gender policing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It seemed pretty clear that clarification was needed from the start. Tony started aggressive quote tweeting me before he ever thought to clarify.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I'm gonna go walk to pick up Teriyaki for lunch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently stating that the nazis took Anne Frank's life away from her and criminalized, incarcerated and killed her is..."horrific antisemitism"? The zionists are getting increasingly unhinged.nnThe cherry on top is that the person they're attacking is a black jew. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Check the timeline. They're a racist trying to claim "cracker" is a slur.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah yeah I know but I wanted to joke about flattening the curve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boomer Facebook posts trying to masquerade as internet culture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I still like how he wants someone else to apologize because his kween has a history of doxing, harassing, and stalking people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Actually, every one of us have entirely debunked your little talking point and showed your dogwhistles and hatred of racial minorities clearly.nnYou have never spoken well, clearly, or intelligibly in this entire thread.nnYou have never been persuasive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I got to that boss my first try, but lost to it in the second phase. My weapon also kinda sucked for that. Was decent for clearing out normal enemies, but was not putting out enough sustained damage to deal with a boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You don't get power in local and state party apparatus without having elected officials on your side and some election wins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my cats, Blaire, puts her entire body into it when she meows, like she's a seagull or something.

She throws her head back and her torso visibly expands then clenches.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neat but impractical as hell. But you can tell people you need to take a phone call from God #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my god, he's an incel too. No girls allowed, u guys. 

Incredibly normal brain on this man. Totally not making himself look like the real weirdo in this situation. 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I mostly agree, but there is a real issue with people drumming up hatred against immigrants and other people who are "different" for all sorts of bad reasons. Roma people are a classic example in Europe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Never said that. That's why I'm citing Mel Brooks in the first place. nnRacial jokes are not off limits. You just have to construct them such that the racial minorities are NOT the butt of the joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dumb question: Is it possible for me to go back to the earlier areas, to get the things I'm missing? Or just...not right now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# This guy literally supported a church that advertises that it is pro-racism and hates LGBTQ people and is now mad that racial minorities and LGBTQ people think he's a sack of crap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I push back on it, they start going on about Bernie Sanders again (Because of course everything goes back to Bernie with these people).

Compared me to Jimmy fucking Dore.

Guy #HASHTAG# calls me a "perfomrative leftist", which is just a "PC" way of saying I'm "virtue signaling"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm also hyperfixated on Endwalker tbh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know you are far, far too high when you actually start to understand the thought process behind the "Why do they call it oven?" copypasta.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I didn't get that sort of leaning to be honest, but honestly, I think you're right that he has done so many pro-trans videos that I should give him the benefit of the doubt on this, and I was being unfair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I -think- they might have also made Kaiten's oGCD animation lock smaller too, but it could just be that I'm better at the game nowadays than I used to be. But I do find that I'm far less likely to clip GCDs from the Kaiten animation lock in Endwalker than I was in ShB.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well I'm not even arguing about normativity. I'm not wanting to constrain what kind of games anyone can make.

I'm just talking taxonomy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# He's also lying about what CRT is, since nobody who actually practices critical theory as it applies to race would say any of the things he claimed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nazis are very upset when you dismiss their opinions based on their racism and violence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Good. That's the point. But the fact of the matter is that I didn't claim I didn't. You're misinterpreting what I said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just let me be a horrible little gremlin Loporrit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The time stamp was literally hours away. Don't lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I try to discuss things with liberals in good faith but hoooly bejesus, this guy is dumb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Really? I assume that when I see pronouns that are obviously intended to mock the entire idea of pronouns, but someone explicitly saying they're happy to be referred to by masculine, feminine, or neutral pronouns doesn't strike me as transphobic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I always just chalk that up to healing magic and HP being an abstraction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still incredible that Elon Musk posted himself into divorce and gained a following of bitter, bigoted incels for doing so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Because there's been a lot of research on the fact that HFCS contributes to weight gain, more than the same caloric value of starch or sucrose or fat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much longer until TERs claim the Kinsey Scale is homophobic and trying to erase gays and lesbians?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, this is a subtweet and a hot take. No, I don't want you to tag the person who wrote the thread I'm subtweeting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# And by the same token, I also had a different roommate that was a crystal-gripping health nut who was by all external accounts slim and in great shape but he was actually extremely unhealthy because of all these weird dietary fads he participated in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Also you get to stack 2 charges of both Meikyo Shisui and Tsubame Gaeshi now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's always projection with anti-SJWs. nnAnti-SJWs won't be happy until the only acceptable media is theirs, and the media is free of LGBTQ characters, women who aren't sex objects, and racial minorities. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I said that I didn't believe that Biden had actually changed any policies from the Trump admin's mishandling. 

Instantly, one of my mutal's friends crs in and tells me I'm wrong.

Okay sure. I'm used to that. People argue with me on here lots. So I asked him what changed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# This is the logical conclusion of the argument you made. You are literally claiming that a slur is merely an insult.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you ask a "GC man" a tough question. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the people in the replies circle-jerking about "purple-hairs". nnThey're indistinguishable from far-right incels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or, you know, you could use a search engine. Andy Ngo's material support of fascist violence and myriad misdeeds are well-documented.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone got a good full body screenshot of Hesperos?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Like that's the thing here. I can absolutely understand the idea of wanting to use different terms or frame the conversation differently.

I can't understand the flat-out refusal to budge a single inch on the idea that being fat can be a health risk, at least for extreme cases.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When lefties are offended by something, you see criticism and condemnation, maybe a boycott, and social pressure. nnWhen the right is offended by something, you see immediate calls to ban it, followed by pervasive legal and industry pressure to censor it. nnIt's not the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Another minor thing is that they changed the positionals on SAM a little too in order to make kenki gain more predictable. Instead of making the positionals give 5 extra kenki, they now always give the full kenki value, but deal 50 extra potency for the correct positional.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I want Mastodon to be good but it's kinda full of crap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It's not about US. Its about how the average person would take it. You really, really can't expect people not engaged in politics to understand the stakes. 

In fact there have been people talkimg about how most people don't believe it if you explain it because it's so extreme.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You simply cannot just monetarily support someone who worked to make discrimination against LGBTQ people legal, and claim you don't actively hate LGBTQ people. It doesn't work that way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're emblematic of the corruption and bias that pervades fact-checking sites. Gotta excuse Harris for this grotesque behavior.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Exactly. I absolutely understand that it's awful that society constantly harangues fat people to "be healthier", and it's shit. Some people are fat and will be no matter what kind of interventions anyone tries to force on them. Leave them the hell alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But yeah I have some transhumanist tendencies but I think I've interrogated my own utopianism a bit more and don't think transhumanism or even post-scarcity will result in all social problems going away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the weird social conservatives suddenly being superfans of JKR reminds me of when anyone older than 16 thought PDP was cringe, and then he was suddenly hugely popular among right wing culture war Twitter overnight when he got in trouble for saying racial slurs and such.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think a baker should be able to refuse to bake a cake for a gay wedding,  the logical end result of your ideology is that you support segregation, as long as the government doesn't enforce it, just private individuals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hadn't done anything with Blue Mage in FF XIV but it's pretty fun to be able to just solo instances without being completely overleveled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't know your intent. I can't read your mind. Intent is not magic.

I know what you SAID. And what you SAID was questionable as hell to say the least. That was the only way I could interpret it, because a TER used a very similar argument on me the other day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I like that but I've never seen it in lasagna. Seems like it could be interesting. Especially in one with a white sauce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stop appropriating the holocaust because you want to kill other people with a disease.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But in general, they're all gonna be words that were used by a majority group against a minority group, and associated with systematic discrimination.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah, I was kind of saying that they are both kind of the idea of "What if the most powerful person on earth were just a regular person?"

But One Punch Man kind of examines that statement in a negative sense, while Mob Psycho 100 examines that statement in a positive sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't like the Bisquick style pancake mixes. They always turn out way too thick. So if you want to make pancakes like mine, you gotta use a "Complete" pancake mix, for which you only need to add water. I get the Krusteaz pancake mix from Costco.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He's already trying to backpedal lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I -just- got a new controller as an upgrade since I got frustrated with the shoddy electronics on old Rainbow ASC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# My god man. The point just whooshed over your head by a mile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That requires cooperation between the two games ANYWAY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wordle 202 4/6

🟨⬛⬛⬛🟨
🟩⬛🟨⬛⬛
🟩🟩⬛🟩⬛
🟩🟩🟩🟩🟩

Maybe I'm better at this dumb little game than I thought.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think I saw the ending here coming. Hm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just accidentally sat on my cat and she didn't even get mad at me. She just looked up at me and meowed at me for further attention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Again, that post and what you've done since is defending the guy.nnAlso, refusing to serve people who support violent fascists is not the same thing as "discrimination" against groups like racial minorities or LGBTQ people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right always tries to pretend they're not obviously Nazis when they get caught openly supporting Nazis. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right: "The left are all satanic pedophiles!"

Also the right: *exclusively run, attend, and judge child beauty pageants*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note that when they say "gatekeep", they're just making justifications to harass women and LGBTQ people and racial minorities in the anime fandom. That's what this is code for.nnShocker, from an old gamergate account, I know.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>