<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Respawn Working On Three New Star Wars Games, Including Jedi: Fallen Order Sequel – IGN News – IGN #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Florida Deputies Dead in Vacation Murder-Suicide #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matthew Stafford embraces wife Kelly on field after Rams clinch Super Bowl berth #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Macaulay Culkin and Brenda Music Are Engaged Months After Welcoming First Youngster Collectively #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indigenous people face a unique risk that is not fully understood, a W.H.O. official said. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Save 50 percent on the Columbia fleece Amazon shoppers ‘literally live in’ — it’s now $30 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘You Took Away My Mom’: Singer’s Son Slams Anti-Vaxxers After Her COVID-19 Death #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rise in antisemitism, Holocaust denial has EU leaders worried #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla Stock Is a Better Buy Than GM or Ford #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ash Barty ends 44-year wait for home champion at Australian Open #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expert, bystander testimony continues in ex-MPD cops’ federal trial #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mexican drug lord ‘El Chapo’s’ appeal efforts rejected by US court; attorneys intend to appeal to SCOTUS #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thailand Beach Declared Disaster Area After Oil Spill #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ashleigh Barty Wins Australian Open Women’s Singles Title #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marriage Penalty vs. Marriage Bonus: How Taxes Work #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Navy SEALs to stop using Washington state parks after residents voice fears of seeing ‘armed men’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Jimmy Garoppolo trade narrative has completely changed for 49ers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missouri’s Second Amendment Preservation Act frustrates law enforcement and gun enthusiasts #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US’ First Execution Of 2022 Is Man Who Robbed Hotel For Girlfriend’s Bail #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pakistan FM Qureshi extends support to Indian people affected by COVID-19 surge #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man, teenage girls shot inside car in Brooklyn, police say #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snoop Dogg performing at Super Bowl halftime show becoming even worse look #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never Go Here During Omicron Surge, Experts Warn #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two shot, one person stabbed in string of Brooklyn homicides #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian playfully mocked by ‘Property Brothers’ Drew, Jonathan Scott in hysterical TikTok dance #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia’s Population Falls This Year. By How Much? Over 1 Million People #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Group in armed standoff with police say they’re the ‘aboriginal people’ of America #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s Now Been Three Years Since Metroid Prime 4’s Development Was Scrapped And Restarted #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taliban hold first talks in Europe since Afghan takeover #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attack dry, flaky skin, even psoriasis, with this powerful moisturizer, now just $14 at Amazon #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene blasted Sen. Lindsey Graham after he called it ‘inappropriate’ for Trump to float pardons for Capitol rioters #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$426 million Mega Millions lottery ticket sold in California #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lori Harvey recalls body insecurities at the beginning of modeling career: ‘I put a lot of pressure on myself to be a certain size’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TCL 305 With MediaTek Helio A22 SoC Launched: All You Need to Know #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chicago police arrest two, including teen, in shooting death of 8-year-old girl #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon’s secret overstock outlet has everything you need — save up to 55 percent #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stocks Face Hurdles From Fed, China; Dollar Firm: Markets Wrap #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michigan superintendent denies rumor that litter boxes were put in bathroom for students who identified as furries #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On MLK Day, Janet Yellen Says U.S. Economy Is Unfair To Black People #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gayle King signs new deal with CBS, spurning interest from CNN #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kyle Rittenhouse is going to court to get his gun back #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US: Hundreds compete in world’s largest charitable ice fishing contest #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alleged teen drug dealer charged with murder after 12-year-old dies of fentanyl overdose #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Big Investor Bought Up Moderna and Nvidia. Two Stocks It Sold. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden voter ‘disgusted’ with the president, says Dem party has become ‘unrecognizable’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cocaine was the secret ingredient in pig-to-human heart transplant #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Incredibly selfish’: Friends of slain N.J. nurse appalled by cop’s actions after crash #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHO recommends first malaria vaccine for African children: ‘Glimmer of hope’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Cruise Brings Top Gun: Maverick to the AFC Championship in New NFL Promo: ‘The Best of the Best’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grandmother Turns The Tables On Scammer: ‘He Fell For That Hook, Line And Sinker’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-bank CEO: $220,000 spent at strip clubs was business expense #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monster Hunter Rise Version 3.8.0 Is Now Live, Here’s What’s New And Different #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans outraged over ‘unacceptable’ release of criminal migrants into US #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Penélope Cruz, the demands of ‘Parallel Mothers’ were difficult — but worth it #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bizarre Last-Ball Tactic In Big Bash League Match Leaves Everyone Astounded. Watch Video | Cricket News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“So What, If…”: Mohammed Shami Comes To Virat Kohli’s Defence | Cricket News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Argentina Formally Recognizes Nonbinary People, a Latin American First #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review: Heartbreaking documentary ‘Simple as Water’ traces plight of Syrian refugees #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Florida Is Fast-Tracking An Abortion Ban That Could Devastate The Southeast #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Koei Tecmo Confirms Fatal Frame And Blue Reflection Sales #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Arabic Netflix film tackles taboos, sparks controversy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brooklyn Navy Yard explosion seriously injures worker: officials #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The DNA of Roma People Has Long Been Misused, Scientists Reveal #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Gov. Hochul, Manhattan DA Bragg meet as crime crisis escalates #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giants know only time will tell if Brian Daboll was right call #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man in traditional Jewish garb randomly attacked in Brooklyn #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Georgia woman allegedly stole lottery tickets from clerk who had just been fatally shot in robbery: police #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uncle Jack’s Steakhouse wants you to tip the kitchen staff #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Triangle Strategy Trailer Introduces Frederica And New Gameplay #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Los Angeles students must wear non-fabric COVID masks at all times, including sports activities, district says #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurry, these top-rated TCL phones are on sale for their lowest prices ever at Amazon — starting at $127, today only! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lioness Kills Keeper, Escapes Zoo With Mate #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hyper Scape, Ubisoft’s Cyberpunk Battle Royale, Will Be Shut Down – IGN #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Happy To Hand Baton”: Gita Gopinath’s Last Release As IMF Chief Economist #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Team Trump Champions Aaron Rodgers’ Election-Doubting Comments #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Hong Kong official resigns over birthday party fiasco #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court’s Stephen Breyer Retiring, Clearing Way For Biden Nominee #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia Threatens Retaliation If Ukraine Demands Not Met #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Spooky” Object Found In Milky Way “Unlike Anything Astronomers Have Seen” #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crysis 4 (Working Title) – Official Announcement Teaser Trailer – IGN #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cathie Wood’s Ark Invest Predicts Bitcoin Could Exceed $1M by 2030 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lady Gaga’s ‘very silly decision’ she made during her Super Bowl halftime performance #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dems plan to topple GOP Rep. Malliotakis in redistricting plan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Francis Ngannou: UFC threatening to sue my manager over alleged boxing talks #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rainbow Six Extraction: Every Alien Archaean – IGN #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teens say dad in racist rant at Connecticut smoothie shop threatened to kill them #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing Tennessee family found dead in ravine #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Nintendo Switch is in stock and $10 off, but only at this online store #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haunted By Holocaust, Israeli Group Helps Afghans Fleeing Taliban #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coast Guard Suspends Search For Migrants Off Florida #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five things that stood out about the KC Chiefs’ season-ending loss to the Bengals #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hargus ‘Pig’ Robbins, Country Hall of Famer Who Played Piano on Bob Dylan, Patsy Cline and George Jones Classics, Dies at 84 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italy’s President Sergio Mattarella Re-Elected, Easing Crisis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zimbabwe Pandemic: Pregnant teens face school battle #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Jersey school district renames Woodrow Wilson High School, citing ‘racist values’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jason Holder Takes Five, West Indies Beat England In 5th T20I To Clinch Series 3-2 | Cricket News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amy’s Kitchen vegan mac and cheese recalled due to milk presence #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drakeo the Ruler’s Family Announce $20 Million Wrongful Death Suit: ‘Where Was Security?’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WWE 2K22 – Official Gameplay Trailer – IGN #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are the 10 worst foods for your health, according to experts #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Florida GOP Pushes Bill To Shield White People From ‘Discomfort’ Of Racist Past #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Larry Gatlin talks getting COVID a second time, shares fury with government: ‘They’re trying to shut us down’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sachin Tendulkar’s “Stunning” Tweet On Rafael Nadal’s Historic 21st Grand Slam Title | Cricket News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Bel-Air Teaser Shows the One Little Fight That Sees Will Move Out of Philly – IGN #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch: Rajvardhan Hangargekar’s Stunning Delivery In Training Ahead Of India’s U-19 World Cup Super League Quarter-Final vs Bangladesh | Cricket News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uncharted Devs Seem to Want to Make Another Sequel: ‘It’s a World We Want to See More Of’ – IGN #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After testing positive for COVID-19 in Jamaica, a couple paid $35,000 for a private jet home — and they’re not the only Americans doing it #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Knows Conditions Well”: Darren Sammy Names West Indies Cricketer Who Can Trouble India | Cricket News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tiffany Haddish addresses DUI arrest: ‘We’re going to work it out’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Random: Link’s Breath Of The Wild Bow Technique “Really Sucks”, According To A Professional Archer #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back pain? Muscle tension? Flip the switch with this inversion table—and it’s on sale for 40 percent off, today only #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Indies vs England: 4 Wickets In 4 Balls, Jason Holder Creates History For West Indies. Watch | Cricket News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple AirPods Pro are nearly $70 off at Amazon — ‘The future is now’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giants’ Brian Daboll wants to form ‘critical’ bond with Daniel Jones #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Roblox and why won’t my kids stop talking about it? A gaming expert explains #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oppo Reno 7 5G India Pricing Surfaces Online Ahead of Launch #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loaded WWE Royal Rumble comes with Ronda Rousey wild card #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deflector – Early Access Launch Trailer – IGN #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicky Hilton Rothschild Is Pregnant, Expecting Third Baby with Husband James Rothschild #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truckin’: Monster Jam Tour rolls into NJ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghan People Starving, Forced To Sell Children, Body Part: UN Food Head #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orcas observed devouring the tongue of a blue whale just before it dies in first-ever documented hunt of the largest animal on the planet #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope in a hopeless situation: How a family’s generosity changed a teen mother’s outlook on her pregnancy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bravo Finally Fires Jennie Nguyen From ‘Real Housewives of Salt Lake City’ After Racist Posts #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kristen Bell Says Husband Dax Shepard Is His Own Doctor And It’s Pretty Disturbing #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ChargePoint Upgraded by J.P. Morgan. Stock’s Pullback Could Be a Good Entry Point. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virginia Republicans push for changes in marijuana law #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[T-Mobile Said to Terminate Employees Not Vaccinated Against COVID-19 by April #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to watch Stephanie Land discuss “Maid” at L.A. Times Book Club #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICC U-19 Cricket World Cup: England Defeat South Africa, Become First Team To Reach Semifinal | Cricket News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-vaxxers arrested after refusing to leave Museum of Natural History #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michigan dad, a Marine vet, says critical race theory contrary to values learned in military #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hideki Matsuyama bringing hot hand to Farmers Insurance Open #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Avenatti Now Representing Himself In Case Vs. Stormy Daniels #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new look at how turmoil is defining the lives and politics of Generation Z #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Troy Aikman talks NFL playoffs, overtime rule, Odell Beckham’s resurgence #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here’s What to Watch as the Fed Gets Set to Raise Rates #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Member of January 6 House Select Committee addresses why they haven’t asked to speak with Trump #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queen Latifah Breaks Silence On Chris Noth’s Firing After Sexual Assault Allegations #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Stamos and Bob Saget ‘clashed’ on set of ‘Full House’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Proof Is In The Pudding”: What Ricky Ponting Said About Rohit Sharma’s Captaincy Credentials | Cricket News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait, how many private jets landed in KC for Chiefs, Bengals AFC Championship? Ten, 20? More! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Astronomers spot ‘spooky’ object in our ‘galactic backyard’ that’s unlike ‘anything ever seen’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 Dead, Many Injured In Stampede After Football Match At Africa Stadium #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Policemen Charged In George Floyd’s Death ‘Chose To Do Nothing’: Prosecutor #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 6 best big-screen TV deals to watch Super Bowl 2022 in style #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under-Pressure Mark Boucher Hails Progress Made By South African Team | Cricket News #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing North Carolina mother and daughter found safe after five years #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sega Is Exiting The Japanese Amusement Arcade Business After Half A Century #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID-19 claims youngest victim in Los Angeles as county sees near-record number of deaths in single day #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Keke Palmer found power and hope in the story of a woman’s escape from slavery in the 1970s #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redmi Note 11, Redmi Note 11S India Price Tipped #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 detectives investigating the deaths of Lauren Smith-Fields and Brenda Rawls were suspended after families criticized police response #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long COVID: 4 biological risk factors could increase chances, according to study #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says Biden can’t enter a sports stadium in the US ‘without being loudly mocked and ridiculed,’ but the former president was booed at a 2019 World Series game #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review: Vagante – A Roguelike Too Empty To Make An Impact #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adams administration still hasn’t sought waiver for Banks to serve as deputy mayor #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the giant intraday reversal in stocks is not sticking #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Tyson doesn’t sound interested in fighting Jake Paul #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caterpillar Beats Earnings Estimates as Supply-Chain Issues Can’t Derail It. But the Stock Falls. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple riles online critics with pregnant man, other progressive emojis #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gerard Gallant wants his Rangers to ‘push’ until All-Star break #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tucker Carlson Claims White People Face COVID-19 Discrimination #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy Unpacked 2022 Set for February 9: All the Details #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet Methuselah, the oldest living aquarium fish #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cars crash into same New Jersey home two weekends in a row #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California jewelry store owner takes matters into his own hands and stops smash-and-grab attempt #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man Killed in Hail of Police Bullets Fired by NINE Cops on Nashville Interstate #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Must Avert ‘Civil War’ Like Situation In Myanmar: China At UN #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When revenge leads to peace in ‘Power of the Dog’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Dover sole worth $82? Rising prices test NYC diners #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BetMGM Bonus Code: Grab $200 in free bets if Chiefs or Bengals score a touchdown #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rangers blow another lead, fall to Wild to spoil Henrik Lundqvist celebration #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain’s sexiest postal employee misplaced 182 kilos by strolling on the job #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Masters of the Universe’ Movie Lands at Netflix, Kyle Allen Set as Lead #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Midnight Ghost Hunt: Hands-On Preview – IGN #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trudeau pans Canadian school’s 2019 book-burning ‘reconciliation’ for Indigenous people #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huawei Takes Sweden to Court Over 5G Ban #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ShowBiz Minute: Kryst, Spotify, US Box Office #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Texas teacher was placed on administrative leave after ranting to junior high school students and calling them ‘complete and utter morons’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jason Momoa Confirmed as Fast &amp; Furious 10’s Villain [Update] – IGN #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Chicago, a New Approach to Gay and Bisexual Men With Prostate Cancer #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mario Kart 8 Deluxe To Undergo Maintenance Later Today #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cash Pours Into Anti-ARK ETF as Cathie Wood Struggles #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cash injection: NY nurses busted for forging vax cards in $1.5M scheme #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Avenatti lied to Stormy Daniels and stole her money, prosecutors say #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Civil Wars Expert: U.S. Capitol Riot Made 1 Chilling Thing ‘Impossible To Deny’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Princess Charlene of Monaco’s twins attend annual ceremony with Prince Albert amid their mother’s absence #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amid nationwide blood shortage, experts say it’s time for the FDA to lift restrictions for gay and bisexual men: ‘One blood donation can save up to three lives’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Clooney: Ben Affleck ‘deserves’ another Oscar — ‘he’s a fighter’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Games with Gold for February 2022 – Xbox Wire #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mortal Kombat film sequel greenlit by New Line Cinema #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Is What It’s Like to Compete on The Amazing Race During a Pandemic #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review: Talking-head documentary ‘Gamestop: Rise of the Players’ focuses on the little guys #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Hudson says famous parents Goldie Hawn, Kurt Russell wanted to have ‘the best family’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bengals’ C.J. Uzomah emotional as he’s carted off during AFC Championship game #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FanDuel Promo Code: Have your first bet risk-free up to $1,000 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nebraska county prosecutor seeks death penalty in fast-food shooting that left 2 dead #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYPD cops make no arrest after woman fatally stabbed in chest at apartment building #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got trapped in Aldi — and no, I didn’t steal anything from the center aisles #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>