<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is wise to remember that on any given morning you cd wake up with a debilitating disease.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Irwin is for #HASHTAG# (D), I think. He used to represent CT's 4th district in the 1960s. He &amp; #HASHTAG# (R)used to flip CT-4 back &amp; forth. #HASHTAG# once called elections there the "biennial classic."

#HASHTAG# was Postmaster General under FDR. They had a falling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was one of the kids in the trial when I was in 2d grade. I had a #HASHTAG# card. I got 7 shots in the trial. My parents were so grateful to Dr. Salk. There were no antivaxxers in those days. We all knew kids who died or were crippled by polio. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She is VICE President not President. Goes with the territory. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join me in supporting Vet Voice Foundation via #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sweet Capitol Hill love story for troubled times.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good. If he had been vaccinated, he cd have played rennid. #HASHTAG# made his choice &amp; has to live with it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so glad my 5 year colonoscopy was completed on Dec. 28th as #HASHTAG# cases in VA are skyrocketing. Only problem was that local #USER# was totally out of #HASHTAG# that you have to drink b4 the procedure. I found some at #USER#. Supply chain? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I went to Harvard Law 1968-1971. My parents did not go to college. My father, in fact, only went thru 8th grade. Legacy admits are more common in Harvard College than in HLS. My kids both went to William &amp; Mary, a state university in VA. Neither went to law school.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This remix of #HASHTAG# by the group #USER# for Chanukah. Must watch for anyone who celebrates!

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Japanese children have worn masks for years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They are waiting for an outbreak &amp; some kids to die first. Nice. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which shows you how much #HASHTAG# really cares for coal miners. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My father wd never ask for directions. Wasted a lot of time (b4 GPS) &amp; angered my mother. No matter how many times he drove to Idlewild (now LGA), he always made wrong turns. No sense of direction. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jan. 6 Panel Examining Trump’s Role in Proposals to Seize Voting Machines #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It seems that everyone in the #HASHTAG# has his hand in the cookie jar following the example of #HASHTAG# &amp; his family. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am already tired of all the bad Christmas music. The classical music is fine. Same for all those happy ending as films. Can I gag now? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Reading all the books about TFG wd be an exercise in futility. I pity the pundits who must read them first work. They all say the Aamer things: TFG is an incompetent ass &amp; kowtowed to anyone who lined his pockets even against the US' best interest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lovely story.

Once a Janitor, Now the Bar Mitzvah Photography King of Montreal #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is there to investigate? We have it on tape. Part of #HASHTAG#'s "listening to parents" campaign?

Have Amelia King's guns been removed. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, he doesn't kiss #HASHTAG#'s ass so you can't expect the #HASHTAG# to welcome the former REPUBLICAN VP.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tourism will take yrs to recover. At age 75, I yearn to travel again, but survival is more important than tourism. I was in South Africa in March 2020--a trip I had to cut short. One plane trip since then: Oregon to visit family. 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But no mask mandates so the unvaccinated are free to spread #HASHTAG# germs around. Reminder: #HASHTAG#'s son attends StAlbans where masks are required. He protects his kid but not public school kids. What a schande is #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER#, thanks for letting everyone know that we do not have to stop living &amp; giving as we proceed to the inevitable. Hope all the dogs you loved &amp; preceded you over the 🌈 bridge were there to kiss you when it was your turn. Love ya &amp; good-bye. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More banned book clubs needed for teens! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do we have to wait until the #HASHTAG# starts assassinating Secretaries of State? Who is funding these people?

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can shove the ventilators down your throats!
We can shove the ventilators down your throats.

Etc. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The article does not support the assertion that it is more difficult to treat myocarditis that results from vaccination is more difficult to treat than non vaccine related myocarditis. So far it is not a problem in the US for 5-11 yr olds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, the #USER# is fantastic! A friend &amp; I went on the way from DC to SC for the total solar eclipse a few years back. At age 75 I doubt I'll ever get to #HASHTAG#. I don't know how I found the podcast but it probably was thru a referral on another podcast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess we will have to wait for the next mass shooting for support for gun control to increase. It won't take long. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The last thing I wd want is soap (whether on a rope or not). I have enough soap bought as souvenirs from trips to last past my death. I was astounded at the collection when I researched what was under my bathroom sink. Anyone giving me soap will be summarily executed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah. Attack #USER# due to his age &amp; then support #HASHTAG#. The ringht wing wish list. Biden Should Not Run Again — and He Should Say He Won’t #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am 75. There are lots of funerals as friends &amp; family die--&amp; you get closer to when it is your turn. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given the #HASHTAG# risk to US athletes &amp; China's lack of transparency, why wd we want to risk the health of US competitors? China cd also hold hostages if anyone criticized anything. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I returned from #HASHTAG# just after the crowded #HASHTAG# spreading airports. It took me 60 hours of traveling to get back. After that, aside from an emergency family visit to Oregon, which had inconveniences both ways, I have stayed close to home. My travel was 3/23-3/25/2020]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He needs to be suspended for the entire season. He basically lied about vaccination &amp; put the entire team &amp; the public at risk. Look what the NFL did to #HASHTAG# for the "crime" of kneeling during the #HASHTAG#. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanna ck for #HASHTAG# cases in 2 weeks. Seems to be a rather small turnout. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And the new #HASHTAG# controlled #HASHTAG# has banned masks on the House floor. Nice opening for #USER# &amp; his anti-masks in school supporters. His kids attend/toney private schools where masks are currently required #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Deaths are going up. Overwhelmingly unvaccinated or immunocompromise. 

Oh well. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They are all guilty. Every last member of the #HASHTAG# in the House &amp; many od the Senators as well. I guess cultivating their crazy base was more important than the Constitution #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The parents shd be charged with aiding &amp; abetting the murders #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Which means he won't give a dime to decrease world hunger. Control freak #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you imagine what FOX wd be saying if it were #USER#'s son? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I once got cert den in 6 wks from the USDC in the 1970s. Involved Moon Church visa overseas. The cts can act quickly when you file your pleadings promptly &amp; the situation is egregious. Opposing counsel patronized me in the ctrm. Working for #HASHTAG# at the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah. Allow more people to die by blocking action on the pandemic &amp; blaming #USER# for the deaths.

That's the strategy. The #HASHTAG# is relying on people being stupid--&amp; they may be right. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the lawsuits continue, the families will end up collecting more than $450,000. Early settlements have a politically bad look which is why #USER# won't do it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That is less than 1 1/2 covid tests per American.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How about an increase in the VA income tax instead. I wd focus it on high earners such as #HASHTAG# &amp; ultra rich who set up foundations to avoid paying takes--such as #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who wd go to the mall when there may be unvaccinated/unmasked people running around &amp; serving you in stores?

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #HASHTAG# blocked #HASHTAG#. Now they will be blaming #USER# for the spike. Consistency is not their strong suit. Next the #HASHTAG# "open up the schools" crew will be blaming School Bds for yielding to their threats &amp; opening up schools. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# is both a US &amp; South African treasure. P.S. I thought the border crossers swam the Atlantic Ocean #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't let the trolls &amp; bots get you down. Most of us real people support you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I hope #USER# enjoys his legal fees in thrall to his god king.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because #HASHTAG# wants to be the #HASHTAG# candidate for president &amp; he doesn't care if he kills a lot of them in the process. Strategy might not work because there will be #HASHTAG#. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join me in supporting Ron Be Gone, Inc. via #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I had no idea what my kids wd do with my books, so I took care of it. Also, if I ever need to go into a nursing home (perish the thought), there will be less stuff to clean out at that time. Best to simplify things while my brains are still intact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are needed all over especially for LGBTQ teens struggling with their sexual identities. I bet many are reading Tony Morrison's books. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She speaks the truth &amp; her ancestors probably fought &amp; died in the #HASHTAG#. My ancestors fleeing Russian pograms arrived after that so, if we measure ancestry by who got here 1st AAs, Hispanics in the West &amp; #HASHTAG# have got a lot of us beat.#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# is forever saddled with mixed feelings about the Clinton's &amp; her lovely exhusband]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I am on conventional #HASHTAG#. I pick &amp; choose my doctors--&amp; I have a lot of them given that I am 75 with both orthopedic &amp; digestive problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problems is that many are too feeble to leave their homes &amp; refuse to go to nursing homes. My neighbor has that exact situation with her 91- year-old mother. She has just fallen again. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I am 75. Prepandemic I was in Europe almost every summer as a result of #HASHTAG# deals. I guess that's over now. I went to visit an ailing relative in Oregon last summer complete with cancelations &amp; delays. I'll drive somewhere next summer. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I had a tooth ground for a crown recently not fun. Much worse if the tooth breaks. I get the permanent crown on Tues. I had a colonoscopy on the 28th &amp; was worried the anesthesiologist would knock off the the temporary, but it's still in place. Good luck with your tooth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aid for me but not for thee--the usual Republican MO. And, yeah, brag about money for infrastructure you voted against while you are at it. 

Kentucky on My Mind #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turning into a clown? I thought that happened a long time ago. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nope &amp; I never restricted my kids' reading either. I did regulate what films &amp; shows they saw when they were small but nothing more than that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# My kids education at William &amp; Mary cost $10K per year in the 1990s &amp; early 2000s. Of course it is more now but private colleges are often at least double the cost of state universities. In McLean many bright students live home &amp; attend George Mason now due to cost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The ground is still frozen so tanks can move. If it were mud season, the tanks wd get stuck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remind me why I moved from New England to DC in 1971 after I finished law school. I have considered moving back to CT in retirement (I was born in #HASHTAG#) but the winters are one reason why I stay in VA despite Governor #HASHTAG# &amp; summer heat.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many people opposed to common sense. Thread 🧵 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The purpose of the move was to prevent the #HASHTAG# from functioning. It appears to have succeeded.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then they wonder why no one is having children. Of course, no one is having children. It must be terrible for parents of under 5s. They cannot safely send them to day care &amp; mothers cannot take care of them &amp; work from home. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bought &amp; pd for thanks to #HASHTAG#' decision in #HASHTAG# but, of course ( ), SCOTUS is not politicized. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If #HASHTAG# is too busy with his wife's cancer to goverrn, he can resign or turn over his powers to the Lt. Governor. Family problems do not allow an elected publicly elected official to simply "opt out" of his job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently bad parenting &amp; defective civics education in his toney private school. Perhaps he shd switch to public school. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Both my kids went to #HASHTAG#. They did go to specialized graduate programs in private univ &amp; had some loans from that but they did not owe a dime or undergrad. If you are strapped for cash, you can always start at Comm. College. The super rich will always have an edge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Do you know what they pay for gas in Europe? It's at least 2x what Americans pay, so shut up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Makes you wonder what the plan is for non fundies in the US. A new #HASHTAG#? You cd just have a large auto da fe party for everyone you dislike &amp; throw all the books banned by fundie school bds on it after you get done with the people. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The problem is that #USER# has 9nly 50 Senators to work with. That makes each one a king.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sadly, the #HASHTAG# seems to prefer autocracy &amp; corruption with #HASHTAG# &amp; ignorance with #HASHTAG# 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents with these sorts of complaints shd put their kids in private Christian academies or just have their kids opt out from the lessons. Each parent will have a different idea of what is desired. Some schools will simply drop sex ed--which is the goal

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I cannot resist needling #USER#. As a family they played both sides of the street for political advantage which makes me suspicious of anything George does. There was that problem with their kid as well. Messy household.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I agree. The only proper pie is a fruit pie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I was 7. I had no idea that being in the #HASHTAG# was saving lives. I lined up in the gym with all the other 2d graders as I was told. Only later did I realize the teeny part I played. It was a happy day when Salk announced the vaccine worked &amp; there was no more polio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How little you know. We are in the midst of a huge fight in the HOA in my development. 2 of us are meeting with an atty tomorrow. The homeowners are suing the Board of Directors to stop an expensive project. The Bd has been bullying us for months. Stress has been terrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the cruise boats continue to depart. . . . #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Didn't open carry pass in Missouri? That shd fix it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Unfortunately, the #HASHTAG# is now dominated by racist nuts &amp; #HASHTAG#. Denying that denies the truth. The ones that are not have agreed to go along with the extremists. I cut ties with my last #HASHTAG# friend. I told her I cd not deal with it any longer. She replied that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[everyone organized to oppose this with lots of people willing to serve on the Board! The Board President has gone silent. Since  no one will vote money to sue ourselves, the capitulation of those behind this is inevitable but it will be a World War for a long time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Wages have gone up since I was in college as well. My Dad had a small business. He probably made $8000 a year in 1964 (if that) when I started at UConn. We lived in an apt while I was growing up--not a house. Everything is relative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#'s kid is protected at #HASHTAG# where masks are required. He doesn't give a damn about public school kids.

Youngkin’s health department fielded questions about science behind masks-optional policy

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminds me that you can cry tears &amp; a t inappropriately when b4 a Senate Committee &amp; still get on #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Hitler, uh, Putin, takes over Czechoslovakia, uh, Ukraine, the Baltics will be next. Then Poland. 

The ultimate beneficiary of this is China. Does anyone else agree?

How Far Would Biden Go to Defend Ukraine Against Russia? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Every time a prescription med goes over the counter, you have to pay for it  put of pocket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They were probably passed out to antivax police. How many NYers did they infect? Where is the husband's proof of vaccination? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# This is clearly not over. By this action the University of Florida has escalated the fight. It is, for example, like right wingers attempting to bab #HASHTAG# in an AP English class in Virginia. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# These kids need to go to state universities rather than over priced private colleges/universities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't buy Girl Scout cookies anymore as Cookie Mints are terrible for my diet. I just give them a couple of bucks in a donation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently in #HASHTAG# being annoying to #HASHTAG# is a crime by order of the Governor. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good for them. I wdnt want to come in contact with an unvaccinated person in a hospital of all places. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If #HASHTAG# is convicted, the case might get overturned due to the weird judge's meanderings. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# NYC is the safest place in the country. You must show proof of vaccination to go anywhere indoors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You do not have a right to put 3d parties who choose to be vaccinated at risk. They have the #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't test a la #HASHTAG#, then people can pretend it doesn't exist. Exactly the "strategy" the #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# guys want to use with #HASHTAG#. Pretending ends up in mass death &amp; then the right tells everyone how phony "prolife" they are. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# International travel is the same disaster it was in March 2020. Chaos Part 2. Only a matter of time b4 the #HASHTAG# blames #HASHTAG# on #HASHTAG#. There is a huge risk in any international travel until the #HASHTAG# is really over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I am door-to-door canvassing on Sat. I found phone banking very frustrating. Most people do not answer their phones if they do not recognize the phone numbers or you reach voice mail. I thought it was largely a waste of time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are 350,000 million Americans. There are 500,000 million tests. Tell me how many seconds until the test supply is exhausted? Then people will be selling the free tests to the highest bidder. Just watch. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And, of course, no mask or vaccine mandates in schools. Hey, #HASHTAG#, why are you not listing to parents? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# Governoring is slightly different than shooting your mouth off &amp; lying in a campaign. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope #HASHTAG# runs for president to counter the #HASHTAG# wing of the Republicans. As a lifelong liberal, I wdnt vote for her but, if she won, I wd be able to sleep at night. History is going to be unkind to the #HASHTAG#. Cheney will go down as a profile in courage. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I never deal with disputes in private messages. It is a way to keep the incompetence of a company in private so no one else can see what is going on. The pharmacy replaced my shot which you mislaid &amp; consequently arrived unrefrigerated. I had them send the 2d shot #USER#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will the perpetrators claim self defense? Some people in the parade were twirling flags that cd have hurt them after all. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the sane won't move to states where a majority are insane. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# is knee deep in the Jan. 6th riot.  She helped organize the buses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In normal times, this wd have ended his political career  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# OCanada, prepare for an invasion of feathers/foam rubber!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I said the same thing. I am no expert but I look at the #USER# #HASHTAG#. A new spike is beginning assisted by those who refuse to get vaccinated. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how many boxes of records #HASHTAG# destroyed by burning, shredding or eating. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wdnt decorate my house with Xmas lights even if he got the vaccine. I guess it is "Freedom of religion is for me &amp; not for thee" once more from the lovely fundies on the right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# shd be, at a minimum, out for the season. If it were up to me, he wd never play professional sports again. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #HASHTAG# needs to investigate #HASHTAG#. Problem: The new Lt. Gov is a gun toting fanatic. If #HASHTAG# is forced to resign, VA wd get worse. The next 4 yrs will be a rough ride. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can only hide so much from our kids. The biggest mouths for opening schools/opposing masks were #HASHTAG# supporters. If kids see screaming parents at school bd meetings, they mirror that behavior. One thing this isn't is #HASHTAG#. n.b. #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We cannot defeat a Senator who is not up for reelection until 2024. Challenging #HASHTAG# wd be futile. AZ voters shd take care of #HASHTAG#. She'll become another corrupt lobbyist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No it isn't nuts &amp; shd have been done long ago as it was done in other countries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is beyond stupid, but, hey, if some conservative talk show host with no medical training advocated it, it must be true because #USER# is a communist. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is probably already here. Tell me: Wd you advocate marooning Americans abroad indefinitely as was done in Australia in March 2020? Oz has a zero covid policy with strict lockdowns. How wd you do that in the US where governors are virus friendly? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't you know #HASHTAG# created the variant in his lab? Or maybe #HASHTAG# has a lab in the #HASHTAG# to create variants in his copious free time &amp; it's a conspiracy to kill off the #HASHTAG# refuseniks? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sooner or later #USER# will have to go in &amp; take on #HASHTAG#. Later means more people die. In 1939 Europe appeased #HASHTAG# &amp; he gobbled up countries one by one. Do Europeans &amp; the US want to temporize while #HASHTAG# moves into the Baltics &amp; eventually all of #HASHTAG#?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah. Every time they approve a medicine for #HASHTAG#, I have to pay more. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The American public shd not be paying the hospital bills for anyone taking a cruise during the time of a pandemic.

It is not as if the passengers &amp; crew did not know what cd result.

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And, if schools had remained open &amp; more kids died, the #HASHTAG# wd be arguing. "They shd have closed schools." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I have a #HASHTAG# but it is a 2008. I am leading the charge to overthrow the HOA Board in an Assiociiation in #HASHTAG#. No Annual Meeting, no votes on anything. The have a dishonest atty bullying the homeowners at our expense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Whoop de doo for her. Her vote was not needed due to some surprising Republican votes Nancy had in her pocket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They won't as the #HASHTAG# now control the #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# wd veto any such bill. Not time to do it b4 #HASHTAG# becomes governor. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I was so sick with measles as a child that I have no memory of it. I was either a preschooler or in an early grade in elementary school. My cousin had polio &amp; was hospitalized. He was part way thru his #HASHTAG# inoculations &amp; family lore is that is what saved him from severe disease]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And people wonder about the decline in church attendance. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did the owner of #URL# donate to #USER#'s campaign or after to obtain this deal? #HASHTAG# And if the promised jobs do not appear?

Youngkin announces $2.6 million investment in Fairfax-based #URL# #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am looking for an attorney in VA who has experience with #HASHTAG# disputes. This involves a serious dispute where the homeowners outvote the Board and the Board will not step down. Follow &amp; DM if you are interested &amp;/or can suggest someone. It involves #HASHTAG# in #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The sad thing is that my ex-friend has been a Republican all her life &amp; has changed as the party became more extreme. I shd have cut her off ages ago but waited &amp; hoped. I simply gave up as she got worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# shd be tried for crimes against humanity at a bare minimum. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That happened big time after #HASHTAG#. Given the tsunamis on the US West Coast, I cannot even imagine the damage in #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# &amp; other Pacific Islands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# At least they gave you some information. In DC "There is a train on the track ahead of us &amp; we will be moving momentarily" no matter what the problem is."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World War III is running into Hitler, uh, #HASHTAG# taking over Czechoslovakia, uh #HASHTAG#. Will #HASHTAG# or the #HASHTAG# be next while #HASHTAG# twiddles its thumbs &amp; #HASHTAG# benefits? Stay tuned. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I just want to say how much I am enjoying this account. #HASHTAG# has sort of been quiet after getting into all sorts of fights on day one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess Manchin &amp; Sinema must be in favor of disenfranchising a lot of people. Thank you #HASHTAG# G.O.P. Cements Hold on Legislatures in Battleground States #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It took 1 day for the fighting to begin. We are all boycotting the dues increase &amp;, since money for any suits to sue the refuseniks has to be approved by the homeowners, the President will end up backtracking, deposed &amp; a neighborhood pariah (already is). Be glad to talk to media]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Speaker in history for putting up with lunatics from all sides &amp; always coming out on top. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone has $6K worth of clothing in college? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Postal Service Board of Governors has to throw out #HASHTAG#. #USER# cannot do that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe LA needs a new sheriff #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I was going to say something obscene so I will stop here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# This is a copy of the #HASHTAG# in France. It is not the one in NY Harbor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Without the support of #HASHTAG#, the US has limited options. I hope the countries in Eastern Europe &amp; #HASHTAG# are prepared for a huge flood of #HASHTAG# as World War III in Europe begins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incompetent, criminal or hospitalized? Was he using the clients for his own ends? Does he have #HASHTAG#? TFG's supporters have all the best people, don't they? Go-to Lawyer for Capitol Riot Defendants Disappears #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And South Africa does have some good medical facilities. The first heart surgery to replace a failing hear with a machine was done in Cape Town.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We do understand #HASHTAG# perfectly
#HASHTAG# will be responsible for a lot of deaths.

What the Supreme Court’s Vaccine Case Was Really About #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Do you mean you are not upset that the annual #HASHTAG# is about to begin--together with the #HASHTAG# paper cup controversy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will this challenge the #HASHTAG# "do your own research" crowd or are they determined to die to show their devotion to their king, #HASHTAG#? It's a rhetorical question. At least there will be #HASHTAG#. Why shd we waste $ on their healthcare? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call the VA Governor by his correct name. Shd we choose #HASHTAG# or #HASHTAG#? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder how much time #HASHTAG#'s son #HASHTAG# will get? Like not even any charges? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a damning interview. How much longer until the reporter is pushed out of #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And telling people to fight with their insurance companies for reimbursement is just nuts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is a schande--as is her husband.

The Long Crusade of Clarence and Ginni Thomas #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 yrs of pain &amp; fighting coming up due to #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But the ones dying of #HASHTAG# are the #HASHTAG#. Ah, they live to kill their own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# At age 75, I neither want or need jewelry. All stuff with precious stones has been passed down. I did not own anything valuable but lots of sentimental family connections. Shoot me if I buy anymore jewelry or t-shirts/sweatshirts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I became a lawyer not a doctor. It was very scary to think what cd have happened had I not intervened.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am sure lots of copies of #HASHTAG# were bought last week providing a boost to the estate of #HASHTAG#. I never read the book because I graduated high school in 1964. I will read it now. The whole faux controversy is racist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the grandchildren who opposed integration &amp; shouted "segregation forever" are now screaming about #HASHTAG#. Pretty much the same ignorance.

Sanitized American history is not history. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turns out that even the electric car owners do not want the vanity project. They can install outlets on their homes &amp; plug in if desired (no garages). The $328,000, BTW, is just for the wiring. It does not include the chargers themselves. So a 2d dues increase.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And, alas, the lights of #HASHTAG# will soon dim again. In fact many shows are canceling performances due to #HASHTAG# outbreaks. The #HASHTAG#, which had fought mask mandates will blame #USER# Offices Shut and Holiday Parties Dim as a Familiar Feeling Sinks In #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# out over the 3rd term. Might be him.

For the rest ask #USER#. He knows buttons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot make this stuff up.

All the best people strikes again.
 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The #HASHTAG# will baptize you after you are dead even if you don't want it. They believe it gives you the last chance to get into Mormon heaven.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids &amp; their lovies. I don't remember fondly the time we had to Fed Ex my son's worn "Kringle bear" when he left it at the Florida cousins. It was a tense 2 or 3 days until that day bear was back in his loving hands.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use the money to help restore the damage #HASHTAG# has caused in #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A lot of people believe that, at this point, the #HASHTAG# have made their choice to die/expose others &amp; shd receive no priority for hospitalization/new therapies. I am one of those people who is sick of the self entitlement of free-dumb fools.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you live in Utah, might want to consider him. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Our HOA bd is negotiating a loan for $420,000. A majority of the homeowners set up their own meeting &amp; voted against it. The Bd simply ignores us &amp; says the vote was "illegal" because they did not authorize it. No Annual Meeting for over 2 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well, if the #HASHTAG# says it is the party of the working class, it must be true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Absolutely a magnificent piece of journalism. And to all the bots/trolls posting on this thread: block.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Nothing has shielded me from anything. And not everyone in McLeanVA is a gazillionaire. You seem to carry a lot of resentment. Going to an elite school is no panacea. It can be difficult socially for poor students. Personal experience here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The antimask/antivax parents are a bunch of loudmouth parents who try to "win" thru intimidation. If #HASHTAG# wants to "listen to parents, promask/provax parents far out number the screaming #HASHTAG# loudmouth in NoVA. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The #USER# interview about #HASHTAG# always brings a smile. I have watch the accompanying cartoon so many times. And, then I cry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly. It is a sign of the retrograde decision the #HASHTAG# on #HASHTAG# will make. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole point is to criticize Biden for whatever he does. Hypocrisy does not matter to the #HASHTAG#. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regret your vote for the #HASHTAG# Biden/Trumpkin voters in VA? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds as if WW III is about to speed up with #HASHTAG# playing the role Hitler picking off the countries one by one while #HASHTAG# fiddles. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They may be prepping a criminal indictment for #HASHTAG# &amp; will roll the contempt charge into it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Time for some traffic problems among Republicans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Realistically no dental benefit wd have added crowns, root canals, implants, etc. Fillings &amp; ck ups wd have been all that cd have been covered--&amp; pulling teeth. I just had one tooth ground for a crown. $1790. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I stopped listening to your podcast, #USER#. Anti #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# do not control the #HASHTAG#. They simply cannot win GQP dominated primaries. The extreme left controls some seats, but just enuf to cause trouble--not the entire party. You need to shut up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't imagine anyone being afraid of black pastors. PS I am white. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If #HASHTAG# moves against mandates, then more workers will get sick &amp; businesses will have to close. The #HASHTAG# justices cd get hoisted on their own political petards.

Supreme Court’s Conservative Majority Appears Skeptical of Biden’s Virus Plan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because they don't want to anger the hard-core right crazies. Without them, the #HASHTAG# cannot win. So they cater to their antivax death wish--which endangers everyone who has been vaccinated. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why wd anyone think that everyone at Ivy schools is exempt from being a no good #HASHTAG# or #HASHTAG#?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am 75 &amp; have difficulty walking long distances. 2 back operations. If there is a #HASHTAG# rally on the #HASHTAG#, I'll pack a cane &amp; come. 

For heaven's sake, give those brave people whatever they need.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The people running this nationwide scam shd be locked up. There will be deaths from it. Who is funding it? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well I am awaiting a "just in case" order of 80 rolls of TP from #USER#. If there is no problem I'll sell the rolls to for friends for exactly what I paid for them &amp;/or give them away to the desperate. The 80 rolls cost $63. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did she let #USER# officiate at her daughter's wedding given this moment?

The disruption of the wedding comes from #USER#'s refusal to speak to constituents. This not to say that I condone it, but it is understandable. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ever evolving names of new trolls/bots. I make liberal use of the blocking function. Very useful. #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>