<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The more he succeeds, the more he makes racists and black people suffering from pull him down syndrome very mad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever I see MaXhosa and Istore at Mall of Africa I'm reminded about how lucky I am to have generous homies. #USER# promised to buy me top stuff at Istore. #USER# promised to spoil me rotten at MaXhosa. In 2022, they'll deliver. ðŸ¤žðŸ¤ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Among US Country Music artists, I believe Don Williams and Dolly Parton have made more money is South Africa than anyone else. Kenny Rogers shouldn't be far too behind them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Whenever stitching came loose, we used to take such balls to shoe repairman to stitch it back. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The problem was the boy behind me. He looked angry. Luckily he wasn't in musth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This confirms one thing, some politicians see illegal immigrants as potential voters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# During Transkei days, Richardson Park in Mthatha used to host regular tennis tournaments. Ngqabane family in Mbizana which were tennis family were always there. Mbizana tennis court was across their house.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My cousins used to help married lady in the neighbourhood who was finishing matric. Husband didn't know and saw them there. He was mad and told them never to help her again. It turned out he had a gf that he transported everyday at their school. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In EC, you can know someone for years without knowing their name. Your paths cross daily but you've never formally introduce yourselves to each other. ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think there's one English phrase used by most cricketers. Even those who don't speak English well. 'Catch it' is the phrase.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My life revolves around Joburg South and I'm at home here. I do everything here. I haven't been to that hellhole for years now. Long may it continue.ðŸ¤žðŸ¤ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Shameless people tend to be arrogant and can manipulate people and make themselves look like victims of your aggression.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite squeeze bottle has cracked. Andiziva mnandi tu. ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're Andre Malan or Ben Curran and your siblings have represented their countries and you're odd men out. It must be tough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I used to hear early morning train from my house daily. These people just came to our country built shacks on our train platforms and then decimated our railway system. Cops did nothing about it. It's crazy. Oldest transport in SA system gone overnight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Soweto is surprisingly clean. I felt guilty that maybe it's us outsiders who trash that historical township. ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like in our families, music bands sometimes have black sheep member. For Rock band ACDC, it's their drummer Phil Rudd. He never strays far from trouble. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who live around Wilge Toll Plaza hate motorists. They stand next to NO STOPPING zones and hitchhike. ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# These people have been hypnotized. They see achievements where there's none. ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Declan Rice is an awesome player in any language. ðŸ‘ŒðŸ‘Œ. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How can ube necousin ebikwagrade 12 in your late 60s?ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Most of those wrecks in Mthatha are owned by my good friend #USER#. It's his side business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's funny in Gauteng as motorists we don't even acknowledge each other back in GP. Come to EC, we greet each other based on GP number plates on our cars. ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We had classmate we never quite knew where his home was. He had family ties in Mbizana, Flagstaff and Stanger in KZN. He called all those places kowabo. We were always tempted to ask where his parents lived. We never had courage. He was always passionate about those places.ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What a great man. Man who spoke with clear mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 1996 WC Sri Lankan triumph and Aravinda de Silva performance still give me goosebumps to this day. My second is Courtney Browne &amp; Ian Bradshaw batting to reach target against Poms at 2004 ICC Champions Trophy. I treasure those two moments. I love underdog.ðŸ‘ŒðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My dad has a son in Port Shepstone. He went to his grave without giving us full details. He gave us hints and left it there. ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South African ladies are still dropping routine catches. Masabata Klaas has just dropped straightforward catch. ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men who disappeared in early December are back home, very broke and apologetic. Please forgive them. ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If #USER# had its way, Ananias Mathe would have been buried at Westpark Cemetery's Heroes Acre. ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Followers of Sibusiso Radebe were defrauded by him and that wasn't enough. They wanted him to be president of the country. They once had political party going. Brainwashed people will be the end of this country. ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are players who're not the most talented but you know they'll give you 100% all the time. Ivory Coast's Serey Die is one of those players. Here in SA, I can't think of Johannes Mine. Those are players you know won't deliberately let you down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Public drinking remains a crime in SA. ðŸ˜ŽðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Those are so-called influencers. While other parties are fixing their shortcomings, Khongi is busy with factionalism. Kulaambutho asuka kuwo umadam ucinga she's the best thing ever to come out of SA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I once had a colleague like this. Uye kwakhe umfumane enxilile ubone something entle iyincome. Athi laamama yithathe xa uyifuna. Her family had responsibility of ensuring they knew who was given what. Following day she'd come and ask her stuff back. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# She's my dear friend. I don't need to explain that. Hamba uyolala. ðŸ™„ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Younger generation of musicians (talented ones) are sleeping on the job. There are many good old South African songs they can re-work and bring them back to life with great success. Asikho apho kodwa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While manning door during graduation at Vista University, guy with no ticket came wanting go in. I refused. He left promising to come back. Mangibuya uzongivulela nakanjani. He came back with drunk Sibeko from Emzini Wezinsizwa. I was powerless to stop them. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Areas like Xholobeni is where isiMpondo in its purest form is spoken. Whole KwaMadiba area is isiMpondo hotbed. The more you move inland isiXhosa starts to dilute isiMpondo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Warner can be thick at best of times. Steve Smith is a fidget. Marnus Labuschagne is eccentric. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cricket umpires are life. After meeting at Wanderers which ended late at night. One character was adamant he was pub crawling after that. He was also adamant he was taking that pub crawling time from family time. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚. Something my friend #USER# would do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Besides Nomhle Nkonyeni, Themsie Times was another actress I knew who aced roles where she used bad language. They were so natural in such roles. #HASHTAG# sis Themsie. Enkosi ngegalelo lakho. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You see a big company with many floors and departments. You go there and find a single individual who thinks he/she works alone. Other colleagues are lazy and clueless. You wonder why the place is not crumbling. Overambitious people Yehova!!! ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the time of the year at the mall you see couple pushing a trolley out of Pick n Pay with a young child and two litre Coke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green fly must be the most stupid creature ever. Once it enters space where it's not suppose to enter, it causes proper shit. The worst thing it can do is to sit on hot food while you're enjoying scrumptious meal and it dies. ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm grateful I'm less paranoid about #HASHTAG#. My two jabs gave me peace of mind. I'm not reckless by any means but I can get out, see places and meet people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't heard a single person in favour of illegal immigrants coming with solution as to how to handle their rampaging madness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He was world class. Late Duma Mnembe was another wold class performer who did both isiZulu and isiXhosa. Nandi Nyembe is another fabulously talented bilingual isiXhosa and isiXhosa actress. On top of that, she's a rape survivor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There's a very good reason I've never lost a cent to pyramid schemes and fake prophets, I don't follow the crowds. Crowds can take to hell quite literally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Polly was flummoxed by DRS at 2003 WC. We were knocked out as a result. Batsmen make good captains. The most successful captains have been predominantly batsman. Clive Lloyd and Steve Waugh, Ricky Ponting, Graeme Smith are case in point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I fear for our future debutants. Politicians masquerading as cricket fans expect those players to be miracle makers. Some of the comments on Sisanda Magala were so unfair for a guy playing his second ODI. Luckily, he's a mature player who has seen it all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I don't even know him. I know some of them on these streets. These are people who'll go all out to convince others that Zille is "misunderstood".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Serious. We had opportunity to discuss this issue when didn't have electricity for 4 days. People seem content with load reduction. I was hoping we would discuss it more since we were gathered near where problem was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dean Elgar, Dimuth Karunaratne and Kraigg Brathwaite are probably the most low profile and anonymous international captains going around. Laidback guys. Elgar is still the best when it comes to dealing with media. Very good in front of TV cameras.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Rory McIlroy should be at the prime of his career, his form doesn't agree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our slip fielding is finally showing good signs. We struggled with slip fielding after retirement of Biff and Kallis. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Don't take Luto seriously. I'm still trying to clean his image. ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ikhona ingxaki Manci. #USER# is busy abusing me on WhatsApp. He's accusing me of favoritism. He says he's the one who introduced you to Stella Artois. He wants that ambassadorial role desperately. He says you used to drink cheap wine and mqombothi. ðŸ˜ŽðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transkeians who lived off beaten tracks were terrified of cops. Makwantini was no different. They ran in all direction at the sight of police van. Growing up near town I never understood what the fuss was all about. They looked silly shame. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm surprised that some Americans are surprised Rihanna is a massive cricket fan. She's from Barbados. That island has supplied West Indies with finest batsmen cricket has ever seen. She was born into cricket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Kallis was lucky to start his career around guys like Brian McMillan who dropped nothing at slip.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Colin Gie gets raw deal when we talk about skillful white players in SA. He was skillful actually.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There are people who've got combined DNA of both. Mandela had both. There are Xhosa people who have DNA of either. Racists have tendency of thinking black Africans are purely Bantu when they try to justify Black Africans are settlers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe Transkei teachers paraded learners who had misbehaved and branded them bad example to other learners. We were even warned to avoid hanging out with them. One of them was my friend. I trolled him for years. ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mugabe trending from beyond the grave. What a lord!!!ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There were older guys when I first moved to Protea Glen in Soweto who used to meet on Sundays, drink and play Brook Benton's music. I was much younger than them those days but had same appreciation of Brook's music. I still do by the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# They come back after bribing people at the border. ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a fan of Country Music band Bellamy Brothers. Shame me all you can, I don't care. ðŸ˜œðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't think you were listening to stuff he was saying during commentary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Late Daphney Hlomuka was an awesome actress. I knew people who truly hated her for being heartless in Hlala Kwabafileyo. She was so convincing. Late Ruth Cele claimed she reduced crime because people were glued to TV screens watching her MaMgo antics. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Recent rains are partly to blame. Ocean knows how to clean itself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# These people even arrogantly justify and defend such actions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I came across three dogs. Two males and one female. Male and female were already stuck in copulatory tie. Third male dog wanted in on an action but was too late. It seemed unsure what to do. It looked envious though. ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not only rich people capable of having many houses. My sister who lives in KwaMadiba, Mbizana has two houses. They're within walking distance from each other. She alternates between two houses. Rural people are life. ðŸ‘ŒðŸ‘ŒðŸ‘ŒðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I gave lift to the most religious young man the other day. He rubbished booze and everything it stands for. ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'll tell you when to deliver my Christmas meal. ðŸ˜ŽðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Those are kindest people in SA. They'll see funny side. We don't take things too seriously in Transkei. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nothing is certain in life except death and taxes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think he should have directed this diatribe to Fighters and RET for support. They think Mugabe was a hero after all. Otherwise patriotic South Africans are tired of this nonsense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Let him be. Those are wonderful people along with petrol attendants. They should be very wise. They work long and awkward hours. In the process, they meet lots of great, strange, arrogant, eccentric people and everything in between.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Travelling in communal transport can be a lot of fun until you encounter fellow passenger who doesn't respect time. You have to leave and they're nowhere to be seen. Even they eventually appear, they give you "what's the rush look". ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My sentimental, historical and emotional attachment to that useless organization is gone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I wasn't currently victim of #USER# incompetence, I would be applauding #USER# and #HASHTAG# actions of making protesters clean up their mess on the spot. Sadly I can't because I have no electricity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Konje an elderly man in Germany tried to rob a bank. During interaction with him, bank staff realized he was deaf. Even when they pressed panic button, he heard nothing. He was arrested. He later tried to sue same bank "for exploiting his disability". ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thumping India 3-0 is something to savour any day. I love it when Bavuma and the boys show haters middle finger. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter activists come here and tell us to support black businesses. That time, some of us are called by first names at eateries in Soweto because it's something we do naturally. We mingle with white folks yearning for authentic township cuisine. Shame. ðŸ˜‰ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reason why clubs should have at least one outfield player who's a competent goalkeeper.
When Outfield Players Go In Goal | Premier League Edition #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our bowlers did decent job in first test. It's a pity batsmen didn't keep their end of the bargain. I hope Quinny takes responsibility for the way he got out in second innings. That match was winnable. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I remember joke where kid was asked to bring parent because he got zero for homework. The problem was, parent had helped the kid. ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What happened Faku. Young reverend who conducted funeral of my aunt and young cousin waziqengqa eMagwa Falls few weeks after performance that left everyone wanting more. He was from KwaMzizi. He had so much to live for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm not local. That is Dalindyebo's land. Maybe if you promise him to vote for those people who bought him car, who knows? ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There was a time it felt strange to hear white person saying SHARP. They say that so often it's no longer strange. I saw two white guys going separate directions saying SHARP to one another just like black folks would do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't because I'm careless. It would get lost. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giraffe has characters that don't usually go together. They're very curious and yet very shy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunil Gavaskar has just described his height as BELOW SEA LEVEL. He's short folks. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Some of them become drug addicts and alcoholics after discovering they're being played and exploited.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sri Lanka in 90s allowed both openers Jayasuriya and Kaluwitharana to go hard at bowlers from word go. They had advantage of settled middle order. Aravinda de Silva, Arjuna Ranatunga, Roshan Mahanama, Asanka Gurusinhe and Hashan Tillakaratne did the rest. Great side. ðŸ‘ŒðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Elephant is a huge animal. Even a medium size elephant is still big.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The biggest headache I ever had with gullible person was convincing her she had been scammed. The number no longer existed. ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Someone once asked me why South African men seldom marry foreign women. I had no answer. ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ndineendaba ezibuhlungwana Jola. #USER# says to me on WA he's not leaving your home until you've proven to beyond reasonable doubt that there's no more food or booze left. He wants to inspect fridges, cupboards and pantry himself. He'll leave once satisfied. ðŸ˜ŽðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't recall #USER# handling Mthatha Bucks matches. If he did, it must have been very few matches. Funny enough, EC based referees like Brian Maze, Stan Swart and Mark Lindon handled many Bucks matches. I was very curious. ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the way, first three cricket world cups after re-admission, SA took only 3 players of colour to those tourneys. Omar Henry in 1992, Paul Adams in 1996 and Herschelle Gibbs in 1999. Only in the fourth in 2003 we saw first black Africans in Makhaya Ntini &amp; Monde Zondeki.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# "GARDEN BOY" and circumcised. Contradiction loud and clear. ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm still not sure whether this thing of Downs signing everyone is good for our football. Especially #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europeans are looking after Paul Biya very well. He looks younger than 88. Only African president permanently based in Europe. ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Second one was a bit tough on me. Nothing hectic though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So disappointing. That Thuma Mina stunt got us fooled. ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Checking Joburg weather can be very misleading. The best way is to check for localized weather. It's a fact Lenz has weather system on its own. People from Lenz can tell you about rain no one else saw. Being a massive place, weather in Joburg can be confusing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In Joburg, they seem to work with powerful people. Under #USER# cable theft decreased in Soweto because he made it one of his priorities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Even there, it's a mixed bag. Some have lost contact with EC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's strange Mpumalanga has negotiated with #USER# for reduced load reduction hours. Gauteng morons haven't bothered themselves. We'll meet in 2024. #USER# mark this tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When you're born on 23rd April like Masuluke and me you're born with advantages. ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love how racists will always downplay role played by farm workers. It's like they don't exist. Yet, they do bulk of the work. Even their lives don't matter. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That Twitter nonsense. Funny we're only told this when criminal is either foreign national or white. Perception is all criminals are black South African men. It's imperative we highlight that it's not usual suspects.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm not related kwaMadikizela mos.ðŸ¤·â€â™‚ï¸ðŸ¤·â€â™‚ï¸ It's Winnie's mom who comes from my family. I was born a Mzaidume and I will die a Mzaidume. Even Winnie was not a Mzaidume. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diego Costa accused Ryan Shawcross of being smelly throughout the match. Funny enough, Eric Dier who speaks fluent Portuguese says his exchange with Costa was friendly. Maybe Costa finds non Portuguese speakers stinky. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What a versatile band. Glenn himself had a solid solo career. Other musicians associated with the band like Don Henley, Vince Gill, Tim Schmidt and Linda Ronstadt all have solid solo careers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm struggling to understand what is xenophobic about asking foreign nationals to enter SA legally. South Africans have been turned back in many countries for not bringing correct documents. People are literally preaching that we should allow free for all situation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm still asking, is there any need for KG Rabada to flirt with no ball line so much? ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# We'll beat him up. We don't play games in Jozi. We beat up rural people who provoke us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They treat him like traditional leader who inherits position from late parents. They forget he was voted for by South Africans across the country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There was local reggae band performing live in Sri Lanka while #HASHTAG# were touring there years ago. They were very decent. Funny enough, reggae music is quite popular in Sri Lanka.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter can be very misleading. Luckily, I do get out and see people laughing and catching up. You even see people of different races hugging each other and having good laugh. You meet nicest people and share jokes. Problems aside, there are great people out there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more I see Transkei Wild Coast's coolest and most beautiful, the more I'm convinced KD Matanzima sins will never be forgiven. State of the roads to those places. ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# When Zotsho turns 70 in two years time, he'll be looking after his troop of baboons kulaa mahlathi aseSajonisi. ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who upload songs on YouTube and then turn off comments are so unfair. I know there are misguided fools but most comments are good natured.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You should have driven straight towards Vaal. There's off ramp near Southgate Mall that would have taken you to Columbine Ave. Once you're Columbine westerly direction, you can go anywhere in Soweto.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Could be anyone really. Including dirty old men.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm only checking my work emails next week. Most people are back at work and I'm still on leave. I'm avoiding depressing ones. ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Don't forget criminals who brutally killed two security guards in Soweto in 2018 were themselves killed in Clermont. They were described by neighbors as quiet, respectful young men. Maybe you need to be more organized in Clermont so that criminals know game is up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There are idiots in Soweto who come and play loud on my driveway. I can't even hear my TV. I've complained to mother of one of the kids involved. I expect to see change this year. Otherwise I'm calling cops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even in the late 70s and 80s, magistrate Lugaju was processing wayward Mbizana men who thought females had no rights. He sentenced one guy to 9 months for touching a lady inappropriately. Guy justified that she had no bf. Lugaju fired back 'she wasn't your gf either.' ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's why I say I'm not sure in what context she was saying that. ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£. She's very young. She's about 13. Both are around that age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She later asked me about it. To maintain peace I apologized.ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder what will eventually happen in Tuchel / Lukaku spat. If left unchecked, it could paralyze dressing room.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PSL coaches should have never abandoned skill based football. Instead, they should have harnessed skill and made skillful players awsre of responsibility to the team. Ntsako Makhubela is skillful and individualistic at times but he can be coached out of that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My patience with speedsters who overtake dangerously and then force themselves in front you once they encounter on coming cars is wearing thin. One day I'm not going to open space just for control. People with self importance are tiring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This is exactly why many young black kids are afraid to be mentored by successful black people. They put you down in every turn. Most black kids aren't born with tons of self esteem. It doesn't take much to wipe it all off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transkeians still use name Goli as blanket name for every place that has mines. I was chatting to a lady in Coffee Bay who told me she lives eGoli. I asked her which part and said Marikana. ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Scientifically, their genes remain related. Athletes from those countries don't take advantage of that sprinting prowess. I guess West African folks don't mind to be represented by Bolt.ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saw skimpily dressed young lady in town in Mthatha today. Curiously, people who were giving her more disapproving looks were other females. ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Traffic at sprawling Qumbu. metropole this morning. ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# were dreaming if they thought people who shouldn't be here running around committing crime would be ignored by suffering South Africans. Now they're being overshadowed by gatvol South Africans they're making half-hearted attempts to deal with illegal immigrants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mugabe abused Tsvangirai for dictatorship reasons. ðŸ˜‰ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Please make #USER# your ambassador. He consumes millions of litres of your product. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's a deep rural area. People don't rent since there's no direct employment. They all survive on subsistence farming. The only time my sister moves closer to town is when she sells excess produce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# New Zealand cricketers always freeze in front of Aussie cricketers. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Useless African politicians are costing this continent so much sporting talent. Every African leaving Africa takes future generations with them. All sporting events are full of African kids and kids with strong African ties representing other countries outside continent. ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Room this expensive must come with chartered plane. ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still have reservations with use of bowlers as captains. I know Pat Cummins did well in recent #HASHTAG#. Once side they captain start leaking runs, they get lost. Shaheen Afridi is struggling to deal with Multan batsmen. They haven't taken a single wicket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kass Naidoo thinks Indian cricketers are super noisy. I guess she has never listened to Sri Lankan cricketers. ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This time of the year in particular is tough for some families. They're stuck with visitors from hell who're taking "feel at home" a bit too far. ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Askies, BeBe and CeCe Winans before I get killed. Ashford and Simpson. Apologies. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# just use your influence and end Load Reduction in Soweto for paying neighborhoods, we'll help you get rid of Khongi once and for all in 2024. If you don't, Sowetans will stay at home just like they did recently. #USER# must go to hell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Change gender son then we can talk. You must better look good after that to attract me. ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Idiots like him shouldn't even be participating in discussions like these. They have nothing to offer. Imagine if black South Africans were as savage as he portrays us. There would be no white folks left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It gets progressively worse as you go towards Coffee Bay itself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shardul Thakur is very dangerous with bat. Get him out quickly. ðŸ¤žðŸ¤ž. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My grannies never beat me up but they template with rules of dos and donts. Stern words are stronger than physical punishment. Being no nonsense parent doesn't mean beating children. He's confirming exactly what is wrong with this country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ladies maar!! We once translated tons of documents for a lady who wasn't sure of her isiXhosa. I did 80%. Two female colleagues did 20%. It turned out she paid them and they never bothered to tell me or give me my share. One let it slip years after. One can joke about it now.ðŸ™†â€â™€ï¸ðŸ™†â€â™€ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moron who was offended by #USER# likes and retweets shows just how much these mini dictators can spoil social networks. How does one get offended by what stranger does or say? ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I like them actually. If they were human, they would be quite eccentric. They look very silly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just watch Human Rights Commission going to court to demand illegal immigrants nabbed by Patriotic Alliance yesterday be set free. They will go back bolder and cause more mayhem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greed has been so entrenched in SA, people are even prepared to destroy our country for patronage. Tenders were a problem from day one. Criminals masquerading as revolutionaries are wreaking havoc. ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He looks like he's appearing on identity parade. Oyena mrhanelwa simrhanela sonke ngulo uphethe intlanzi. ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yandohlula loo nto ndiseseprimary. I don't remember any of my books with plastic cover. I was very useless at it. ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 's Khongi unity is exploding on his face. To think he dumped South Africans for that futile exercise. Shame man!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We're paying the price for not holding incompetent politicians to account. Sisulu would've been sacked long time ago in countries where accountability is treasured. She can't even point to any achievements.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 year old resident is pressing all the wrong buttons this morning. Judging by niece's voice she's getting frustrated with each passing minute with him. When he does this, it does not usually end well but he does not learn. ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚. Let's see how you count millions of illegal immigrants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'll pretend I didn't hear that until I receive my apology at 17h00. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ema hanyane papa. Re na le mathata we need to her to sort first. Ema pele ka bontle.ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bumrah gets Malan. Hardy boytjie. Well played. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Khongi's strategy is beginning to lose steam. They would lie to us and then delegate noisy drama queens like Mbaks, Mokonyane, Bheki Cele, Pemmy Majodina, etc to hoodwink us by making all the right noise. South Africans are slowly waking up. ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All SA biggest political parties are reluctant to deal with illegal immigrants because they also benefit. Illegal immigrants are convenient cheap labour for them and their electorate. Poor and working class neighborhoods have to deal with crime wave perpetrated by some of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You need to be a test purist to appreciate players like him, Rahul Dravid, Cheteshwar Pujara, Kallis, Chanderpaul, Kraigg Brathwaite, etc. They don't appeal to everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# These are scars we're left with as family members when our loved ones get killed. I feel her. I a deep way. Before thinking about killing someone, think about their families. ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sis Nomfusi was more after me. I bought mine at Roadhouse where Engen garage is and Phumlani. If I'm not mistaken she has ties kwaJwacu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Spare a thought for me as a neighbour. One time I was speaking to daughter and her isiZulu speaking friend. She kept on switching to SeSotho when addressing me. I was tempted to tell her my isiZulu beyond fine. I was speaking in isiZulu with her friend. Very confusing. ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Those people can defend ultra, extreme right wingers known for terrorizing defenceless black people. They'll find reasons as to what those unfortunate souls did to offend that racist moron. ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Andibukelanga. He's still trying to act insane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ama2000s mawayekwe. Ahamba odwa. Struu God. I've seen two girls in early teenage years eKhwezi. One said to the friend "umntu makabe specific uba ubone ntoni, ituwa okanye umntana". I don't know what they were talking about but that comment was alarming enough for me. ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No one can explain exactly why our country is crumbling, but it is crumbling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I'm also his biggest fan. Some players grow up in international cricket. QDK, Kallis and Boucher grew up in international cricket and got better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all know what bad behavior is. Strangely, people will always seek to explain bad behavior by their favorite politicians because in their eyes, they can do no wrong. ðŸ™„ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My late dad had difference of opinion with other man while drinking at home in Harding. He left to fetch something. He came back with lots of sticks used in stick fighting and pellet gun. He put all them down and decided to bite the guy instead. What a waste of energy.ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They have same problem of illegal immigrants from Latin America in the south who're prepared to take any pay. Farmers in that area are taking advantage of that that situation. Farmers in LP, NW, MP and FS are known to do that as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smaller keepers like Jorge Campos, Fabian Barthez, Badra Ali Sangare can surprise you with their agility. There was attempt I was sure was sneaking above Sangare last night but he punched it over the bar. #HASHTAG# take a bow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# People want to be left alone with illegal immigrants employees because they exploit them and they can't complain. Farmers in NW &amp; LP are doing that. When workers complain about pay &amp; living conditions, they threaten to turn them in at Home Affairs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is first #HASHTAG# with our Patrice Motsepe at the helm. Let's see what happens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africans of all races know exactly how to co exist until some racist moron or fake Pan Africanist on social networks tell us we shouldn't co exist. Sun City is a proof.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When everything else fails, act insane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of Africa's greatest musicians in my book. Forever missed Noli. 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I still haven't recovered from being blocked by association by Mrs Letsholonyane. She went berserk and blocked everyone who tweets about football regularly. I was blocked for knowing #USER#. I wanted to disown him but it was too late. ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Along with our former world heavyweight champion Corrie Sanders. ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I took wrong turn in Mngungu when I visited my sister in December. I only realized when I drove into a river. I was mad because I had walked on that path many times when I lived in Makwantini down the road. I felt silly and embarrassed. ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Some people on social networks don't go anywhere. I've met wonderful people of different races on my travels. Sadly, I've also met few scumbags across different races.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EC people are very strange. They know all the looters. They know all corrupt people. They know all people stifling service delivery ephondweni. Come election time, they actually separate them from their Mandela / Tambo ANC. They go and vote for Khongi. ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Same people who go around talking about WMC have destroyed businesses belonging to people of different races, including black people. It's just anarchy.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>