<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Does that mean she's incapable of acting responsibly?

Probably - remove her.

Then let her constituency decide if they want to re-elect her.

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Getting stats created from multiple sources is much easier than people think, I still have to wait a week after month end for telecom data, and that's computerised. I'd give up on the people tested data, just be sure the trends are still headed the right way and we are good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Last night there were more out on our road.
I join in because I like to show my appreciation and because I get to meet the neighbours (at 10 feet plus)  who normally I never get to meet.
It's building a community spirit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just signed the petition calling on the government honours committee to knight #USER# for his extraordinary achievements and phenomenal fundraising for the #HASHTAG#. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The summary of the majority of Tory Cabinet tweets are :- 

"We took the bait and spouted hate"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Face coverings are a game changer too.

Staying home, you can't catch it if you don't go out.

We've mass gatherings here (protests) when you talk about their stupidity - people think you are racist - No, I'd just like them to live.

I'm promoting #USER# for #HASHTAG# mayor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Sturgeon: May election move 'huge miscalculation' #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not joining - I'll just keep away from everyone, so I'm not needed to be included. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The latest The Simon Hamer Daily! #URL# Thanks to #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hospitals are making excuses.

We have a friend who has a lump and is just getting fobbed off using Covid as the excuse.
Cancer op's should be proceeding normally.
We're in the East Midlands, low risk of Covid here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hugh Grant needs to understand AZ vaccine is the only one that does not rip off the public. It may not fit with his fixed view, but it is still valid for use #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# His day job is a Scorched earth consultant, he's just not used to working at heights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Honestly Who really goes M&amp;S to shop today? 20 years ago M&amp;S supplied great goods at premium prices - today - it's a boring place to shop at inflated prices. Get back to work - agree - but don't think Covid is a part of this - it's NOT. Next replaced M&amp;S for clothes 10 yrs ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - 'Virus-fighting' scientist gets magnets stuck in nose #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great bit of common sense to the situation #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL# Good luck on your new life. Living in the transport mobility hub and the educational centre of Europe has its drawbacks, it is not for everyone. With 100K Chinese coming here to study we were bound to suffer a big effect from Covid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Make sure you change the start bit to 44, and knock off the zero for your number.

Preferably use your mobile.

Straight forward for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news to see #USER# tweeting humour again on twitter. Looked him up and found out his husband is many years younger. So in solidarity, I announce officially today that my wife is now her WiiFit age of 26 #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Former Speaker John Bercow expensed £1,000 taxi fare #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deaths per million in Europe - "but we're doing so badly" Europes third biggest population, but we're not third - there's several real economies doing much worse.

Elsewhere in the EU #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep, Richard, I agree - we are punishing various parties because many people do not give a flying f~ck about anybody else but themselves. When you add to that we've done more tests than France and Spain combined, the realisation comes out, ppl do not really care. 20% isolate ?? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well done, a love this balanced view on figures.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sad to hear of your issues, it could be the lack of posting brings you up on their radar issues.

Bots are quite often set up in advance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - European elections: How disinformation spread in Facebook groups #URL# Unlike the house price drops and mass unemployment forecast by the remain campaign]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Molly - we all try to act surprised by his "thought" patterns, because it is sad for him that he'll put himself at risk, along with all those he cares about.

Sadly, in reality, we are all not at all surprised. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sensible opposition -the UK is not going to get it - labour either splits or reforms - it is not effectve.

Lib Dems - the words have lost all meaning.

Accept Boris, just get him aligned with what we want, and he'll deliver. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine being so deluded that you as a single member state believe you control the whole of the EU, and states that have just left the EU.

It is called doing a #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Give it your full support then.
Answers below
Regarding civil liberties - most people use Google for search and Google hoovered up wifi passords on Streetview

Data is already exposed and collected by Google.

The risk of this app is 1% or less of what is already on their phones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the AZ effect Europe needs to wake up and start using the AstraZeneca vaccine as we do, first doses first, then 2nd doses at 12 weeks later #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Iran plane downing: Person who filmed video 'arrested' #URL# you cannot do anything in Iran unless Iran's leaders approve it first, especially if you are a woman #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Rubbish - I love to hear about what is happening to a Turkish pop group]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# labour must accept there is no trust in Jeremy as labour leader #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# and I'm accused on here of being brainwashed #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "negotiations"

#URL#

The line from "Love Actually" comes to mind - ending in David Beckham's right foot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Scotland needs to remember - the English will judge the Scots if they continue to vote for the SNP whilst the English prop up their pathetically managed devolved Gov't - education, police, economy .... to join the EU ... that's falling apart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve please stop posting the truth - people who refuse to see it will have a meltdown. We have took after their view of virtual reality, which is "we are still in the EU". #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What about the

"just by staying at home we are saving lives"

Did you conveniently forget the bit of great advice in there?

Your tweet is disingenuous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Could it be that people don't agree with you supporting Trump, and just decided not to listen anymore?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The latest The Simon Hamer Daily! #URL# Thanks to #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, Gary we are - it is called a referendum + election result. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The MSM - it came from them.

That is why the public are cancelling contracts and switching off.

However, just like labour, they are still not listening.

MSM "You will adopt my opinion"

No no no .... we will not, our life, our choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# your response is trying too hard to make a point out of 1 of hundreds and thousands of posted items #HASHTAG# as if everything else was checked first #HASHTAG# it was posted before they approved it, they just changed it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is suggesting "Who to follow" that I follow someone from the media that openly spits at other people. Your thoughts? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# Mine are "NO, thank you for your suggestion" 🤣]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# List of lists List tasks/projects/goals/admin/finance Work same hours as at work. Take breaks Hydrate Have a window open for fresh air Read emails ONLY at start, after lunch, mid afternon - add to lists. PLAN PLAN PLAN Hug loved ones during breaks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The latest The Simon Hamer Daily! #URL# Thanks to #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read it and get educated you #HASHTAG# stuck in a mind rut people. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently we cannot get Europeans for childcare and social media jobs in the UK. #HASHTAG# 

I guess they are too busy closing off their borders. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Karina, we went to our local fish and chip shop last week, staff had no masks on, 3 of 5 of the other customers calling while we waited did not wear masks (one of them had a diabetic wife). We all need to act with care - where idiots persist there'll be regional punishment. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16M UK twitter users, under 9K tweets with Deborah in them, and a lot of them are about a scientist in the USA.

Your idea does not have traction, we're out ... of the EU, and you need to accept it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Brexit shutdown slashes UK car production by 45% #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A doctor writes about supermarkets and panic buying #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 18 days is more realistic - but you know Piers - he's not realistic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Get new/virus software installed.
Run a check.

Could be your phone is hacked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Summary

Our salaries and biased opinions are more important than pensioners incomes.

How about an app to load into all smart TV's that blocks all that is needed so its no longer needed for pensioners? Anyone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boomer Remover and Nigel Pearson (born in 1963) in the top 5 trends on the same day #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So there's a shortage of PPE (inc masks) for the NHS according to the BBC - and the BBC first question tonight is "should the public be wearing masks?" Why do they not understand the NHS need masks, much more than the public #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Switch off the media

just don't listen or watch the media

Talk to your friends, family and neighbours.

we don't actually need the media

Try it, it is fun #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's a state of mind
Trump occupying your head

Time will prove I'm right ............. and that Trump failed all of USA for 4 years.

PS I vote conservative in the UK, it is different over here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC discussing the break up of the UK, 11.50 on the BBC NEWS

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Coronavirus doctor's diary: The strange case of the choir that coughed in January #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - France to introduce digital tax in new year #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BLM, and "I won't wear a mask" protests during lockdown
University student parties
Let's say 60% of identified only are self isolating

The human race is too stupid to make a #HASHTAG# worthwhile, it will make no difference apart from closing off incomes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust an idiot with a dogma running free in his head to not read the facts. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daily update - we were 2 weeks behind Italy roughly - improvement?

Italy Active        UK total
Cases               cases
7th  - 5061       5018    21st
8th  - 6387       5683    22nd
9th   - 7985       6650    23rd
16   - 23073
22nd - 46638]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then Germany has issues with people taking it seriously, as do all Europe, including the UK.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Trending with Good Morning Britain Today's oxymoron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world is falling apart - but the wine rack is full at Aldi Come on idiots Stop buying toilet paper - buy wine - you all deserve a really bad hangover for depriving the needy of what they need. Nice friendly security guard in Aldi - searching for morons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I worked with a lass from this branch of Midland Bank 1970's, it floods, her first days work was ironing notes dry. You can imagine her Mum's reaction on going home. "What did you do today?" "I was ironing the money" "Wow, they take a lot of care there"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[following policies that the majority disagree with and still expecting to get the majority vote. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labour's problems are simple.

1. They don't represent the majority views
2. They don't have a collective view of where they are headed
3. They have MP's that would not be able allowed to  represent any other party
4. They are the party of division and hate #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meat packing plants a big place for #HASHTAG# to spread!

Why is that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you blink, and you fly into a banana, and you can't get it off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - UK unveils new special visa for Hong Kong's BNO holders #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't look for it either, it just pops up in replies on others tweets. What bothers me most, is that it is posted with a, "look how nasty I am" badge of pride to their followers. I was saying to my other half last night, there seems a swing towards normalising hate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which pandemic hypocrite is interviewing me tonight? Or am I being interviewed by a biased left wing organisation? Where do I go for my eyesight test? Who was testing my PPE was in date before I took over and what was their job and for how long?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Remember Bots must not interact.

Yellow Card]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Theresa May 'cannot support' government's Brexit bill #URL# shock horror #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Well they should know they can buy a pint from the supermarket at less cost, is that your point ?
#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Balanced opinion is still needed

Your tweet is not a balanced opinion.

He's one of the few "leaders" that willingly puts other peoples' lives at risk - repeatedly

Agree we shouldn't let Covid rule our lives and I don't,  but I'll not be risking others to make a political point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You are living in the past from about 4 years ago. Brexit is the will of the people. If you don't like it, you still have to learn to accept it. It has already happened we left the EU Take the sensible and pragmatic approach of moving on with your life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# stay strong - don't let them bother you, which I'm sure you do not, it can be difficult for people having to stay in and perhaps they're getting tetchy - but you should not feel the brunt of their boredom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# thanks Mats.

I'll be a bit more upbeat than most folks,  I might moan about them moaning though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Coronavirus: Why this self-isolating dad told his daughter he was in Africa #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Quick inform the MSM, they'll want to let the UK know what you have discovered as they have not seen it yet.

Just kidding - they don't care they are behind this unsettling feeling amongst those that still listen to their utterances.

Thankfully the public still thinks ....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Has the Former Director of Public Prosecutions fired her from labour as an MP yet?

No, he's been writing a column for VE day in the papers 

He's joined the MSM instead because they are so popular right now, as is rejoining the EU  🤣🤣]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wow

That must mean there's a new industry of cannon manufacturing, supported by coal smelting of iron from melting down disused planes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# In fairness Frances, you would need to find a slightly drunk conservative to give balance.

It is not a look they're going for right now.

After 31st December there will be millions.

😂😂🤣🎂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not been on here for about 2 weeks, not missed it.
If there were #HASHTAG# a new app for delivery of food would have had a 10% rise on the day.
We shop late in the day, the shelves are still full enough of food for everything anyone needs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Would there be any secret service left? 

he'd infect them all, by illegal drive arounds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It is actually dropping faster.
In one week it has gone from about 7000 cases to about 5600 cases, that's a 20% reduction.
ONS figures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America and the UK are seperated by a common language. Here are some examples

Chips
Pants
Period
Crisps
Cookies
The right to bear arms
Conservative

Add any more you can think of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tests France 1.384M
Tests UK 9.4M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC Sport - Wimbledon 2017: Ilie Nastase says organisers are 'small-minded' #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Tata Steel: Job fears at Port Talbot over furnace plan #URL# Another clueless Kinnock, who travelled under lockdown. Was he doorstepped?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Richard, I'm in Wales, I can see how little respect how ppl have for other ppl.
Leicester has a labour mayor, and 3 central Labour MP's and they'd no idea of the sweat shops?
There is a common denominator!
#HASHTAG#
The Economy will bounce back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So come on, whose turn is it to roll.
Do it quickly

2020 must be stuck in Jumanji mode]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stuff by sea, is only allowed from the EU. It is not from the rest of the world, because that is so much smaller. There's a 4 day delay in decision making in Scotland and Wales, caused by a disease of the mind called political posturing. It dies out gradually after elections]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government of China: Get the world to stop Chinese animal markets - Sign the Petition! #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you remember when we learned the leader of Nottingham City Council earned more than the Prime Minister? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - North Korea: Trump and Kim call each other mad #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There'a a #HASHTAG# hey Carrie, how about we get married whilst they are wasting their time attempting to be upset about what we do to keep them safe."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Solar panel imports 'harm US producers' #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Data breach hits agency overseeing White House communications #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learned nothing from 10 years unelected as the party to govern the country. Try the tories will destroy the health service - next Try white girls will never get raped under our leader - next Try knife crime has dropped in London - next Try we won the argument Try another vote #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Emerson Lake and Palmer
Wishbone Ash
Uriah Heep
Black Sabbath
Abba
Cool and the Gang
Rod Stewart
Clifford T Ward
Al Stewart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# and the control continues - try controlling German banks first]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Your first drink outside the house in about a week will taste strangely odd, then you'll remember this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have a fish and chip shop near us, the staff don't wear any PPE, so we have not bought from there in the last 6 months
People will choose with their feet whether or not there are passports. If we do not feel safe, we won't go

Passports or not ppl will need to feel safe #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Speedy recovery to all, Richard.

Sending best wishes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We'll always be top of the Covid cases chart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fixed attitude - happy to accept a block. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If it has taken this long to choose wearing face coverings, I'll happily wear one because I know that decision will not have been made unless it was needed.
Enough of people being upset because they just do not like something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG looks like I'll not be able to roam on my mobile phone in the EU. Oh wait I never go to the EU on holiday #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Watching Bloomberg - the idiots blamng WHO when he did zero in February.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The latest The Simon Hamer Daily! #URL# Thanks to #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 29 days we won't have to listen to #HASHTAG# anymore. Today's funny was listening to a health expert from the EU trying to say we've made a bad decision not waiting for the EMA, after receiving streamed information on the vaccine since 9th October. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - FBI Director James Comey 'terminated' by Trump #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The media is being exposed for the two dimensional thinking it likes to portray, that in normal circumstances it gets away with, without criticism because we are all at the day job.
Yesterday Sky said the tubes were full - rubbish - see my earlier post about a friend in London]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great thread Robert, as a leaver, and what they call a Gammon on here, with hundreds of both Lidl and Aldi over here and their commitment to build more stores, I decided the food shortages we could suffer, can be supplied by these EU based companies. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Still gets her MP's salary - I would guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Read their timeline

Take a view - your choice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Iran plane downing: Second day of protests turns up heat on leaders #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# "Right turn Clyde"

Happy Birthday

"Feel lucky punk" you should do, you reached 90 and lived it well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The latest The Simon Hamer Daily! #URL# Thanks to #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's your take on reality.

I'm actually on dry land, and it is a century on.

i suggest you catch up wth life as it is now.

Ships no longer barge into icebergs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The latest The Simon Hamer Daily! #URL# Thanks to #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# when you cannot find a hot tin roof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'd guess it was just another failed left campaign against those that love Europe but do not believe in the EU.

Welcome back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# is good for what?

Catching / Passing on Covid to your friends &amp; relatives
Getting a criminal record for attending an illegal event
Destroying your future career

Black lives matter but be aware, all attending are acting like morons in the midst of a pandemic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Loads of people wanted the test and trace system. They demanded it was put in place. Now it's a waste of money. If only it had not caused the pingdemic we'd all now be happy, yes? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Part 1. I will respect the referendum Part 2. I will try and frustrate the outcome Part 3. I will vote against the outcome Part 4. I will lose the whip Part 5. I will no longer be an MP You could predict this in a spreadsheet #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Donald Trump suggests delay to 2020 US presidential election #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Just like you, I know there's a strategy to derail Boris, but after listening him tonight I felt warm in my heart. With Cameron I felt confidence but not warmth. Boris brings people together, it is a rare trait. He rarely criticises, even the Daily Mail bloke he just corrected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Coronavirus: Cummings attended meetings of key scientific group #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to love Richard and Judy telling it as it is #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just switched over from Beth Rigby on Sky News to Pointless - was it a subconcious link by my mind?

Probably

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't think any SNP supporters follow me. Unless it is based upon hating the English, the "logic" of wanting to leave the UK, to join the EU is lost on me, as we prop up their finances, and the EU does not want them to join.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voted for Brexit
I've been to Hong Kong
Would be totally happy to have 3M Hong Kong people find their new home here.

Yep, still love Europe
Watch France24 for news, Bloomberg for finance. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My guess is the vaccinator got some air in the vile. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ian, you've successfully out talked me.

I'll sign off now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The guy is very busy with the Covid pandemic, I guess Fauci has given him a call while the golfing is going on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - French election: Macron 'most convincing' in final debate #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, my sister volunteers in a hospice.
We look after our mum - mostly my sister.
Please pass on our thanks to you daughter - we truly appreciate her work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Think yourself lucky.
In France they are not testing at all.
Numbers of 1.384 M has been the same for at least two weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daily update
As of 9am on 2 April 2020, 163,194 people have been tested, of which 33,718 were confirmed positive.

As of 5pm on 1 April 2020, of those hospitalised in the UK who tested positive for coronavirus, 2,921 have died.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# bit easier in this one - the bonus was a bat doing loops, but no photo of that #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not quite so much panicking in Mansfield, as there is elsewhere.

I've had no issues either, did a bit of shopping when I went to collect my prescription on Friday night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make sure you do the 3 most important things in your day first. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use 111 to speed up the process of getting it checked. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #URL# 

looks like she just was not aware of them, that's called a lack of racism when you don't notice the colour of the people around you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - More going bust as personal borrowing surges #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's see how we compare to Italy

I'll update daily

Italy Active cases       UK total cases
4th March - 2706       2626    18th March
5th March - 3296       3269    19th
6th March - 3916       3983    20th
12 March - 12839
19 March - 33190]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The Queen holds the Trump card though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They were going to get the Apple Settlement off you somehow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scotland's choices
1. Run by Alex Salmond then #URL#
2. Run by Nicola Sturgeon now #URL#
3. Run by Boris and possibly then
4. Run by EU #URL#

🤔 #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to Trump ... nodded off

It is a script - he understands nothing of the pain of his people.

"Almost ever body's out now"
"Going to be a very painful two weeks"
"I know New Jersey so well"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The latest The Simon Hamer Daily! #URL# Thanks to #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sending best wishes to all of the USA on the sad  anniversary of 9/11

I can still remember watching the second plane hitting the towers after I picked the kids up after a night shift, and saying to our kids child minder, this is a planned attack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have one sixth of all Chinese students over 100K in the UK, major airports, open borders, and we have cramped public transport.
Spain March 19
Italy Autumn 19
Skiing in Italy in January
We'd no chance.
PS France is not testing 1.38M tests #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sturgeon - not understanding the meaning of the EU acting slowly and the UK acting quickly, and "we'd work quickly with the EU". #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Joined in July 12
Your profile requires an update.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If there's #HASHTAG# in their user name, I just block them.
They refuse to accept democracy and therefore deserve to be ignored and marginalised.
UK had 2 votes on leaving the EU, the referendum and the Dec 2019 election. 3 and a half years to make their case and still we voted leave]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definitions of an oxymoron

Corbyn's momentum
Labour leadership
EU negotiations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No, I'm way to cheap for them to challenge it.

Moto : Keep them low = keep them long.

However, my industry is much simpler than most.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daily update - we were approx 2 wks behind Italy - see thread - are we parting ways?

Italy Active        UK total
Cases /dead       cases/dead
12th 12839          26th  11658
13th 14955/1266  27th  14579/1019
14th 17750          28th  17089
19   - 33190
27th - 66414]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Ed Miliband tells Labour conference: We're the one-nation party #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The latest The Simon Hamer Daily! #URL# Thanks to #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The real world is neither on here, or on Facebook.

Facebook thought labour would win the last election, and would remain in Europe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# and if labour had continued in power - the debt created above would have looked quite small. Corbyn still wants to borrow and tax.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe's people are probably queueing to vote #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So I guess you think it is responsible for French to allow boats to cross one of the busiest shipping lanes in the world in the dark. It is not me, that is not making sense. Get a sense of realism. They are putting these people at risk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Similar to Kier Starmer going into a pub then? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you vote for indyref2 Sturgeon will ensure there'll be no more thundersnow - a source has told me 😉 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walked into town yesterday to pay cheques in, deliver franked mail and get some exercise, walking through the park for safety (extra space) and saw 6 youths playing football on the 5 a side pitch.
You can't fix stupid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labour "I'm not going to stand here and Pretend"
Are you sure, you are not pretending to be an effective opposition?

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you on twitter?
Response was laughter.  
He's not on twitter.

I understand that response]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Except Belgium has that score per death per million, followed by either Italy or Spain - parody account information supplied by an idiot trying to make a point. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# As you say - we can't - but we owe it to the public to enjoy as much of their lives as we can, but sadly we finally have to say - we can't trust you to look after others, so we are shutting pubs. Found this surprising her drink could kill her if he ... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Marcus was born in 1997, as Blair hit power. Labour were in power until 2010, by which time he'd be almost 13.

He joined the Man Utd academy from the age of 7.

Source - wikipedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two men have had enough, and decide to fly into space to go for a short break to get away from the stupidity of the human race.

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# France24 actually reports news.
It is like the BBC from 30 years ago.
Worth a try.

PS I voted for Brexit, but still love Europe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If so France, Germany, Spain and Italy are way ahead of the UK, looking at the present numbers of serious and critical ill patients.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Happy Brexit Christmas Jo, loved your 12 days of Brexit on your tweets.

FYI - my anecdotal research on watching Covid stats would say, several EU countries (including the Czechia Netherlands) sadly probably already have the mutated virus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish there was something relevant I could say in this crisis ... oh yes Stay Home Whilst out/shopping stay 2 metres apart Wash Your hands Save lives Job done. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#ー19uk #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sofie Ridge is always confused. She never understands when numbers are dropping every week, in deaths, in hospitals, in ICU, and in infections that the R must be below 1. Why not Sofie, is it not clear to you? It is to the rest of us. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fell asleep in a Meat Loaf Concert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peston quoting twitter now - that's journalism dead then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To give a bit more clarity - for others Mike #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The latest The Simon Hamer Daily! #URL# Thanks to #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Connect online.
Talk over the garden fence - at a distance.
As I've done tonight put out two neighbours bins - one witn a cararact, one with serious illness.
Be creative - try it.
Don't complain just think about it.
Offer your car to a #HASHTAG# carer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Watching from across the pond, it looks as if Trump owns America 

He is accountable to no one!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's strangest from mix from UK trends combination Bernie and Del Boy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Is that how you view Switzerland and Norway?
I think the EU actually disagrees with your "opinion"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree - we should vaccinate the elderly in the rest of the world before our kids.

Ex parent governor #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Looking at how quickly we got over the banking crisis caused by a lack of proper regulation of the banks (Canada and Australia had no banking crisis), I think 7 years would do it.

But that's OK you can just believe in the gloom that suits your narrative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Your follower ratio says your tweets are garbage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - What is a rating agency? #URL# Answer, somebody that rates others that we don't rate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She can't even get his name right 😂😉👇

Her followers will be devastated, because they were relying on her for a factual report (that's sarcasm by the way) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Warnings

Enough said]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Leicester looks like people are really annoyed with 5 labour MP's that broke lockdown. Not to mention the SNP MP Ian Blackford #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Apart from saying Tax Exile in your original tweet - #HASHTAG#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>