<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful #USER#!  

You are an Inspiration Eric! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ole #USER# did and got beat...

52 - 7! 

The Stanford Football Program no longer exists after 3 Years of Candy Ass Practices and Non-Existent Strength and Conditioning...it's just Candy Asses, Lazy Asses, Arrogant Asses and a Disgrace to #USER# University!

#HASHTAG# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here's the link to Stricklin press conference....

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really #USER# #USER#?

Be Thankful Total Candy Ass like Joe Biden is #USER# and surrounded by #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# because #USER# President...

We have your asses in Oval Office demanding to know why #USER# poisoning Sailors and their Families! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 2007 - 2009 ran into Joe Judge in Alabama some event and talked kid 15 minutes or so and walked away thinking...

"Something's not right about that Ole Boy!"

Look up few years later and he's on Belichick's staff #USER# then #USER# Head Coach for God's sake!

Gump Smarter! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18.5% in America?  

Pro Tip to Men Just Getting Married &gt;

Keep your own checking account and have your paycheck deposited into it and if Wife pays bills transfer what she needs to her account so she can pay em!  

No reason for wife to know it costs $600 to play Pebble Beach! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ole Napier opening up with Utah and Kentucky ain't no joke #USER# and then at Vols in Week 4!  

We'll go #USER# 7 - 4 or 6 - 5 headed to Tallahassee to play FSU on November 25! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hell the #HASHTAG# BBQ joint in this list bunch of 20-somethings in Ft. Worth!  

Best thing about this #USER# piece of BBQ Joints is if you have a dream to open a BBQ place or anything else go chase that dream! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bowling Green Massacre will go down in American political history right along with Pocahontas #USER# is a Native American = #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This like Fantasy $$$ Train and Manna from Heaven for these Bastards and plenty Damn Morons line-up around the block to do whatever the folks in Power tell em to do!  

Our Doctors telling us...

If you healthy these Booster Shots not needed...2 Shots give you lots of immunity #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also Aggies lost to LSU which fired their Head Coach weeks before and was down about a dozen players when they played and if Bryan Harsin had the Common Sense of a Ground Squirrel he run the ball against Bama and Tigers beat Saban too!

Wake boat raced Aggies without DC and QB! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Sherman quality guy who not gonna walk out on his team still chance play in #USER# even if Mike terrible hire for A&amp;M!

People in Louisiana just don't realize what a Total Disaster hire that Brian Kelly is...but they will in the coming months #USER#! 

#HASHTAG# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Batshit Crazy Lunacy! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you get down into the weeds of mathematics and physics of the Universe one thing you find is that there's...

Helluva Lot We Cannot Explain

...and Thomas Edison still right&gt;

“We don’t know a millionth of one percent about anything.”

We still in the cave without Damn Clue! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yall seen this Bosa kid play?

Un-Blockable!  

Just a Freaking Football Player! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Touchdown LSU! 

This is all for fun with Coach O already run and Hell...Tigers might beat A&amp;M next week! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like a 3-Wood and have hit a Driver on 16th at Cypress Point a couple of times into the wind! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It be Abraham Lincoln and Oh Boy do have lots of questions for Abe!  

Lincoln only 56 years old when assassinated but entire 20th Century been different including outcome World War 2 if he not kept Union together...without unified American Republic hard whip Hitler and Hirohito #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine getting Florida Football Coaching job and NOT...

Attacking Each Day with an Enthusiasm Unknown to Mankind!  

You only get 1 shot in life and your ass HC at Florida and you known as...

Lazy Ass Dan Mullen!

Your ass should be fired....Fire Dan Mullen's Lazy Ass today! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This over in the East Bay of San Francisco! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're under 65 and relatively healthy your chance of dying from Corona Virus if Un-Vaccinated...

.01%

If you're under 65 and relatively healthy your chance of dying from Corona Virus if Vaccinated....

0.00003%

We sitting in the 0.0003% group and others will roll the dice! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Dabo just land on Earth from Pluto?

Your ass is making $10M a year Son...you think they paying you that kind of money to educate kids or win football games and if you don't know the answer get on that rocket ship back to Pluto! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George #USER# Damn Moron only he's not as Public about being a Damn Moron as the last Worthless Loser #USER# Commish Larry Scott!

No one we know would hire George to Shovel Shit but of course the #USER# Presidents were talked into hiring this Damn Fool!  

#USER# = Morons! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh, that's right...99.9% of "Foreign Policy Elitists" in America NEVER served in the US Military! What a surprise....#HASHTAG#!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask Kagan if he even put on uniform US Military while advocating young Americans be Fighting + Dying all over the world...that would be #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Free Pass of Eligibility for 2020 season still impacting CFB Teams because everyone got extra year to go to school and most these kids not headed to #USER# so why not hang around play football another year and go to college? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure same % of #USER# didn't believe Dumbass Donny was legitimate President for 4 years and you know what that =

All of you Damn Idiots obsessed with Politics 24/7 365 are Deeply Mentally Ill!

Worked 7 yrs #USER# WH...

99% of Wash DC are Total Losers! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #USER# are TOUGH so not surprised they are Favorites! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humor will knockout Dumbass Donny and Hal Riney taught us how to do Great Humor when all of us working for #USER#!

You should see the stuff we already got in the can on Dumbass!

#HASHTAG# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not exactly Ellis Island but send some these folks to Reno, Nevada where we got 30K+ open jobs and we cannot hire people for 3 of our companies for Any Wage + Benefits!  

Surely some these people will work for $25 Hour + Full Benefits including Healthcare Insurance + 401K match! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You got no Damn chance!

Dawgs roll! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ole Bryan Harsin gotta be kicking himself right now!

He been patient at Boise State little doubt he be Washington Head Coach right now and he been on list at USC as well....now he's 6 - 6 at Auburn...got few big AU Boosters ready to run his ass...and needs BIG 2022 to save job! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guessing Putin wants the #USER# to send the Russian Navy to the bottom of the ocean if they think they gonna disrupt sea lanes and it take about 90 minutes for #USER# to sink Entire Russian Navy!

This your chance #USER# move US LNG to Europe in Massive Quantities! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Old Boss #USER# had it Right! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Houston about to roll-up Cincinnati and make all this Foolishness Look Silly and Iowa has great shot at beating Michigan because Jimmy #USER# will be still be talking about beating Buckeyes and "A New Beginning" in the Springtime and Baylor easily beat Pokes so.... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guido is a Fascinating Character but there lots of Fascinating Characters #USER#!  

Trying to reduce "Randomness" in life something we work hard on reducing in Advertising Business because the better we can predict if an ad campaign will succeed or not! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See that #USER# and #USER# drink the same liquors! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wowza!

And forget Jimmy G! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got A Damn Idiot is still running the #USER# even though Larry Scott fired over a year ago? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrible decision by Mac Jones there....he had 2 #USER# WRs wide-open in middle of field and on right sideline!  

Jones makes Fast Decisions but sometimes he makes the Wrong Decision! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #USER# a Damn Mess that new Commish #USER# not going to fix because George a Damn Moron but what would fix #USER#...

Competent Head Football Coaches

Lincoln Riley 
Kalen DeBoer

At USC + Washington nice start but still Lots of Candy Asses like David Shaw at Stanford! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tenderloin area San Francisco been Total Disaster decades...no one cares even with Billions $$$ spent nothing changes. 

What forced us out San Francisco...our younger women employees in 20s and 30s telling us they frightened to go out at night in the City

Shameful #USER# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow...look at this! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This be tossed out of court in about 2 seconds #USER#!

You have Lost the Damn Plot on what life about #USER# because 15+ Desert Storm Vets #USER# know what the Saudis are...

Pure Damn Evil!

Your ass is in bed with Pure Damn Evil Son and shame on you! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ole Mattress Mack! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Sarkisian creating Heroes all over Big 12 Country and word from our Texas-alum buddies in Austin is that Sarkisian has lost control of Horns program and this entire thing could Totally Collapse!  

4 - 6 with...

At West Virginia
Kansas State

....left

Got 4 - 8? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There $100+ Billion US Taxpayer Dollars was sent to Iraq and Afghan that are now in bank accounts around the world and that's just a fraction of the Trillions $$$ that the US pissed into the ocean in the Middle East because we elected...

Very Damn Stupid Beings to Presidency! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we need #USER# these Fascists now running and hosting your show like #USER# think Student Athletes should donate booster clubs get these folks send some their paycheck up to Bristol #USER# because that makes Perfect Damn Sense! #HASHTAG# #USER# actually play CFB? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walk into any Casino and these are Slot Machine Players that sit in front of those machines for hours in Non-Human trance wasting their precious time on this Earth doing something that we cannot fathom...$$$ isn't that important and life is lived doing things not wasting away! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 1 #USER# and beneath all the Craziness Bill was One Helluva Basketball Player! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billions and Billions $$$ of Real Estate and Businesses in US from looted Russian $$$ and the US should have long ago seized that property and tossed those Russians into jail and set them up for trials at the World Court in Hague!

Let's do it right now #USER# #USER#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This never work at our Ad Agency because meetings begin with someone yelling thru bullhorn...

"Meeting....get your asses moving!"

...followed by setting 22 minute timer and then opening up various beers and pouring adult beverages!

When 22 minutes up...we all walk out! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Florida hire 60 year old Bob Stoops to take on Kirby Smart and rest of #USER#? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How does anyone at Syracuse tolerate this Crapola So Poorly Coached Football that Dino Babers is putting on the field?  

This team looks like it has No Coaches At All! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Birdcage #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jim Mora at UConn?

Really?

Bozo the Clown do a better job Edsall but they really need someone at UConn that recruit like Total Madman and knows how to Coach Football and Mora....very marginal work at UCLA! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on now Kirk....Gary Patterson so far behind the times and so stubborn that he knows more that any human on Earth about Defense any AD be Nuts hire Gary and Va Tech AD said he want someone actually embrace the fans...Gary wants them kissing his ass 24/7 365!

Not A Chance! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those folks didn't get to see Jim Valvano coach...kinda like Rick Pitino but Crazier and Jimmy was a funny, funny man!  #USER# 

#HASHTAG# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What it is is what knew about #USER# working on Capitol Hill in late 1980s....

Never Underestimate #USER# Ability To F Things Up!  

Was in Iowa at State Fair working for #USER# in 1987 when Joe quoted Neil Kinnock directly in Dem debate....Just Pure Damn Idiocy! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goodness Gracious....for you Youngins out there is Real Music!  

Great Music + Great Lyrics + Passionately Delivered by the Great #USER#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill O'Brien an Awful Excuse for a Human Being and Coach and as you can see from this #USER# list and Total Joke at evaluating talent but then Trent Baalke GM of #USER# worse than O'Brien so of course he's trying to hire Billy Boy...all in our humble opinion! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also Dovol's fastball has a ton of movement on it and no one could hit it for last 2 months!  

Also you don't have anyone on bench to pinch hit for Flores who was 0 - 17 lifetime against Scherzer?  

It's just Damn Idiocy Choking at the Most Critical Point of the Season! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved #USER# from first time met him in early 1980s when he did amazing work for #USER# on Capitol Hill...was told many times before shook Senator Dole's hand to put out left hand instead of right since his right arm destroyed in WW2

An American Hero

#HASHTAG# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geez...only 20 years after we put US Military into Afghanistan!nnWhat an Achievement!  #HASHTAG# nnIf #USER# not gotten his ass rolled by Pentagon in 2010 we long ago had US Military out Afghanistan which Helluva Lesson &gt;nnCandy Asses don't know how tell Generals #HASHTAG# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Bet makes Helluva Lot of Sense not that we bet on sports!

Gotta think Buckeyes keep rolling and CRUSH Maryland and Birdie tells us #USER# that Aggies on edge of...

Total Damn Meltdown under Jimbo!  

Aggies may have come up with $75M+ send Jimbo's ass packing next year! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since Auburn probably have interim AD in December 22 #USER# once Harsin fired be tug-a-war between...

We Want Kevin Steele Dumbasses

Common Sense folks want Bill Clark

Let It Rip Folks want Hugh Freeze

In the end the next Auburn Head Coach will be....

Jamey Chadwell! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If #USER# like Donny Boy gonna do nothing but kiss Fascist Thug Xi's ass of course China gonna make a move on Taiwan #USER# #USER# #USER#!

Maybe 2024 folks we find Non-Candy Ass Coward who spends 4 years on knees kissing Fascist Ass around the world?  

#HASHTAG# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What in the world Jay? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Even better on Ohio State - Michigan Game by the Late Great Keith Jackson -----&gt;  

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With some #USER# of course! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never Change Pat Perez! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How about just walking your ass out on the stage and singing #USER#?

This ain't Rocket Science...it's Just Freaking Music! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's Killer of American Cities #USER# &gt;

Whack Job Liberal Nuts who don't want anyone else to live in Cities their asses live in and #USER# San Francisco full of Pure Damn Evil Bastards who Hate Hard Working Folks!

These are Evil Un-American Worthless Bastards! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't think the Future of Democracy in America is at stake because don't think we gonna stay in this 50 - 50 stalemate with both parties running Worthless Loser Hacks like they did last 2 Presidential Elections!

#USER# kicking Dumbass Donny to curb and gonna sweep 2022 and 2024! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walked thru football offices #USER# many times when #USER# Head Ball Coach and it wasn't that much different our High School Coaches offices...been thru Saban's operation #USER# and it's like #USER# franchise on steroids!  

Who in Hell are all these people Nick? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday #USER# You Funny Bastard! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is gonna be a Helluva basketball game! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a Crazy Ass World we are living in! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Judge Total Joke as Head Coach

Daniel Jones Total Joke as #USER# QB

Besides that everything fine with New York #USER#!

Anyone thought or thinks Joe Judge qualified lead a Pee Wee team forget #USER# franchise go immediately to the Closest Insane Asylum...your ass needs help! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you found Stupidest Human Being on Earth he/she not produce these Asinine Rules #USER# but then does anyone think any these folks running CFB Postseason get a job Shoveling Shit if they not working College Athletics?

Didn't Think So!  

Where do we find these Morons? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If #USER# wasn't such a Candy Ass Coward #USER# #USER# #USER# the NSA have team in Europe ready take down entire Moscow electrical grid if Putin makes move on Ukraine but last 5 #USER# Kissed Putin's ass so on knees and Kiss Putin's ass it is! 

It's Damn Disgraceful #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ole #USER# is a Genius... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This kid is gonna be a Helluva #USER# QB! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Shaw been running Crapola Power Puff Practices for 3+ years now

Gary Patterson Too Damn Stubborn change his Pee Wee easily attacked Defense

Chip Kelly's Offense....Whatever!  

Pat Fitzgerald ALWAYS takes off season after Good season....he's a Total Lazy Ass like Mullen! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Francisco is run by Very Evil People who care nothing about the Citizens and especially the Kids of the City or California!

This is The Definining Characteristic of #USER# California...

An Utter Contempt for the People of California! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phil already doing comb over in 1980! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can find the Final Results for this contest here...

#URL#

...and 2 folks tied at...

51 - 29

That's 63.75% Winning % which is Pretty, Pretty Good Picking Against the Spread! 

500 or so entries X $1K = $500K but $1M in Guaranteed Cash Prizes? #HASHTAG# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's just lots Meaningless Exhibition Games expanded because #USER# need programming to sell in December!  Back when few us playing in bowl games 30+ years ago you had to Earn It not fall backassward into 6 wins and yell out..."We're Bowl Eligible!"

Laugh...it's all a Big Joke! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Karl Dorrell really nice guy but we watched his time at UCLA very closely and what happened is when Bruins had TONS of talent it was wasted which led records of...

6 - 7
6 - 6
10 - 2
7 - 6
6 - 6

Colorado NEVER come close have talent UCLA had so recommend Rick have list handy! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What in the world Jay? 

Do you drive a car at someone trying to hit them unless you been drinking alcohol?

What in Hell Jay Son? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If masks made any difference in stopping or getting a virus do you think American Medicine let anyone walk into a hospital and see anyone including cancer patients with no one wearing a mask which case before Pandemic?

Either they Damn Morons or knew masks make no difference! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just what in Hell going on here #USER#?

What kind 2-Bit Podunk #USER# you working at #USER# #USER# this Horseshit going on?

Watching Oregon game Dave Flemming broadcasting over public service channel technology!

Need get Bob Chapek's ass on the phone today! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bury Russia's Asses!  

Bring Russia To Its Knees just like #USER# did the USSR in the 1980s #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#!

As #USER# told #USER# before Desert Storm...

"Don't Go Wobbly Now George!"

Putin handed West opportunity to remake world! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biggest worry about Franklin being hired by USC is moments after his ass moves into his office at John McKay Center he will have his new Fat Boy agent calling around to get his name in mix for other jobs!

Franklin now taking Lunacy to new never seen levels in history of CFB! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating but those us haven't had Corona Virus Test last 18+ months but are 2 Shot Vaccinated many us think we had Corona in Spring 2020 and we had few "episodes" in 2021 after Vaccinated feel down for day or so...maybe had Corona Virus in nose and Vaccination got after it! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas loses at Baylor and Sark drops to 4 - 4 with game at Iowa State up next Steve gonna find out again what the Hot Seat feels like!  Hell with only Kansas left as Sure-Win will Horns even get 6 wins in 2021?

At Baylor
At Iowa St
Kansas
At West Virginia
Kansas St

Hmmmm.... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone spent anytime in Germany knows most Germans would happily submit to Putin or Anyone Else wanted conquer and enslave their asses!

The Germans of today see conflict as something would distract their asses from their Pitiful Petty Lives that they are Self-Consumed about! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love know #USER# who in Hell exactly gonna do all those manufacturing jobs they came back US?

Our asses trying hire for entry level jobs Reno, Nevada at $20+ hour with Full Benefits and we can hardly get anyone come in for interview Son!

We Need Millions New Immigrants! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At your house or street or personally threatened out in public by someone you have every right defend yourself but any our kids loads up gun and goes to where riot going on then...

We have Totally Failed As Parents because we have Stupid Shits think their asses are the Police! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas D this play = Sub Pee Wee! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saying blackface is No Big Whoop is a "gaffe?" nWhy don't we throw out some Obvious As Hell and Slanderous Jewish things and confident you will call them a....Gaffe! #HASHTAG# there Helluva Lot of Folks in media live in a Total Fantasyland!nALWAYS spend time with Normal Folks! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ain't that the Damn Truth!  

Zillion years ago was with date at some fashion show that Dwight and Joe Montana got talked into doing in San Francisco and we backstage after event and thought date was going to attack Dwight right on the spot she melted so much what nice he he was! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rarely seen such a Combination of Arrogance and Incompetence like see with Washington Coaching Staff right now!

Most Coaches know their limitations but what is going on at Washington right now with Jimmy is truly unique...someone needs wake Jimmy up before he gets his as run! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was reading interview Kevin Spacey on film he did Clint Eastwood directing and they film a scene that Spacey thought was just quick run thru and Clint says...

"Action"

Spacey does scene

Clint says...

"Cut.  That's good."

Your ass better be ready to act with Clint = 1 Take! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well take a look at Lance Leipold Records and you see a Football Coach!  The guy won 6 National Titles in 8 seasons at Wisconsin-Whitewater then turned Buffalo into a Winner!  Sark was Average at UW and USC and Bozo put up BIG numbers coaching all that talent in Tuscaloosa! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We haven't talked to Ad Agency client yet who thinks sponsoring a college football player will move 1 item of merchandise but can see in a local market it could build up goodwill and sales!  We tried selling NIL deals for "X" players but no luck yet.  Maybe have 1 in the hopper! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get self-proclaimed "Christians" reacting to rape claims by women like this...who raised these animals...on Briles coaching again #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your ass gives up 41 points if anyone in Media asking about the QB position you know you got...

Lots of Ignorant Folks in the Media!

The 1 Constant when Georgia gets beat is this &gt;

Kirby Smart's Defense Totally Melts Down because...

Kirby Gets Tight and Chokes Game Away! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a world we live in where Fascist Gov'ts build walls...

Keep Their People In

...and America builds walls...

Keep Folks from all over world longing for Freedom + Opportunity out!

Be Thankful your ass lives in place that so many desperately want to live in!

#HASHTAG# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We got so many Damn Idiots taking so many Tests it's hard to do this Deaths to Cases Ratio make sense!

Forget Positive Cases because we got Damn Idiots gonna take Zillion Tests Sick or Not and focus on...

Hospitalization

Deaths

When that goes down that's end of this Pandemic #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How could official standing feet away call that a catch?  We 1,500+ miles away at Lake Tahoe...

Not A Catch!

#USER# officiating ----&gt; #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Michigan #USER# done best summed-up this General Robert Neyland quote &gt;

“Gentlemen, touchdowns follow blocking as sure night follows day”

Just Getting Your Man and maybe block 2nd guy on every play HUGE and few teams CFB do it well in Running or Passing Games today! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revealing story #USER# White Folks California live Most Segregated place in America and go for months never interact with Black person...we took one our Cali White Liberal friends to #USER# game where tons Black Americans living + loving life and he absolutely shocked! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful Day at Neyland! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auburn took over on downs with 2:06 at Alabama 41 yard line with Bama having 2 timeouts.  If you assume 10 seconds for 3 plays that's 30 seconds and then 40 seconds for 1 play no timeout and Bama shoulda gotten it back with...

56 seconds left

Bama got it back with 1:32 left! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We knew by May 2020 this Corona Virus really goes after Older Folks and if #USER# been #USER# we put into place...

Comprehensive Plan Protect 65+ which 75% of US Corona Virus Deaths!

This ain't Rocket Science...just Simple Common Sense and America led by Damn Morons! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just read out your Tweets to guy sitting over in corner of the room drinking coffee watching replay of last Georgia - Alabama game and who used to be #USER# Intel Officer and he says &gt;

Tell that Damn Idiot the US Gov't known Aliens on Earth and they known it since 1950s! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We got Member #USER# made a Helluva Living right after college doing Magic Show at Comedy Clubs around America ----&gt; $100K+ a year easy and he be happy show this teacher Magic indeed does happen in this world...start with putting her in box where he cuts folks in half! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love see Oliver Cromwell transported into 2021 and hear his views on things...now that would be one Damn entertaining rant to watch and just make sure his ass doesn't have any weapons handy!

Hell bring along Charles I along with him...really Hilarious those 2 in 2021! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly!

Biggest Problem in America today we got Parents raising Kids....

Freaking Ignorant about US History and/or Frightened To Death of World!  

So many young folks been convinced we destroying the Earth...this planet be here Billions Years after our asses long gone folks! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta have a Great Quarterback to Win in #USER# and entire organization gotta be focused on getting one you don't have a Great One...and we mean GREAT!

It's Everything!

“Sure, luck means a lot in football.  Not having a good quarterback is bad luck.”  Don Shula #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ole #USER# Best We Ever Seen! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No idea why Colorado State hired Steve Addazio who now...

4 - 10

...in 2 seasons.

No idea what ADs thinking these days but do know they are influenced and listening to some Very Stupid People on coaching hires! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No College Fan Base drinks like...

LSU and Wisconsin! 

Wisconsin tailgating is just LSU North and we been at Wisky + LSU Bowl Games where LSU and Wisconsin fans drank bars out of....

All Their Damn Beer!  

Ask Bartender for beer...

"These Crazy Ass Folks drank all our beer!" #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geez...355?  Hope you got someone spotting you on that #! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Memo to #USER# Management + Ownership &gt;

We told you when we heard you thinking about hiring Joe Judge that we...

Not Hire His Ass To Coach A Pee Wee Football Team

...but then we met this Boy years ago and he's about 100 IQ points short of Forrest Gump!  

Hello Again! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your ass running Business where losing Hundreds of Millions of Dollars a year like many Private and Post-IPO Bio-Tech Companies now doing how anyone think these Legitimate Businesses?

Most like $BLUE are Damn Frauds powered by All $$$ #USER# poured into US Economy! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 handle on #USER# #USER#!

Up 150% in last week and still running!

Crypto Billionaires here we come #USER#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of it is #USER# lost touch with All Reality and just got his ass handed to him because he hasn't a Damn Clue what he is doing or for what he wrote about for years before he got into Politics...starting with the simple word...

Freedom!

The public hates a Hypocrite! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Doctor tells us he wouldn't take this Merck Corona Virus Pill nor would he recommend his patients take it...he's still thinking about Pfizer pill which he is leaning toward recommending which you gotta take first 48 hours you get Corona...read this &gt;

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Might? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when bought $1,000 worth of stocks 1983 in first stock purchase and told some older guy that at Cocktail Party in Washington DC and he says....

"Oh....don't you think stock market just a bubble that will burst soon?"

Invest for Long-Term...Bubble Talk is for Losers! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matt Rhule could command $8M+ a year over 7 years in the College Game this year and know for a FACT a Huge School was willing to pay Rhule that kinda $$$ just a few weeks ago!  

Take the $44M with #USER# or accept $56M guaranteed in college game!  

Rhule is a College Coach! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've lost your mind Son!

If not for Total Dumbasses George W. Bush and Dumbass Donny #USER# have...

Presidency
Senate
House 

...right now because Left full of Whack Job Lunatics and #USER# will have All 3 again after 2024 Election and Dumbass Donny's ass still be in Palm Beach! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Louisville Athletics is just a Damn Mess! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro Tip Son from Folks been going to Auburn Football Games on The Plains for 30+ years &gt;

There is No Bottom To Auburn Football so quit looking for it!

cc #USER# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[+Zillion #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington already had #USER# nephew who looks like he can play to us so better Haener stay his ass in Fresno!  

Huskies gonna be throwing the ball around with tough running game in 2022 and that will be great to see after whatever the Hell UW been running on O last 2 years #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This isn't True...we got about...

1,100 Americans A Day Dying from Corona Virus

...and about...

200 Americans A Day Dying from Drug Overdoses

Both are still Way Damn Too Many!

What we gonna do on overdoses...beg people quit taking drugs that will kill their ass? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sooner these Worthless Baby Boomers gone from American Politics the better! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frightening thing about Riley at LSU is if he can score 40+ points a game with Defensive talent you can attract to Baton Rouge that you can't get in Norman that makes LSU big problem for rest of #USER#! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Solution at this Miami Community Event &gt;

We need to run Manny Diaz's ass right out of Miami! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming back from Reno to Lake Tahoe the other day over Mt. Rose Pass got behind some Candy Ass driving one your #USER# #USER# and thought those cars could handle Son?

Finally his Cowardly Ass pulled over and Yukon got back to business getting back to Lake Tahoe! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you under 50 years old and healthy Survival Rate for Corona Virus =

99.99%

If you under 50 years old and healthy and get Corona Virus Survival Rate for Corona Virus becomes =

99.999%

It's an Insurance Policy and long as they don't go Hospital if they get sick #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can easily see Liberal like #USER# kissing Fascist Thug Ass all around the world #USER#...but #USER# Reagan Conservatives? #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Damn Idiots were saying world was ending 6 months ago because of a Drought!

It's called Weather Patterns which swing wildly in California between Wet and Dry years and even decades and WE KNOWN from climate records it's been that way for....

Millions of Years...at least! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who could have predicted Kirby Smart go 12 - 0 then...

Coach #USER# Champ Game Like A Damn Coward?

We all just watched Pitiful Auburn D shutdown Bama and Kirby goes...

Nahhhhhh....we'll play Candy Ass Defense and be fine!  

Does Kirby have access to Bama's games in 2021? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It also tastes like Crapola! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People trying make getting Freaking Vaccine Shot into "Freedom" issue...

NEVER Serve America in US Military and would run Cowardly Asses to Canadian Rockies we get in real shooting war!

Don't worry...Combat Vets #USER# fight for America...our asses not afraid of a Shot #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 more Great Reasons to Buy #USER#!

#HASHTAG#
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When trading Fixed-Income at Bear for Ace in 1990s the really big equity traders didn't get back to work until after Super Bowl which February 13 this year so hard move market forward without those folks pushing things! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anything and Anyone but the Damn #USER#! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on #USER#...it's time to admit your Love for All Things Vandy and that every time #USER# loses a football game you a little die inside because you are...

Commodore Bill and have room at house full of Gold and Black Vandy stuff including this Vandy Pennant! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohio State played Average Crapola all season = #USER# and 1 Average Team = Oregon Ducks and Ducks...

Whipped their asses in Columbus with their best player!

Any of you actually watch these games or just look at scores...

Ohio State is Average Football Team...so is Michigan! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can add more oil production and should but 90%+ of it be exported since we have plenty of oil in America...all the gas stations have gas...it would eventually bring down price of oil worldwide...eventually like months from now! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ole DA #USER# sending out Violent Thugs to commit more crimes against Law-Abiding Citizens of San Francisco and if you are in SF right now you are not safe...ANYWHERE!

Get on this yet another outrage #USER# #USER#!  

Our hometown destroyed by Pure Damn Idiocy! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ole #USER# seen this?  #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Move your ass out of California! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly...but now #USER# that would take IQ higher than #USER# number!n#HASHTAG# about to HAMMER American farmers and all you Damn Morons voted in #USER# primaries cranked-up this Horseshit can be So Damn Proud! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No doubt and our Grandparents + Parents lived thru most of 20th Century which saw 150M+ die from...

Wars
Viruses
Genocide 
Great Depression 

...which why Our Parents and We with our kids don't tolerate crying over Meaningless Horseshit!

You are living in Damn Fantasyland now! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Idiots are the Biggest Frauds on Earth and if your ass really thinks CO2 controls the Climate of the planet and it is going to kill us all then if you do ANYTHING that emits CO2 then you are a....

Total Damn Fraud! 

Either Act On What You Believe In Or Shut the Hell Up! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You want to see one the Greatest Plays in #USER# History watch right before Half of 1981 #USER# vs #USER# Playoff Game with Miami down 24 - 10 and fighting like Hell to get back in the game...it's right here! -----&gt; #HASHTAG#

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geez...this pretty good for 1896 and this back when Swiss Guards were some serious guards protecting #USER#!  They got their guns ready to go! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who in the Hell wears masks at their house at party or anytime else inside their house for that matter?

How many Total Damn Morons do we have living this country exactly who go about their daily lives Frightened To Death of Damn Everything? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Only a dozen of us spent years in the Middle East in US Military...#HASHTAG#! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It all comes down to...

Is Kirby Smart gonna Coach against #USER# like a Frightened Damn Coward like he did in #USER# Title Game or is he gonna Coach like a Man and Real American?

If former bet the house on Bama and Saban!

Kirby is Frightened of Nick and So Damn Pitiful! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Montana US Senator Jon Tester played football! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone #USER# taken our kids to Plymouth, Mass and don't know an American be able to live under the Puritans rules although it would be Highly Entertaining to watch American Christians and the Puritans of 17th Century reaction to each other!

Very Damn Entertaining! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone tell #USER# that Nebraska just ran Mike Riley's ass out of Lincoln after 3 seasons with...

.500 Record

..and now Loyalty is reason Huskers keeping Scott Frost for 5th Year with .357 winning %?  

Riley's buyout was $6.2M...try if Frost's was same his ass been run! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Thank You Great Leader!

This is Freaking Madness that a Government Official in the Western World thinks they can determine whether The People can....

"Go ahead with Christmas plans!"

No one is going to believe this Horseshit in the future...none of it! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats Jimmy #USER#!

#HASHTAG# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all the praise of Jonathan Smith his record at Oregon State &gt;

Overall:  14 - 26
Pac-12:  10 - 21

Also his record against FBS Teams with .500+ Records =

4 - 21

Come on now...maybe let the Kid do something first before we say he's done something! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful Bob! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We got a fascinating game in Baton Rouge on Saturday because...

Coach O loses = Probably no saving his job

Dan Mullen loses = 3 Losses on Season and a Total Disaster and going right to the Hot Seat!  

Neither Coach Can Lose This Game! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burrow has potential be as good as Brady and Rodgers...he has...

Great Accuracy
Solid Footwork
Quick Decision-Making
Strong Leader

....but Joe also make bad decisions some that jeopardize how long he plays in #USER# such as knowing when to give up on a play or get ass on ground! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #USER# says Oregon has around 420 people in the hospital for Corona Virus in a state that has a population of...

4.2 Million = 0.0001%

Got keep all this in perspective folks because the Media folks want your asses Frightened to Death of Corona Virus and Everything Else! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coaches Hot Seat Quotes of the Day - Sunday, December 12, 2021 - Joe Namath &gt; #URL#
"To be a leader, you have to make people want to follow you, and nobody wants to follow someone who doesn't know where he is going." Joe Namath #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a Total Disaster it be if A&amp;M lost to LSU in this last game!  

Aggies got #HASHTAG# 2022 Recruiting Class and doubt they'll lose any recruits if they end up at 8 - 4 in Year 4 but Kevin Sumlin Year 4 at A&amp;M...

8 - 5!  

Jimbo getting close to the Hot Seat #USER# #USER#! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Work #USER#! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a name for a QB ----&gt;

Gunner! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UCLA is run by people who haven't done 1 Day of Real Work in Real World and live in a Total Fantasyland on Westside of LA that not only Totally Detached from Reality but full of people Frightened to Death of the world before this Pandemic...now they are Woody Allen + Larry David! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geez....20 years ago! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coaches Hot Seat Quotes of the Day - Thursday, November 25, 2021 - Thanksgiving ----&gt; #URL#
"As we express our gratitude, we must never forget that the highest appreciation is not to utter words, but to live by them." John Fitzgerald Kennedy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your ass eat a Twinkie but not take Corona Virus Vaccine you are Deeply Mentally Ill because lot better chance Twinkie kills your ass than tiny cell process stops a Deadly Virus from killing your Dumbass Twinkie Eating Ass!  

We'll eat a Twinkie + Fully-Vaccinated #HASHTAG# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ole #USER# could get #USER# on #USER# right now and add 20M+ homes to network but that take someone with 2+ IQ knew how cut a deal and there's also new TV deals to be had even with current TV contracts but #USER# hired Idiot Dumber Larry Scott!

Seemingly Impossible! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ole #USER# did it!

Great Job Son! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catching Jimbo Fisher's Post Auburn Press Conference on #USER# show and guy here #USER# who played and worked Bill Walsh says...

"Jimbo just asking his QB..what's his name Calzado...to make too many passes kid cannot make!"

Call plays your Damn QB can make Jimbo! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So your saying that Fire Chip Kelly's Ass PR Campaign run out of Westwood in cooperation with several members of LA Media who willing to carry the H2O of Worthless Losers has failed?

What A Damn Shocker!  

Doesn't Kelly's Buyout Go to Zero in January or sometime soon? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This gotta be the Corona! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a Damn Joke you folks are #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# and your asses on track to make Jimmy Carter look competent and take it from folks who were there...Peanut Boy one the Most Incompetent Boobs ever hold any office in American History! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We definitely descended from these Etruscan folks #USER# ---&gt;

"to their notion of a life well-lived. Here may be seen scene after scene of music-making, dance, acrobatics and juggling, sexual encounters, feasting, drinking, hunting, and obscure rituals of magic." #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can talk about China having supersonic weapons all you like but doesn't change FACT there are ALWAYS 2 #USER# Boomer Subs off China's coast and they hit America with some kind of weapon...

All of China would disappear from the Earth in 3 hours!

Let's not play Stupid Games! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CHS Quotes Day, Tue, Oct 19, 2021 - Don Shula ----&gt; #URL#
"The ultimate goal is victory.  And if you refuse to work as hard as you possibly can toward that aim, or if you do anything that keeps you from achieving that goal, then you are just cheating yourself." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The former #USER# Intel Officer #USER# who can read body language and voice inflections like a Wizard been telling us for few weeks now that Cristobal acting like he leaving Oregon for another job.

Haven't a clue what going in Eugene...but it's odd for sure! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not only this but all the Damn Nonsense that goes on at CFB games now starting with music blaring so Damn Loud you cannot think makes going to games miserable as Hell!  

The TV Timeouts are a Total Absurdity but they generate too much $$$ to ever change that! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ole #USER# employee #USER# says...

42 Bowl Games Just Great!

...while #USER# makes Millions $$$ on those 42 bowl games!

You might as well ask Paul if #USER# and #USER# love beautiful women! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow!

When we trading Bonds back in 1990s this would have made traders Millionaires if you been smart enough to see this move coming!  

The 30 Year Treasury Bond at 1.68% just Unbelievable #USER# #USER#! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 buddies ours trade Oil for a living make Bukkus Bucks told us they hearing that American Frackers cranking back up and in 6 months US be back cranking out 20M barrels of oil a day so OPEC has 6 months to make hay then Oil be stabilized around $50 to $80 a barrel for awhile #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We'll got 10 - 2 or 11 - 1 for Lincoln Riley in 1st season at USC! 

Toughest games on USC's 2020 sked &gt;

1. At Utah
2. At Oregon State
3. Notre Dame
4. At UCLA

If Trojans can handle Beavers and Utes on the road Riley have good chance to go 12 - 0! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>