<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden is the worst President in American history. This congress has committed so many crimes and deceptions it's the biggest Threat to Democracy ever. Big tech aligned with politicians manipulating the weak as they destroy America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're all suffering TDS and they're communists #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# when I had first covid I had weird dreams. I treated a bunch of folks with delta. They all had weird dreams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget John Kerry was a traitor. He came back from Vietnam as an officer wearing a bunch of medals and ribbons with political aspirations. That's when he joined the America is evil crowd. Veterans against Vietnam whose founders didn't serve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sadly it is their plan to turn us into a 3rd world cesspool #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They want to toss some children around. Probably enjoy humiliating children #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the liberal reviews they attack Oklahoma for lacking culture. Good job my neighbors that keeps the communists out. I love going to Oklahoma to fish and plenty of country folks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fauci and the other Democrats experts are talking about a possible variant coming in March that the vaccine and natural immunity can't avoid. Let's hear the opinions of other experts who have been silenced by the communists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What they ACLU used to be. It's now a radical progressive censor. The court of cancel culture. Both Democrats and Republicans should defend free speech. America can't survive with political parties determining what's allowed to be spoken #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tards don't want good news..They're waiting for the unvaccinated to die to feel justified in their covidian mindset #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# there are many PA residents in my area who get food stamps from California]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PA Gov ordered folks to stay home for snow storm. Reading community Facebook pages the liberals are posting stay home to save lives and tying it into the vax. If you look at the profile of the instigator they're democrats from other states.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good news. I have had it 3 Times now. The first time was a strong flu with respiratory issues and no hospital. 2 ND time I treated myself. recently had a mild with sore throat, headache and congestion. Took vitamins and over in 6 days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schumer is making the rounds on MSM tonight announcing an end to the filibuster to save democracy and pass the voting rights bill before election 2022]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# it's a spray to kill viruses. He didn't mention covid but that was the underlying message. You can Google micro ban and it comes up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world is tightening it's belt as inflation grows. China is investing in creating more products and technology. They're seeing the opportunity to spring ahead while we waste our money on a green no deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# thank you we're definitely not prepared for it. Country folks are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The democrats are attacking Chuck Todd, Andrea Mitchell and Jake Tapper calling them traitors. They're saying they should work at fox news lol. I agree that they're traitors but they are dem puppets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brian Stelter is a talking turd. He's as much a journalist as Elizabeth Warren is a native American. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[POC suffer more from climate crisis than Caucasians lol. They never miss a chance to race bait.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# according to their govenor they're just about all jabbed lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are the Majority! A tide of voters in 2022 will empty these useless politicians out of office. That includes worthless Rhinos and progressive democrats. I welcome Democrats or Republicans who want to work for all Americans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MSM is claiming emergency medical people are disgusted with unvaccinated. Alluding nurses have contempt for these patients. It's probably true for a percentage of the mentally ill democrats working in our medical field.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate attack by Democrats today claims minorities are affected by climate change more than Caucasians. Two attacks in one lol. Climate and racism is a double header]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things are not going to get better. They know it's all falling a part. They know there will  be investigations. Many crimes against humanity have been committed and Treason. They will do what's necessary to maintain power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol democrats are trying to trick black folks again. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senator Booker is on TV claiming black folks have to wait twice as long to vote as white folks. Probably because of the racist hwys and bridges]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rhetoric on vaxx mandates are growing fast. If you live in a Democrat state you are going to see a vax passport it's inevitable. It will be soon because they're going to keep this going past 2024.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate change affects low income school districts the hardest lol. In other words black folks because all white folks are rich lol. Democrats are the scum on a toilet bowl for all the harm they have done to poc. Everyone is the same stupid communists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do we have to know this person is non binary? The real message is democrats don't know how to control inflation.What ever this person is or does is irrelevant #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I took a hit for the team and went thru all of the MSM tweets. No mention of covid tonight so far. It's all Trump and climate crisis. A Few mentions about Biden moving forward determined to save the planet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God bless America and all you Patriots.Jesus Saves completely it's easy to do. My daughter and I are heading home for the night. We got a couple hours of work left to do on the crosses. Pray for America. Goodnight Thank you all for sharing time with me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most small businesses work month to month on their planning and inventory. My daughters business is being destroyed due to an inconsistent supply chain, Suppliers are casting small businesses aside to stock corporate stores at high margins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 40 degrees out and folks are wiping out the grocery stores. Its supposed to be 30 degrees and wind chill in the 20s. The local news told folks to get blankets and wrap up in them at your house. Never mentioned turn the furnace on lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have been on that for two yrs. We are going on with a normal day. God Bless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for your service. God Bless His family. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I met this man when he was running for Govenor. I was in PA settling my parents Estate after they passed. He came in a small town lunch joint to eat. He was friendly but just plain old dumb. Clueless, no vision and zero leadership qualities #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# and they're cheap. I can buy avacados for 25 cents. They're not worth eating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We've found out many got caught. Rich folks can get a Dr to endorse things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demi Lovato is singing songs to the ghosts of people who have suffered sexual trauma. Democrats are applauding her. I would call the nut house]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They've done nothing for Americans. They played obstructionists with Trump yet he still got things done. They really don't have any plans to improve America. They're running on division. I believe Democrats are trying to start a civil war. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gay people could be diagnosed with PTSD due to the suffering of oppression as a gay person. They would be entitled to benefits. I'm calling bs and standing with gay folks I see no discrimination or a need to get involved with their lives. Do You!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things don't seem right do they? It might be paranoia but it seems like something big is coming. They see the majority of Americans don't like anything they've done. I feel like an escalation is coming. They can't allow an election they know the outcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I buy green organic and wrap the tips with saran wrap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a win for all Americans Democrats and Republicans who want to trust their vote will count. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have been told I will not build anti bodies to covid from infection or the vaccination due to medicines I take for an autoimmune disease. I have lived life normal thru the whole event. I used to go out regularly but due to inflation I have done less.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm thinking about registering as a communist. I might as well disrupt from within. I will tell them Hillary and Obama send me notes. They believe everything else so they will buy that. I got this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[agree my brother. As long as folks listen to politicians and media it can't happen #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wasn't it hilarious for Jake Trapper to act angrily when he just learned they had been lying on hospitalization numbers. He knew but needed to keep the communists appeased #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course not just the same as democrats claiming voting rights protects black folks because they don't know how to get an ID. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have been on the vit d, vitc,zinc, multi vitamin for 8yrs. When you take immune suppressors it's part of your routine. I have been on Qwercitin for 8 mths. I took iver when I had 19. I'm not doing anything extra for omni.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats destroy. They don't know how to create opportunity to support yourself and your family. Here's a check stay home and do drugs is their philosophy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I had a friend who was 42 a runner who got sick quickly and passed away in two weeks. I also had 5 friends who were dying already in the hospital yet listed a covid death. Who wouldn't wonder what is going on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see the US embassy in Iraq was attacked and bombs going off in the green zone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# yep and I smell rat in many places]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats are claiming black and Hispanic folks have been less likely to get the vaccine than white folks. Probably claim tommorow they can't find a place to go. They can't use the internet lol. Color has nothing to do with medical decisions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The govt is going to mandate boosters for employers enforcing vax mandates. Not announced yet but possibly Tuesdays phony president speech will]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There is a bunch of fighting in my comments amongst followers right now over that tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I couldn't concieve her theory. She said racial depictions of black people spitting seeds out were derogatory. I told her I spit the seeds out too lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I seriously believe the vocal majority suffer mental illness. We wouldn't ask a status to treat another human being. I can't fathom that type of thought against another person. They believe unvaxxedd children should be bullied at school]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're not doing the lock up method for covid. We're living together I have a sore throat now and extreme nasal congestion. Dizziness and weird dreams. We just want to all get it and get it over with. a little Omnicron will help your imnunity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buying votes won't help the democrats. Those tricks don't work anymore. All black lives don't matter to democrats just the obedient #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My daughter and I were in Tyler yesterday at a hobby lobby. I saw you posted a cat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Typical political BS. Your thread has little to do with anything other than division. What a disgrace to medicine each one of you contributors,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elitists are destroying Americans right of choicr #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Democrats are saying now we undercounted covid deaths. They're going back thru and changing deaths. We know if you got hit by a truck but tested positive you counter as a covid death. It says it in the fema funeral expense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A black Conservative stating this will be ridiculed and mocked by Democrats. Don Lemon were to say this it would be a sin to question it. That is to be a Democrat! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time I watch this I sense the elitist evil. May the wrath of God fall on people who ignore these actions #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Democrat has created a false narrative that conservatives are against gay folks, POC,diverse culture,education, freedom. We're the exact opposite of that.I live by you do you and I will do me.I want all Americans to do well and be prosperous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abortion is another race baiting issue for the democrats. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The communists are back calling for a boycott on Pepsi over donations to the Republican party. If this isn't full blown communism what is it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Reading about David stealing a man's wife and knowing God loved him makes it easier to understand how undeserved we are of his grace. But I'm thankful for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's degrading to a person who spent their whole life dedicated to law. Worked their way up thru courts with hard work and dedication to being a judge. Their nomination will be due to skin color not their achievements.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor Mr Smollett was caught lying and found guilty of what I consider a serious crime. Big money was spent investigating this Hoax. He will be punished severely. He will have to sweep a floor for two days. That will teach him #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They signed me out and made me take down the Facebook comments. Harassment they called it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Democrats are claiming the economy is booming and soon to pass Reagan economic boom that Bill Clinton road the coat tails of. They don't live in the real world to know normal folks are struggling to get by.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I agree they state it themselves  then fifteen minutes later the narrative changes #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrat cities are in chaos. God Bless him and his family #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Christmas eve democrats and MSM no joy. No mention of Jesus just racism hatred for America. I sure wish we could just agree to separate  and let them live their lives and us ours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Total BS. These people are all paid to push a narrative trying to create division. What a bunch of elitist clowns. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You got to love the communists. Senate Republicans block the fair voting rights bill 51 to 49. I didn't know we got control of the Senate back. Alot happened while I was out fixing my fence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol because it's painfully obvious all tires aren't turning in the same direction #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sanitizer is the product of the day. Sing happy Birthday twice while washing your hands again. Know one had been buying sanitizer and I have been buying it at 50 cents a jug on clearance. great for cleaning tools]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Polls and belief in the system mean nothing anymore. If They did the guy in Florida would be in the Whitehouse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks dropped their vax mandate for employees. Science is working again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's stated incorrectly. Concerned legislators block suspicious voting bill  to save Americans voting rights #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They challenged the election the whole time President Trump was in office. Today it's a threat to our Country to even ask about thr 2020 election. Biden asked tech companies to censor those who disagree or just ask questions #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The very same censoring China did to Drs leaking information on covid we're witnessing the Biden administration and big tech do to America's top experts on Covid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish that would happen in America. The people with different views working it out together instead of politicians creating division for power. We the people have allowed politicians to divide and control to long #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Total race baiting clown show #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats are trying to make Sinema and Manchin sound like klansmen for not obeying the race baiters fake voting rules bill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The spirit of our founding fathers and the brave service members who stormed Normandy is still in our hearts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You would think covid didn't exist at all. They only have one topic and the house is holding the voting rights bill for showboating tommorow. All the communists are going to be speaking tommorow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats are comparing Jan 6th to 9/11 but call the Jan 6th event the old confederacy lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daughters shop is in a rich folks tourist area. Most of the tourists are northeners and they haven't been coming since covid. She's had this boutique 5 yrs but now we can't get those supplies. so we're making what we can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats are claiming Atheists have a higher vaccination rate than religious folks lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love how the Democrats are always recycling Howard Dean as a wise patriot. He's like a stereotype car salesman or a bad game show host. He's not even good at acting out his part.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I try to not get focused on the way our country is going on Sundays. I still like being on here but I don't check on any of my information to avoid getting upset lol. I'm not going to throw out Christmas fun, it refreshes your mind to just enjoy the peace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was reading a big Democrat influencers tweets and comments. He was showing pics of dying and dead conservatives. He and his followers were ecstatic and especially so that they were Christians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats won't watch this because it shows Biden and congress are lying about voter suppression. Race baiting is all they can accomplish #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those of you who have followed me a while know I read small town community Facebook pages in Democrat states to see what they're thinking. It's becoming a real movement to shut schools down for flu or common colds as a normal program]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm more cynical than you my friend. In my 69 yrs of life I have never witnessed such hatred for others]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to get off I'm running on data and I don't have unlimited like you rich folks lol. Hopefully the internet will be up soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This administrations response to Covid has crippled my daughters small business to near extinction. It has killed my 35 yrs of growing commercial roses and shifted all the business to Ecuador and Columbia. US roses are dead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every year in September homeless folks start trickling in. Like migratory birds in the spring they head back up north. Many just don't have the means to start over and some only no that life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CDC is releasing today a new 10 day isolation if you have been around anyone with covid. They just keep going like the energizer bunny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Each person must vote as they choose. I am disappointed in some of Abbotts decisions. In my opinion he can win handily against a Democrat. Christian Democrats vote high for him. Huffines is making promises he can't keep. No property tax?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who is against the democrats voting rights bill is a racist and is mocking MLK. Race baiters holiday coming up for the democrats. Most Americans honor Dr King and the Democrats have turned his life into their socialists agenda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got the lady at the fireworks stand to put up a sign for us and I sold her 10 caps #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The govt is putting together a vaccine that will defeat all Corona viruses and combine it with a flu shot to defeat both. It will be a one shot and done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their is a Karen in our shop right now! she is from Colorado and feels very unsafe because people aren't wearing masks. She said she feels safe in our shop knowing we're vaxxed being in the public😬My daughter is showing her earrings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coca cola has gay Santa commercials. I'm not homophobic but I'm against this. Why do we give up a tradition. I don't blame gay folks it's just more Democrat division. Don't let your kids near Santa he's a Democrat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many folks this time of year suffer grief or remorse. I want you all to know that there are many people praying for peace to come to you. My heart goes out to all of you. Heavenly Father hold these folks in your loving arms. In Jesus name I Pray Amen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know they're worse. It's reflective of a failing congress wasting all its time on fruitless investigations. Trying to pass bills that doesn't help the average American. They've played politics since day one and forgot Americans struggling #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# i take all. I had to stop vit d two months ago due to my numbers being to high]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If some of my tweets seem like something is missing it is. Twitter is removing parts of some of my tweets. I was banned 12 hrs yesterday for something stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# sure helps with trust in medical showing your politics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never seen so many unhinged folks as the democrats have managed to manipulate. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm staying here until I get shut down. I have another acct on here as well. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's dropped 30 degrees in the last hour. The wind went from 5 to 30 mph quickly blowing in a cold front. Two hrs ago it was 78 deg it's now 49. It's supposed to get to 30. Horses are loving it but the chickens sound like they're being murdered lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God bless America and all you wonderful Patriots. My daughter and I are going to stop at a new local pizza place for their grand opening. They're selling crawfish pizza by the slice. I will be back later tonight. Thank you for sharing time with me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They're talking about the high numbers. Democrats are lining up in dem cities by millions to test daily. Some have to test to go to work. MSM makes it sound like 1.3 mil tested positive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a crazy time to be alive. Protect your children from people who support this insanity #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever Democrats are in power the amount of frivolous lawsuits in America explode.I have a friend who's in the scumbag lawyer group of suing everyone for anything. He was very excited for democrats to gain power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since I have been at my daughters store more than usual. I have daily heard  folks talk about medical procedures they've put off due to covid. Many with serious issues. I wouldn't want to go either when I think about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If they don't do the right thing America will be two countries. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The democrats are after Billy Gates. Turns out our little computer nazi was sexually harassing his female employees. I myself would've thought him more of a homosexual. No offense to gay folks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rachel Maddow is as much of a journalist as Elizabeth Warren is Native American. Maddow is a Capitalist who found a following and is running to the bank with it. She can't possibly believe the stuff she says but her cult does #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The majority of Americans are Caucasians why are they dividing folks by skin color other than votes. They're going to make people quit watching programs that are diverse because you get sick of it. White folks buy the sports junk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate I can't go fight against these big accts. The big Democrat accts followers will wipe you out. I blocked alot of them just to avoid confrontation. Last summer I went after the Brooklyn dad commie and they blitzed me a week lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new mask out that is promising is called the fish face. MSM claims everyone in Oklahoma is wearing one. Could I hear how many fishface masks all my Oklahoma friends own?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The communists influencers on here are calling MSM right wing hacks lol. They're claiming how presidential Biden was during his speech and GOP controlled news is plotting against him. How delusional do you have to be to reach that conclusion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You got to listen to this all the way thru lol #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a Biden regulation that wastes billions on big govt. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think folks are just used to the insanity. It's normal to see homeless folks living and crapping in the cities. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It makes zero sense unless they know something about this created illness #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is going to be a toilet paper war. Wal-Mart is shutting down locations with heavy transmission of covid. I guess the dark winter will be sponsored by Wal mart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was a stressful day. My son was broke down in Columbus OH. It took me 4 hrs of calling for a wrecker to get a commitment to come get the car. All day on media the Jan 6th scam and democrats are on TV crying.b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italian business execs are meeting with Putin to work together. They want nothing to do with our Democrat regime. We have no alliance we're the clown country of the world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Racism, hatred, division is part of the mentally ill. Democrats manipulate these folks #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrat experts disagree. It's the new age science that defies common sense. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# you think with the fear they have they wouldn't go near a hospital]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# it's probably in my creek. It was an iPhone and my daughter can't locate it off her phone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I know it's a Chinese thing like the gambians here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truth is it ran it's course and is running out of steam like every virus in history #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats don't believe it. It's just more division and control of their followers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wear one of those hats as my work hat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scotland will be removing covid restrictions. It's amazing that this accepted as normal in a free world. It's the norm now to rejoice for some poor folks under tyrannical rule being ALLOWED FREEDOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Veterans for Biden are traitors to their oath. Christians who vote for democrats who support Govt funding of killing the unborn need to pray for forgiveness. Democrats are legitimizing pedophiles. Stop avoiding your crimes Democrat voters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm on gab. I quit posting because they kept signing me out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To celebrate getting all our Christmas special orders done we ate fresh salmon sandwiches for breakfast. Living like rich folks lol. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats are claiming this spring and summer they're heading to country folks to win them over before 2022 election. I'm excited for them to meet my advisor #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[of course he's a Democrat he's a rich elitist. Poor folks still vote all these rich folks who control their thoughts and speech #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every mainstream media is having discussions about Virginia and they're not happy. To be honest in my opinion they can't concieve anyone disagreeing with their point of view. They're truly disgusted that white females could vote Republican.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rainy days will hurt our economy. Storms will slow our recovery aiding in continued shortages and inflation. Lol Democrats are tying a climate twist into their failed progressive policies. We're not perfect but American Capitalism works]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course all the rich folks want to keep raping the country of its wealth #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the new attacks will be race baiting, Calling conservatives terrorists and attack on Christianity. They're labeling us as the confederacy and climate crisis will become the new covid. They're going to express anger more to try and be more believable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goodnight patriotic Americans . Jesus Saves completely it's easy to do.God Bless America!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We got an order today for 12 crosses to be placed on veterans Graves. Fortunately I had them already cut from wood so my daughter and I have been getting them epoxied. We need to put their name, birth and death date on them. P up tomorrow 😬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There we go back to normal the new variant of concern #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever has this happened in America. Imagine the outrage if this occurred in a Republican administration. I would be against it no matter the party. A dangerous precedent is being set. Republicans could do the same and censor liberals #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[everyone watching the Trump rally. I'm on RSBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 9/11 I would've marched to war to defend NYC. Today it means nothing to me. I hate that Ellis Island and our statue of liberty is in a city that stands for Socialism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's because we're thru with it. Let it come and allow us medical treatments. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The communists are claiming we need more immigrants to come in to fill the worker shortages. In PA were my one daughter lives most folks went on permanent welfare. That's an issue that democrats create]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've had a good day at my daughters store. A store near us is closing down due to retiring. They brought up a bunch of their gift inventory for us to sell. And we're the only gift store open in our area, We might stay open late and make some money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daughter and I are going to the rich folks sushi joint. My son sent me a gift card for Christmas from there. I will be back later tonight. Thank you for sharing time with me today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't watch football but the communists want Aaron Rogers to lose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti Semitism is being driven by the media and the progressives.Twitter is full of tweets attacking Jewish folks. Media and politicians throwing fuel on the fire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's just a paid race baiter
 they don't believe or care about the subject. Some folks make their living spreading manure. No disrespect to the influencer it's just dirty capitalism. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# everyone jumps to universal Healthcare. I'm talking about affordability and accountability on cost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We not only have a tyrannical govt we have all the rich elitists telling us how to live. Many bands are leaving spotify under Democrat tech elitist pressure. All rich folks who made their money singing about freedom of speech lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have been working on my daughters car for 4 hours. A month ago it wouldn't start I got a battery then replaced starter then alternator. Had a mechanic hook up a computer to it and no errors. I believe I have a wire exposed so I'm running thru those]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I woke up excited it's Christmas eve and went to my coffee shop. They have 3 tvs on with the news on. Nothing but racism and hatred with lies and godless stories. What a sick world democrats have created for so many people. They are enemies of Americans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine a United States Senator claimed to be a Native American and used that to gain advantage. Elizabeth Warren knowingly lied about her heritage for power and financial gain. Why wasn't she prosecuted and terminated?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I got a Congresswoman and Dr involved. She's in a private room now and he's there with her. They're trying to get her stable to go home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MSM is claiming if it wasn't for them America wouldn't have known about gay folks lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 2020 12% of the voters were black and democrats claim 90% voted Biden. The real number they're focusing on is the college vote. They claim 76% of college grads vote dem.Working white folks number of voters dropped off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# mold and mountain cypress are high in my area]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It wasn't that many years ago I voted for people in both parties. Prior to 2008 I voted democrats and Republicans. I was always focused on local and state elections. Then the federal govt started getting in states affairs  so I had to pick a team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Craziness is common in Democrat kingdoms. Folks who live there probably pay no attention to it. It's just life in a Democrat area #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's a paid opinion artist and has an influencer type of following. She's doing what they pay her to do. She's a smart manipulator of her followers #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The geese aren't native to Texas. These are Canadian geese that migrate to Mexico for winter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daughter has to buy them little thin gloves for using Epoxy for her business. They were 12. For a hundred at Walmart they're now 43.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats know what's best for your child. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the perfect example of race baiting. Many businesses in this shopping center were evicted due to being closed by a Democrat mayor for covid. No rent coming in from any color of business is an issue to a property owner. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MSM headlines Trump tryed to steal 2020 election.We will make sure he can't steal 2024]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They've definitely swung the algorithm around. We're separated by different opinions and like minded folks are grouped. I have two other accts and I see very little cross over. Be more active in liking tweets by people who are minded]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just saw on TV they've cancelled the term Eskimo kisses. It's insensitive to Eskimos. Reminds me of when janitors became custodial engineers. What's wrong with janitor it's a job description like mechanic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# that's a cdc report. I'm assuming 2021]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Merry Christmas to you and your family. God Bless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# my area boycotted them and presented a petition we wanted a couple self checkouts but we wanted employees working a register. 60 days later it was completed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red states are booming. We're doing well because everyone has equal opportunity to improve their lives. If only Democrats spent time improving economies instead of racism and regulations their states would prosper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The very word minority used by Democrats to differentiate folks by skin color is debasing. The real minority are poor folks many of which are trapped in a govt system designed to keep them there. Poverty doesn't know race or beliefs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daughter and I went to a bakery this morning for a 91 yr old neighbors birthday party. There we're 71 people at that party crammed together. No one afraid just folks laughing and having fun. No employees wearing masks at any business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're admitting they've been lying. But trust me now #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Country folks and faith in Jesus Christ will save our country alongside city folk Patriots.We might be down but we're not out. As they say it's not over till the fat lady sings. We see people waking up daily. They're more of us, they are just louder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daughter and I have been busy today. We had over 800 sets of earrings she had made. I put a sign on the highway buy one set full price and get 2nd at half price and folks traveling for New years have been coming in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The communists and their BS need stopped. Cancel the proponents of cancel culture #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The majority of Americans have know idea Antifa exists. And many that do think they're just college kids acting out. We know they're convicted pedophiles and rapists along with terrorists]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>