<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The definition of a H.N. Sorry there's no other way to put it,and I'm not meaning that to be offensive. He is just truly the definition of it.

If you want to support 'White Wellness" and spit on Black people, that's on you. He looks like hes trying to be Jimmy Walker. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# (France Variant #HASHTAG# (CyprusVariant, which combines both the  #HASHTAG# and #HASHTAG# together 25 cases in Cyprus)

This is what happens, when the sworld dodes not join together to fight a threat to all of #HASHTAG# but instead use it to harm humanity #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalists need to be clear, when they write about Omicron. Its fatal to those who are UN-VACCINATED.

Also, welcome to #HASHTAG#, folks. 25 cases in Cyprus. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

SENATE FLOOR TODAY

Thanks for this as I started my coverage late. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

A new report finds that misogyny is flourishing online and motivating gun violence.

 #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its not just injected in your face, anymore. It's now attacking younger folks. And it isn't pretty. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you aware that Joe Rogan is on 20 platforms, and that all of the other podcasts are also on those platforms, including me? Whrfe can I go where Joe Rogan IS NOT?

This is my point and it is this.

Start to #HASHTAG#. 

I am amazed people do not understand this! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TRUTH BOMB

If we are going to have book burning's in this country, then lets start with Mein Kampf, and the Art of the Deal. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#
Sen Tim Scott (R)#URL# mentioning Jim Crow, and how glad he is he doesn't live in those times. (Sen Scott is an avid Trumpist)**Warning this testimony may be upsetting to some Black viewers**#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple is giving the terrific Musicians that are pushing Spotify to remove Joe Rogan red carpet treatment. Fab.
Now maybe they can also promote #HASHTAG#.
Such as other podcasts on Apple that are LIBERAL!
Joy REID
Rachel Maddow
Daily Kos
AND YOUR TRULY!

SEEMS FAIR!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is the real thing we should be focusing on. To the GQP everything is a "Privilege" and not a right.

White Privilege. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

LIVE FROM THE SENATE

Sen Debbie Stabenow (D)#URL#  is now speaking in the senate well. She is particularly eloquent and also very elegant, and gets my style award for today!!
#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

What the Tonga Tsunami looked like, when it hit. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# All the Death Cult Governors are attached by an umbilical cord that wraps around their nether regions. All Democratic Candidates work as one well oiled machine to work against them. Its all one big glorious symbiotic relationship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am an actual Journalist/reporter. and this is the first Podcast i did on my new Channel.

Enjoy.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEN TED W LIEU

THIS MAN  HAS MY ABSOLUTE RESPECT #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where I live, there are no more N95 masks, which means that everyone who is running astound is probably using a useless surgical or cloth mask.

Where I live some of the richest people also live. They should help us by purchasing some N95 masks for us poor people #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting story. I wonder if  This is something the Secty of the Interior can look into or even knows about? is this possibly part of her jurisdiction, or is this not the Secty's  purview? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#
Native Hawaiians another group that everyone thinks are not Americans. Because many Hawaiians are also Hawaiians loyal to their Queen, and remember their country which was overthrown by the US .But they fight for America, pay taxes and serve tourists. AMERICANS 50th #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*WARNING*
The following statement is sarcasm. Grow up.

She boned up on her paid role, by reading "Hooked on Ebonics, Trump Edition" Then, she denied she ever had parents, to spare her family the embarrassment. later claimed to be from the Planet Venus, and named El-Nar. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know why you are being handcuffed. You fit the profile.

Black, and "off the plantation".

Disabled

Not a Trump Supporter

Speaking out

Not a sell out

Black lives only matter if they support "White Wellness"

SUE EVERYONE #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believe it or not, poeple believe if they eat right and exercise they can't get covid. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not President Biden that is blocking the voting rights bill. 

It is Republicans

Covie is correct. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me just recap a bit for today.nnSenators squashed the right to vote equally.nMcConnell made a racist remark about Black folks.nBoebert made racist remarks to a group visiting the capitol about their YarmulkesnRep Bowman got arrested for protesting for voting rights.n#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

Did this You tube 'True Crime"  person, just interview an family without their consent? Why is the camera pointed at the ground? This is exploitation at its finest, and it needs to end. Fake "Investigators", with no press cred.!#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is similar to many immigrant 'Assimilation" Phenomenons we have often seen in American diaspora generations. Becoming more conservative and NIMBY . Italians, and Irish, Asians, and Hispanics and some Black folks  have the same.

This is a good read! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 25 years ago, Democratic Women did not side with Fascists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# THISnnAlso the thought of many indigenous folks today as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lets to more!nnPleaseRonDeSantis (everyone)nPleaseBoebert (Jewish folks, for her Yarmulke Comment)nPleaseRightToLife (people who died from covid)n I can go on... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# 

President Bidens call with Sauli Niinisto, the President of Finland

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, I went on a live show on youtube, into the belly of the beast. The host was kind, and patient, But In know none of them liked what I had to say. I thought I could keep it cool, but I lost it over these 'true crime" youtubers, and their pretending to be journalists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Krysten Sinema.

Republican Employee of the Month. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Hawaii its so bad, that after forcing vulnerable Polynesian kids (Many of whim have diabetes, obesity and asthmatic problems) back to in person classrooms, security guards are now 'babysitting" them becasue teachers are out w covid. Because parents are #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

NEW BREAKING NOW

PUTIN SAYS HIS DEMANDS MUST BE MET

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every one should own one of these shirts. Not just one. One for every day of the week!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, and that was in my podcast today, as well.

Beautiful thing is, some of the nominees, were born in 1979, so YOUNG.  All are so wonderful. I cannot wait for one of them to be elevated to the S.C., and I just hope it is soon as possible.
(Last 40 Min)

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, when he says racist, he means '"Anti White " or "White Wellness".

Pure white supremacy.

He isn't even trying to hide it anymore.

That is what he said. In plain sight.

Guess those folks that are Black and stuff are all for this then?

Supporting the "White Wellness" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's be clear. The Misogynists in the party of NO! (Republicans) do not want women to work. They want them at home, being forced to have lots of kids, and baking cookies. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# up info on what documentation undocumented immigrants may breed to get a vaccine. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# 

This is a podcast I up-loaded to my new podcast site, from an older podcast. But it is still relevant to today's news. The sound is not as well mastered as my other podcasts.

Please give it a listen, and download all of my podcasts for free on many  platforms #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

I like to term it a "Rigour-Mortis" of the cranial brain stem" myself. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh to think as a child does. 
Life would be much sweeter. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kicking that over to the USA feeds. 
Resemblance much? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I refuse to believe this man didn't cheat . How is this even possible? Yale and Harvard? That must be a typo.; Has anyone double checked these claims?

If that is true, Harvard and Yale have some serious issues.

They should null and void any degrees given. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hands down, it's the Long John *No Gross comments, please*.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ron tossed them from his private jet while he was escaping to another vacay (sarc) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

For anyone looking for that smoking gun, for the Jan 6th Coup attempt?

This gentlemen just admitted he came up with the idea, so.

It's also a lovely plus that he is a person of color.

Extra own the libs-ish yes?

Why isn't he arrested right now? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A WILD RIDE!!

I had to delete every twitter, and people already downloaded my INCORRECT version! In every description, I said JFK instead of RFK in descriptions. Everything has been corrected. i am sure lots had a good laugh over that.#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is definitely the worst thing ever created. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are going to see a lot of Canadians posting on my twitter feeds, today. That is because there is a huge anti vaxx protest in Otttowa today, with the Canadian Wing of the Trumplandia Battalion 666 Deep Gravy  Ya'all Quida Brigade. With plans to go to the American border #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 6 hired black folks, and the black keynote female speaker, are offstage, and only brought out for the photo ops. This is the actual reality of a Trump Nazi White Wellness rally. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The number you should all be looking at, is the 0.7 percent if indigenous folks in the country.nnGENOCIDE COMPLETE.nnA tiny bit under 60 percent of this country, is white.nnWhites are not "dying off', immigrants are not 'taking over" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That about sums up what Hitler wanted to create when he created the Gestapo. Heartless blood thirsty killers who had cold hearts and believed in White Supremacy They want you to fear them.nnBut a bunch of antifascists called the Allies defeated them. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how black people have often responded to the indignities they have suffered. With grace and dignity. FYI #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen Ron Portman diagnosed with Covid. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably one of the most relevant pieces of journalism right now. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# 

The Biden-Harris administration announce support for waterways and ports today.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope those Red State truckers appreciate that the President has their back. Our President does not care who you voted for. he still cares about you. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

#HASHTAG#

See my entire expose, of the group that was outside of the Wells home. It goes a lot deeper then you think, with the three main protagonists, Marissa Zdazinsly, Jonathan Lee Riches, and Andra Griffin all Trumpists. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smart sheep trains puppy not to herd them. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They are disconnected because they are WHITE SUPREMACISTS and live in their own little bubble. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sky is blue! But Hunters laptop.

The world is in crisis!

But Hunters laptop.

I have gas! 

Hunters laptop. 

(Replacing Hillary's emails)

These carnival barkers have zero originality. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just had the strangest idea. So, it seems that Americans abroad, either dual citizenship or military can actually votge by mail, and register, even if they squelch the votes of everyone else. Do we have to leave the country, to vote?

Seems very odd, doesn't it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then why are these two hale and hearty as they are both obviously severely "Unwell". #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YES

And if they wont teach the history of slavery, we can teach them the history of the KKK #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Many are not vaxxed because they cannot be.
 *IE severe anaphylaxis, uncontrollable high blood pressure, immune suppressing life saving drugs*. 
Refusing to vaxx and even to mask is wrong!! 
But refusing to treat people?
Let them die? 
I can't condone that. 
But I get it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Joseph R. Biden, Jr. today announced the designation of a Presidential Delegation to Banjul, The Gambia to attend the Inauguration of His Excellency Adama Barrow on January 19, 2022.

The Honorable Richard Carlton Paschall III, United States Ambassador to  Gambia,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump supporters are all mentally ill. Our President is not going to be cruel to someone, who is not in his right mind. Our president acts, the what Jesus would have, and shows compassion, even while turning the other cheek.

Example of a true Christian, on the Lords birthday. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My investigation is narrow and focused on a certain group.  You can see who these individuals are, by looking at my profile, under. They are indeed, middle aged woman, for the most part. (Spoiler alert: I am a middle aged woman myself) #HASHTAG#. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I personally screen-capped over 100 comments, regarding how much Betty is "hated" from the BB site. I haven't put then up yet, because I thought it would be a bit too much so soon after her passing. They are indeed claiming that all over the Fright Wing Media. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

#HASHTAG# is trending.

See below, for the number to ask that be done

It is a public number, and breaks no TOS. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IF that doesn't bring it home to people like the Black Republican Senator, and other Black folks who continue to suck at the Trumpist teat, nothing will. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank You, FLOTUS 46!

The Real Americans, love you and appreciate all you do to uplift our country and truly make it great again.

And also, may I say, with complete sincerity, the following... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Pro Abortion Rights saying ever:

It's not whether an embryo is a person, it's whether a woman is." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#. More contagious packing the hospitals with the unvaxxed.

#HASHTAG# 
Hold my beer #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# 
Please check out this 30 second soundbite from my podcast, Monday Madness

I hope it will interest you in downloading the entire podcast. It is free. You can listen on other platforms like IHeart Radio, and Audible, and TM Radio (Apple-Podchaser SirusXM apps #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hi Tony great episode! I am on a mission to #HASHTAG#.

I am standing in Rogans sandbox with my tiny grain of a podcast. Yours crocks of course, and is incredible. I think you can give Rogan a run for it!!
I can't do it as well as you! 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #HASHTAG#
If we can get as many downloads as Rogan (200 million), and Spotify starts promoting Rachel Maddow Joy Reid Daily Kos and other podcasts (Including myself), and removes Joe Rogan that would be great. Joe Rogan is on the same platforms we are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

BREAKING STUNNING NEWS

PAPERS SERVED ON WILLIAM BARR THIS MORNING!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hawaii up next.

Or is it ok to say 'Onipa'a" but be fine with greasing the tourism slavery wheel, and perpetuate the annihilation of native Hawaiians by yet another disease brought to Hawaii so that others can get rich off of your labor? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much you wanna bet MTG is VACCINATED?nnHow much you wanna bet, MTG doesn't care on e iota about Jewish folks? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Both are delicious, but I am partial to Coconut milk, and also coconut creme, which is rich and delicious in any hot beverage. The Coconut milk in cartons, is mixed with soy milk usually. I find Cashew milk also rich creamy and delicious.
Purchase GMO free, certified organic..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not watching Abbott in this clip. I am watching the paid black guy in the back. Making sure he shows himself, so he can get paid after they shuffle him off back behind the scenes, and send him on his way, before things get too rowdy at the KKKlan meeting. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

TPR first reported yesterday, the WHO is taking  a similar approach it did when Omicron developed. 12 cases in France originating in Cameroon are being studied. However they have known about the variant, called IHU for awhile.
 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

Documents show terrorism (domestic) in filings.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hawaii. By forcing our most vulnerable keiki, (Pac Islanders), back to school, and allowing rampant tourism and cruise ships here with a UNDERVACCINATED population and OVERWHELMED medical facilities-you are harming our most precious resource.
Native Hawaiians.
#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They National Guard and the police are completely compromised. they are bending over backwards for these fools. they are shutting down streets, hunkering down. I don't see that happening. they only do that when Dems, BLM, and Antifa supporters march. Why I put up the articles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hitler did not allow Jewish folks to wear gas-masks, as he was gassing them to death, in indoor rooms which would have saved their lives.nIt was to cause harm, and  and kill people.nnDeSatan and Abbot wont let folks wear masks or get vaxxed to save their lives, and it is killing #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You are absolutely right, Mama Enabler Pitbull with lipstick." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#
President Biden Assassination attempt.
All week- my new podcast (See my pinned profile tweet) I have been weaving threads about people who have been radicalized.
This is absolutely the fault of those attempting to radicalize Americans
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan sees the US military now as a threat on its bases. Not good, people. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Bannons Breitbart yesterday, the open racism, on a thread dedicated to the Aubrey story, was startling. Rethuglicans operate on a thug criminal mentality and cruelty drives them,. so they have angles others dont think about becasue they are not psychopathic. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I sleuth-ed this out earlier. I literally just waited until he posted it. Nice to see others also caught that.

He was just "hangry!" #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They have dirt on him. Or have terrified him w threats. That is how these folks operate. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stopping "White Wellness", White Supremacist Hiteresque KKK dialogue, begins with white people themselves.

It is up to everyone who is white to do their part to call out racism, every single time without fail, in thunderously loud rhetoric. 

IMHO it would be over very soon. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is she auctioning them off to benefit some charity or help her "Be Best" program, which I believe actually stands for 'Be best At Grifting?"

How the convo went-

"Hey Melania, I need you to auction off your hats."

"That's fine, I look fat in hats anyway." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*Spoiler alert*

*Rudy G and company photos recent YES he's still around!*

When you want to do that Star Wars bar scene, but you run out of shiney costume material. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

Today History is being made, as the first woman to command an aircraft carrier, Officer Amy Bauernschmidt makes us all proud. 

So much for women not being allowed to serve in the military. 

(Something Trump was considering during his time in the Oval). #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just purchases a huge chunk of a Hawaiian Island. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not just in this situation. Many tribal people, after "Discovery" by whites, were reported to also practice infanticide. nine time out of ten, it was also untrue. 

That is why we need to preserve history ACCURATELY.

Many people post contact-myths still persist. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Would you do me the honor of listening to my podcast? I am trying to get more people to support tiny little grains of sand like me, that have to share 20 podcast platforms w/Joe Rogan. #HASHTAG# 
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He sleeps great. He was a plant, as is Sinema.

We should be blaming OURSELVES for voting his rear in.

Ir took DINO's, some Rethuglicans jumping ship to make sure he went over, and some conservative independents to slid e over the Dem ticket.

Remember how we rejoiced?

FOOLED #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hawaii is having a BRUTAL SURGE of cases, and now, cruise ships are set to return here, in January.

What they do not realize is, if we are all sick, or dead, we cant be their little tourism slaves anymore.
There are 22 ventilators where I live.
Hawaii - over 3,200  cases today #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#

OPENING PRAYER FOR VOTING RIGHTS BILL SESSION IN THE SENATE TODAY

**Note this was a viewer created clip, and NOT named by me**

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

Here is a journalist (Not a trumper) interviewing the Buffalo head Boy. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a recently done chronological timeline, in the grand scheme of the universe, the Earth has existed for about 37 minutes, and consumed almost three fourths of it's resources.

That's not good odds, folks. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I addressed this today on my Podcast. You can skip to the last ten minutes, where I specifically make this arrgument.

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

"An Event Cancelled is better Than A Life Cancelled" #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You may be interested in a recent podcast i did, mentioning Gov Younkin and his insanity. It is in the Amgelia King section of the podcast.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#
LIVE FROM THE SENATE FLOOR
Sen Rick Scott, (R)#URL# polarizing and controversial figure in the GOP at this time, is currently speaking in the well vehemently against  Voting Rights Act and rule changes.#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just like MLK discovered when he was arrested. Black men don't have rights. And if you are a Black man in a wheelchair, that goes double for you. 

Becauseyou offend 'White Wellness" by A. Being Black, and B. Being disabled. White Supremacy cannot abide either of those. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

From the Chamber, LIVE as of a half hour ago. Schumer threatens to change the rules.

Do it! Get 'er done! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So who wants to take bets on who is going to be crowned Prom King to deliver Trumps message, so he doesn't incriminate himself? 

Maybe Donny Jr will read it off the teleprompter?

I smell a rat in this whole 'Canceling the Jan 6th speech" thing. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you #USER# for that link. It has been a crazy day siufting through al.l of this. and thanks again, as well, to #USER#. Lets hope some fglopod come s of all of this.

I am planning a podcast for this soon. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

JEN PSAKI is currently live
CC caps are on, so no excuse for misreporting her words.

She is wearing red, and suffering no fools today. 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manchin($ R/D) is how I wrote his name yesterday during my reporting. I am unapologetic on that. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great check out mine then, pinned to my profile. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Podcasts can be very boring to listen too. Especially when they mostly yell. I have a podcast. it is very new. It is on every single platform that Rogan is on. I am not leaving any of them. I am staying to #HASHTAG# him, in the podcast venue.

#HASHTAG# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

STILL GOOD IN THIS WORLD

NEVER MESS WITH THE IRISH!!

Irish folks ready to fight the Russian navy!!

GO EIRE!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI is now following up on election day threats. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am just going to throw out some journalistic hunches here. Now, this probably isn't right to say or speculate, but a building full of mostly Jewish folks and immigrants, that collapse like a bomb went off. I know there may be other explanations, but my mind just goes there #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Jordan, men brawl over women's rights.

All the one's on the women's side, are the keepers. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not all Americans. Just the POC, LGBTQ, Millennials, Jewish folks. ect. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And, I  assure you, that was also the hoped for result, by his GQP handlers. Because tanking the Dow when its doing great is what they were hoping for. 
Just like driving up Covid numbers . It's all part of their Death Cut Cruelty Plan. 
They want to destroy Biden at all costs #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can now hear soundbites for all of m,y podcasts, to see if you would like the sound and tone of my podcasts, and then you can download them all for free on over 20 different platforms. The links are under the video player, just click on MORE to see them all #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# country and lets be real, Native Hawaiians have news coverage too, folks. Native Alaskans, America Samoa, Guam. Puerto Rico, US Virgin Islands.nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

Huffpo rightfully puts the blame where it belongs. On Senate REPUBLICANS

(Jen Psaki who is now LIVE (See my feeds) is restoring my personal faith in things. ATM.)

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He looks like one of those people,whose Dad is actually his Brother -Uncle. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

President Biden approves funding for Alaska, and disaster relief.

No paper towels were tossed during the sttement.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeap, that's about it.

Pretty crazy...eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its pure Nazi propaganda, with dog whistles to just kill off Democrats, which replace Jewish folks and others. They would love to see us all in the ovens. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are more American than me! Generations of mine were (immigrants)nnAnd look, you have REAL patriots in your family!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

The plight of the Afghani people, is a complete offense to all of humanity, and is one of the most despicable situations in our history as a human race.

Christiane Amanpour breaks it down wonderfully.

I will be doing a follow up on this story in genera #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Dear Senator, I do not know if you saw my reporting yesterday, but I gave you my Style Award. You looked simply elegant, and your testimony was brilliant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How sane responsible parents celebrate New Years Eve in 2021/2022. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud boys have moved their venue, "Summer of love not hate" to an abandoned Kmart parking lot, just put the info up. While Counterprotestors and Antifascists are set up at the Waterfountain in Portland. Venues are not far apart in the same area. Police are stand off #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GQP thugs, SS troops, and gun enthusiasts are determined to ruin the one year anniversary of GF memorial. Even blocking the GF law, to dehumanize and deflate POC around the country.nnDon't let them. They want a race war. Civ 2 and carnage. That is their goal.nnHold fast,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He also advocated for the KKK and White Supremacists. Because he supports their platform of hate. However, it was a thing of beauty when Cory Booker came out right after him, and gave one of the best orations of his career.nnUse these folks as fuel to fire you up to resist #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are not the death cult, or the cult of fear.

We are the party of action, and resistance.

Manchin was never one of us, and never had a clue. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas. Here are some memes I made, along with a news slogan.

"Forget Brandon, Go Biden!~" #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want him removed. Retiring is too dignified for him. I think Justices should not serve for life. that is my opinion. With Biden in office, we have an opportunity to get another strong voice on the Supremes. So that is a plus. Omicron may yet give us more spots. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[28 seats to fight for. We better get going. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

As a journalist myself, I fully intend to check this out thoroughly. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Field Team 6 baby!

As opposed to the Gravy Team 6 on the opposite side. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

For us in Hawaii that means EMPTY SHELVES. All of our goods are  mostly shipped here via barges. Some on planes. Tourists are coming , cruise ships taking our PPE there is now a shortage. Hospitals are small here. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

TSUNAMI UPDATE

Just to let you all know, I am fine, and there was a small Tsunami generated, the largest of which was in Hanalei, Kauai, at 2.7 feet. We are all good and grateful to have dodged yet another Tsunami bullet .

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diana-

 is still the Queen of Hearts. 

Still Princess.

Nothing will ever take that title away from her. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Nationalists have been posing as Antifascists for a very long time, and have perpetuated most of the violence, they then turn around and blame on nBLM and Antifascist groups.nnHitler Tactics 101.nnPay attention. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We love Steven. he is a true e gentlemen and really a very cool and down to earth person. He isn't very tall, but he has a tall mind.

Love from Jurassic Park. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That fake Ebonics energy was probably bolstered by a  few greenbacks before she got to the mike.

A black woman stumping for white supremacists, is supposed to make our heads explode and own the libs.

But all it does is make her an embarrassment to her family. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

A coup has overthrown thew Government of Burkina Faso.

BREAKING NEWS RIGHT NOW #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Please see my new podcast, where I explain it all. If foloks really want to get rid of Joe Rogan, then simply #HASHTAG#. Conservative podcasts are dominant. Joe Rogan is on every podcast platform. So am I. Should I leave podcasting then, and let Rogan have it all?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

I am putting this up, because I explain my Anne Coulter reference, I go after DJT, and I go after platforms that spew hate, I touch on Gaza, and a whole lot of other subjects. Its as viable today as it was in May. Even more so. Relevant and still timely!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#
BREAKING NOW LIVE SENATE FLOOR
#URL# Michael Bennet (D) is now speaking on the Senate Floor Re voting rights, speaking if difficulties caused by voter restriction laws.

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do me a favor. If you know anyone who as CREDIBLE information on any of this, they can hit up my DMS. I am open for news tips, but they have to be verifiable. So help me out? I am an actual journalist, so I can't go off on rumors or speculations.  hashtag, #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

#HASHTAG#

Marissa Zdazinski, has a long history of outrageous behavior, but this last stunt, may be more critical to her, then any of her other zany attention seeking adventures.
#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all know they will come only to incite, and armed to the teeth. The question is how will they be dealt with. That is the interesting question right now. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

Betty White.

I have not yet fully processed her passing.

I am saddened, deeply by the loss of not only an icon of entertainment, but an icon of humanity.

RIP Miss White!

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bilbo has become my favorite  Twitter dog.

Just something about him. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So that's like everyone including the kids?

Sounds legit. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the GQP, charges of pedo stuff and other legalities are actually things that are in their favor. Their supporters love bad boy criminal types. Really gets their voting juices flowing.
Question is how outrageous do they have to be to top themselves?

Its like  Hunger Games #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So basically people are shedding hard spray, spit, sweat, and other bloodily fluids, but they could not see this as a problem?

Listen folks its time to grow up and realize. Millions will die if we do not settle down

This pandemic is like nothing the world has ever seen. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have been getting bombarded on both sides on this. Here is my final statement on this 

I AM NOT LEAVING. I am staying, and I am going to grow my podcast, and give Joe Rogan a run for his money. That  is where I am at with this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senator Lankin talking about 'Only being a little bit pregnant", and 'If I filibuster its evil, if a Democrat Filibusters its fine" Reminds me of a whiney 12 year old who simply cannot get his way. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is fine, with the Texas Governor. Little children dying makes him smile. as long as they are Democrats.

 *Disclaimer, my opinion, not a statement of fact. Allegedly* #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do agree on that. Absolutely. But what U.R is doing, is exposing a White nationalist Domestic Terrorist Organization.  NS is off the table, though I do agree. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# and  sensible gun control advocates had a huge win, when MAGA gun lovers wanted to go to a county fair, and open carry.nnYeah. "Here's a gun now go"open carry" some Democrats, or folks that are masked".nnThat would not have ended well.nnNice to see some VICTORIES today. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# 

Someone would lie a word with you, Mitch. its about your American Citizenship in their country. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

President Biden will give a speech on voting rights

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then stop pushing tourism, and give people TIME to get boosted. Most in Hawaii have not had access long enough. You have to wait up to 6 months. So stop worrying about your bottom line, and worry more about making vaccines more accessible. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Sullivan R trying to make the case on the Senate floor that Alaska is somehow not "Jim Crow" and more liberal than the Speakers state. This is a state where indigenous folks had to fight for a peice of land no one wanted. (Unalaska). ANNEXXED. Colonialized🤣 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The country this missive is talking about is not the US, but Nazi Germany, and the Antifascists are American troops from the 1940's. This is what trump a actually addressing. A few years to late for the American Victory. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bovine Poison is selling like hotcakes, but we can't get people to take a vaccination to save their lives.

Because...wrinkles? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is an "All-Caps" kind of a day for me, today folks.

Deal With It. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is really disturbing about the growing developments in Ottawa, Canada is, as the monkey-see monkey-do mentality keeps going around like a dog chasing its tale, I fear the American Whack-nuts will copycat off of this- As they are copycatting off of the Americans
Pure insanity #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# 

HEINOUS!!

Nazis are now running rampant in our streets, and harassing random people?

Are you kidding me?

Arrest each person involved here. this is a criminal act caught on video in plain sight in the middle of the day,

Since when are we 1930's Germany!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOD BLESS THE ONION.

Watch the sales of "Artificial arms"  on Amazon go through the roof now~! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every R Senator is Seditious. Complicit. and an accessory to the crime. The whole group of them. the party should  be defrocked, defunded, and disallowed on any ballots. They can regroup; under some other name, but the Republicans should be stricken from the national election #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They should follow their own mandate, and see how long it lasts, with all of those elderly folks in tier offices.. Mandate would be back in 24 hours. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wand them to stand up for this (white) world and the kind of (white) world we want.nnHATS IS TAUGHT IN THE HOME.nnThe real reason White Folks that are racists, home school, their children is becasue they do not want their kids going to school with people of color.nnOWN IT. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

ANTI VAXX STATE TROOPER DIES OF COVID

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is that, if you do not mind my asking?  I feel it is a good way to expand my journalism, without going on YouTube or Facebook. I am truly interested in your answer, BTW. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Essentially Bannon was paid 500,000 to protect himself. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

President Biden transcript from the US Conference of Mayors

Combat disinformation by taking directly from sources for reporting.

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was something I have felt all through the pandemic. that no one cares about certain populations, because if they passed they would save money for by the government. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who buys anything named "Gilead" was thinking it was something else. 
We know where "Captain" Ron Paul's thinking is at. 
"White Wellness." #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My podcast today covers this story with my commentary.

Please check my profile for the pinned tweet at the top that is the podcast, called Monday Madness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon, future jail-bait seems "concerned" as he listens to a woman, who stands on the shoulders of "Liberal-leftist" women who fought for equal rights to even be allowed into west point whine about protecting her fellow country-folks from a lethal virus.nnSad. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MY THOUGHTS FROM THE SENATE HEARINGS

Tammy Duckworth is on the floor being frighted that our elections may be 'Federalized" and people might get "Healthcare". You cannot make this stuff up, folks. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last post, he was getting a snack, on Dec 28 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

Watch LIVE here:

Currently Nancy Pelosi is offering a moment of silence, and stating that no legislative business will be done today. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rudy Giuliani seems flushed and ready to go as he is surrounded mu muscly Trumpian beefcakes, and good looking fascists, as they make a Rudy Sandwich!! Former Cross dresser Rudy, seems beside himself with joy, 
Someday they will all come out of the closet together. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BEST DISS TWEET EVER FROM A SEATED POLITICIAN!! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They will return cruise ships to Hawaii, even  to the outer islands, where there are few beds, and fewer ventilators, and  now going through an unprecedented surge of infections and deaths.

Just like they did before. No one cares , cuz boats gotta boat. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#,   that do not like white supremacists, or folks that carry swastika flags around, are going to be counter protesting folks that are white supremacists and carry swastika flags around. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On #HASHTAG# Day, lets see some real threat. Lets face them and take action to stop them. As thousands of White Supremacists are flooding our nations school boards, in an attempt to eviscerate and erase Black History, lets do what we can to stop it.  Black Authors forced off shelves #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Replacement Theory? You mean, White Supremacy, and Nazi scare tactics?nnWhen we say 'Replacement Theory', its just "CRT" in reverse.nnIt sounds pearl clutchy. nnCan we just say it straight?nnWhite supremacy, and they hate Black folks   and Jewish folks being enlightened #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#

ALL LIVES IN ONE PLACE

Click here, to see each live-stream of each hearing and committee today.

#URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She was thinking, fame fortune grifting and general mayhem. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden turns the other cheek, in an example of what it really means, to celebrate the Eve of Jesus' birthday. #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>