<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[West Virginia managed to distribute just under 13% of its federal rent relief funds. Disgraceful.  #URL# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cities use exclusionary zoning, land-use restrictions to further segregate neighborhoods, drive up housing and rent costs. Revising Fair Housing Act to include economic discrimination might close one loophole. Hm? #URL# #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAPS IN CRISIS: Ipid registers criminal case against National Commissioner Sitole for dodging questions on Kinnear assassination #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sudan's pro-democracy movement hopes to force a transition to civilian rule #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Coup #HASHTAG#Uprising]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An architect of critical race theory: ‘We cannot allow all of the lessons from the civil rights movement forward to be packed up and put away for storage’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | The government abuses its power over pregnant teenagers — again #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democracy delayed in Mali spurs sanctions from neighbours #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tenants’ long wait for home ownership comes to an end this year #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Destructive game: analysis: EFF’s apparent U-turn on pan-Africanism raises questions about its stance on immigrants #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dance and despair for India in memory of murdered journalist Gauri Lankesh #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[14-year-old girl shot by police remembered at Los Angeles funeral #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal Bureau of Prisons confirms outbreak of COVID-19 cases at Mississippi prison #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Army Veterans Awarded $110 Million in 3M Earplug Lawsuit #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennessee Judge Who Illegally Jailed Children Plans to Retire, Will Not Seek Reelection #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happened to Christina Tahhahwah? Just another Native American jail death #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alabama bill stops short of ending all shackling of pregnant women - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We’re Going to Talk About ‘Bruno,’ Yes, Yes, Yes #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Striking Clover workers meet to discuss way forward #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jordan’s sole refuge for people with disabilities risk closure as COVID-19 dries up donations #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billionaire’s Star Rises as She Takes Bold Stance on Racism in Brazil #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Domestic workers are women workers are workers. Period. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex Traffickers Target Teenage Girls in Nigeria’s IDP Camp - Women’s Media Center #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what "return to normal" looks like: ignore pandemic, ignore needs, 30 days behind and you're out, period. And they call it "public housing", but there's little concern for the actual public.  #URL# #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Southern Africa's Namaqualand daisies are flowering earlier: why it's a red flag #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stem cell donor: Son gives father a second shot at life #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Explainer: Why is marital rape not a crime in India – and can the courts make it one? #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From mercenaries to citizens: how the Nubians gained acceptance in Uganda #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world’s 500 richest people became $1 trillion richer last year #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The power behind Sudan’s protests via #USER# #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Uprising]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Abortion Law, the U.S. Is Unusual. Without Roe, It Would Be, Too. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change what South African men think of women to combat their violent behaviour #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Nothing Will Be the Same’: A Prison Town Weighs a Future Without a Prison #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elderly woman forced to isolate under a tree in remote community due to lack of facilities  #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sudanese forces open fire on anti-coup protesters, killing 7 #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#Coup #HASHTAG#Uprising]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Va. News: Hospital capacity and marking medical history #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15+ years sexual harassment, discrimination against women, gay, bisexual men. Refused housing, if applying; evicted, if tenant. Pays largest settlement ever; dismiss retaliatory eviction decisions, repair credit of affected tenants #URL# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zelma Lazarus (1936-2022): Creator of the Lifeline Express hospital train touched a million lives  #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Healthy Births for Incarcerated Women: Women are the etc. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge throws out massive Gulf of Mexico oil and gas lease sale #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Where are my rights?” African refugees vs. UNHCR in Lebanon #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghanistan faces widespread hunger amid worsening humanitarian crisis #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to know who is most vulnerable to COVID? Here's an index that can do that #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happened to Mariam Abdullah and Rebecca Maher? Just another death in custody #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Latika Roy Foundation Is One of India’s Prized Assets #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe's marginalised Roma people hit hard by coronavirus #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The relationship between incarceration and premature adult mortality: : Gender specific evidence  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100 people, two ruined toilets, and “no-one cares” #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revealed: the Flint water poisoning charges that never came to light #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joni Mitchell Plans to Follow Neil Young Off Spotify, Citing ‘Lies’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if every country were renamed according to its most notorious prison? The Republic of Zimbabwe could become the Republic of Chikurubi. The United States of America could become the United States of Guantanamo. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ACLU Demands Better Protection of Pregnant, Postpartum and Nursing Women in CBP Custody #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Northern Virginia Schools Immediately Vow To Defy Youngkin’s Order Ending Mask Mandates. Good News.  – DCist #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lauren Smith-Fields died of an accidental overdose on a Bumble date, police say. Her family disputes that.  #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Activision Blizzard employees continue strike, ‘Call of Duty’ players bark about bugs #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've received death threats, State prosecutor in Ssegirinya, Ssewanyana case tells court #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Portraits of resistance: A photo book recalls the courage of the CAA-NRC protests  #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An upcoming British edition of 'Capitalism and Slavery' makes news, but the Caribbean has always known the book's worth #URL# via #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redwood Forest in California Is Returned to Native Tribes #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘The ice is separating!’: Dozens of fishermen rescued in Wisconsin after big ice chunk breaks off in Green Bay #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chicago’s “Race-Neutral” Traffic Cameras Ticket Black and Latino Drivers the Most #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richest 1% of UK households are worth at least £3.6m each #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Landlord adds a clause to the lease that says, for a modest reduction, tenant gives over to the landlord the power to evict during an eviction moratorium. 100% illegal. But hey, tenants have to know that, right? #URL# #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Found Him Writhing in Pain': Family of UP Teenager Who Died After 'Police Assault' #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India strips millions of women in Assam of their citizenship. Call it femicide #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few pills a day could keep severe COVID away: What you need to know about two new treatments #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donors to the rescue of special needs school looted in July unrest #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK’s propaganda leaflets inspired 1960s massacre of Indonesian communists #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Coronavirus Testing Is Falling Short in Many Schools Across the U.S. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not nice ... and typical. In the US, the struggle for affordable housing involves turning single family zoned districts into multifamily, denser. In both Jamaica and the US, of course, the issue is the level of corruption within `development', historically and today. Good luck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New research: how Covid-19 has made life harder for South African women #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laboring for Home: Working to Stay, Working to Move #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys Sold by Trusted Villager Turned Human Trafficker | Inter Press Service #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sacramento sheriff is hiding information about jail COVID outbreaks from the public #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In PG County, MD, Black Brown women lead struggle against eviction, for permanent housing, rights, dignity. Nationally, among renters, 5 in 10 Black women, 4 in 10 Latinas report living in households w delayed rental payments #URL# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did people pay rent? Borrowed from family, friends; SNAP. For low income households, impact of lost income total, requires total support, legal aid, help w moving costs, credit repair, assistance w deposit, costs for new place  #URL# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rich man, poor man: the income of 1% of the richest Namibians is equal to the combined income of the bottom 50%.  #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Honduras, Barbados and beyond, women direct the conjunctural moment of hope #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Promises Made By Modi, Khattar Unfulfilled, Anganwadi Workers Continue Strike in Gurgaon #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black Sexual Violence Survivors Are Telling Their Stories — Only to Be Punished #URL# via #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grim reality of domestic workers portrayed in poem #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prime minister, as a refugee I have done everything Australia has asked. Nine years on, why am I still in detention? | Mehdi #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five Guatemala soldiers sentenced for raping Indigenous women #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Va. parents file lawsuit, schools vow resistance against Youngkin’s order making masks optional #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colombia saw 145 activists killed in 2021, ombudsman says #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahmaud Arbery’s killers sentenced to life in prison, two with no possibility of parole #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Syrian refugees that time – and Canada – forgot #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech-boosted English classes reach more migrants #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The EFF surrenders a key progressive principle #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In South Africa, a victory for Jane Bwanya, the Constitution, and equality for all! #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where is the global outrage at the destruction of Kashmir and the assault on Kashmiri women? #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘The biggest task is to combat indifference’: Auschwitz Museum turns visitors’ eyes to current events #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ISIS, Thriving in Unstable Places, Proves It’s Still a Threat #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Load shedding and food insecurity: The plight of students’ food insecurity in South Africa’s  higher education landscape #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Central African refugees are caught between a rock and hard place in the Democratic Republic of the Congo #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marshals Service employees have alleged racism for decades. Their case may finally be heard. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls are criminalized for `misbehaving’, boys aren’t. Running away, skipping school, disobeying a parent sends girls to juvenile detention. It’s been like that forever, and it continues, especially for girls and gender expansive youth of color.  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalist killings in Mexico raise concerns among colleagues #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysing Women’s Labour In India’s Gig Economy #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A life’s work to heal centuries of grave injustice #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our asylum system should prioritize giving asylum seekers a fair shot to make their case. Instead, we start with the goal of a quick deportation. #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hundreds at Rikers Protest Conditions, Citing Covid and the Cold #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis | Djokovic Debacle Exposes Australia’s Xenophobic Policies #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rape trial of Greek sailing coach begins as #HASHTAG# gains ground #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no data on people harassed into moving out. Not surprisingly, given the moratorium, the number and rate of informal evictions increased during the pandemic.  #URL# #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lauren Smith-Fields Was Found Dead. Her Family Had to Beg for Answers. #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farmers Reject Nicor's Pipe Dream #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apartment fire victims mourned in mass funeral: ‘People are dying because they lived in the Bronx’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For C.D.C.’s Walensky, a Steep Learning Curve on Messaging #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Carrot and stick' regulations aim to increase shallow aquifer use #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Most Livable City?’ A 30-Year Gap in Life Expectancy Exists Within Vancouver  via #USER# #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world is ruled by women who fight: The Sudanese women’s revolution continues #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not enough housing, too many people with money looking to move, and, oh yeah, predatory speculators add to a toxic stew that will last for years #URL# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada must end the over-incarceration of Indigenous people #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bordering on peace: Mexico and the United States #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caribbean Virgins, Caribbean Whores: Unlacing Goodness / Dismantling Perversion #URL# #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honduran president’s fall from grace poised to end in US indictment #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Third lawsuit seeks 'meaningful change' a year after reported physical, sexual assaults at NJ women's prison #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate-resilient 'super beans' boost food rations for refugees in #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congo Basin peatlands have trapped years' worth of carbon. How can they be protected? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Outlandish Bird and Its Army of Women #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five African Countries. Six Coups. Why Now? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watchdog criticises Government over Female Offender Strategy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seclusion rooms at mental health facility 'inappropriate' - Chief Ombudsman #URL# #HASHTAG#  #USER# #USER# #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Killed by indifference’: France shocked by death on busy Paris street #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalist Sajad Gul was booked under PSA as he could have got bail otherwise: J&amp;K administration #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tropical Storm Ana kills more than 70 in Madagascar, Malawi and Mozambique, leaving thousands stranded #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three Union Kitchen Stores Seek To Unionize – DCist #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California’s cruel and usual prisons: who cares? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politicians divided South Sudanese refugees. Sport can re-unite us. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 32,000 late school applications, says Western Cape Education Department #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Tennessee couple tried to become foster parents. They were denied because they’re Jewish, lawsuit says. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PAUL TIYAMBE ZELEZA - The Possibilities and Perils of Leading an African University | The Elephant #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Atlantic route to the Canary Islands saw the highest death toll in over a decade. Mass tragedies involving migration have increasingly become normalized #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africa parliament fire suspect charged with ‘terrorism’ #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Denmark’s hard line on Syrian refugees is an aid group’s ethical dilemma: #URL# (#USER#) #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A self-described ‘Freedom Convoy’ of Canadian truckers opposed to vaccine mandate arrives in Ottawa. And who funds this?  #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The smell of money: why locals think Peru’s billion-dollar fishmeal sector stinks #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Mexican states roll out vaccination mandates for bars and events   #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rents, home prices skyrocket; wages relatively stagnant; affordable housing stock diminishing; rate of evictions stayed high through the last year, of which 35% were approved, which is a high rate.  #URL# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turkey third country with most content removal requests from Twitter - english #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL# South Sudanese refugees face uncertain future in #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Community project helps Kenya aim for climate goals one mangrove tree at a time #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Bulli Bai’ And The Gendered Layers Of The Objectification Of Muslim Women #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More migrant deaths were recorded in South America last year than in any previous year. Mass tragedies involving migration have increasingly become normalized #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LITTER BUGS: Hawkers suffer while pollution suffocates Komani River #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ANAND MADHVANI - We Are Not the Wretched of the Pandemic | The Elephant #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alberta Court to Australian Coal Baron: You Lose  via #USER# #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Podcast: “As a Muslim and a woman, I am the most vulnerable in this country today” #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is Canada still deporting Roma people to persecution? #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police chief calls for new ‘spiking’ offence  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[J&amp;K Police Affidavit Shows Army Made Contradictory Claim on Hyderpora 'Gunfight' Intelligence #URL# via #USER#  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘I started campaigning before I could even vote!’ Amika George on period poverty, politics and the power of protest #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18,000 people have been fined for doing what Boris Johnson did #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kidney Failure, Emergency Rooms and Medical Debt. The Unseen Costs of Food Poisoning. #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At one Texas prison, men are building community through radio #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They Promised Quick and Easy PPP Loans. Often, They Only Delivered Hassle and Heartache. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maryland lawmakers put forth bill to remove racist senator’s name from Chevy Chase Circle #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From France, more than a bill, an act of resistance for women’s rights #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Children of immigrants ‘held back by employer discrimination’ in UK #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In ‘African Origin’ Show at Met, New Points of Light Across Cultures #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Venezuela, a soldier can be sent to prison for being gay. The courts could change that. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAYS OF ZONDO: NPA and Hawks face ‘Herculean’ task in wake of part one of Zondo Commission report, establish task team to review cases #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report on parliament fire confirms systems failure #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#: Bring back the thousands, bring back the hundreds, bring back the one #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outspoken Saudi princess released after nearly three years in jail #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16 Men Died in New York City Jails Last Year. Who Were They? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fairfax County supports increase in state contribution to Housing Trust Fund to $125 million, new housing tax credits, down payment assistance, state funding for legal aid for tenants facing eviction #URL# #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For now". One of area’s largest landlords, RRHA previously lead in filing eviction lawsuits in community ranked high nationally for evictions. What is public about public housing? Not service, the public or housing #URL# #HASHTAG# #USER#  #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mass tragedies involving migration have increasingly become normalized: Europe saw historical highs in migrant deaths.  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FCI Waseca did not fail to assure the safety of incarcerated women; it refused to do so #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chemical pollution has passed safe limit for humanity, say scientists #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E.P.A. Chief Vows to ‘Do Better’ to Protect Poor Communities #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seed exchange in Colombia promotes traditional knowledge and food sovereignty #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bullying: Going back to school a nightmare for some kids #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frustration grows over deaths and ill treatment at immigration detention centers in Japan - The Mainichi #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Domestic work and the global: Sri Yatun’s story #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whistleblowers allege abusive culture at Women's Huron Valley Correctional Facility #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Nova Institution for Women, Canada’s special hell for women, COVID runs rampant #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heart attack patient raises alarm after NHS advised him to make own way to hospital #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales of Electric Vehicles Surpass Diesel in Europe, a First #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugandan writer charged for tweets about Museveni, son #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Ayotzinapa Chapter 3: All Souls
A mother prays that she will one day know the truth about what happened to her son. #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earth Has Exceeded Its Safe Limit for Chemical Pollution  via #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perspective | How a teenager got more women of color added to history lessons in one of the country’s largest school systems  #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For allegedly cheering Pakistan cricket team, Kashmiri students charged with cyberterror, sedition  #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘We’re being pushed into poverty’: Voices of women who took on the unicorn start-up Urban Company #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perspective | Youngkin’s tell-on-a-teacher tip line drew jokes, but behind the laughter is a serious concern #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fears for African refugees as coronavirus hits crowded Rome squat #USER#  #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do Indians want from the Budget? A ‘Covid surcharge’ on those who profited from the pandemic #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OPINIONISTA: Mental health in this time of virus capitalism: Now more than ever, we need revolutionary acts of love #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In South Asia, a virtual platform to share and to heal for survivors of abuse #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drugs, real estate and money laundering in Senegal #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ECONOMIC FASCIST FIGHTERS: Bitter taste: Migrant gives SA R100m vaccine boost while Julius Malema sticks it to foreign restaurant staff #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cville `paying attention' to housing inequality, but Black households, esp Black women-headed households, still suffer most displacement, eviction, harassment. City plans to change its zoning laws   #URL# #HASHTAG# #USER# #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Affordable housing for youth who age out of foster care. 23,000 every year, across the U.S.,36% of whom, disproportionately Black, Latino, Native American, end up living on the streets, to absolutely no one's surprise.  #URL# #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Inside Pakistan's first retirement home for third-gender people #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Coup in Burkina Faso, Protesters Turn to Russia for Help #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Refugee Day: Grassroots groups support African refugees in Covid-19 struggle #URL# via #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘For the first time, I felt free’: Pakistan’s women-led livestock market #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deaths in Scots prisons are rising as figures confirm 'worst fears' of families #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>