<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# All white people were expelled from India. India a country England was said to have colonized for 200 yrs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Look at the cabinet. I said when Trudeau met privately with Canada's most powerful Imams before 2015 election he promised them run of ROC under Quebec auspices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Remember when the multimillionaire greedy butts and telford stuck it to the taxpayer for moving expenses?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right in time for Christmas. Next variant just before Easter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I just know to put this threat on a pregnant woman is evil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I took the shots under duress like many have. I am not anti vax. I'm anti fascist mandates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Post national Canada. While Quebec becoming more nationalistic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many people coming to realize they've been lied to on a massive scale. As the Conservative populist wave began with Trump and went around western world covid used to derail it. Now they need something massive to cover covid plandemic #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# O'toole first off the mark condemning truckers for media contrived statue/ flag nonsense. Right up his alley. Pleases media. Acts patriotic. Stabs brave patriots in the back. Make no mistake these truckers ARE patriots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's what Trudeaus attacks on white English speaking Cdns is all about. Uniting all these groups against whites. Demonize whites as racist while flooding ROC with immigrants. The Quebec way of keeping power]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Strange how in towns outside GTA young white men are working in stores and fast food restaurants. In GTA even areas with sizable white populations almost no young white Cdn workers. These are in grocery and drug stores too. Replacement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That would have been an intelligent response. The left know Cdns have been so beaten down with political correctness for decades they immediately cower in defense.Same when they use white supremacy, instead of ignoring we try to defend ourselves. Fcku em.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I felt sorry for the girl. May have been her first job. Maybe a student. The men looked in their 30's. Funny thing is this area one of the few areas left in T O with mostly whites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Far left rebranded NDP but power still based Quebec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Multiculturalism is invasion. Japan isn't allowing masses of foreigners to come in and push out their people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Toronto police can send 4 officers to arrest unmasked man but say they can't respond to the many calls they get every day because they're understaffed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In US blacks are largest group rejecting vax. The carpetbagger brings in massive immigration to ROC and turns them against white anglo men.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Is that due to massive testing around Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Interesting choice of words. He could have just as easily said Cdns given his penchant for rrplacement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Immigration is a racket. Can you imagine the $trillions being made off this mass transfer of people. To add to the robber barons wealth we're destroying our energy industry so investment syndicates can invest in middle eastern low paid energy worker labour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Globalist news. Always Far right while far left NDP  Bloc Liberal coalition get a pass #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How do police get there so fast and so many. I recall waiting hours for police to respond when a friend was threatened by neighbours. Many people don't even bother calling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I'm triple vaxxed and was at rally. I have no right to demand others get vaxxed. Pure cowardice to not show up by Conservatives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# $14k per employee and remember most provinces under different stages of covid restrictions in 2020.Some even had lockdowns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They reject our constitution. Why is that? Why do they refuse to respect our  constitution? Send them packing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trudeau tipped globalist hand. Even Torstar ridiculed his taking 50k Syrian refugees. Now he says 40 k and no one blinks an eye.Conservatives can't pretend any longer  We know they moderate globalists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mayo of Toronto announces non white people will be given priority in obtaining gov't housing. Majority of immigrants for years non white and already were head of line for gov't housing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Its insulting to Christians. Look it up. Freeland wished Muslims happy Ramadan. She never said to them seasons greetings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Of course the Star always concerned about minorities and don't give a shit about Quebec lording it over ROC. Cut them loose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It seems lgbt,feminists  and newcomers on record to bring in UN agenda to English Canada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Bill C75 allows prosecutors to reduce penalties for crimes like rape and child trafficking to fines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Meanwhile mayor and Toronto city council say non white people to get priority for subsidized housing. They just made it official because its been that way for some time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simply Amazing with that many people coming  together with so few problems. 2 flags,some garbage. Its all they got. I'm waiting for their next bombshell,lets hope no truckers are caught saying the "F" word in front of these thin skinned aholes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Our hospitals were overwhelmed in Ontario since at least Wynne.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# An English prison is still way above the life they had in Africa. Its actually an improvement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Betrayal is a horrible thing. Politicians disguising themselves as Conservative will not be acceptable any longer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# For decades elderly scapegoated as tax burdens. In Toronto they're bringing in drunks. 40yrs old and up. They will never work and will be provided with benefits for life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First it was cabdrivers, then gas stations, then department stores, grocery and drug store chains. Health industry. Left destroying high paying energy sector jobs. Soon Quotas will be instituted in the trades #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The fact this race baiting Guy that has never got more than 26 seats in 2 elections and media give him so much attn. Speaks volumes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I don't apologize for being white. Or need non white approval. Even in areas in GTA with large white populations there are very few businesses with whites. Grocery store chains and pharmacies hire mostly non whites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He will knuckle under to his Quebec overlord. Ford should for once show some spine and refuse locking down Ontarians while Trudeau allows Illegals to cross at Roxham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should Quebeckers be allowed to hold cabinet positions when Quebec hasn't signed constitution #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And taking one of the great men of history off our $10 bill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Would you be called a Conspiracy theorist if when these vaccines first come out you said  we will be conned into multiple vaccines a year. 4th shot started in Toronto. 4th  shot in 12 month period.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ha. AT least its piled up. and neat . I see so much filth in Toronto now especially along once pristine ravines. Grow up, do yo get out much. This would be considered a neatly packed stack of garbage in Toronto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor Tory is afraid to say that guns is not the problem,take away the guns and you have stabbings every day anyway. Too much immigration is the problem. Maybe Tory should be talking about racism against white poor people in applying for subsidized housing #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The press is left. The difference between left and right is left seldom wavers from the plan. The politicians on the right seem to crave acceptance by media. Only Trump and a few American pols challenge media and know how to fight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Meanwhile I see co ops and Ontario housing filled with young Hispanic and Black illegals while our own poor are being pushed out if shelters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Its always in English Canada isn't it. The Quebecker never spreads this divisiveness in his beloved Quebec. Every Quebec PM since Pierre Trudeau has been undermining white men in ROC. Securing their non white base by uniting them against whites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He used to speak at Catholic churches in the US and Canada.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# When Trudeau called White men outside Quebec racists and misogynist it should have brought gov't down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The Conservative populist movement died after their first meeting with Trudeau.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If its like GTA this problem existed long before covid. We had people rec'g care in beds in hospital hallways long before covid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Of course all the white Christian mayors in major muslim oil producing countries appalud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# India  cleansed all whites from that nation,  1.5 billion Indians and not one white person in any gov't. Its basically war against whites going on for over 100 years. Mainly thrpugh immigration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Some poster on here said the mughuls responsible for 80 million deaths in India over the centuries. I doubt that or else we would hear about it.Or would we? Then there was and is persecution of christians for centuries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Guns are used in crimes, people stabbed and perpetrators right back on street. Media drops story lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They're only effective in putting their feet on the necks of Canadians. With help of bully media that slap us down the minute we dare question globalist narrative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You can't beat that combination. Big Pharma has been trying for decades]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We know hospitals were overwhelmed in GTA long before covid. As a matter of fact hodpitals were beginning to feel the pinch around the mid 1990's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I saw patients lined up in beds in hospitals hallways. They were being treated with very little privacy. I saw this in 2 hospitals in GTA. Long before covid and during Wynnes time. 100k immigrants a year in Toronto alone  our system is overloaded]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# White people don't have their own doctors. The only occupations not victimized by tfws and economic migrants are  journalists and teachers. That will change as their usefulness not needed now. They were judas goats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The pink turban. Hospitals in some GTA hospitals stopped showing results of sex of unborn; turns out unborn females aborted and male births far outnumbered females.SubsequentlyLiberal party condoned sex selective abortions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# C'mon Brian. I've been  to plenty of freedom marches. Never heard racist comments. You're promoting a lie. Fcku Trudeau. What about when he called white Canadian men outside Quebec misogynist and racist. You should demand an apology from him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I still find it horrific we  had politicians in this country who brought in preferential policies to persecute white Cdn men. At the same time increasing immigration from non white countries. Evil pure evil. 40 years of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harper, Kenny, Joe Clark and Brian Mulroney. Globalists all #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto police make two arrests in months-long human trafficking investigation #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The goal of every western gov't seems to scold and shame its people into submission. MASS immigration is one way ti take a country right out from under its people. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did he say that in English in Canada. I notice Quebec politicians push the racism narratives against white Anglo men. Quebec carpetbagger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We've had hospital hallway medicine for years before covid. Feds increase immigration to Ontario and ROC while Quebec decreases its immigration. Increasing number of seniors using foodbanks and Canadian homeless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# and here we were worried about a staged violent event. Cdn media is so Controlled and people so brainwashed they turned these simple acts into an issue. Years of watching protests of every sort. People stood on statues and memorial even draped flags around never an issue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Saw video on another site. Can't find it anywhere here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# City gov'ts in Ontario formally came out and announced subsidies will be given first to nonwhites and immigrants. Poor white Cdns can pound sand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If this was Mel Gibson who pointed the gun on a movie set news media wouldn't be so forgiven.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Same in Canada. Our PM has banned Christians from the Liberal party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't it amazing how after decades of denigrating our culture and history. Of having statues torn down and founder taken off currency. All of a sudden these journalists, mayors Premiers, party leaders said nothing but all of a sudden their SO offended and so patriotic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# interesting all media cover the same things and ignore the same things. Interesting African refugees covered daily and Ukraine and Sth Africans whites ignored. Amazing how little attn paid to our old rec'g hallway care and how much attn paid to providing housing for newcomers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doug Ford chose to tweet about January vaccination at same time as start of game. All the tweet responses saying he didn't go far enuf. Why do I think those are bot responses #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In Toronto the Left wants to cut back on police spending and put more into housing. Toronto council announces non white people will get priority for subsidized  housing.Its been that way for years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lets get the discussion going relentlessly. Our system is in need of change. God bless these truckers. I saw the wonderful people lined along roadsides and on overpasses. They know our country is being hijacked. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Toronto Sun gov't funded? Is this why columnists kept pushing Gov't to take large numbers of "refugees".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The western world is bringing about its own demise. Want to see what the globalists want for us. Watch the commercials on tv. White men have practically been deprived of representation. They're turning us against each other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When Terry Fox made that run; Cdns never would have accepted these lockdowns. 1981.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Before he was taken out  Ghaddafi threatened if anything happened him African "refugees" would flood europe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nonsense. Putting a flag on a national symbol. I call bullshit to your opinion you  hoped to avoid commenting on convoy. Like the rest of bought media you were waiting for something you could pounce on or sink your teeth into. Like this nonevent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# First we have to get rid of damnable preferential policies penalizing white english Cdn men. Over 40 years of it. Whites minority in GTA and still victimized by preferential policies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# An immigration system so porous, allowing over 1 million from Africa Asia Latin America forming voting blocs and our politicians whoring for their vote. The individual vote meaningless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# According to Gary Allens book  British and American bankers financed Bolsheviks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Media and politicians creating propaganda white supremacy is a major force as a political movement. Over the last 150 years whites have been driven out of every African and Asian nation. All immigration has been from non white to white nations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ford did the same thing. The Star was stroking him for a while and he was purring. Ford called Freeland a champion. The Star was praising him. Then they turned on him. They sucked him in big time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't you just love it when one of the foreign born cabinet ministers trudeau put in Canada's cabinet to lord it over us call to replace white people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# biggest for me is the parade of politicians at every level using the mantra they are keeping us SAFE. In high school in 1968 /69  Hong Kong flu we never had them come out with shit like that. This SAFE BS appeals to the many newcomers from areas  where gov'ts micro manage lives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Just keep flooding Ontario to keep Conservatives gov'ts behind the 8 ball with hospital care. Daycare, education spending. Create the problem then blame the premiers for not keeping up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a month ago. No shaming and scolding for non Christians]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We need a Canadian version with they can stick mass immigration up their ass added]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What about his personal chef? Do people believe this bullshit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Systemic racism was when PET stopped immigration from western Europe and it carroes on to this day. Systemic racism is preferential policies first brought in by Brian Mulroney when he doubled immigration. Systemic racism is successice govt's ignoring South African refugees]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# China is behind the illegal migration from Africa to the west if you ask me. Why Trudeau and Biden don't ban athletes from going to Olympic games is behold me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Our gov'ts unlike Japan not interested in its people. The retail boom, minimum wage and mass immigration go hand in hand. To secure control by globalists and rig elections.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trudeau should demand Blanchet apologize for saying you were a terrorist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Interesting point and I heard that red haired people will all but be non existent in about fifty years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I tell you they have abandoned Old stock Cdns. Its all about the non white new immigrant vote. In GTA thats #URL# immigrants and non whites want no part of Canadians. They detest them. That's why they never attend these marches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If whites are not having children and you increase immigration; that's replacement. Our immigration levels since 1980's rose every year. We are taking in more in a high tech low labour intensive economy then in 50's to 70's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# From a leader, any leader, let alone PM its Despicable. Certainly since he went out of his way to target one group; white males outside Quebec. Certainly warrants non confidence vote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lots of highrises already built and planned in GTA. Toronto has hundreds of highrises planned. 80 and 90 stories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why would they be embarrassed about brave people fighting for freedom. They are not embarrassed by brave men who fought wars to keep this country free either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He realized his previous message was cultural appropriation by omitting Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Conservatives have been left of centre since Joe Clark. Clark still has influence in that party. Open borders Joe and Brian Mulroney. Conservatives retreating ever since]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 4 years. A lot of Trudeaus immigrants will have voting rights by then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COVID-19 no longer a ‘socially critical disease’ in Denmark, health minister says #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Cdns will wake up when the country has been taken out from under them. Too late]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Almost 40 and a teacher when he did that. In the year 2000. Media gives him a pass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Sorry to see so many of the convoy commentators who backed convoy getting sucked in. Disgusting to see them scour to prove they're not supremacists. The left  called their tune and they jumped]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CSIS destroyed secret file on Pierre Trudeau, stunning historians #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our hospitals have been overwhelmed for 20 years in GTA and getting worse.👇 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why? Why not concentrate on Singhs hateful spiel. Or Trudeaus anti white rant. Hundreds of 1.000s  of marchers across the country. 99.9 % of them good. Why let the left derail you. Stop jumping to their tune]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Canada picking up the tab for countries that are REFUSING to stop overpopulating. We shouldn't be importing their mess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mr Trudeau bars pro life people from his party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If truckers asked for permit Far left city council would have rejected it giving police authority to stop trucks from entering. They're here now. Hold the rally and use gofundme funds to pay fines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Gov't sent police to intimidate entire Christian congregations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I support the truckers. They should keep in mind the deviousness of the government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Covid has destroyed the election  hopes  for the wave of conservative premiers elected a few years ago. It has split conservative voters and united the left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I started following this. Shocked to see some " journalists" even handed reporting. Lo and behold if I just didn't read them condemn convoy because of two flags which were IMHO plants by the left. Don't ever believe them. They sucked Ford in so much much he turned on his base.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Be interesting to know the colour of those let go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I find that hard to believe but I saw a young Cdn girl working the counter at a coffee shop. Her colleagues were two men in late 20's or early 30's conversing in their own language. They spoke English but why bother]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I buy monthly pass for $128. Seniors.  Toronto council wanted to abolish senior discount make us pay full . I've seen seniors not have enough on their presto card being centred out by drivers for not enough fare. If u don't buy pass its easy to lose track how much u have on card]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If you don't fall in line with liberal dogma ur automatically labeled racist. Clever of Trudeau Singh Nenshi to label anti lockdowners and anti mask as white supremacist. Its a dog whistle to their base. Subtle form of hate speech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There really sucking the life outta Christmas. It used to be so cheerful when Business assns decorated city streets. In Toronto its been stopped. Doesn't even look like Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And Diwali. Last month Justin  visited Brampton and took part in a feast with a crowd of celebrants. No scolding for them its all sunshine and happy Diwali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Every western nation doing the same thing. Increasing immigration while locking citizens down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well done Andy thanks for your excellent work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# For the last 40 years in different phases. Whites minority in GTA and still victims of preferential policies brought in by Mulroney for federal sector and expanded gradually since. Reverse racism is the mild term for what I call it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I was in high school. No lockdowns.  a moon landing, woodstock and some very good movies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They have their own countries back home now they all get together to marginalize   Canadians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why are big box stores allowed to import workers from one country. Security firms too. If a company recruited only white people it would be racist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lets  have a board member of WEF running Canada. Personally I think if anyone replaces the overseer it will be even open borders Hussen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# GTA already now Ford wants thousands of migrants for rural area.  Feds using debt to build housing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How about that Mexican looking man who appears as a janitor. One time showing a stupid white man how to use a
 vending machine or new one where he shoots a puck with a shovel with white men so astounded they stand with their mouths open]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great meme. Its not just Trudeau. We had 9 years of Harper and his immigration minister Kenny. Kenny changed the demographics of GTA. Trudeau picking up the  immigration deluge. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I believe he's evil. Much of the left same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How can they afford to house young African refugees in brand new town homes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The scary thing is so many people think that is possible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Over 54 African countries all ruled exclusively by black people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# They've been beaten into submission by years of political correctness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# A 14 year old child stabbed to death last year outside Sherway Gardens. The Killer was out on bail for armed robbery. Media dropped story after a few days. Killer under 18 so probably out now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Side effects. Forcing perfectly healthy people to risk side effects]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Our Quebec overlords. Did people not see him bringing in foreigners in cabinetn to run ROC under auspices of Quebec.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The biggest swindle in history. Moving millions of people to the western nations. All the while gov'ts locking down its own citizens they're increasing immigration in every western country. Gov't using debt to give them housing and benefits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They did for Diwali. Our Quebec overlord even went to Brampton and participated in a large feast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Just like when I'm on a crowded TTC  bus. Every 2nd seat empty but people standing over you. With city ordering busses to keep windows open to fight covid you can see their breath vapour coming thru masks in freezing temps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They're actually bragging about increasing immigration while they locked Cdns down. Can they be more brazen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The deception is white supremacy. The reality is white removal. Like they head in most of Asia and Africa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's an interesting question. Congo not only has covid but outbreaks of measles and ebola not long ago #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That guy is pure evil. He betrayed the people who voted for him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# There's no way that almost all non whites in Toronto agree with these mandates. Over the months gov'ts have been gradually demonizing whites. Trudeau came right out and called  protesters  racists last week. Our politicians have been using dog whistles to new Cdns for years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It should be against the law for grocery; drug stores and other stores to refuse to hire whites so they can meet some gov't quota. Or to receive tax benefits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Kokanee groper blackface enthusiast race baiter to name a few. Great credentials for leader of a country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Grow some balls and demand NDP fire Singh for his hateful anti white racism. Those brave men didn't die to have our rights taken away or people like Singh spew his hatred]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tell Trudeau and Legault to stop sending Roxham rd crossers here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Even the most pro vaccine enthusiast must be getting a bit sceptical. Mayor Tory starting 4th dose for LTC in Toronto. How the fcku can anyone not be a little suspicious of shooting untested vaccines into your body 4x in less than a yr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Like any industry. If globalists weren't in charge these forced vaccines never would have happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Imagine if Quebec would have separated in 1995. No Quebec politicians working to undermine white people in ROC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Our politicians said nothing with constant attacks made against founders. Now they're so offended. They were gutless when leftists truly destroyed monuments. They're brave and patriotic now with towing the media /left line]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Exactly. I guess if he was around when thousands of Canadians fought in ww2 he'd be the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# People have been leaving small town Canada for decades. U are right. Why did Ford ask Trudeau to double economic migrants? Surely other areas if the country had unemployed to send]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Look at that cabinet our Quebec overlord installed to Lord it over ROC under Quebecs aegis. One straight anglo white man token]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That won't have much media coverage. Less than the Christmas parade massacre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Also thousands of habitually lazy who have an excuse to sit on their arse all day. Order in groceries order in meals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trudeau is taking in 50k how many more do u want]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lets not forget while Kenny immigration minister he flooded GTA with immigrants especially Raitt's Milton riding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ask when Quebec will sign onto constitution/ charter of rights and why he believes Quebec a separate nation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Looks like its adorned with phallic symbols.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why is this built back better bullshit pushed on well run western nations? Why not build back better  the 2nd and 3rd world back better by demanding the leaders  start looking after their people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We have a far left gov't of trudeau singh Blanchet centred in Quebec.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# People with anorexia identify as obese when they have ribs sticking out. Should we go along with them and say yes they are fat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Doubled immigration and introduced preferential policies in federal hiring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ontario and Quebec control it all. Premier Ford and Trudeau on same team. Kenny as well. Ford wants mass immigration to please developers Trudeau to maintain power for Quebec. Massive swindle in shifting to service economy. Canadian males thrown out of energy  jobs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Trudeau taking in 50k why are Cdns responsible for crimes committed by Taliban?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They run Canada. Liberals are centred  in Quebec.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I agree with u. He has been consistent and attended protests. If Theo ones to condemn any politician how Singhs Tweet today calling convoy drivers  who believe in superiority of white blood line]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Do we have a democracy? I would say our government has been slowly been taken over by globalists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Or disagree with our anti Canadian government granting special programs for non white people. As immigration continues to make whites a minority in cities]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I saw article. Millions of persecuted Christians he should write about. African Asian Warlords using immigration aided and abetted by Politicians and organized crime for decades]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There will always be the odd nutjob that waves fascist symbols or wears blackface. Dealing with hundreds of thousands a few nuts slip through. The good thing about convoy supporters is they don't support or vote for them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# India 1.5 billion people and not one white person in any government local or federal. Odd isn't it if England was said to have colonized India ata time India had 500 million people. Why can stores hire almost exclusively from there but it is racist to target hire whites?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I call bullshit. I don't think Canada is that much different and this wouldn't happen. Why doesn't she go to one of the all muslim countries that genocided not muslims. That's what people like this actually want]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Put money in hands of newcomers to keep retail sectors humming. All generated by debt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Quebec politician once again carpetbagging in English Canada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How could that guy who put those hateful symbols on the flag possibly think that was a good idea? I mean, we used to say the same thing about blackface. In high school in early 70's if someone wore blackface. How did they ever think that was cool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "I really mean it this time voice" Rex nailed it. The school marm constantly scolding shaming and now and then a pat on the head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Unconscionable. People line up at 7AM for appt. Many turned away at SDMs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Its been going on in Toronto for some time. I see it in the grocery, fast foods and drug stores. Replacement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Correction. At the time Great Britains population 10.5 million. Indias 500 million. How could they take it over? They built the railroads, introduced a common language which brought together constantly warring groups. If I'm not mistaken they also helped removing moghul overlords]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# FLQ did more to secure Quebec power over Canada than any politician. The threat of separation was used as a weapon for decades. Now they run it all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thirteenth and Lakeshore. Another area being ruined. Always was a safe area. Now entire city being turned into crime hole. What a shame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I guess the shaming and scolding of Trudeau and his far left media mob has taken its toll.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I said the same thing when this hysteria first started in Toronto. No masks but distancing. I saw all these people lined up to get in grocery. Six feet apart but still standing in same spot for 15 minutes breathing down each others necks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I would recommend 2 yr reserve training. We have that as volunteer service now. I weekend a month one night a week. Should be mandatory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Look at what Quebec PMs brought us. Multicultural mass immigration and destruction of English Canada. While Quebec controls its immigration and protects its culture. Flood ROC with immigrants then Quebec pols stir up immigrants against white Anglos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# When mayor Nenshi and Jagmeet Singh say anti maskers and anti lockdowners were white supremacists its obvious what these masks are for. Even anti white anglo Trudeau said anti vaxxers racists]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>