<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Half tempted to call out today because I already feel terrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# As someone who was once that, the indoctrination you go through is hardcore. I deployed during the height of the war in Iraq in 2006, and have not been fully the same since. It changes you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah chopping off heads, throwing gay people off buildings, enslaving women, totally legit guys. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Haha sorry for disinviting you to the Thanksgiving dinner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So damn proud of you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hahaha! Well you did a thing so that is what count. When the OR slows down today i'll try to come up with something ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dale Murphy is legit one of the nicest guys to ever play baseball or any sport, and racist cops got him heated. Prayers to his son. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I guess this means I officially got to stand at the back of the venue now. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LeBron trying to keep his man employed lol #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 20 year old just asked me if Taking Back Sunday was a 90s band...WELP ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not going out??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You've had a pretty great past couple of days! Glad to see it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pantera was the best band of the 90s don't fight me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# In Northern MX it still is. Just look at the Padres and Dodgers gear in Baja, last time I was in Sonora I saw alot of Diamondbacks stuff too. Not just new stuff, but throwbacks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good call. I just hate paying crazy delivery fee's ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet these kids totally weren't influenced by their parents. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could not have asked for a better group to handle the daily stress of working in an OR day in and day. Truly a family of veterans caring for other VETS! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I only referred to gays as fags guys what's the big deal? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Dis foo called the worker "Boy" he must be a fucking transplant....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I can say is please vote, and vote for Joe Biden. We got two choices, and he is clearly the better of the two. We can't afford another 4 years of the current asshole we have in office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh trust I get you, my fandom goes back to the Eddie Jones/Nick Van Exel days. I don't fault Lebron too much, but they've lacked direction and an identity ever since Phil left and Jerry Buss died. It sucks because this team means so much for the city. I like LeBron tbf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most Raider thing ever and that includes trading Khalil Mack for peanuts ðŸ˜‚ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTF is wrong with these people. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You almost forget the Chargers exist until you turn on the TV.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favorite Juninho goal ðŸ™Œ So glad he is back. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My feet are killing me and did enough cardio for 2 months but it felt so good being out there again. â¤ðŸ’ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They're both out of touch; One just uses the fear of another to keep the donations coming. They'll never get a cent from me unless they make changes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just like my toxic ex the Dodgers keep sucking me in ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yay protected tweets, because a certain person in my life creeps my Twitter....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally someone said it! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ITS DA JEWS!!!!!!!! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That is legit what the guy who hit me was doing. Just at a lesser speed, so glad to be alive ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nah he's too busy being a stalker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also it was via video chat cause I transferred for a promotion and damn so wanted to virtual hug my old boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buzz sustained. Girlfriend is cussing in Japanese thooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Navy veteran here, the current POTUS is a fucken abomination. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went for a 3 mile run and I felt alive. All the stress and crap I had to go through this past year felt like being released. Nothing but a new life ahead of me with the people I love first and foremost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Serio. He was not a serious candidate either, it was all a ploy to siphon off votes from Biden so people didn't have to feel guilty for voting for Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Need a 2 BR, because I want an office space. I saw some good stuff under 2k but then they attach an HOA fee. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because ppl can't possibly rehabilitate right? I worked with some who have served decades behind walls, and are some of the most humble around because they have a second lease at life. They acknowledge their crimes, but we as a society need to recognize they are still human. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# *Whispers* I have looked at housing there and can afford it now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than ever please! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Honestly thought Dorados would be way more drama but alasss. He played it safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You have the Reign right next to you too ðŸ‘ More fights, less $$$.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# July! ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If it is like mine tonight I am like.... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm always down for new podcasts! Will def give a listen on the drive home tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# SPERM DONOR ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# On the flipside we'll never score the rest of the season sooooo ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man I got to get use to being up this early for work again. Totally worth it though ðŸ™Œ #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I once saw a Filipina take a frying pan to her cheating husband. Nothing like waking up at 5 in the morning to the scenes of a white dude running the street in nothing but boxers lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fernando Valenzuela is probably the most famous athlete in the U.S. that Mexico ever produced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Never compare yourself to others, because we all have our own story to write. The fact you're still pushing is a victory and speaks volumes positively.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cancelling Bernie. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Before either was Section 8 in Chicago, Soldier Field was always rocking. Glad to see them back in the city after yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hell yeah leave it to the golden generation to slap the shit out of their boomer kids. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Awwww damn man that sucks! Hate to see formerly good places go bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# WTF! Talk about a bunch of running generalizations and elitism. What a clown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pope is more liberal then most Democrats lol #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many people need to die because of white terrorism? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No I get it, ECS exists for the first team and clubs with the Sounders name. Which is dumb that something like Tacoma Defiance even exists in the first place. Never understood the re-branding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Dad's aunt is 87 and fighting COVID right now, it is not looking good. She was like another mom to him and I just don't know what to say or help ðŸ˜”  Please keep following the guidelines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# White flight polluted their brains. I always laugh when people think Chicago is this place bordering on cartel level violence. Stop watching faux news boomers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No doubt about it, but it is still respectable for an exhibition race. It's not Daytona or Talladega after all?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ms. Gain, 1st grade, West Whittier Elementary. Whittier, CA. 1994. Gave me a love of reading and music that never went away. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Some openly embrace that model minority myth. A lot of Filipinos I served in the Navy with are more Republican and conservative then Alabama. Catholic Church plays a role too just like the Vietnamese community.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sooooo are you gonna go to the PDX date #USER#?? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well hey priorities, tailgates are worth the miss ðŸ’ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hearing him wanting cut veteran benefits and social security is making it all the more tougher.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Like I have to mute the TV broadcasts at times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It would be the wrong day anytime. Ghouls like that are trash, good on you homie for doing what was right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And CHRISTIANS can do no wrong am I right? #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# ðŸ˜ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It got me hyped after a few years of rudderless vision. Sold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Shield. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Plan on it hermano, good people exist out there and you're definitely one of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The 14 hour days, getting called in on day offs and the influx of scared PTs is just a grind atm. I had to take a breather ðŸ˜·ðŸ˜ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# *Totally not negotiating a contract offer from Chivas* It is just a coincidence lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stay grinding. The fact you acknowledge it, is the first step to progression. I had this ephiphany a few years back and I am so glad I did because it opened up alot of new opportunities. DMs are always open if you need advice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I mean in this election, it should not take any convincing. 170k dead in 6 months, wtf else are they suppose to say? If people can't see the contrast, they were going to vote for Trump anyways.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fuck that dude!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Mookie, but I miss this dude in LA. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dude. â¤ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I'm from Southern CA, but was stationed at NAS Lemoore. I liked my time there, it was different and laid back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't have that power ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy is a member of a church. #HASHTAG# Apparently being promiscuous is acceptable, but lord it's a sin to be a monogamous gay man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFG needs to be protected at all cost. I want to be 40 and in a punk band too ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hell yeah!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# BECAUSE THE BIG GAY MAFIA ERIN IS TRYING TO TAKE FREEDUMB AWAY FROM CHRISTIANS #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My beard will be gone by Monday and I am so sad...Damn you Rona making me wear n95s ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thanks bro! From Chaffey to this, it has been a grind the last 8 years. Hope all is well âœŠ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hi key want to take my Dad too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't be the only one on my TL stoked to have Tool on Spotify now ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ðŸ˜‚ Well that is one way to pass the time lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Same!!! I'm doing a staycation in a few weeks and gonna enjoy every minute of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DTLA on NYE, no other place I rather be ðŸ™Œ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So says the one who keeps replying back? You call others "emoprogs" yet get emo over Sirota #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They're both trash and just when I warmed up to LeBron I remembered why I dislike him so much lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm faded so I thought I was hearing things for a second ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# True that! I do miss all the nearby taquerias, carniceras, and all the other places though ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Autzen seems like such a fun place but I would have to go as a neutral because i'm going to die ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I know right!! One thing I respect about my parents is they always said it was their job to take care of us and to not worry about them. Now, that is hard for me to do, being that I am in well off financial state. So I def give them money or buy them stuff out of love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love all my peeps, and hope to see alot of you next season! First time STH and can't wait ðŸ’™ðŸ’› In the meantime my schedule is free âœŒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where the fuck is the GOP leadership!? Fucking spineless cowards afraid to do anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think those kids in those cages would love to attend a match. To be apolitical in this climate is a denial of basic human deceny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What the fuck!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Crabs in a barrel, I have a feeling people are going to start looking out for their own interests. Solidarity is not cutting it ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I used to pay attention to that lol Now I am like ehhhh, not here to please all I need is the real ones and those who make me happy ðŸ˜Œ I know you got plenty of those ðŸ’™ðŸ’›]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But $25 gift card thoooo lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't use the vet card often, but I take real issue with those who think blindly supporting a wannabe dictator makes you more "American" and "Patriotic" then others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They always want to make it on the hot ass days ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love Serie A and La Liga but the xenophobic and racist ass supporters just need to go already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Orange County is the worse....Save for Santa Ana.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nOt AlL CoPs aRe baD... #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lets just hope they don't destroy any more furniture after they start crying lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thanks for always being there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thank you, back at you! Hope the virtual date went well ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Intense AF. I'm not ready for tommorrow ðŸ˜·ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'll remember you as a constant light who makes others feel loved and respected â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooooo boy, they definitely are. Saw it first hand when I was in the Navy. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I keep seeing assholes like this race around without a care for anybody in the public. It's so fucking sad and horrible. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mitt Romney is giving Hawley the death stare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, just wow. Fuck the mask coming off, this is burning a cross at the MLK memorial. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #USER# can you play #USER# again? I want to see all of Glendale and North Hollywood at a match once more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Awww Bruce ðŸ˜¢ Hugs to you all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Dude I work in a hospital as an assistant chief in a department that primarily supports surgical procedures. We do not have enough PPE, so idk where you're getting that info.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monotone tweets lmaoooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# People don't realize how hard it is to beat an incumbent too. It does not happen often at the executive level.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I swear these people think 74 Million Americans are just going to shut up. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even when they piss me off nothing can make me quit this team. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never understood dudes who txt shit like this? Do you honestly expect the other person to be like "Sure that sounds great!"...LAFC is so trash ðŸ˜’ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's all about conformity and uniformity. When they say the military is not a democracy; They mean it. ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hopefully things change in November. It blew my mind how so many in California nearly fell for the Koch brother backed initiative. Thank god there was enough to say NO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Seriously. Idk where these people come from or their logic? It's not "Freedom" to ignorantly dismiss legit health concerns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Been to countless LA Kings games hermano, keep your eye on the puck, and enjoy the atmosphere. It's like a mix between a soccer match and a NBA game crowd wise. ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on DeKalb come in so I can sleep lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think it is great all around because  each region is so different. The north is definitely more influenced by the rancho culture;  While the south has a more indigenous feel to it. Hermosillo is underated as a food city.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See what happens when anti union sentiments take hold. Fuck charter schools too. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet your machines worked just fine you piece of shit. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get your money Corey. Time for the mini rebuild to start for the Dodgers. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of these takes on here are fucking too much. Republicans are actively trying to steal an election and people want to shit on Dems. Considering pandemic situations, Biden ran a great campaign. Next stop putting a Latinos in a monolith. We're different!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you have to like every fucking tweet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Aaaaaaaye i'm down. Gonna need a couch thoooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh god, gonna play this on the drive home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think that would be a pretty rad idea. You would probably get a few though upset that it wouldn't be in PDX proper tho. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's not about blaming the left, it's about realizing the reality of the situation. I think Biden is fucking trash, but he has reason and listens to people. Trump does neither on top of being a fucking fascist. That is the contrast I need, we can do nuances later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's funny how people want to claim "family" after ignoring you and your siblings/parents the last 10 years. Nah, I got no hate but that blood stuff means nothing to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hell yeah dude, it looks fresh ðŸ‘Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Here for you amiga if you ever need a talk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So after feeling like shit for a better part of the day; I feel fine. I think this vaccine is doing it's job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Gay, white, males creating a exclusionary culture? Why I am just shocked....#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This. They're just waiting to ride out Trump so they can recoup any lost standing within the GOP. Cowards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Too serious lol Like can I not have to work nights because I need the differential pay? ðŸ˜‚ Adulting is too difficult haha Gonna need a queen who can deal with me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Waaaaat? What the fuck were they suppose to do, Republican were going to vote regardless of posturing. Direct your anger at people who refused to vote in 2016 because their candidate wasn't the nominee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have an aunt who teaches HS Algebra in Kenosha, my hate for him is deep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ATM direct patient care, in normal times elective and emergency surgeries as a lead surgical tech. Grateful to not be furloughed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Juuuuuuly! Come hang â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Definitely one of the best LAHC bands to come out. I used to have a pullover but it got it lost when I moved back to the states from Japan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well they also had Congress when they came to power in 2016. I hope we flip the Senate in January.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I always get so heated when people ask me why I support El Tri, I shouldn't have explain when it is so blatantly obvious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# come hang ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the next one happens we're camping out in my living room ðŸ˜´ðŸ˜­ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mom: School cafeteria worker
Dad: Union Welder

Son: Surgical tech supervisor #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Get the hint dude, and stop being thirsty lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you soon Seattle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ooooo look at you, I just got a feeling i'm gonna need it when it happens ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ahhh girl, thank you for keeping me sane ðŸ’•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We might have a new president elect next week and I hope more than ever that we do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm just going to watch the 2002 MLS Cup and go cry. Sigi meant so much in those early years, and literally grew the game here. ðŸ˜­ #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I will gladly vote and volunteer for you if you ever choose to run for president ma'am. You represent all that is great and right about our country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While his crime is horrific, he paid his debt to society and headlines like this just perpetuate the cycle of the formerly incarcerated not being allowed to move on with their life. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait to see my friends again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh no ðŸ˜© Glad you're okay!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well no, but it was covered by other reputable news outlets soo...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Ayeee there you go ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm gonna love living alone again when this is over, but I hate it right now. My socializing is dead af.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I wish that was the case, I feel like I am 50 ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I very much feel comfortable in my aesethetic lol #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sadly probably not, the one time I did talk about racial profiling to a group of people I got made fun of so bad. Like this white dude from Arizona could not fathom being profiled for being Latinx or AA. Never said anything politically the rest of my time in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching my nephew #HASHTAG# ball it up has been awesome this year. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Same minus the work in 10 mins lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're a third world country masquerading as a first! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This hits so close to home because I have friends at both Cal Lutheran and Pepperdine. Either of them could have been there for whatever reason. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I will be in July!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# July 11-15th!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I want brunch from the spot in Eagle Rock ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They literally missed the whole point of the movie ðŸ¤·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My phone was acting weird this morning and it couldn't send txts sooo if you received multiple messages. That was me in a panic trying to figure it out in the most basic way ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yesssssss! If she is happy who cares? Not anybody elses business. The only thing wrong is that Giants jersey ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man take me back to seeing Lucero again. This pandemic sucks so much. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe Jermaine Jones signed with Ontario Fury. I might actually have to go to a game now after saying I would the last two years...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dedicate my day to all the strong women who have helped me become the man I am today. Wither it be my mom, sisters', friends, relationships, etc. You're loved and valued by me and I appreciate all of the lessons and advice you've given me. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# My ex was PerEZ so #HASHTAG# ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much for being "essential" ðŸ¤· #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG# The sons and daughters of "rapists", "terrorists", and "illegals" foot the tax bill for his secret service protection.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hates Mexican labor, but sure loves their prescription drug cost. America 2020 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you! Nothing but love for my Salvi gente. Low key your horchata is better ðŸ‘€ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Then again Google Maps doesn't mean anything lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a moving piece by #USER# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One lives in Florida and I want to see his meltdown in Gillum gets elected.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>