<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Last week Twitter literally suspended me for "misinformation" saying that studies suggest #HASHTAG# is an effective drug against covid #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Product of a whole year may cover a trip between London and Paris.

WEF is ran by a bunch of children who get billions from billionaires and governments to ", find solutions" and they come up with childish unproven concepts that don't make any economic sense at All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now you can produce beers and wines that have CBD and THC instead of alcohol.

This can potentially revolutionize the cannabis industry and at least when it comes to edibles, it can replace farming. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pentagon's middle finger to #HASHTAG#'s China puppet governor that ordered shutdown of US Navy's fuel storage facilities, bad for Hawaii economy, Good for #HASHTAG# + there'll be major US navy and air force expansion in S Pacific

 #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden's negotiator with Mullahs literally does mullahs PR and propaganda and is the mouthpiece of the anti-American terror regime that treats women like subhuman slaves 

Iranian women don't even have the right to expose their hair and he's cheering letting a few play soccer! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Left 10,000+ behind in Afghanistan without an evacuation plan after giving the Taliban greenlight to take over Kabul and now greenlighted Putin without an evacuation plan!nnBiden can deter Putin by giving Ukraine NATO membership &amp; deploying NATO troops to Ukraine, that simple #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Al Gore should take a trip and enjoy what he loves the most: ice and snow

Why is he in Florida?

Record Snow Sweeps U.S., Drives Northern Hemisphere Snow Mass 450 Gigatons Above 1982-2012 Average; + Scandinavia Suffered Cold December  #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's literally a sanctuary and global command center for many jihadis, Berlin and Paris have been catching up with London as well, specially north African Islamists who fled secular Arab states and used Paris as sanctuary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's an insult to millions of people protesting in the streets to label them as foreign agents like the typical Russian conspiracy theories whenever a Russian proxy regime is challenged by popular uprising. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Instead even tweeting about the studies that suggest benefits of medicine is banned

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama's homeboy finally got a decent job in the Biden administration #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We're talking about language not alphabet, Einstein. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤£

The languages invented or adopted alphabet afterwards

Vinca signs evolved for 1000s of years until Greeks reinvented them as their alphabet, like Arabs, ottoman Turks (later Latin) and Persians borrowed Aramaic alphabet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You can run psychological and disinformation operations, deploy trolls, etc to get people come out and protest, but Kazakhstan isn't even on Washington's radar and US doesn't have troll armies or cyber warfare assets of such. Russia, Iran and China do. If US could, it'd do Iran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# CCP is on its knees fearing the economic crisis that are emerging in China and its own long term survival. CCP's biggest fear is collapse of its empire and disintegration like the Soviet union]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Like what? Florida is more alive than ever, NY is dead, no tourist wants to visit NY because they can't go to a restaurant without Covid pass

Name some of her achievements, like yourself, has done nothing positive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even 500 charging cycles @ 2000 miles average means 1,000,000 miles, 5 times the maximum life span of most combustion engine vehicles

Battery Breakthrough Provides Five Times The Driving Range Of Lithium-Ion At A Lower Price | Torque News - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the difference between dictatorship and democracy

Dictators don't get their legitimacy from the ballot boxes, they're supreme and hold absolute power

In democracy, they get elected to serve and people have the right to protest if the elected leaders fail them #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CCP bluff knowing what kind of cowards they're dealing with in the white house after seeing how Biden handled Afghanistan, Iran and Russia

Otherwise CCP is frightened by the idea of all out war with the US knowing it'll not survive as a regime if Americans fight 'till the end #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Looks like a cats face when it's getting to attack and bite your head off ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She had a virginity surgery, but can take a whole fist after "losing" it ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Sounds like Twitter after the communists take full control of the US. Also a great idea for a sci-fi movie script]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've only seen tiny ones, they have different species]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While 100,000s of Chinese government PLA cyber army trolls AKA 50 Cent Army (wumao) flooded the social media in 2020 pretending to be BLM, in order to create chaos and help Biden, these Chinese people are also showing their love for the black people #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's spare change, blackrock owns $9 trillion in assets, about half of China's overall GDP, HSBC holds $3 trillion in assets. Evergrande's entire portfolio is less than $400 billion.

was a symbolic favor for CCP to give Chinese investors confidence and give evergrande lifeline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They can't comment on an ongoing investigation but since the day one they concluded that the former president had to be impeached (after leaving office ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚) because he clearly called for peaceful protests to bring the Senate attention to the election irregularities?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this covid? Either that worker was worked out while being sick or I suspect there might be a whole different pandemic there. Covid doesn't just kill people like that while walking in the streets.

Something is up in Xi'an #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They've always backed the Taliban (since the invasion) and follow Kremlin's guidelines. The objective is using taliban the same way they use al-Qaeda, Hamas, houthis, al-shabab... it's IRGC-Hezbollah top heroin supplier for 100% of Europe and American market]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone lost an amphibious tank, it's been floating near an Indonesian oil rig in South China Sea. 

Looks like it has a bunch of unpaid parking tickets too #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Lmao ðŸ¤£

How many hours do you think people worked under Mao and how much they earned? There was no money paid, they couldn't even grow food, they started producing iron in the farms and 20-50 million starved to death, after Mao killed anyone who resisted

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama's Make Russia Great Again foreign policy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think many people would feel more comfortable with robots that look like robots, even dogs and spiders, not humans. It creeps them out with all the doomsday sci-fi movies about human looking robots and terminator wars #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's not how things work in the US. Citizens, industries and whoever has a policy interest form NGOs and institutions that influence Washington decisions. In this case the mullahs, CCP, Russians, EU, globalists... and other mullahs friends have powerful NGOs, we don't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I call the Islamist black, not Green. Black is the color of most Islamists including Shia 12ers, ISIS, taliban, Hamas, alQaeda...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You need to provide identification to buy guns or get abortion in every state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many of the leftists still sympathize with taliban #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The people with the motive were the ones who had planned in advance to use that day as a justification for demonization, crackdown and incrimination of their political rivals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And driving a Toyota Corolla, probably everything he has were stolen from the people they murdered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Honestly, if NATO accepted Ukrainian as a member back in March and April when Ukraine was begging for expedited membership and before Kremlin caught up with the weakness of Biden administration, by now Russia would've been used to the new reality of Ukraine being part of NATO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran Islamic regime working with the smugglers, kidnapped her farther Ebrahim Babai in Maku (near the border of Turkey) while trying to reach turkey for asylum and then tried to deceive her to go to Turkey near Iran border to kidnap her and transfer to Iran. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nearly all the $$ in Iran is in hands of the IRGC, mullahs and their families and their anti-American children conveniently invest $500k in fixed assets in the US under EB5 program and get American green card and eventually citizenship. Meanwhile asylum seekers are denied entry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So how come pakistan installed the Pashtun supremacist taliban that is trying to eradicate Persian language from Afghanistan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That's correct, but where the Anatolian culture &amp; languages came from? All have ice age origins. Human population spread around the coastal lines during the ice age, migrated North and west as ice began to retreat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Finding baseless fake news BS to prove a BS is used by the weak minded

I have little tolerance for trolls and dumb people trying to prove dumbshit using BS screenshot from a BS website]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the assistance director of NS appointed just a few months ago even privileged enough to know if the FBI had such involvements? 

People need accountability or lose the remaining trust they have in the system #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# self proclaimed "trained marxist" BLM founders doing their "global citizen duty" supervising and boot camping stealing of Venezuelan election #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I thought, the Vikings looted them from some other civilization, they didn't have industries as sophisticated to produce such objects

Horned 'Viking' helmets were actually from a different civilization, archaeologists say #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Intersex is a very rare biological phenomenal, and result of cellular mutational error during the early stages of pregnancy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Let's colonize Greenland, Antarctic and Arctic, then apply that model to moon and then Mars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden should relocate and deploy at least 20,000 troops that are currently stationed in western Europe to Ukraine and other eastern European countries in addition to speeding up Ukraine's NATO membership #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The only country that has the right to request or reject NATO troops in Ukraine is Ukraine and its democratically elected government. 

This is an insult and assault on sovereignty of Ukraine that this gang of china, Russia and their puppets making such demand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's what mullahs did when they took over Iran, still most Iranian music and artists are banned under stone age Islamic/Sharia lawsnnKhomeinists inspired other Islamists to take over countries, taliban is one example]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Forget transcripts

Why they didn't question the socalled Trump supporter riot organizer under oath on the senate floor, and how this rioter suddenly became so trustworthy that the democrats are shielding him? 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This woman who may become the POTUS by default and without being elected, doesn't even know that the USA is a democratic constitutional Republic not a majority mob rule tyranny of majority.

It's very dangerous! How did she graduate from the #HASHTAG# ? 

#HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If anyone truly deserved to be charged under the Riot Act of 1968, it's Ray Epps #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it was a suicide vest toy for children, it's definitely an accurate labeling ðŸ˜‚ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Can you please mute their disgusting jihadi songs when posting their propaganda videos, if you can?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IRGC's naval superiority submarine ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚

It's 100% green energy propulsion and never loses power because it doesn't have any, uses foot pedal instead. Apparently they stole this naval technology from Leonardo da Vinci drawings but didn't go below surface, so they removed the roof #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Supposedly a language similar to Sanskrit was the foundation of all Indo-European languages that spread by the migrating Caucasian civilizations that moved West from Indus valley-iranian plateau-mesopotamia-Mediterranean toward Western and northern Europe when ice age ended]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Supply Chin 

All made by fascist regime in China]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Back the civilized Afghans wipe out the Taliban like we did in 2001 with very little expense and use of American military. CIA toppled the Taliban on horseback with little help from the air force, no tanks and only special forces. But betrayed the people who helped us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Although there are many South Sudanese refugees who've lived in the US for decades and many of them are educated and law respecting people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I didn't say petrochemical use

It's the most affordable, abundant source of hydrocarbons we use to produce Polymers and countless other applications. But as a fuel it's going to become too expensive compare to H2 that can be generated cheaply as long as there's cheap electric]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oil is the mullahs lifeline, it's like a $$ printing machine, iranian oil is the cheapest to produce, flows out of ground on its own and piped to the tankers &amp; billions flow in without having any economy or economic policy at all, then use oil $$ to hire lobbyists and bribe west #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least the administration was honest enough to call this an act of terror. Although antisemitic Islamic terror would've been a more accurate description #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It was so cheap that building gas power plants from scratch made more sense than keeping coal plants open]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Your buddies khamenei puppet houthis should be free to exterminate the black Africans in Yemen and everyone fighting them is evil? nnAll you Islamists are racist genocidal scumsnn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She has a ticket to Trump event and has a first amendment ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ she doesn't even know that First amendment doesn't apply to privately organized events that can get anyone kicked out for any reason or no reason at all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The founders of China's AI mostly worked for US tech giants like Google or labs like Bell Labs and gov backed universities research programs

A Chinese American who once worked for them told me why Americans are so dumb, we could've walk away with whatever  we wanted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Putin knew that Trump didn't play around and was aggressively defending eastern Europe. Once Biden came to office Ukrainian government got panicked and begged the US to speed up NATO membership, knowing that Putin was preparing to take advantage of Biden's weakness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Hugh Hefner didn't need to drug women to have sex with them. He had more than enough willing women than he could've handled

Cosby was an ugly old dude that apparently didn't have the game, so he ended up drugging women to get sex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Nobody went from Europe or America's to hunt slaves, it was already a commodity in Africa and middle east for thousands of years dominated by Muslim traders and black Africans were primarily the hunters. Arabs the merchants and owners. Europeans took advantage to develop Americas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Also many of the South Sudanese refugees who became US residents joined the US military.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He's just trying to justify spending billions on his failed space program that barely touched the edge of the space, let alone being near any planet, forget about building colonies in space, and is trying to act like he's making sacrifices for humanity's future ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Twitter truth police got me suspended again. Meanwhile data suggests that when there was no vaccine, these medicines could've saved lives, regardless of the #HASHTAG# Truth Police on the internet

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh, I see ðŸ¤”

So you went all the way to Florida to look for DeSantis??? ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£

Did you miss him that much? 

What a great excuse for fleeing leftist controlled NY to GOP Utopia of Florida ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Great news, herd immunity is near

Meanwhile fatalities are near record low

End all restrictions and let people and economy return back to pre-covid normal #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually it's Putin who should address the security concerns of Ukraine that's now threatened by invasion, Putin deployed 100,000 troops on the Ukrainian border and threatens invasion, Russian propaganda Reuters doesn't say that it's not Ukraine that threatens Russia, opposite #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Who talked about refugees? Anyone who comes to this country legally can have equal access to all the freedoms a legal immigrant enjoys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's CCP's made-up BS to justify building orbital satellite killing technology to use against other countries satellites]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A typical jihadi Pakistani neanderthal's logic:nnLet's attack the American Jews and hold them hostage to force the American justice system release our jihadi terrorist who was planning to kill Americans for Taliban and al-Qaeda!nnðŸ¤£ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚nIslamists are the Lowest life form on earth #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's not there yet, but robots that are being designed today can be able to do nano precision surgeries that no human can possibly do and much faster and error free than humans, that along with instant tissue printing, artificial nerves,... and other emerging technology]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US military strength is unmatched, but it's always the weakness of Washington and the #USER# that emboldens the tyrannical Expansionist adversaries, and lead to conflicts. The way US abandoned Afghanistan, appeased Iran Mullahs, Putin &amp; Beijing, they don't take NATO seriously #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Qassen only knew how to destabilize countries and train, arm, fund and move around terrorist proxies and militias with the blank check he had from khamenei, multibillion dollar IRGC-Hezbollah narcotics trade and all the IRGC/Iran assets available to him. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# 70% makes sense

And it's possible that some lab somewhere engineered it to wipe out the deadly variants and create herd immunity. Too many mutations that doesn't seem natural to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Meanwhile, $2 trillion was blown away on the Mullahs nuclear circus alone according to zarif, that if it was invested in infrastructure, manufacturing, tourism, urban planning, water, agriculture, aquaculture, transportation... by now it could've added trillions to the GDP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either tied to IRGC-Assad-Hezbollah (the biggest drug smuggling network in the world) or ISIS buying from Assad (using its pharmaceutical factories to produce them) and smuggling to Jordan with destination of Saudi Arabia and wealthy Persian gulf countries #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Nobody brothers Russia if it minds its own business and treats its people like humans.

Indeed nobody even cared about Russia's domestic policies until ukrainians decided to gain sovereignty after a century of being ruled by Russians and Russian puppets and kremlin took revenge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've seen many disgusting and horrifying things in real life that these movies bore me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goes back to 1960-70s when the KGB made plans to help the American cultural Marxists take over academia, education, media, entertainment, environmental orgs...even cultural Marxists takeover religious organizations

By now you have generations of brainwashed "educated" zombies #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I've seen ruins of Armenian villages and churches near Van, specially the area around the castle where Persian king Xerxes has an inscription from 2400 BC when Armenia was an ally and part of the Persian Achaemenid empire. They buried part of the remains under a new park! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Ask Biden why he lifted sanctions that was imposed on the gas pipeline that deterred Russia from invading Ukraine and distrusting Russia's major source of revenue? Now with Nordstrom 2 pipeline replacing the Ukrainian pipeline he has no obstacle and US lost its main leverage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yep, I'm surprised they didn't become household pets like dogs already, very similar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In #HASHTAG#ÄŸan's #HASHTAG# eating "bananas" has become such a luxury, that millions of Turks got outraged and the government deported the Syrian refugees because they could afford to eat bananas! nnTurkish economy has been free falling for years now! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And the reason is that the leftists are in control of immigration and don't like Trump loving "right wing" Iranians becoming Americans. Iranians overwhelmingly supported Trump and his Iran policy. Leftists hated that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They have a bunch of kids running their media who finds cool stuff from researchers that don't make economic sense at all. A massive investment of tens of millions in mirrors, lenses, gas to fuel reactors, refinery... Needed to maybe produce enough in a week for a single flight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Where is the studio and who's doing the staging? I used to build stage models like that for movie sets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If the USSR lasted for a couple of decades longer, they would've transformed regions like Ukraine and central Asia into Russian speaking regions who had lost their ethnic identity all together, but Soviet life was cut short and the gradual project was left incomplete]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The vast majority of China's minerals and fossil fuel deposits are located in Tibet and Xinjiang, without them China would've been a much smaller economy. Gradual ethnic cleansing &amp; genocide and denying them existence guarantees CCP's survival #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He did it all by himself

Mike Pompeo tells The Post how he lost 90 pounds in six months #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real "grandma killers" were democrat governors of the 4 states that coordinated the nursing home murder scheme and got away with it when they helped Biden oust his rival

#URL#

What happened to DOJ investigation on the nursing home scandal? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# If Russia joined NATO back then and the US helped Russians dismantle the KGB, by now Russia would've been a great ally and a normal and certainly more prosperous European (or Eurasian) country, but under current conditions, it's not possible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mullahs TV brought this stupid couple to talk about the conversion of the non-muslim wife to Islam (yet Iranians have been leaving Islam by millionsðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚)

Ridiculously, husband &amp; wife can't even understand each other's language. The husband made up something totally different #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm not sure how many of Iranian ships can even reach the Pacific ocean and what use those 1960s ships can have in a conflict involving China and Russia. It's just a symbolic China-Russia axis show of force]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Brain ðŸ§ 

Blame her stupid choices, not the society

Stupid people like her are the society]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pimpollahs Zainab also has a capitalist great Satan Instagram account. All that jihad to "liberate the oppressed from American imperialism" is now the "anti-imperialists" addicted to American corporations and tech trends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plus, Biden did all he could to scare people from getting vaccinated while Trump was still in the office. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Really, those poor bastards spend years smuggling all those equipments piece by piece, only to get blown up back into pieces in seconds shortly after getting operational ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I tried but couldn't bring that to English ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤£ 

The Persian version is hilarious ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm calling on president #USER# to release the transcript of the calls he made with both #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# and see what he did

Sounds like he's throwing Ukraine under the bus and already greenlighted to Putin for invasion, even has details of how Putin told him he'll invade #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# The problem is that Washington is so divided that nobody even takes US seriously to make a deal that would last, once the Russian war machine starts moving no one knows how, when and where it's going to stop. But if US fails to protect eastern Europe, all credibility will be gone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No surprise

London is the biggest breeding ground of Pakistani jihadis outside Pakistan #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's partly how we got inflation, by gov not market m, dictating wages to employers. As a result they're getting paid less $$ inflation adjusted #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They eat fruits though, and Chinese eat them of course ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# FDA or CDC? I thought FDA deals with vegetables related food ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course, like #HASHTAG#, the Russians are running the show and are going to get rewarded by the mullahs when they get hundreds of billions from sanctions relief. Nearly half of JCPOA $150 billion unfrozen funds went to Russian arms, infrastructure and energy contracts and Syria #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No biologist needed "evidence" that birds had evolutionary links to the reptiles. They even taste similar. It was always obvious that the birds are living dinosaurs, morons #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to bring lots of manufacturing to America and I figured out the blueprint for it that also makes the climate doomsday cult happy #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They could've simply wrote a check to these greedy clowns instead of humiliating them like this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's an AI boat dumbass
It launches itself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile china's puppets in Washington are keeping Americans preoccupied with #HASHTAG# circus after wasting Americans time with impeachment of China's biggest enemy for 4 years #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That was the US trade relation with China and EU/Germany unfair treatment of US exports. NAFTA actually saved industries from getting wiped out by keeping a big chunk of supply chain within North America where trade was fair &amp; balanced 
Canada &amp; Mexico's growth boosted US export]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Similar to the Hasan Al-Banna the founder of Muslim brotherhood of Egypt, Iqbal was a leading political Islam revivalist (modern Islamism) who influenced Islamists such as Iranian Islamists who proposed creation of Islamic Republic including khomeini himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# 30-70 million lives during the first 3 years of Mao alone (30 million was the official CCP estimate that's certainly underestimated like every other negative report) 

Now do Stalin genocides, Vietcong, north Korea (millions every decade since their takeover), Cambodia...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China knows, whoever controls the robotics and AI tech, will rule the world's future

Meanwhile US invests a lot more time, money and energy on installing Chinese made solar and wind than building the next gen intelligent robots AKA intelligent slaves

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Most Africans and other non-Arabs never fully convert to Islam until modern day Islamic revivalist movements

If you read the post islamic Iranian literature, it's full of glorifying drunkenness, orgies and all other things that are supposedly "sinful" by modern Muslims]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think the BLM naming was influenced by the Fidel Castro trained black Marxist separatist guerilla BLA (black liberation army) #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hypocrites demonize Florida Governor Ron DeSantis for not restricting life and business in Florida, but themselves flee NY restrictions to Floridan freedom, and maskless of course ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤£

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Good job folks

Those lowlife scums prey on normal vulnerable people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Great corporations that took decades to build fall because scumbags like this take charge

And he lied under oath to the US senate about the number of people they fired]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Me too

Actually I like chicken head soups, never tried fried]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selective Separation Could Help Alleviate Critical Metals Shortage - CleanTechnica - #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This explains why #HASHTAG# loves creating crisis, Terrorism and instability around the world, mostly through proxies like Iran, Syria, north Korea, Sudan, Cuba, Venezuela... regimes.

#HASHTAG# takes Russian citizens attention away from economic failure &amp; authoritarianism at home

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good point

Only people from Hong Kong have large families, the people in the Homeland could only have one child and as a result their children are often raised with excessive attention and attachment to their family, very emotionally soft/weak, can never become good PLA warriors #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# She's a Kremlin puppet. Started her career working for a Russian firm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# US never had any interest in Africa, let alone "non-existent US imperialism" scare the Africans

The only times US even bothered and look at Africa was when millions of Africans were exterminates by guess what? Africans

And US role there is only security and humanitarian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's still a tiny irrelevant Russian puppet communist political party, but numbers of their votes grew by 10 fold during Obama's second term (obviously most of them voted for Obama, but didn't like Hillary) #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤£ when they hire a bunch of clueless interns to run their social media, they think their biggest critics who follow them are their fans ðŸ˜‚ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# 2021 could've been the last year of the kremlin puppet occupying Islamist tyranny in Iran if Trump had another term.

Mullahs won't last a day if Americans really decide to get rid of them, and you know it. Iran fought Saddam for 8 years to keep him off one province... You know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# inspired by communism and their obsession with pure communism being the solution for everything. However, unlike communism that promised physical liberation of humans from "economic inequality" the Islamists want to force everyone to go to heaven, they kill you if you refuse ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# A black person born in America is already a lot more privileged than an Asian, African, Latina or middle eastern who migrates to America trying to figure out everything from scratch and struggling to have things that are born in America have for granted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# 10,000 ft/s (3,048 m/s; 6,818 mph) and reaching altitudes of 215,000 ft (66,000 m)

That's impressive for a gun using $5000/shot worth of explosives.

They looked him up for selling weapons to the apartheid regime that was fighting the Cuban backed communists, then he defected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The problem is people's thinking and how they get emotional and react irrationally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine being so wealthy to afford to buy your own American political party #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Em buys cartoon monkey version of himself for half of mill 

Eminem Bought a Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT for Nearly $500,000 #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New photo

Commander Hasib Panjshiri of Afghan #HASHTAG# is already a legend in guerilla warfare.

Him and the #HASHTAG#/Afghan nationalists under his command have scored many victories against the Pakistani ISI led #HASHTAG# and al-Qaeda terrorist occupiers in #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# TV is for entertainment and killing time, I can get more news reading stuff and tapping into my social media sources in 15 minutes than watching TV for 24 hours and have the choice of extracting the key information I'm looking for without distractions and commentary BS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The IRGC used artillery against the villagers in Balochistan province. 

This is what they did to syrians, now deploying against Iranian citizens #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How you take oil out of Kazakhstan without going through Russia or China, dumbass ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This idiot was in charge so was Biden, they could've built more testing equipment like Trump built them from scratch and built 100,000 ventilators in a song month by simply directing the private industries that make them #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's always been a Russian colony, Russia doesn't need to invade, owns the place and has military bases there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's what I always thought the US justice system should do instead of having the inhumane and Taxpayers draining prison system. Create penal colonies in the least populated parts of the US like the British did to develop Australia. Let them create their own economy and pay tax #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They hired a career terrorist assassin, why not Zarif? Afterall Mousavian is Zarif's partner all along]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# And most of the seniors are pushed to criminal divisions and the counterterrorism and counter intelligence is mostly the newer generation agents or the ones that have mainstream academic mindsets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Oltmann infiltrated #HASHTAG# and heard Eric Coomer the security director of #HASHTAG# telling the Antifa supporters that he made sure that #HASHTAG# had no chance of winning! nn#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Blatantly

Climate has been changing for 4 billion years and no climate model can even breakdown how much of climate change is natural how much due to human activities and in what ways, a bunch of doomsday theories by illiterate children like AOC and Thunberg #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Too many pages of history you've never been told by your YouTube and marxist academia historians]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 70% of Americans support infrastructure spending, but the majority don't like all the unrelated garbage they're trying shove down the taxpayers throat. Tell your elected reps to get rid of all the nonsense and have an infrastructure only bill, even if it's $1 Trillion more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The problem is lack of futuristic planning at the government level

Without new planned cities like the planners of New York and other successful 19th-20th century planned, plus more efficient construction methods, there won't be a serious renewal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These crybaby pussies can never go to war with a superpower

#HASHTAG# is a paper tiger that has only lost wars since inception, the cowards are only trained to beat up and kill defenseless citizens of the #HASHTAG# empire

Can't even operate copycat equipment

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Under Putin JCPOA, mullahs got to keep 100% of nuclear program intact and after expiration had the freedom to build nuclear weapons. It's noteworthy that JCPOA practically gave mullahs a legal path to nuclear weapons that were otherwise in violation of NPT &amp; arms control treaties]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Very different than the high tech chips that TSMC has global leadership]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If you read my tweet I explained that. They never protested that day, the democrats change the strategy and told their leaders to order all their thugs to avoid going to Washington, some elements may have took part pretending to be part of the pro Trump protests]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Money rules the world, and now China is back in the game full swing, thanks to Washington remaining in Covid coma and political partisan divide that made Americans each other's biggest enemies!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Actually not, for example before Persians and other Iranian tribes such as the Medes  migrated to the Iranian plateau from eastern Europe at around 3000 BC, there were many other semitic and non-semitic (mostly distinct like the Elamites) languages that were dissolved gradually]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They were nearly wiped out when Obama decided to make peace with them and then Trump stayed on the same course giving them legitimacy and time to get help from Iran, Qatar and Pakistan and rebuild their forces]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# We have a bunch of clueless mental patients running the US foreign policy! Even a 5 year old tells you that it's beyond illogical to ask your #HASHTAG# adversary you are at war with to talk down your #HASHTAG# adversary that happens to be the top ally &amp; partner of your #HASHTAG# adversary!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Seeing the dumb real or fake Republicans attacking Ted Cruz One of the most qualified, strongest, most dedicated, most aggressive and most educated constitutional conservatives, I think the Democrats are going to have a very easy win in 2024

Republicans are their own worst enemy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# China will eventually have a major economic crash, no doubt. But boosting its trade and investment abroad can only help CCP navigate out of the mess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Let's see if any of the rocket engineers #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# have an opinion about Iran's rocket launch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# This maybe a Kremlin game to push Turkmenistan into the collective security organization (CTO) that Uzbekistan and Tajikistan are already members.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden made it to the Senate by giving empty promises and from there made it to the white house over the course of decades the same way

Foolish voters believe every nonsense clueless and careless politicians promise them with no record to backup their claims #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you remember when Trump contracted Covid, the best medical experts in the world prescribed the #HASHTAG# cocktail that was still under development, with remarkably quick results that Trump called it a "medical miracle" and said we should produce lots of it.

What happened? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Russians would rather push Beijing to go to war with the US and take the backseat, if Russia invades eastern Europe, by their definition it's war with the US no matter how Americans see that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep, the Russian actors told their puppet Trudeau to impose Soviet style laws and mandates, so the truckers protest against it #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Once someone employed by a government agency, it's a lifetime career and often they create jobs for friends and family members when they move up and keep expanding the big government waste]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It can become the main backbone of their economy and place them on the energy map, even if the net profit is going to be small, its overall impact on the GDP will be based on the net export of hydrogen and much of the cost of production would create jobs and economic activities]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# As of 2020, the vast majority of vietnamese population had strong favorable views of the United States, the highest in the world and 3 times higher than Germany, a NATO "ally" 

#URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Same with Iranians, there are thousands in turkey and elsewhere trying to apply for asylum legally, hate the mullahs, love the USA and freedom and mostly educated or want to have better future in a free country, and qualified for asylum. But US only sells green card to IRGC kids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Laser weapons are potentially the most effective of all anti-missile defense, specially the pulse laser weapons can deliver very powerful pulses (as opposed to continuous beam that require pointing at the target for a period of time to disable it)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Iran is a potential market of $5+ trillion if it becomes a democratic free market economy and totally end isolationism and protectionism.

It enjoyed constant double digit growth for more than two decades in 1950-70s.

Regime change is the first step to get there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WARNING: VERY GRAPHICnnThe Genocidal #HASHTAG# in #HASHTAG# slaughtered black (African) #HASHTAG# and burned them alivennI still can't make a sense of why #HASHTAG# removed them from Terror list!nnWhere's #HASHTAG# when black lives really matter?? #HASHTAG# aren't humans? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's what I said more than a month ago

Omicron is the actual vaccine, probably better than their phony mRNA vaccine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It says the video is private and can't be viewed without permission]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They're actually the virus components, the actual spike protein instead of giving the immune system a whole disabled virus to build immunity against]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I warned that the Biden Administration's foreign policy weakness was going to bring us closer than ever to a world war, not the other way around. The weakness &amp; childishness of #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG#, #HASHTAG# ... policies gave #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# the signal that it's time to expand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# At least they're big enough to hold up ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# That's pretty much the origin of the Indo-European cultures that expanded in the Iranian plateau, Mediterranean, black sea, central Asia and Europe over the course of thousands of years and mixed with local cultures and languages creating all branches of Indo-European languages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Most of the Mediterranean and middle east were Aramaic and non-semitic and non-Indo-European languages before the Indo-European expansion and later the semitic languages (mainly Arabic) wiped them out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You don't understand how western academia works. Academic research Programs related to every region is largely funded and directed by the people from the same ethnic regions and linguistic background. They look at the Persian and Roman art and science that fell under empire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Let me correct it:nn "Most of the men behind the Asian child sex trafficking, sex slave massage parlors are white men with small penises" nnHad nothing to do with racism. Totally irrelevant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# TruennThe Pakistani alQaeda sympathizer specifically targeted the Jews that the Islamists consider their main target. This is an act of antisemitic jihadi terrorism not gun violence. And a planned attack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me interpret this one:nnMullahs saw how #HASHTAG# extorted Europeans over keeping the Syrian refugeesnnNow Mullahs are trying to extort #HASHTAG# in exchange for keeping the #HASHTAG# in #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The consequence of polarization of US foreign policy

Most of the Fox news anchors and hosts are political operatives and talk show hosts, not foreign policy experts, and repeat the populist narrative.

Overall, most Americans oppose interventionist FP &amp; favor isolationism #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hide any object that can be picked up and thrown, specially kitchen knives ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Islam was spread by swords and genocide, still does]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Finally China made its first invention since the invention of gun powder in 800 AD:

Invisible toilet partition stalls

ðŸ‘ðŸ‘ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# More than what the rest of the socalled "insurrectionists" did

It's hilarious that you leftists now defend one of the most instrumental people who took part in the "insurrection" clown show ðŸ˜‚ðŸ‘ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He thinks Trump is still in the white house and fox news is part of the US government making decisions on foreign policy ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤£ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Are you kidding me? The cost of keeping a single prisoner incarcerated like a zoo animal is more than the average salary of university professors and people with PhDs. 

Instead, give them a one way ticket to somewhere unpopulated in Alaska to live and stay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# No Einstein, ancient Greek came from the same origin as the rest of the Indo-European languages and became distinct when the ancestors of Greeks migrated to the Balkans and from there to western, northern and gradually southern black sea and ultimately Mediterranean. #URL#]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>