<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# “C’mon Man!”: Biden Again Misrepresents Georgia Election Law While Supporting State Boycott – JONATHAN TURLEY #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Maybe 1984 is the instruction manual. Send aid to Ukraine. I support that. More Afghans predicted to die of starvation than the war. Do you hear any compassion from DC?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Perhaps more than they do. They sure seem confused (on purpose?).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The problem is Little Rock seems to be poor housing and low wages. Working ppl can't afford anything else. They have to live with the violence &amp; hope their kids survive. Affordable housing &amp; integrated housing..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm gonna miss these guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Biden's job and he flubbed it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do you have a blog on this. Trying to see how this could play out. Climate change is natural and man made. We need to eliminate the man made part if possible but that means all nations agree. Some are way too poor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I'm hearing Honda not as great as before. Subaru highly rated. Quite a lot of work. Hard on newer vehicles with computers. Had an old 65 Ford truck. Took it apart,fixed,put back together. Didn't drive it much when we got another truck. Sadly pack rats ate the wiring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Government Secretly Orders Google To Identify Anyone Who Searched A Sexual Assault Victim’s Name, Address And Telephone Number #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A few decent dems-not many lol. Things will get better slowly I hope. Starts when Pelosi is no longer in office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Go bad early 60s. MLK jr was a commie,a threat to this nation,a womanizer. Still his message was heard,changes started. MLK in spirit is till here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A pandering,racist,fascit,RW imperialist oligarch front.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They want to give us everything. They love us. Should have provided health care decades ago. A huge bill. Somewhere in it I bet are exemptions for big $$ donors. If Pelosi is pushing it,I don't want it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Oh u racist,sexist Bernie Bro. Women are pure,perfect,compassionate,maternal. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# OMG $1200 for insulin! About 3-4 yrs ago my cat took human insulin. Vet said can go past 30 day expiration. She got better but back on insulin. $35-porcine. Congress should expose real costs to make insulin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They have a major flaw. They think we're stupid &amp; they treat us that way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh yeah! Sad because I saw ppl donating $1 or just a few to Hillary. Prob all they had.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But now she'll run on I told you so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# LOL but aren't all white people racist. Now you after their women. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So you just dismiss the 5,000? That's an abnormal high proportion. Thought you weren't racist. Why can't they be integrated. Ghettos are hotbeds of violence. Families trapped there because of poverty. THEY MATTER. Goodbye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You are so welcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Haircut?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Well that helps explain it. It does sound like high school. But y'all is regional for adults &amp; children like you guys in the NE. Those terms don't designate gender. But thanks for explaining. I'll try harder not to grit my teeth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Why an Englishman?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hubby ate monkey in Viet Nam or so he says,prob to make me turn green.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Read how math is racist. Lots of info. How some college dorms are "segregated" by race in guise of AAs bonding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They're not pushovers. They have economic ploys that can cause food shortages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I said I wouldn't get the booster but since Colin Powell died I will. Sasha, you are probably better off vaccinated with your medical problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No it doesn't stop the fires but can perhaps save a house. Keep dry grass,vegetation away.  I guess curb appeal tops all. Hubby retired retired forest svc. He was always on call for fire but here more moisture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# John F Kennedy: "A nation that is afraid to let its people judge the truth and falsehood in an open market is a nation that is afraid of its people."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I didn't vote for Trump. Think he did some good,some bad. Biden's biggest accomplishment is going to be making Trump look good. I do think he'll run again &amp; prob win just bc ppl need to have the say in elections - not party hacks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Pretty exciting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Night all. So tired. Stock up,stores getting low on same things like pet food,paper and cleaning products. Food prices are not kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And Fort Detrick. Cleaned it when it was evacuated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Swinging on a Star - Bing Crosly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The Nazis did and the leadership in government fully supported Mengele.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Canada seems to have problems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good night all. Have a good evening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I have some left if you're hungry. Tossed with olive oil,minced garlic,parmesan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Mothers &amp; fathers where by DNA or surgery love their children,want them protected. Have you seen the gingerbread cookie now a unicorn. Cartoonish,language aimed at grade-school level. Our kids are not up for grabs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Biden bowed to Taliban. Old song-you may remember -You knew I was a snake when you let me in. Biden didn't give NATO warning. It was a NATO operation. Biden stabbed them in back as well as Afghan ppl. Haven't heard lately-any Americans &amp; allies still stuck there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And tie it to inflation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Any injuries?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She lives in a daydream world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's awesome. I really love Mash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Plenty of think tanks in DC. If they aren't directly in government they still play big role like Brookings &amp; war]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Stop being simple.LMAO who the hell are you?  Get lost and bother someone else who suffers fools. I don't. Buh bye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Grand Rapids couple dies 1 minute apart from COVID-19 #URL# They were fully vaccinated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Benefits? As far as data listened on NPR radio to state of data-a total mess. The vaccine is short lived. I certainly do question the benefits. If so good,why more deaths in 2021 when more ppl vaccinated,than in 2020 when vaccine just rolled out. Something is wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Jack doth protest too much. The government uses division and sometimes even money. Lends itself to ppl questioning &amp; even to conspiracy theories]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I know they have. I know CNN's tributes are over I have a dream. They won't touch much of what he wrote. MSM has too much influence &amp; gullible minds like quick news. Anyone who lived thru the time sees it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hillary's Russian hoax put us all through the McCarthy era again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Ukraine not in NATO. Not NATO's fight. Help the best we can but not bring on WWIII. I fear for the poor nations who have no involvement but will suffer food shortages. No one every seems to care about them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He started off as social justice warrior. That went to sh-- quickly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Do it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Not much culpability-we can't sue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# She didn't say that. Ahem...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Wow. I've heard areas around NYC where no cell signal. But can't you get cable or dsl?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Okay that's it. Tweet again,I block you. If you are an adult,I sincerely wish you the best. Your right to chose if an adult.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Well you know back in the days the Democrats didn't want those super predators mingling with the white kids. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So prosecutions that happened using "evidence" from this drug lab won't be looked at again - SMH what a system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Glad you fixed your "misspoke." Funny Hillary used that word a lot,about wore it out. What makes me happy is #USER# actually corrected it. They sure don't do that when Rachel "misspeaks."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Guess it's all we got. We shipped jobs overseas. Over 200 yrs of our history have been war. We are modern version of Rome. My hubby fought in VietNam. He didn't even know where it was. He was just a kid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# EVERYONE SHOULD READ THIS! Time to tell establishment go green now. Already 20 years too late.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Governor is lowering taxes-some activists question how much more the rich are getting. Meanwhile poor may not pay income taxes but they get hit hard at grocery store.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And we also fund them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think a lot of attention paid to talking heads is the problem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Someone posted something the school teacher wrote years on. Can't find it. Too tired last night.Dang! I didn't know it was a movie in 2008. I saw docu many years ago as an after-school special my kids watched.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Me? I want to walk more. I already have a terminal disease. A walk in the woods is worth whatever I have to do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah I think they'll have to do something tomorrow. Doc seldom there. My misfortune to get him last time. We've had some unpleasant conversation. I can make vein his neck stick out lol. Hubby said I was mean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Spring &amp; fall. So beautiful right now &amp; not a lot of severe weather so far. Arkansas is so beautiful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How The U.S. Lost Control Of This Giant Iraqi Oilfield | #URL# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Fine to hand out just not a campaign appointed poll watcher doing it. Media has exaggerated GA voting rules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Under Obama,stimulus $ for roads. Money spent repaving road to diamond mine. It didn't need it. Other roads did. Diamond mine a tourist attraction. $ for internet. We didn't get it but nearby town with cell,cable,dsl got it. Go figure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I am. Own the food supply,control everything. Land is a good investment tho in many cases.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Started today. I was locked out for 3 months. Why?? Back on a few weeks,locked out 6 months. Then told suspended. I appealed,said I'm writing corp HQ. So got an apology &amp; back on. I guess they have to find some way to mess with us. I really try to be nice,civil. I hate censorship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Leaders do evil things. I think most ppl here &amp; in all other nations just want a decent life and a good life for their children. It's governments that do the evil,seldom the ppl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh come on. Cities burned. Police stations,federal buildings. Let me guess-msnbc. Thousands arrested? Show me your source.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Beautiful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And politicians always follow thru on campaign pledges #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Gold &amp; bitcoin are also currency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Only those who hate free speech. Different opinions need aired in the sunlight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wish him well. A third party is desperately needed. I can't see how the Dems hold congress in 2022]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why did kid do it? For kicks? How can children become such monsters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Know nothing but RTing so more ppl see it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wonder if that's how I got a flare-up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# What! That's so wrong. Oh wait the politicians said no one is above the law right? #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think we do. The government could care less.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Oh plenty of ppl I miss on here. Rest of them that jump in or somehow a follower,not so much. I don't judge ppl by political party but those I judge brainwashed I wish would go away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do We Need “F” Grades? More Schools Are Saying No. – JONATHAN TURLEY #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Why I think more her doing than Obama's. He's smarter than her IMO but she still seems to run a few in the DNC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Get lost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I wasn't on for six months,locked out,yet my account said suspicious activity. Then suspended. I kept appealing. Said I'd contact corporate. Suddenly back on,twitter apologized. Someone is just messing with me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Well that does sound good. I had pretzels &amp; dip. I'm not elite,just a hillbilly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What have we learned since Afghanistan? Our allies &amp; some Americans left there. Even military dogs left in cages to die. We can't go all out with the president we have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Moot point. The parents won. McAuliffe lost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Conspiracy theorists are domestic terrorist? Oh well the I fully accept that Epstein committed suicide &amp; that the elites would never engage in sex with children. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Cancel medical debt. College was a choice. If smart enof for college,should be smart enof to figure out they could or couldn't afford it. And it's not just racial. Makes jr colleges free,extension of high school]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Fix the neighborhoods. Ferguson was left a wreck. AA businesses gone. Jobs lost. I listened to interviews with ppl who lived there. What business wants to locate where there are gang bangers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Right,thanks. I have Bradon moments. One wasn't vaccinated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If she's not permanent suspended and then allowed back on,the supporters will come back. Can take 2 days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes! His best. Pet Cemetery was good. Chills. The movie was awful,too much gore. All those big rigs going down the highway in the background]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[paste 5- When the evidence of eyes &amp; ears r negated by dogma,it is evident that society is in big trouble. When it embraces the childish outlook of transgenderism it implicitly acknowledges that it has lost the capacity 4 serious thought.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I think Haig was in shell shock. At least he gave us all a hint that Armageddon almost happened. Was he trying to calm nation or himself? Media &amp; the ppl had no idea what was going on at that time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nope. He's beyond redemption. George Floyd had more impact that MLK? He needs to resign]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She was a font of bullcrap. She pushed the Russian hoax. She said hospital overfowing with ppl who ODed on horse wormer. I used to watch her but she isn't the same as she once was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI reports homicides up 30% in 2020 in Arkansas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Trans-gender women are biological males no matter how many hormones. Bigger lungs,hearts,muscles. DNA says their males. I'll stick with science.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Big pharma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# He meant teaching truck driving. He  &amp; Cor Pop drove big rigs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Just a string of tweets. Anyone can put anything on twitter. Military ppl on both sides have communication equipment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No they shouldn't but a parent in debt because of a sick child tops college debt. Make community colleges free,then last 2 yrs let them read the fine print. I don't think their debt should be foisted on taxpayers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And a gentlemen. He should have exposed them all. If he were potus now,think how much better it would be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Looked it up,didn't find anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When she lost her phone,we got some insight into this woman. Why is she still at State. A Clinton hold over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Republicans rape. Democrats just good old boys having some fun &amp; besides those women are bimbos who asked for it. #HASHTAG# #URL# began to move on from Bill C. bc his policies were good. Rape is fine to the D party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Absolutely. I saw police shoot &amp; kill an armed AA man back in 1958. It wasn't even in the news. But things have improved,not perfect,a long way to go. Most policemen IMO are decent ppl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Infusion? Antibodies? I hope taste,smell comes back. What an awful thing to go through. Be careful of sinus infection-they can go south especially when weakened from a serious illness. Wishing you the best. Take care]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mean hater or Republicans? You want to save democracy? Uh - okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nothing's been set. This is repeat of turbulence of late 60s,early 70s. Worse violence,capitol bombed twice,hundreds killed,Watts riot,on &amp; on. Everyone surely is over reacting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good night all. My prayer is Joe Biden resigns tomorrow. If that offends anyone,well good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Back at ya!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't see a limit on bank lending.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Biden said early on he didn't think Ukraine should be in NATO. Speaking of crimes,AG going up the line in HC's campaign. Can he get the queen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But Biden says George Floyd had more impact. Sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think Bernie will vote against it. Have to run something down-told $450K for families separated at border by Trump are in Pelosi's bill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# FFS a riot,someone pooped on Pelosi's chair. A rioter was killed. All summer cities burned,looting,violence,death. Two don't compare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's not 3rd world. So you call names. That's how you debate? Get lost and don't bother me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So do you work for free? Not just 1/6 defendants most ppl can't afford lawyers either to fight criminal charges,get a will,etc. You seem out of touch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I watch every night. I go thru from beginning to end &amp; then repeat it all over again. My fav character is Charles &amp; Radar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Have to read that site. Not familiar with it. DNA damage temporary. Did read somewhere scientist saying man made pointed to the spikes. Looked like somehow did that. Oh well,can't remember but I think it's man made.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# The Little Rock Nine. A white girl screaming making a horrible face. Yes teach them. Then say years later the white girl,now grown,became best friend with the black girl,now grown,and they wrote a book together on those events]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# And lower drug prices for those who get the flu in spite of the shot. Big Pharma can make a profit and save more lives. SUPPORT LOWER DRUG PRICES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Might want to grab a history book. Start with Whisky Rebellion and go forward. Puts 1/6 in perspective. Doesn't make 1/6 right but makes it way low on the totem pole. Biden divides when he calls names]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They already know is my guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I love black cats. So pretty. Grade them tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# NR hope the cloud lifts &amp; soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# They'll run from noise so not that much danger to humans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I didn't vote for Trump but Russian hoax falls into the category of treason IMO. Those behind the Russian hoax tried for 4 years to undermine a president they didn't want as well as the voter. Altho statue of limitations is up,this should surely still be prosecutable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Journal therapeutic meds recommends it for covid. Then Maddow pushes the opposite &amp; some still fell for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Denied medical help! Oh FFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Who's lived under communism? Except for a few hippy communes for a brief period,communism has never existed. We have socialism here for the powerful. Same with soviet system. But communism,not yet. We need to evolve more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Cooked too hot &amp; too fast eggs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Food is crappy but I did see or read about our tastes changing as we age. Eat a lot now I didn't before. You can find hot dogs without cereal,best that can be done. I adore hot dogs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Thank you. Twitter hardly a font of truth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Who knows what little tidbits are in BBB to alleviate pain for corp,mic,mega rich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Ivermectin has long been approved for use in humans. There is more than horse wormer. Local doctor here has used it &amp; not lost any patients even a 100 yo woman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# But it's okay when Democrats do it. Remember how those bimbos held poor Bill Clinton down. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But we can go out in great style with that $10,000.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# At this point,nothing certain. Idea Putin is losing is ridiculous. And what is China doing? Just waiting? Are we ready for that. Biden showed the world he's weak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Wasn't Varney that said it. It was spokesman for uber.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Dems have a strategy. Promise everything &amp; then whine that the Rep won't let them do it. I wish politicians would work for us and not just the party over all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Well the lost the Putin in the White House narrative. God help ppl charged with a crime when msm involved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Too much to ask I guess. Like Carnegie. Screwed over everyone. Then in old age felt guilty &amp; built libraries,museums.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# One of the most important men in history. I also looked up to him but I wasn't a child. I just look at lot younger LOL. No I can't post photo. Camera broken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# SMH-do you think new mayor can change things? He seems tough on crime. Crime wave has to hurt NYC's bottom line.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If school requires mask,then kids mask. If not,then some won't. We hear masks work &amp; they don't work. No one is giving solid info. I'm a fan of masks. Mayo says they work. No one is taking control of the messaging]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Everyone suffers. Saw clips of shelling and flocks of panicked birds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I watched what went on January 6. Only person killed was a female vet shot by police. While the whole stunt was stupid it was handled. Idiot from AR sitting in Pelosi's chair was just acting out. The shaman was ridiculous. Thousands outside were peaceful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If the haters are on twitter,consider it good. You rattled their cage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# When didn't have insurance,use to buy antibiotics at feed store. They've stopped that now. Same mfg,same safety,exact same antibiotic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# What did you have? Learn MMT. How did that prove your point. What it did prove is you like to smart off. Bye Bye. If you have FACTs to present,do so. Smart mouth doesn't cut it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Bombarding me doesn't work. I am vaccinated because I'm elderly. My daughters are not-their choice. 2 of my 4 grand children chose to be vaccinated. If I were younger I would not get vaccinated. Simple sealing of data a red flag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I fear Trump can attack under that authorization for use of military force. We don't have wars anymore. Just because there's bombs &amp; millions dead,it really isn't war. #HASHTAG# Congress failed 2 abide by Constitution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Read a paragraph from New Yorker on Dr. Mengele.  Well respected by the leaders for his scientific knowledge. Sound familiar?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I'll think about fasting. Right now pretty miserable. Broke down &amp; made appointment tomorrow with nurse Ratchet because Nazi at front desk wouldn't just ask her for RX. Rural health care in AR. We rank 50th nation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# My 7 yo grandson does not need to know about anal-oral sex with an adult male. You like kiddie porn? Go to school library. You damn right I want that book banned from children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't know who she is either. Thought because I'm old,but you're young. So maybe she's doing it for publicity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# For a while &amp; less than you say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's rigged against all but the elites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I've looked around at several sites as they pop up. None are cheap,even WalMart but a bit less expensive. But dehydrated ice cream sandwiches is a huge incentive to spend more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# BBC - why not DOJ. Oh I guess looting is reparations. Go away. My daughter was in law enforcement. A caring,compassionate person. What tripe the neolibs push.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wreck of the Edmund Fitzgerald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If I have a cow it is a storage of value. Definition of money is very,very complex. If I can get $500 for my cow,that cow was a storage of $500]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[War Propaganda About Ukraine Becoming More Militaristic, Authoritarian, and Reckless #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Gotta watch them furiners &amp; Jewish commies! This here Pope preaching commie stuff! #HASHTAG# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# LOL well u gained one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh no! You didn't! Did you wear gloves? I cut them once without gloves. Burned for hours. Vietnamese friend said soak in hot water. Vietnamese experts in hot peppers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# What is ECU &amp; IOT?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Get the politicians out of it. They are fanning the flames of something that is going away. It's better than before but sure seems like the woke want us to regress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If Sander were potus maybe congress would straighten right up knowing the people on to them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# EU still likes us. We'll see after the cold winter &amp; their reliance on Russia for heat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Right now need NATO to stand up. Biden won't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I understand that. I think it's wrong. Not saying it's right. But investment corp can go belly up. Doubt the IMF will as it is not an investment corp. It's world's governing of national financial markets. Totally different. To them,gold reserves are like a good credit scores.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's winter here one day,spring the next. Insanity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Easy to get her into this country?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# That military spending is necessary to kill thousands of children. But they're not in the US so they don't count. #HASHTAG# mixed w anger &amp; bitterness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Wonderful. Now on to homeless problem and crime?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I follow these 2 ladies. Might be good for you. We don't always agree. We bounce back &amp; forth but no one gets angry. One is very conservative,the other an ex-Berner now conservative. #USER# #USER#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A female Ivy league swimmer broke all previous records but was beaten out by a trans-women. Female swimmers work hard. Female sports if often a means to go to college. Why are biological males allowed to strip us of rights? -2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Good question. Truckers for sure. How we got food,fuel. BTW average truck driver now makes $14,000/week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Had a doctor I trusted. He wasn't afraid to say I don't know. They didn't know,never happened before. Old saying-honesty the best policy. Now no one believe much of anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay. I see a solution to future trials. Let's do away with trial by jury. Let's vote,just like a political election. We're heading toward fascism. Why delay. So much easier, don't need to understand law,MSM will help u decide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal gets lap dance from  male student dressed as sexy girl. Cheerleaders in hooters outfits. Book in school library-sex with dildo. Let kids be kids. The world rushes in all too soon. -2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes Democracy Now has gone down. ACLU has deserted people. If you object to biological boys in girls' sports,you are a hater - so says ACLU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study finds political bias skews perceptions of verifiable fact – Harvard Gazette #URL# Democrats and Republicans both wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# No one ever gave me that. I just sat,slept in recliner for months puffing away on inhalers. Legs swelled,hard to walk. It was hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Nothing was as divided as the civil war that killed hundred of thousands. I live in South. Voted twice for Obama. South also traditionally Republican. May or may not have had anything to do with skin color. I think you have distorted picture of rural South]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# We took antibiotics for everything even bacterial infections. We used disinfectants to fight common bacteria. We overdid it. Time &amp; place for antibiotics and disinfectants. We have to live with germs. Our skin always has staph on it but our immune systems fights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Did you hear about indictment (27 pages) against Hillary's attorney Sussman for the Russian hoax. Strange,he was paid by the HC campaign. I'm shocked I tell you,shocked. More heads will prob roll but she always escapes]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>