<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah! It's women's fault that men don't stop others from attaching a woman or stopping a rapist!! It's not their own cowardice or simply lack of giving a shit. It's ALL WOMENS FAULT!! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Says the guy drinking alone in Mexico arguing with a random internet person. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ‘ðŸŽ©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# HAHAHAHAHAHAHA Yeah sure. Women are just flighty and silly and need psychopathic men with zero empathy to lead  them... #HASHTAG# ðŸ™„You're a pathetic excuse for a man Ray.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You just played yourself. You have just as much say about it as a guy with a gun that shoots a pregnant person. ie. None. Unless you're willing to shoot ppl which I wouldn't put past you folk tbh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I'm sorry you think you have any right to tell anyone else what to do with their bodies. We don't need your understanding or seal of approval Chris. Keep showing your entitled a$$ all over twitter though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Me too. It breaks you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I almost liked it too until I re-read it for a second time. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mine was in October 2015. ðŸ’œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You must be #HASHTAG# then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I have both those subhumans blocked for good reason. You might consider doing the same. You don't need to take more abuse from ignorant assholes like this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# on not in* my bad ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I have been thinking this as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You get reciprocity when you answer this question. Last chance before I block your boring a$$]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You can think all kinds of things. What you don't understand is that your thoughts don't dictate other peoples actions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Thanks it's what I was going for! ðŸ¢ You sound like an ignorant cockwomble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Only reason I am still fucking with him hahahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# LOL so disingenuous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #URL#

This song feels particularly relevant today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entitled. Now you know where he got his from. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Mommy did it for him his whole life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# There are plenty of reasons a person might not want to continue a pregnancy or cannot continue a pregnancy. Every persons body and circumstances are different. You don't get to choose for other ppls pregnancy Karen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# LOL Aww did I hurt your wittle fee fees? Why don't you go drink about it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah no. Some men think they have the right to touch you.. beware those men.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# It was really hard because I found out that I have a genetic mutation that won't ever let me have a healthy baby at the same time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Lost mine in the exact same way. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You can however have*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Then why so proud of having your kids within marriage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# This is who you are whether you want to admit it or not. Vile, judgemental and abusive. #HASHTAG# Of course he is a 'follower of christ' WWJD? Harass women who've had abortions of course! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's the same in Canada. People on disability live 50% below poverty line and are being made homeless. Many are accessing MAID which is Assisted death because they can't afford to live.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah going thru nine months of sickness, pain and swelling to squeeze an 8 lbs baby out of their vag and then spending the next 18+ years feeding, caring and raising someone is just an "inconvenience" ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Doesn't matter. You get to decide who you fuck and you don't and if you use a condom or not and if you choose to get a vasectomy or not. Those are YOUR choices. You don't get any say once a pregnancy occurs because it's not your body it is growing in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You literally have not talked to men about it. Prove you have or happily GFY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I don't owe them any single shred of respect while they are being transphobic and speaking against asexuals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just went to buy some bananas and check it out.. I'm gonna look like a fetus. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Boo fuckin hoo. A nazi flag was flown in Ottawa Canada yesterday. White supremacism is still a huge problem. Let me know when black people ever have the power to cause a fucking genocide in North America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 'baby'/fetus inside them could be the next Manson or Dahmer too. Their strawmen and emotional extortion are BS. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# What ever do you mean? Married people and christians NEVER have abortions! However the evil wh*res who can't keep their legs closed will wait right up until the moment before birth to MURDER their babies. ðŸ˜œðŸ˜œðŸ˜œ#HASHTAG# nnSounds like every 'prolifer'/antichoicer on this ap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I had a pregnancy in 2015 and I found out that my very wanted pregnancy wasn't going to reach a happy conclusion. 23 wks I had the abortion. Trisomy 18 and many other complications. I could have died. *sending you so much love* ðŸ’“ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It just goes to show that they aren't pro-life at all, just anti-choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Too bad you can't control other peoples medical, moral or health opinions right? Because that's what it's really about. When do I get to have an opinion that matters on your healthcare? oh yeah... never.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I was just talking to someone about this. They said their friend who is autistic puts their condiments down there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Your profile says you stan Jesus. Do you think Jesus would treat adoptees like shit? I don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It sucks. ðŸ’œ It is what it is. I don't put my faith in too many ppl these days and certainly not ppl I don't know. Less disappointing that way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I'm not spreading propaganda' she says as she hashtags #HASHTAG# when she #HASHTAG# not to have one. #HASHTAG# is prolies and pro propaganda. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If our government gave a single fuck about disabled people this wouldn't be happening. It's needless. The guy next door should have a full time cleaner coming to his place, he can't afford it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#URL#

This is the world #HASHTAG# ppl are fighting for. Prolife is for #HASHTAG# 

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# NOPE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone elses twitter acting up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# 1. You have been repeatedly asked not to contact MeruroM.
2. You're being here IS the bother.
3. You are asking for something, for ATTENTION. 

Get f***ed stalker. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I'd rather listen to Fran Drescher than listen to you. Enjoy being full of hate! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# There are no words. ðŸ’” #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I mean I was mad for a second there....
 
but then I found my lighter. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And I would specifically tell her my boundaries as well so she either would stop propagandizing her religion at me. Boundaries are important.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Yeah as soon as you're unable to work for any reason you become a waste of space I guess. Doesn't matter if you are kind or if you want to work but can't. Disability = lazy asshole that takes money from hardworking taxpayers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Your pic is way less of a problem than your personality. But you do look like the unibomber in that pfp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# If they have an unplanned pregnancy and wish to keep it I don't see why they would be having a conversation with me. But if that's the case I would try to help them any way I could.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Exposed. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# She's an ignorant tw**waffle, that's why. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Random dude: Hey nice to meet you. *reaches out hand*

Yeah I don't shake hands. Pandemic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# ðŸ˜‚ This is so ignorant it's funny. I pity the woman that dates you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never come across a more pathetic excuse for a person as the person I interacted with this morning. I'm amazed at how far people will go to try to make an erroneous point on twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Of course. Only if they have the time, energy, or inclination. Or maybe someone could point you in a direction of a website with good info.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# On the bright side I would rather you do that then attempt to hit on some poor woman there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Almost anyone can accidentally make a baby. It takes more effort to make a pizza than a baby.ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Pregnancy can kill or significantly harm me. I can choose whatever is best for me and my body and so can everyone else. You don't get say in anyone's reproduction but your own Karen. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Says the dbag that won't answer a single question posted to them. ðŸ§ðŸ˜† #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Not to be a bitch but that's what you get for eating HATE chicken! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, I mean obviously men think about abortion way more than women! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's basically saying that we are our base instincts and we have zero impusle control. We just haaaave to have sex with every person of the opposite gender. It also leave out the reality that people are not all cis and hetero.. like it's just such a fucking dumb Q.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read this statement and tell me prolife cares about anyone but themselves. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Also when you propagandize.. yeah you're gonna get some pushback.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# LOL I'm sure everyone that wants or needs an abortion will check with you first.. oh wait, they won't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It doesn't look that great and I forget it exists most of the time. ðŸ˜‚ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Oh right I keep blocking and unblocking you right? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anything to rationalize using a nazi flag right? #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If someone needs to babysit a grown man so he doesn't do something illegal he doesn't deserve the job. Fuck Jeopardy. I'll never watch it again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# So I mean, you can say whatever, but the only pregnancy you have control over is your own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# If your religion improved morality your priests and cardinals wouldn't be sexually abusing children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Me too. Never gonna happen. They have plenty to say and nothing to prove their tripe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It's so completely fucked up that all of you children and teens have to live in fear so rednecks can have their guns. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Oh I completely understand why arguing with people such as yourself isn't effective. You're wilfully ignorant of the facts but also indoctrinated (usually christian) and you lap up all the B.S. prolife propaganda like mothers milk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Blocked her at that point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I think you are a dealing with internalized ableism. I hope you figure that shit out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right? LOL He is an "actor" and I'd say may he never get an acting job but with his personality and matching good looks I don't think I need to worry about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I thought we were mad she bought some expensive cookware..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# It's damn good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I get it. ðŸ’œ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish it wasn't true. But healthy food is expensive AF. How are people on ODSP supposed to live? ðŸ¤·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# That's because your country is a joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Rose is hilarious. ðŸ˜‚ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# LOL Keep showing your whole a$$. You aren't making catholics look any better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Right?! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My gramma has dementia and COPD. My mom is going thru chemo. They shouldn't have to have a drivers license to renew their healthcards online. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You can't disagree with a persons opinion bro. It's not a fact. She said she doesn't want a cure. If someone does then that's THEIR opinion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I mean it looks like a poorly drawn eyebrow under his actual eyebrow.. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# These people are beyond ignorant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# No one signs a contract. A fetus doesn't pay rent. IT LIVES INSIDE OUR BODIES not a fucking apartment. Get over yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're so pretty.. I can't even. ðŸ’œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If you don't mind alot of violence Bound is a fucking great movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# People that treat me poorly because I have autism and ADHD are the reason I struggle with depression and anxiety NOT the autism and ADHD. Sure there are things I struggle with but I am a fucking awesome artist and I wouldn't be ME if I was neurotypical.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He says as if this isn't his alt account for trolling and abusing women on twitter. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6/
I asked his mom and she said no. I realize now it was never about protecting him or his wellbeing it was about protecting her and her wellbeing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# My mother's dead. Not suprised you guys are necropheliacs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Could be a factor. Either way you are perfect the way you are. â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# The french fries look more satisfying then a picture of white jesus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You can end it by not replying. Pretty simple no? And yeah when you troll ppl for hours about abortion you're gonna get pushback. Common fucking sense. Get some.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah I'm sure I should have just given birth to a fully gestates stillborn for YOUR comfort. ðŸ–• #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boo fucking hoo my wife was fired because her employers refused to allow her to transmit a disease to her elderly patients.. ðŸ¤¡ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truly shitty thing is that my body regulates to the medication really fast and then it stops working and I have to stop taking it for a while and then get back on it again over and over and over. #HASHTAG# of #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too true. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Hate follows. They just want to see what you post so they can troll.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Please don't ever listen to these so called 'prolife' people on this app. They are woefully ignorant and usually are spreading disinformation via liveaction. They like to lie so they can demonize anyone that gets an abortion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First shot didn't hurt or bother me at all. Second shot I felt weird and my arm hurt and was weak for a few days. That's it. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Yes but if someone cut the tree down it wouldn't have produced.. Which you can do if you feel like it because its your yard!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Oh prolife don't answer questions posed to them they just make wild and uneducated statements.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah women don't know what those things are when they are the ones that have to deal with being pregnant.. yeah we are just irresponsible sluts that never use birth control and have abortions ALL THE TIME. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Yeah, because I dared to point out guns aren't toys and shouldn't be treated or looked at as such.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Cool. You can keep posting different cases of murders in Texas if you feel like it. Disprove my point or begone. I'm bored with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# loves to call women cum dumpsters when they won't even be responsible enough to wear a condom unless asked. Fucking losers. #HASHTAG# 

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Like.. your bio family is important to you... isn't their bio family important to them? It's natural.. like damn. Sounds like AP's are being possessive and unfair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh and on your bio it says your a follower of christ? I'm sure if Jesus was here he would be harassing women who got abortions too!! #HASHTAG# Vile piece of distended pig rectum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["not trying to be rude" Yeah you don't have to try. You're just naturally a judgemental person. You should work on that while other people work on their issues. No one fucking asked you for your opinion on the thread. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A catholic man with an opinion about abortion?? Usually catholics are so loving and understanding! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just try to take it as a way to educate others that don't realize some people actually do need these meds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expects answers but with no reciprocation. SUPRISE! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I couldn't hold onto the nurses false sentiment of "You'll be here again under different circumstances" I had really believed her but she was wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Most of my family look alot alike. My brother, my mother and I are all look pretty much the same lol #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's super cold and windy outside today, yesterday it ice rained. I can't wait for winter to be OVER and be able to take my dog on real walks not walking 2 minutes, freezing, and then running back inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mom is going thru chemo and also has diabetes. She was really sick last night and my dad took her to the hospital. I hope she will be okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You're a complete waste of time. Enjoy my blocklist with all other other disingenuous antichoice mofos. ðŸ˜˜ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dead don't die is the worst zombie movie I have ever seen. The cast was mint so I was expecting a good movie. Awful. Awful movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# It looks peaceful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Thanks. I am just making a point that her statement is bullshit.ðŸ’œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Actually calling 2 people narcissists isn't respectful. Go away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# And why do the same people that say both of those things then call those children bastards?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Also it's kind of hilarious to me that the people arguing against bodily autonomy also don't understand other boundaries like a block on twitter.. I feel bad for the people that have to deal with them in their lives since they don't respect other peoples boundaries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I come across enough asshats on this app I am not going to bother seek them out, unless I am blocking their ignorant asses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter: We wonâ€™t suggest this Topic anymore.

Me: How about not ever suggesting me a topic? I know what I want to read about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Lamentations 5:11
They ravished the women in Zion,
The virgins in the cities of Judah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# You also say this ALOT. I reported every single one of the times you said this exact same thing as spam. Have a lovely day! #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A girl has no name. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Right. A person exercising their bodily integrity by ejecting a zygote from their body is exactly like the catholic church murdering indigenous children!! How could I never have seen it before?!?! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Again, DGAF what your opinion. It doesn't effect anyone's life but yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Most of the bad feelings could be illuminated of people just stopped treated disabled people like the shit under their shoes or actively gaslighting them for having opinions that don't fall in line with yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Tell her she didn't lose any friends because no real friends would treat someone mentally ill with abuse. She is a decent human and that is worth a thousand of those types of 'friends'. An internet stranger is proud of her too. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Go look up the amount of gun deaths in america vs canada and come back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think that the theory of evolution is a 'lie' please just do me a favour and block me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# "Lost family" Nah they are the losers in this one. To be honest even before the pandemic I knew I didn't want anything to do with those specific family members.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You going to answer in a timely manner or should I just mute you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It's a meme genius. I didn't make it. And I don't care where he got the throne. The fact is they have billions upon billions of dollars they aren't using to help a single soul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nice activist work not caring. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Switzerland,  Belgium, Netherlands, Luxembourg, Canada, Australia, and Colombia euthanasia is legal. Those countries are pretty developed don't you think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# A prolife catholic? Wow I am SUPER surprised #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I blocked all of them. They are obviously ignorant af and happy to be so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# They literally refuse to answer any questions but expect others to deal with their sealioning endlessly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Then I guess you should wear a condom every time or get a vasectomy because that is all you can control, your own reproductive organs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# STARDEW VALLEY!!!! Do you have a PC? I'll play co-op with you lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Took long enough. ðŸ˜‚ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care how intelligent someone is, if they are too arrogant to bother to explain and cite sources for their opinions and just expect me to take them at face value I am not going to pay them any mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# I was expecting a baby and then I found out it would never live outside my uterus due to genetic abnormality. I didn't get to have a baby. This is not rocket science Gerry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I was very disappointed in how it played out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# But I love getting the same tweet over and over again from different people about the different types of government that we have and who is responsible for what..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I didn't give you anything. You said some foolish propagandizing shit in a thread the other day and made it so no one could reply unless they were your followers. You had alot of time to think about it during your thread. If you didn't think ppl were going to take issue with it..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The geese are like, yes the hu-mans understand we are their overlords. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I did was ask some questions. She is feeling so fragile she had to protect herself from my questions LOL 

#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Nina's Heavenly Delights, Imagine me and you, Journey, Sea Purple, Better than Chocolate, Bound, But I'm a Cheerleader, My Days of Mercy..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# LMAO. Let me know when men risk their health and wellbeing gestating for 9 months. Until then your opinion has about as much weight as a teacup poodle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to get off twitter for a bit. The disgusting abuse forced birthers dish out is just enraging sometimes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# "Haskell has said that he devised his D&amp;X procedure because he wanted to find a way to perform second-trimester abortions without an overnight hospital stay, because local hospitals did not permit most abortions after 18 weeks."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# $20 bucks says he can't answer this honestly or just won't bother to reply.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't enjoy cooking most of the time. My executive dysfunction says cooking is too many steps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I'm glad you're laughing as much as me about this 'conversation'. ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# How does your RT help end abortion? Oh right it doesn't. You just like harassing women online.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# is for #HASHTAG#

Their points below are so compelling. /s

#HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# proponents always think this way. Women are not irresponsible. Most women use birth control ya knob. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# You're gonna all lives matter this person? SMH.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# LOL 8 out of 10 ppl are for abortion. Just because 20% of you are loud about it doesn't mean sh*t.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# They have to be antagonistic because being genuine in their discourse is never going to happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re-watching Criminal Minds. They had this woman Agent Seaver on there for almost a whole season and her character didn't even get a good bye scene. It was just "Oh yeah she transfered to another job" lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh well. I am sure she feels bad too thinking I'm going to hell. Religion fucks up families.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Same but also tired of fighting with the medical establishment for someone to assess me w/o having to pay thousands of dollars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yeah, one of them f*cked up my cookies on googlechrome and one of them didn't work at all. Thanks. People can be total dickheads on twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Probably not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# What's it like to only use twitter to harass people?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since all you dudes do is stare at at our tits, yeah we got the memo. Women deserve to be comfortable without wearing a bra in public. Avert your gaze. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Random: Once Tricia Helfer and Katee Sackhoff did a live stream and I was in the chatroom with ppl and they were going to give away a shirt and I said something funny about one of their stories and Katee said to send the shirt to the funny one and she was talking about me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# love to pretend they are the victim. The indigenous children are the victims here. You are just a dumb@$$ that doesn't want their precious church to be held accountable for genocide. #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I got put in twitter time out for telling one of them to GFT but it's totally cool when they call me a murderer. I mean calling someone a murderer isn't abusive or anything. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# She is usually quite careful how she words things which is why she is still here. She'll mess up one day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Don't you put it in your mouth will always be my fave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Good for you! Now you just have to learn when certain things are literally none of your business and you'll be all set.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nah too hard. Would rather her husband bitch about something stupid on twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# I don't get why she is highlighting her own ignorance...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is fun... Please to all the ice rain gods don't let me slip and fall. ðŸ™ƒ #URL#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If I were vampire I would just enthral some ppl into giving me their $$ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Rape is not the same thing as forced breeding much like a woman is not a fetus. If these concepts are too difficult for you you might wanna sit out the discussion Dave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Also the same way you can't tell anyone to continue a pregnancy and expect them to listen is the same way you cant tell strangers to get married or how to conduct their sex lives. You really have control issues doncha Dave?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# Cope with what? LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Because that's impossible. If you are in labour they come out breathing and having bodily autonomy. You are really bad at this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USER# You wouldn't be the first woman that slipped thru the cracks.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>